Chapter 489: The debate about Chang Shan Yin

They won but Ma Ying Jie did not show any arrogance, instead he said: "Warm pond valley is easy to defend and hard to attack, possessing large areas of warm pools. The great blizzard is about to come and this place is a naturally protected place. By obtaining it, my tribe has a base of operations. We can advance while attacking or defend if we retreat!"

"But the thing I am even more happy about is obtaining over two hundred thousand terror claw horses. With these horses, uncle can greatly raise his horse group's scale and increase my Ma tribe's supreme might in the coming heroes assembly!"

His uncle was none other than one of the current three great enslavement masters - Ma Zun!

When Ma Zun was mentioned, all the Ma tribe's Gu Masters showed admiration.

"Before we left, uncle had told me: It was not easy for our Ma tribe to become a large scale tribe. Only after several hundred years of accumulation, efforts and extraordinary fortune, were we able to reach this state. But as the tribe grows, defending this foundation is becoming more difficult. Even by striking warm pond valley, we have only obtained a base to preserve the fire. The only way to preserve the whole tribe is to advance a step further; that is to enter the Imperial Court!"

Ma Ying Jie looked at everyone before continuing: "Imperial Court blessed land is Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's grace left to his descendants. Especially that Eighty Eight True Yang Building, which has the inheritance of the Immortal Venerable! Uncle said my bloodline has already fulfilled the criteria to enter Eighty Eight True Yang Building. If I can obtain Immortal Venerable's inheritance and later become a Gu Immortal, our Ma tribe will become the new super tribe of northern plains!"

"Super tribe..."

This phrase immediately caused the Ma tribesmen to show a spellbound look.

"Young tribe leader, you are a once in a hundred years genius of our tribe. Our tribe's future lies on your shoulders."

"Lord Ma Zun might be taciturn, but he really cares about the tribe in his heart and has a far foresight...."

"Being able to witness everything and fight with young tribe leader is my lifetime's glory!"

"Young tribe leader, lead us to brilliance."

Ma tribe's Gu Masters cheered excitedly.

Ma Ying Jie smiled.

In truth, Ma Zun had never said anything like this, and these words were all his own fabrication.

Borrowing Ma Zun's prestige, Ma Ying Jie added light and color to his name. Just think! Even Ma Zun looked so highly of him, so the others would have to be blind to not support him.

Ma Ying Jie was also not worried that Ma Zun would tear apart this name after he knew of this.

Ma Zun was an eccentric; he spoke extremely few times even as a child, his silence almost made his parents think he was a mute.

Ma Zun loved horses and was jokingly called 'horse maniac' and 'horse fool' by the tribesmen when he was young.

He had a reclusive nature and never married in his life. He only loved horses and would live with them all year round, with not even a slightest bit of interest and concern towards worldly powers and affairs.

Ma Ying Jie's gaze brightened like stars: "All of you are the pillars of my Ma tribe, with many outstanding points that are worth for me, Ma Ying Jie, to learn. I am still young, Ma tribe cannot be supported by me alone. In the future, I hope to rely on everyone's help."

"What is young tribe leader saying!"

"Young lord's words make us blush with shame."

"Over these years, young tribe leader's performance has deeply entered our hearts. We will definitely follow you!"

The group of Ma tribesmen quickly agreed.

Ma Ying Jie continued: "Although uncle Ma Zun has entrusted his hope on me, we still need to look at destiny to obtain the Immortal Venerable's inheritance in Eighty Eight True Yang Building. But even if I can get it, there are many inheritances left all over the Imperial Court blessed land besides the True Yang building. Thus, all the tribes who have had entered the Imperial Court throughout history, had a huge raise in their strength. Every time I think about this, I cannot help feeling excited."

The tribesmen laughed heartily.

"Not just excitement, even my saliva drips out every time I think of it."

"Haha, young tribe leader does not need to have too much pressure. If we lose, we can come back again. Our Ma tribesmen are warriors who will never surrender!"

Imperial Court blessed land was similar to Tian Ti mountain in that Gu Masters often left behind their inheritances.

Northern Plains had a very cruel environment with there being a great blizzard every ten years; the snowy disaster engulfing the entire northern plains. The blizzard would cut through everything like knives. Many inheritances set up in the wild would be destroyed.

Thus, setting up inheritances in Imperial Court blessed land had gradually turned into a tradition of northern plains.

Imperial Court blessed land had many other inheritances besides the Eighty Eight True Yang Building's Immortal Venerable inheritance, waiting for their fated person.

Of course, this fated person had to first enter Imperial Court blessed land to be able to receive the fortuitous destiny.

Being able to evade the blizzard and live safely, along with the inheritances spread everywhere was the reason why the struggle for Imperial Court would cause intense contests between all the tribes of the grassland.

This contest involved the whole northern plains and was of an extremely large scale. Small scale tribes wanted to survive, mid-scale tribes wanted to advance, and large scale tribes wanted to defend their foundation. Not only righteous paths, but even demonic path Gu Masters wanted to enter the blessed land and seize the Gu Master inheritances.

For this struggle, the heroes assembly came into existence and slowly took form till it became a firm tradition of northern plains people.

As the great blizzard approached, all the famous regions of northern plains would hold a heroes assembly at the same time.

"We have annihilated Fei tribe this time, it will bring us great benefits in our progress in Tian Chuan's heroes assembly. As long as we can subjugate Cheng tribe, our Ma tribe will have a strong lead!"

"Right, only by winning the heroes assembly, can we attract more experts and make many tribes attach to us.This is the first step of the great battle of Northern Plains, and also the most important step."

"We are looking to enter Imperial Court blessed land, so we need to survey other regions too. Yu Tian's, Meng Qiu's and Cao Fu's heroes assembly, all need to be observed closely."

Just as Ma tribe's higher ups were passionately discussing, a messenger Gu Master rushed in and delivered the newest intel to Ma Ying Jie.

Ma Ying Jie's face turned gloomy as he read the intel and shortly after, handed this intel to the group beside him.

Everyone read it one after another, letting out small exclamations, gasps or conjectures from time to time.

"Dong Fang tribe has already subjugated Zhao tribe; with this, they are the ruler of Cao Fu's heroes assembly."

"In Meng Qiu region, Nu Er tribe has actually sent Nu Er Tu, their momentum is very terrifying, I am afraid Lui tribe won't be able to hold them off."

"There is also an uproar in Yu Tian's heroes assembly. The Wolf King of before, Chang Shan Yin, actually appeared!"

"This Chang Shan Yin is really fierce, he actually led Ge tribe and challenged three tribes, even defeating Pei Yan Fei!"

"In Yu Tian region, Hei tribe's Hei Lou Lan and Liu tribe's Liu Wen Wu are the elites. Now that the Wolf King has appeared, this will definitely have a big influence. It is very difficult to say what will happen in Yu Tian's heroes assembly."

Soon, everyone's discussion focused on Fang Yuan.

Chang Shan Yin's identity had already spread for many years in northern plains. Now, suddenly, he resurrected and was causing a stir.

Ge tribe was only an ordinary mid-scale tribe, but with Chang Shan Yin's meddling, they were able to forcibly challenge three tribes and even defeat an expert like Pei Yan Fei.

Especially when they made inquiries and found Ge tribe's newly appointed tribe leader was only a rank three young Gu Master, their evaluation of Chang Shan Yin raised by several layers.

"Every ten years, heroes emerge and vie for supremacy with monsters and freaks emerging from every corners. It is only that this time, such a great character jumped out."

"Young tribe leader, if this Wolf King Chang Shan Yin and our tribe's Lord Ma Zun fought, who would win?"

Everyone could not help having some worries.

Ma Ying Jie slightly furrowed his brows.

If it was other path's Gu Masters, it would be alright. But this Chang Shan Yin was an enslavement path Gu Master, an expert in fighting ten thousand with one.

He could change the situation alone with his huge troops!

"You have all read the intel. Enslavement path's Gu Master's strength depends on the scale of their beast group. Chang Shan Yin has reappeared only recently, so the beasts he has are only some ordinary turtleback wolves, night wolves and wind wolves, and also has only three myriad beast kings. One has died and another is heavily injured, how can he compare to my uncle Ma Zun?

Ma Ying Jie coldly snorted and continued to raise the morale: "Uncle Ma Zun has a horse group with three hundred thousand horses. Adding on these terror claw horses, the scale will expand to five hundred thousand! Besides this, he also has a horse emperor, nine myriad beast kings and five mutated horses. Now say yourself, can the Wolf King be mentioned on equal terms with him?"

The surrounding Gu Masters took a sharp breath; shocked and happy.

"I didn't think Lord Ma Zun's strength would be so big!"

"The insignificant Wolf King is like a baby when compared to Lord Ma Zun."

"Five hundred thousand, such huge scale. It is enough to annihilate seven or eight mid-scale tribes."

Ma Ying Jie changed the subject: "But wolf king Chang Shan Yin still cannot be underestimated. My tribe is going to become the master of Imperial Court, we will run into this person sooner or later. More importantly, in case he joins the heroes assembly and attaches himself to a Huang Jin family, he will definitely receive huge assistance. Large number of Gu Masters will help him to subdue wolf groups and urge him forward."

The joy on everyone's faces gradually dimmed down.

This young Gu Master heaved a deep sigh and continued: "We have swallowed Fei tribe, this is only the first step of our journey. Next, we will be facing even more strong opponents. We need to unite together, only then can we defeat them and enter the Imperial Court."

"Yes, young tribe leader is right."

"Young tribe leader is wise and powerful, I am in great admiration!"

"With the leadership of the tribe leader and young tribe leader, our Ma tribe will definitely rule the northern plains!"

Everyone was unconsciously battered by Ma Ying Jie's few words and became even more aligned towards Ma Ying Jie.

This Ma tribe's young tribe leader let out a pleased smile in his heart.

On the surface, he showed a light and confident expression.

"Father, you died such a miserable death..." Right at this time, a tragic cry sounded from the foot of the hill.

This sound attracted the Ma tribesmen's gaze.

Ma Ying Jie looked at the battlefield where corpses strewed the battlefield; a child had thrown himself on a corpse that was filled with scars and cried very grievingly.

"Brat, get lost. You are already my Ma tribe's slave!" An adult man at the side beat up the child and dragged him forcibly.

But this kid struggled with all his might and bit at the adult man's wrist.

The adult man screamed, loosening his hand.

The kid scampered along the way and again threw himself at that corpse, crying bitterly.

"Sigh..." Ma Ying Jie let out a sincere sigh, "This misery and suffering is not what I wish for, but in these troubled times, who can live well by themselves? If you don't die, then I die. Human power is so insignificant. I will do everything I can to protect our tribe to not let the children of my Ma tribe suffer such a fate."

"Young tribe leader is benevolent." The surrounding Gu Masters also sighed.

Ma Ying Jie pointed down: "This kid is a loyal and filial person, but is facing this difficulty because of me. One of you, go stop him and bring him here, he will become my personal servant from now on."

"Yes, lord." His attendants answered.

They did not dissuade it as adopting servants was a tradition in northern plains.

Moreover, what threat can a thirteen year old kid who had not awakened his aperture possess to their lord young tribe leader?

"Kid, get up!" A higher up of Ma tribe stopped the adultman from beating the kid and grabbed the kid's neck.

The kid struggled fiercely: "No, I want to be with my father."

"Kid, your father is already dead. Your luck is good today, my tribe's young leader has noticed you and is taking you in as his personal servant." The Ma tribe's higher up said with a gentle voice.

But the kid did not listen and only kept on crying: "Father, father!"

Suddenly, he stopped and looked sluggishly at his father's corpse.

"Ah! You are not my father, my father's skin is darker than yours and his nose bridge is higher than yours, he also has some white hair...." The kid talked to himself in shock, before furiously kicking the corpse and started crying again, "Father, where are you?"

Dark lines appeared all over every Ma tribesmen's forehead.

Chapter 490: Second Aperture!

While the chaotic situations converged in Northern Plains, the transaction in Lang Ya blessed land also reached the end.

"You want the information of Eighty Eighth True Yang Building? Hmm...it is not impossible." Lang Ya land spirit muttered before looking at Fang Yuan with a sharp gaze.

Lang Ya land spirit's obsession was related to space escape Gu and Great Dream Immortal Venerable.

Moreover, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already passed away and Lang Ya land spirit was also not the Long Hair Ancestor himself, but a different living entity.

"When the Immortal Gu house was refined, only Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was there as the bystander. How could you know such a secret?" Lang Ya land spirit asked.

Fang Yuan smiled.

In his previous life, Ma Hong Yun entered the Eighty Eighth True Yang Building and obtained the inheritance of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Later, Ma Hong Yun was defeated and was chased until he mistakenly entered Lang Ya blessed land and obtained the destiny left behind by Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable. Lang Ya land spirit saw his tracks and while discussing, spoke of this secret.

Ma Hong Yun became a Gu Immortal later on, turning into a cornerstone of the northern plains, a great hero who resisted the invasion of the Central Continent.

In an intense conversation once, he spoke of this secret which then spread out to the world.

Naturally, Fang Yuan would not admit this fact in front of Lang Ya land spirit.

"I have inherited the inheritance of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable. And have many clues regarding Giant Sun Immortal Venerable as well. The reason I know of this secret is actually is from calculations and deductions," Fang Yuan answered with a slight arrogant smile appearing on his face.

Lang Ya land spirit looked at Fang Yuan's expression and suddenly realized something as he asked: "Are you?"

"Yes, junior has some attainments in wisdom path." Fang Yuan casually lied with an extremely honest expression.

Lang Ya land spirit sighed, the gaze he looked at Fang Yuan carried a complicated expression.

Wisdom path appeared long ago; tracing back its origins, it was created three million years ago in ancient times by an almighty rank nine.

This person was a rarely seen female venerable.

She was called by the world as Star Constellation Immortal Venerable. She controlled heavenly court as the second generation Immortal King.

It was rumored that she had once held wisdom Gu itself and created the wisdom path.

Before her death, she deduced heavenly secrets and made three arrangements for the three millions years after that.

After her death, three Demon Venerables appeared successively in human race, each charging their way to the Heavenly Court but were blocked by these three arrangements in the end.

Being able to calculate the appearance of three venerables, one could see some grandeur of wisdom path from this.

"Kid, you are actually able to deduce to this degree, it seems you have indeed obtained the essence of wisdom path." After learning Fang Yuan was a wisdom path Gu Master, the land spirit's tone unexpectedly became milder.

To this age, there were extremely few true inheritors of wisdom path, but even then no one would have contempt for wisdom path Gu Masters. Wisdom path Gu Masters were good at scheming and deductions, and many of their enemies would not even know how they died.

Moreover, since ancient times, refinement path was closely connected to wisdom path. To comprehend the world and deduce Gu refinement recipes, Gu Masters would need to use many methods of wisdom path. Many Gu refinement masters and grandmasters would request help from wisdom path Gu Masters when they met a bottleneck in creating recipes.

Lang Ya land spirit was disgusted with Fang Yuan's slyness, but when he knew Fang Yuan had extraordinary achievements in wisdom path, his attitude became gentler.

Lang Ya land spirit liked refining Gu, and naturally also liked researching and innovating Gu recipes. In this process, he would naturally encounter many obstacles which would be hard to resolve with just his wisdom.

"Maybe I will have to request his help to deduce recipes in the future?" This thought emerged in Lang Ya land spirit's mind.

As the saying goes: One can be austere if he has no selfish desires.

Since Lang Ya land spirit had some request for Fang Yuan, his attitude naturally turned better.

He summoned a rank four east window Gu and held it.

This gu was a rank four Gu under information path. It was like a ladybug but its carapace was square shaped like a window frame and was especially used to store information.

Lang Ya land spirit poured his thoughts within it and loosened his hand only after a while.

East window Gu opened up its window-like carapace and flew, making a circle in the air before flying towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan sent out his thoughts and checked it; his face immediately revealed joy.

"This is the information you wanted. Now, it is your turn." Lang Ya land spirit reminded.

Fang Yuan chuckled: "Since second aperture Gu has formed, I also am somewhat impatient to use such a good thing. I will send you the news before I use it."

"Slow down!" Lang Ya land spirit showed its cleverness, "How would I know till when you are going to delay it? You are a wisdom path Gu Master, you are the top in scheming, are you still thinking of using this to cheat me again? We have not transacted this east window Gu yet, hehe, with my one thought, the east window Gu on your hand will self-destruct."

Fang Yuan frowned: "Could it be you don't trust me?"

Lang Ya land spirit had suspicions all over his face: "Hmph! Just the fact alone that you are the inheritor of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable, I can't trust you. You are so crafty and also have wisdom path methods; once you exit the blessed land, can I still be able to chase you? In case, you delay and take the chance to extort again, what would I do?"

"Then how about you tell me what should we do?" Fang Yuan impatiently said.

"Of course, now. Use this second aperture Gu right in front of me. Only then can I be at ease." Lang Ya land spirit stroked his grizzled beard, pleased at thinking of such a good idea.

Fang Yuan grinned: "Heh, I am only a mere rank five now, how can I use this Immortal Gu without immortal essence? Wait till I go out of the blessed land and ask for grandpa to help me."

"Your grandfather can help you, but I can't? Don't speak rubbish, lend the second aperture Gu to me, I will personally do it!"

"This..." Fang Yuan tried to make an excuse.

The land spirit saw this and felt that Fang Yuan had really wanted to trick him, thus his attitude became more firm.

Fang Yuan looked like he had no choice and reluctantly let Lang Ya land spirit help.

Lang Ya land spirit received the second aperture Gu and poured immortal essence in it before throwing it to Fang Yuan.

This second aperture Gu turned into a bean-sized green light and flew into Fang Yuan's body.

Fang Yuan's whole body shook intensely.

The bean sized green light first poured into Fang Yuan's navel area.

But in there, it was rejected by Fang Yuan's aperture and could only hop over to the center of Fang Yuan's chest.

Then an explosion sounded like the thunder from the sky.

The bean-sized green light exploded and formed into a new aperture that looked both real and virtual.

Second aperture!

"This is second aperture?" Fang Yuan felt his chest and mumbled to himself in a daze.

"Nonsense, what is it if not the second aperture?" Lang Ya land spirit rolled his eyes, "Second aperture has great advantages to cultivators like you, providing even greater advantage when you become Gu Immortal. But, if you are still thinking of having the third aperture Gu, that is impossible. You would have to deduce and infer this whole new third aperture Gu's recipe."

Fang Yuan returned to his senses and looked profoundly at Lang Ya land spirit. The other intentionally raised this topic; no doubt it meant that he wanted to cooperate and deduce the Gu recipe.

Lang Ya land spirit's face reddened when he saw Fang Yuan's evident gaze.

Fang Yuan laughed and said his goodbye to Lang Ya land spirit: "We will talk of this later, I will take my leave now."

"Get lost, get lost!" Lang Ya land spirit repeatedly waved his hand.

Only when Fang Yuan had completely left did Lang Ya land spirit let out a breath of relief, a trace of humiliation appearing on his face for having his intentions seen through: "This sly kid."

But when he thought of Fang Yuan's last words which showed the intent of cooperating, Lang Ya land spirit's eyes flickered brightly.

He stroked his beard and could not help falling in daydream; he had dozens and dozens more of incomplete Gu recipes.

"Since that kid could deduce such secrets, he definitely has extraordinary achievements in wisdom path. With his help, I will be able to make some breakthrough in most of these Gu recipes, and thirteen of them could even be perfected. But just two people's cooperation is far from enough to complete the remaining seven Gu recipes."

""But I need to be vigilant when I interact with this kid in the future to avoid being schemed by him. Fortunately, I was cautious today and made him use second aperture Gu on the spot, otherwise I might have been blackmailed by him again! Eh, something does not feel right... I wasted immortal essence to activate the second aperture Gu!""

After exiting Lang Ya blessed land, Fang Yuan returned to Hu Immortal blessed land through stargate Gu.

Under his management, Hu Immortal blessed land already showed many good changes.

In the beautiful western part of the blessed land, large numbers of wolf groups and small numbers of fox groups were co-existing with each other.

Wolf groups' arrival might have disrupted the easy life of the fox group, but they did not disastrous casualties.

The credit for all this went to the large numbers of iron shell flowers planted on the ground.

Countless pink rabbits lived in this sea of iron shell flowers.

Pink rabbits could be easily multiplied and became the main source of food of wolf groups and fox groups.

At the eastern part, dreamy starlight pervaded the area, covering all the lakes with starry gauze.

The wide expanse of dark clouds were planted with star fragment grass. The star fragment grass grew rapidly, and while they could only occupy the central area of the dark clouds at first, now they had already spread to the edges of the clouds.

"Fairy Yao Guang's planting methods are really good. Star fragment grass are the food of starlight fireflies, and at the same time their growth is rapidly increased with the help of the starlight fireflies."

Fang Yuan repeatedly nodded his head. It was precisely because of the exchange for the starlight firefly group's breeding insights from Star Lord Wan Xiang, Fairy Yao Guang and others, that he could avoid many detours and obtain quite a bit of gains.

"It is only that although the starlight firefly group is also expanding, but the number of starlight firefly Gu are instead decreasing. These days, I have been repeatedly using stargate Gu, the consumption of the starlight firefly Gu is much higher than the rate of their creation."

Fang Yuan then turned his gaze towards the lakes on the ground.

These lakes were created by him drawing in the water in reverse to quench the fire.

Now, many water wolves were living around these lakes. These water wolves made their nests beside the lakes, eating the blue jade crucian carps in the lakes and sometimes going ashore to devore the earth skin pigs who came to drink water.

Blue jade crucian carps and earth skin pigs were both animals Fang Yuan purchased before. Now, large groups of them had adapted to the new environment under Little Hu Immortal's control and became a part of the Hu Immortal blessed land's food chain.

Especially the earth skin pigs, its reproducing ability was stronger than even pink rabbits and could eat almost anything, including mud. The pig group's scale was gradually expanding. If not for water wolves and poison beard wolves, the number of earth skin pigs would have been thirty to forty percent higher.

Chapter 491: Expansion of the wolf group

What Fang Yuan was most concerned about was air bubble fish's situation.

The lakes where air bubble fishes were placed on was carefully selected by Little Hu Immortal. Above these three lakes were the starry clouds where there was the most dense amount of star fragment grasses and also large numbers of starlight fireflies.

The air bubble fishes grew on these lakes where there were no water wolf groups, and even the numbers of blue crucian carps were very few.

These three lakes were personally protected by Little Hu Immortal to let as much precious air bubble fish grow smoothly from the fish roes and mature.

Now, there were many newly hatched fishes moving about these lakes.

These baby fishes were similar to goldfish with round bellies, small and pointed head and tail. However, it was not brightly colored as a goldfish and was mostly milky white. It also did not have the wavy fins and tail; their tails were small and exquisite.

Moreover, their swimming method was different from other fish species. These baby air bubble fishes were moving while bobbing up and down.

"If there is no big change, at around the end of this year, Eastern Sea's air bubble sea will be poisoned because of a fight between Gu Immortals. The price of air bubble fish in treasure yellow heaven will greatly increase. But I don't have enough air bubble fishes for my own use, let alone sell them in a short period of time." Fang Yuan pondered.

Whether it was the starlight firefly Gu or air bubble fish, they were both long term investments. It would require at least a hundred years for him to start receiving the profits.

Regarding the knowledge in breeding air bubble fish, Fang Yuan did not buy it from outside.

With his know-hows from his past life, he could increase the reproduction rate of the air bubble fishes by thirty percent. That is to say, he was at forefront among Gu Immortals at this.

Fang Yuan was satisfied from this inspection.

He praised Little Hu Immortal, causing her to feel extremely happy; her face reddened and her snow-white tail excitedly wagged.

However, Dang Hun mountain was still in a worsening condition.

Standing on Dang Hun mountain, Fang Yuan could sense a kind of dying aura. This caused Fang Yuan's mood to become grave.

Dang Hun mountain was the most valuable thing in the whole Hu Immortal blessed land. Starlight firefly Gu or air bubble fish could never be able to compare to it.

Fang Yuan returned to Dang Hun palace and summoned Little Hu Immortal, activating connecting heaven Gu to link up with treasure yellow heaven.

Just as they connected, several divine sense were transmitted.

"Are you selling gruel mud or not?"

"I will add a pair of hole earth Gu on top of Gu recipe."

"Although my remnant recipe only has a treasure light of sixty-five feet, but I can give some hairy men as complementary. Everything can be discussed."

　　...

These divine senses were all regarding the transaction for Gruel Mud.

Fang Yuan had put large amounts of gruel mud for sale before, directly requesting Immortal Gu Gruel Mud's recipe as the exchange. As this concerned Immortal Gu, this transaction had attracted many attention.

"Although Gruel Mud is one of the necessary materials to refine the Immortal Gu. But the Gu recipe's value is no doubt many times higher than Gruel Mud. These Gu recipes they want to exchange for have already reached the highest price."

Fang Yuan took a glance and knew the time for the transaction was ripe.

The prices everyone gave had reached the maximum amount possible with little difference between them. Fang Yuan looked at the prices but took a fancy upon one side.

The other was called Immortal Mudfeet; his Immortal Gruel Mud remnant recipe had a sixty-five feet high treasure light.

This level of treasure light was a bit lower than the other competing bidders. But the message he left showed he could add some hairy men to complement for this difference.

Normally, Gu Immortals raised hairy men to help them in refining Gu.

With the help of a large number of hairy men, Gu Immortals would not lack rank five Gu, but they would have to keep on trying for Immortal Gu.

Treasure yellow heaven transacted slaves and hairy men were one of the most popular among them, with price that was often higher than slaves of other races. Rockmen could not even be mentioned together with them.

Fang Yuan had already intended to buy some hairy men back at Lang Ya blessed land.

Thus, he had been excited when he saw those hairy men at Lang Ya blessed land. Unfortunately, Lang Ya land spirit did not yield in selling them, and Fang Yuan could do nothing about it.

Now, he required a large number of wolf enslavement Gu.

He already obtained rank one to rank five wolf enslavement Gu recipes from Lang Ya land spirit. He only lacked these hairy men to help him refine them.

If it was only him and Little Hu Immortal who refined the Gu, they might not be able to refine the amount he required even in two-three months.

Immediately, Little Hu Immortal conveyed the divine sense.

Immortal Mudfeet also happened to be present, immediately replying: "I am willing to add in ten thousand hairy men!"

But Fang Yuan was disappointed when he looked at the goods: "Although you are giving a lot of hairy men, they are all young ones and won't be a big help in refining Gu. What I need is the old hairy men."

"Old hairy men? Then the quantity will be decreased." Immortal Mudfeet pondered before replying. In these years, the hairy men's population in his blessed land had reached an excess so he was trying to get rid of a batch and was thus selling them cheaply.

After a round of haggling, Immortal Mudfeet finally agreed to sell over three thousand old hairy men and over seven thousand young hairy men to Fang Yuan.

For this, Fang Yuan had to add in half an immortal essence stone.

The transaction was finished. Fang Yuan checked the remnant recipe of Immortal Gu Gruel Mud.

The recipe was indeed damaged with only sixty percent of the contents in it. And the contents in it should moreover have been tampered by Immortal Mudfeet many times which required Fang Yuan to comb through them for the real contents.

This was not surprising.

Immortal Gu recipe was very precious, and if it was him who sold them, he would also tamper it like this. Although the treasure light would decrease after the tampering, the competition between Gu Immortals was precisely like this.

"With this remnant recipe, I have a foundation to deduce the complete recipe for Immortal Gu Gruel Mud in future; it will be much easier than deducing it with no foundation! More importantly, Immortal Gu Gruel Mud is with me. As long as I don't use it, no one will be able to refine the Gu. I can still keep on selling the gruel mud and profit."

But he could not bring the Immortal Gu Gruel Mud to Hu Immortal blessed land for the moment. After Fang Yuan left Lang Ya blessed land, he used many methods to cover the Immortal Gu's aura and bury it.

This was something he had no other way to deal with.

Before he became a Gu Immortal, he could only deal with it like this.

Most of the Gu Immortals who purchased these gruel mud wanted to refine Immortal Gu. Unfortunately, it was impossible for them to reach their objective.

Fang Yuan continued to put gruel mud for sale while checking the wolf groups.

Wolves possessed very strong reproductive ability, and most of the blessed lands would get rid of the surplus every once in a while.

Thus, there were many Gu Immortals selling wolf groups in treasure yellow heaven.

"The wolf group suffered a huge loss in the battle with the three tribes, I need to replenish the number of myriad beast kings. Eh, someone is actually selling wolf emperor."

Fang Yuan was pleasantly surprised.

The structure of beast groups was quite simple, they were separately classified into - ordinary beasts, hundred beast king, thousand beast king and myriad beast king. Above myriad beast king was beast emperor.

Rank five wild Gu resided in the beast emperor's body. They had the battle strength of a rank five and could control myriad beast kings.

Ying Ming and Ba Huang whom Fang Yuan used in the three kings blessed land were dog emperors. These two dog emperors were able to help him to hold off the attacks of rank five Gu Masters. Unfortunately, Fang Yuan was later occupied with escaping for his life and could not attend to them. He did not know if they were killed in the battle or were taken in by others.

Normally speaking, very few Gu Immortals would sell beast emperors as the beast emperors were a reflection of the blessed land's strength.

Fang Yuan looked at the particulars and realized the reason.

It turned out that this was an old beast emperor with wounds all over its body. The wild Gu on it were badly damaged with only two-three remaining.

"It seems a new wolf emperor appeared in the night wolf group and fought with the old wolf emperor. This old wolf should have been killed by the young wolf emperor, but the Gu Immortal moved at the crucial time and put this old wolf emperor for sale." Fang Yuan Guessed the reason correctly.

But even so, this old wolf emperor still got three bidders.

Divine sense kept on exchanging and finally, Fang Yuan used two immortal essence stones to buy this old night wolf emperor along with over eighteen thousand night wolves.

Then, Fang Yuan continued to buy thirty thousand turtleback wolves and ten thousand wind wolves; among them, there were two turtleback myriad wolf kings and one wind wolf myriad wolf king.

Adding in the previous wolf group, Fang Yuan's wolf group reached a hundred thousand.

"This is the benefits of having a blessed land. I can stand on the shoulders of Gu Immortals and casually transact beast groups, instantly recovering their size and also would not have to worry about feeding or logistics problem. But a hundred thousand is still few. Ma Zun, Yang Po Ying and Jiang Bao Ya, these enslavement path masters have beast groups of at least four hundred thousand beasts. Especially Jiang Bao Ya who had over six hundred and fifty thousand beasts in his prime!"

The heroes assembly was to begin, where heroes rose and vied for supremacy.

Fang Yuan knew he was unable to avoid competing with these people with his identity as Chang Shan Yin.

So he had to expand his wolf group further!

Fang Yuan started to buy again, buying ten thousand water wolves which contained one water wolf myriad beast king and 6 thousand wolf kings.

Then he carefully pondered for a while and finally decided on vermillion flame wolves.

He bought eighty thousand vermillion flame wolves from different Gu Immortals.

In northern plains, vermillion flame wolves were quite rare compared to turtleback wolves, wind wolves and night wolves.

Vermilion flame wolf had red fur all over its body which shone like fire. They attacked fierce and quick and had flame path Gu worms on them. They could very easily destroy the grassland and create an inferno. If one could use this superiority properly, they could cause enormous casualties to the enemy.

Fang Yuan's plan was to have a wolf group of a hundred thousand vermilion flame wolves. He only got eighty thousand after buying from everyone, so the task of buying the remaining twenty thousand was given to Little Hu Immortal.

"Six vermillion flame myriad wolf kings, one water wolf myriad beast king, three turtleback myriad wolf kings, two wind wolf myriad beast kings, one mutated beast white eye wolf and one night wolf beast emperor."

Fang Yuan surmised his wolf group's battle strength had increased by tenfold at once.

If it were common Gu Masters without the methods of Gu Immortals, they needed the help of a large tribe to reach this stage and even then would require six-seven years of searching all over the northern plains.

There were all sizes of wolf groups in northern plains. The small wolf groups often only had few hundreds and were not good enough. The large wolf groups had tens of thousands in numbers and were difficult to take down.

Capturing wolf groups required careful planning or it was better to not do it. A bitter victory would not work, and only by getting a decisive victory could one get the most harvests.

Fang Yuan's current leap to success seemed easy, but actually could be concluded as a Gu Immortal's methods.

Chapter 492: Getting another mutated wolf

"This way, the wolf group's numbers have hit two hundred thousand! But... this is still not enough." Fang Yuan eyes were shining with contemplation: "I do not need to gather ordinary wolves, by that time, someone will naturally bring them to me. Now, I need to prioritize on my upper-level battle strength."

Although there were beast emperors on sale in treasure yellow heaven occasionally, they would be quickly bought by Gu Immortals after appearing for a short time.

Fang Yuan knew that it was not realistic if he wanted to buy a few more wolf emperors. Thus, he placed his attention on mutated beasts.

Every mature mutated beast had battle strength equivalent to a myriad beast king.

Any first-rate enslavement path Gu Master would have a troop of mutated beasts as their trump card and ultimate force.

For example, southern border's King Quan had a mastiff group, Jiang Bao Ya had the mountain drilling rat group, Yang Po Ying had the thunder eagle group, and Ma Zun had the pegasus group.

There were many wolf-type mutated beasts. At this moment, four types were sold in treasure yellow heaven.

The first was blood forest wolf.

This wolf had a huge body, almost like a mound. An adult standing beside it would look like a fox standing beside and elephant.

The blood forest wolf had blood red fur, and the fur looked dry like wormwood. On each of their backs, there was a 'white forest'.

These 'trees' are actually the blood forest wolf's bones, they protrude from the back and grow vertically upwards. The white bone trees have blood red leaves growing on them. As the trees grow closely to each other, it looked like a 'blood forest'.

After a blood forest wolf gives birth, it would send the cub into the blood forest on its back, and the huge space would allow the child to live comfortable. The blood fruits on the trees would provide nutrients for the cub.

Blood forest wolf were like mobile fortresses, although they were not fast, they had overwhelming strength. This was something not even myriad beast kings could do.

The second type was shark fin wolf.

This was both a land and aquatic mutated beast, it looks like an elephant but there were smooth and shiny crocodile scales on its body. At the same time, there are sharp deep blue fins on the side of their bodies. On their backs, there are rows of fins that resembles a shark's, these fins form a line extending from the wolf's head to its tail.

Shark fin wolves had the greatest defense among mutated wolves, at the same time, they could fight underwater.

The third was frenzy wolf.

The frenzy wolf has a silver and grey body, it has three eyes and a body that was not large, around the same size as thousand beast kings.

But those who looked down on it due to its size would often pay a terrible price.

Once the frenzy wolf battles, it goes into a berserk state, it moves extremely fast and would not stop until the enemy is dead. Especially after its third eye opens, its battle strength will surge by five times!

Once the three eyes are open at once, regardless of the battle results, it would die.

This was a type of wolf breed that disregards their own body when entering fierce battles.

The fourth was the white-eyes wolf.

The eyes of the white-eyes wolf were pure white. They had extremely good eyesight, even during the night, their vision cannot be obstructed.

In treasure yellow heaven, there was one blood forest wolf, three shark fin wolves, two frenzy wolves, and five white-eyes wolves on sale, they were all bought by Fang Yuan.

At the same time, far away in southern border's Shadow Sect blessed land, Old Man Yan Shi squinted his eyes as he stared at the connecting heaven Gu in mid air.

Fang Yuan bought wolf groups in bulk, even wolf emperors and mutated wolves, it attracted the attention of this wisdom path Gu Immortal.

"This Fang Yuan, he suddenly bought so many wolves, what is he trying to do?"

This mysterious rank seven wisdom path Gu Immortal who had always stayed in the background frowned.

He tried using his Gu to make a deduction.

But the result was that Fang Yuan wanted to rear wolf groups for profit and business.

This result did not satisfy him.

"Hu Immortal blessed land's environment is most suited for growing fox groups. Although wolves are similar to foxes, they are different after all."

Blessed lands are blessed, they were the land of fortune. But every blessed land was different, they received different blessings.

For example, Hu Immortal blessed land was most optimal for raising foxes. Foxes that lived in this area would grow better and breed faster. As for Lang Ya blessed land, it was suited for refining Gu, the environment was suitable for hairy men to live in.

Shadow Sect blessed land benefited the cultivation of soul path Gu Masters.

The instinct deep within his heart told Old Man Yan Shi that Fang Yuan's actions had much deeper meaning.

But wisdom path was not all-knowing, it had its weaknesses. Otherwise, wisdom path would rule the Gu world, there would not be a scene of variety where many paths flourished.

Wisdom path needed evidence to make deductions. The more evidences they had, the more reliable their deductions would be. The wisdom path Gu Master would be guided towards making a more accurate answer.

But for Old Man Yan Shi, although he was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, he would never have expected Fang Yuan to be from the future.

Old Man Yan Shi had deduced that Fang Yuan used Fixed Immortal Travel Gu to go to Hu Immortal blessed land. But he would never be able to guess that Fang Yuan went to northern plains.

If Fang Yuan had sold divine travel Gu in treasure yellow heaven, he might have been able to make the connection.

But Fang Yuan was vigilant, he sold divine travel Gu to Lang Ya blessed land. Old Man Yan Shi lacked the most critical piece of information, thus his deduction ended up being wrong.

He tried for a few more times, but he still received the same result.

"Do I really have to use my vital Gu for this?" Old Man Yan Shi thought of this as his pores expanded, as traces of cloud smoke flowed out of him.

The white cloud smoke rose up and gathered above his head, forming into a rumbling cloud.

The cloud was misty, once it appeared, a thick Immortal Gu aura burst out of it.

But this rank seven Immortal Gu had an indiscernible aura, it was like the stars in the night sky, there was no way to locate it. It was also like the scent of a lotus from a thousand steps away, the presence was extremely faint.

Every time the cloud rumbled, there were infinite changes undergoing inside, there was no way to understand it all. If outsiders forced themselves to comprehend it, they would receive ambiguous answers.

This was Old Man Yan Shi's vital Gu — Heavenly Secret!

Heavenly secret Immortal Gu!

It could expose the secrets of heaven and earth, even if the Gu Immortal did not have any evidences or clues, it could directly lead them to the truth.

When Old Man Yan Shi found out that killer ghost doctor was under the slavery Gu, he used the heavenly secret Gu to deduce that Fang Yuan would one day return to southern border.

Thus, Old Man Yan Shi set up this trap and waited for Fang Yuan to come.

Right now, Old Man Yan Shi was hesitating, he was wondering if he should use heavenly secret Gu.

Although heavenly secret Gu was powerful, it had a weakness.

Old Man Yan Shi would not succeed every time he used it, out of ten tries, at least eight would fail. Once he fails, Old Man Yan Shi would face the backlash of an Immortal Gu.

If this backlash was common injuries, so be it, but it was extremely powerful and caused anyone to feel fear.

Old Man Yan Shi's soul and body would be intact, the heavenly secret Gu's backlash only targeted his lifespan.

Once he faces a backlash, Old Man Yan Shi would lose ten to seventy years of his remaining lifespan!

A Gu Master's cultivation to raise his rank did not have any effect on his lifespan. To extend their life, Gu Masters had one way that was the best, that was lifespan Gu.

Lifespan Gu can be used to increase a Gu Master's lifespan without any consequences.

Other than that, there were other unorthodox methods that could increase lifespan. But each of these methods had either weakness or flaws.

"My current body has around eighty years of lifespan left. Even the most severe backlash will only take seventy years of my life, I will still have ten years left, it is enough to execute my heaven defying plan! But these small matters would usually not give a huge backlash, most likely, I will lose about thirteen or fourteen years. But..."

"Is it worth it for me to use heavenly secret Gu for this? This act of defying heaven will definitely be noticed by my enemies when I reach the crucial stage. In the future, I will still need to use heavenly secret Gu to predict the future."

"But, if I can get the fixed immortal travel Gu that Fang Yuan has, it is a great help towards my plan. Just talk about now, if I had fixed immortal travel Gu to attack Lang Ya blessed land, I will be able to attack or retreat at will. What can Lang Ya land spirit do to me? I will not have suffered such a huge loss this time."

Old Man Yan Shi thought through it, and decided to give up.

Although heavenly secret Gu was powerful, it was a huge trap. The chances of success was simply too low, furthermore, the consequences of failure was too severe, Old Man Yan Shi did not want to waste his lifespan for nothing.

Back then, in order to deduce that Fang Yuan had fixed immortal travel Gu, or where he went, he first spent seventy years and got a result that stunned him for a long time.

He was in central continent!

He was in Hu Immortal blessed land!

How did he get there? What opportunity did he get, in order to get a visual image of Hu Immortal blessed land?

Okay, Fang Yuan started hiding inside the blessed land and refused to come out, Old Man Yan Shi's plan to take Fixed Immortal Travel Gu flopped before it even began.

But thankfully, he used heavenly secret Gu and expended another eighty years of his lifespan to find the most possible opportunity to strike.

In the future, on some day, Fang Yuan will return to southern border and join the battle of Yi Tian mountain!

For this Fixed Immortal Travel Gu, Old Man Yan Shi spent a hundred and fifty years of his life.

"Nevermind, since I got the results already, I shall wait here for him. The matter of him raising wolves is not a concern. As a wisdom path Gu Immortal, how can a mere mortal escape from a scheme that I made myself? Hehe."

Old Man Yan Shi snickered as he opened his eyes.

His eyes were like the white-eyes wolf, there were no pupils, only white color.

He stared at connecting heaven Gu, his lips becoming more curled as he said: "You are a mere mortal but you wasted a hundred and fifty years of my life. In the future when you die from my plot, it will be your greatest honor. But now, don't think you will have a good time!"

Old Man Yan Shi worked for a while, very quickly, Fang Yuan felt something amiss inside Hu Immortal blessed land.

"Oh no, someone is buying the materials for refining wolf enslavement Gu in bulk!"

Fang Yuan wanted to buy these materials, but Old Man Yan Shi was a step ahead of him.

He quickly tried to buy them, but faced much obstruction. A number of Gu Immortal purposely raised the prices against him, causing him to spend a lot more, and the total amount of materials he procured was less than expected.

Fang Yuan squinted, his gaze sharp like a needle: "Someone is intentionally making problems for me. Hmph, it can't be Lang Ya land spirit, it does not have such influence. Then, other than Immortal Crane Sect, it can only be that mysterious Old Man Yan Shi!"

"Hehe."

Suddenly, Fang Yuan laughed.

If it was before, he would be helpless against such a situation. But now, it was different.

He had a large number of wolf enslavement Gu recipes. These recipes ranged from rank one to five, and at every rank, there were different types of wolf enslavement Gu recipes.

These materials that the Gu Immortals obstructed him from getting were merely materials in ordinary wolf enslavement Gu recipes. Many Gu recipes had innovative ideas and took different routes, especially Lang Ya land spirit's personal recipes, how could these Gu Immortals understand the use of these materials?

Chapter 493: Surge in Battle Strength

A moment later.

"Hmph..." Fang Yuan's gaze was cold as he memorised these Gu Immortals' names.

Diao Sou, Great Immortal Ju Shi, Dian Huang Tianmu...

"Old Man Yan Shi, so it was you." He finally understood who the people finding problems with him were. Because most of these Gu Immortals were the ones who attacked Lang Ya blessed land back in his previous life, according to his memories.

"These Gu Immortals mostly come from northern plains, but there are also some from southern borders, eastern sea, western desert, and central continent. If I count Old Man Yan Shi as well, this hidden and mysterious Gu Immortal organization is truly huge!"

Because of this uncommon clash, Fang Yuan learnt about many secret details, he was secretly shocked.

What kind of force was it, who created it?

In his previous life, he had absolutely no idea about it, he was kept in the dark.

Such a huge force was hiding in the background, they were not a simple poisonous snake, but a ferocious tiger hidden behind the trees.

What were they planning, what was their motive?

In the future developments, during the battle of the five regions, what influence did they have in all of these events? As for Old Man Yan Shi, what was his role in this mysterious organisation?

Thinking back about their earlier strife, while it seemed like they were aggressively attacking, they did not use their full strength after all, they had perfect control over their actions.

Outsiders would not have sensed anything, they would only think of this as an ordinary contest.

Even himself, if not for his five hundred years of memories, he would only think that he was unlucky and faced fierce competition when procuring materials.

They struck secretly, interfering with him and found that they could not stop him, thus they stopped.

The entire assault was like throwing a rock into the water, after several ripples, the water surface returned to normal.

Fang Yuan was clear in his heart, he could escape from their assault this time because of Lang Ya land spirit's recipes, but that was only a foundation. Most importantly, the other party did not want to expose themselves or attract any suspicions, thus they did not go all-out.

Although Fang Yuan was a Gu Immortal in his previous life, he was only a mortal now.

Although he had one blessed land, he could not compete against the cooperation of two Gu Immortals, as well as such a mysterious and powerful force.

"The reason why I attracted the attention of Old Man Yan Shi is most likely due to fixed immortal travel Gu." Fang Yuan thought to himself.

Back then, he used a mortal body to refine an immortal Gu in front of everyone, it was simply too glaring and attention catching.

Immortal Gu were something not many Gu Immortals had. Not to mention fixed immortal travel Gu, such a top tier rank six Gu? Naturally, it would attract the greed of Gu Immortals.

The problem was that high profile he had!

But Fang Yuan had no choice, back then, the situation forced him to do so. This also resulted in the best outcome, there was no better way out of it.

"After such a long time, I'm sure the news have spread already. Immortal Crane Sect is definitely investigating this thoroughly, but that is a good thing."

"The clearer they investigate this, the more they would learn about me. I am only about thirty years old, I am a vagabond from a destroyed small-mid sized clan, I am a lone cultivator, or rather, I am a demonic Gu Master!"

"As such a person with low aptitude and lacking resources, I actually managed to learn about Hu Immortal blessed land's scenery and was able to refine an Immortal Gu? How is that possible? This is like an ant becoming a giant and swallowing an elephant, or a pig that grew wings and flew even higher than eagles."

Or using a phrase from Earth, this is scientifically impossible!

"This way, they will definitely deduce that there's an expert behind me! Someone of this level has to be a strong and mysterious Gu Immortal. I am merely a chess piece that this person is using behind the scenes."

"And because of this, if they want to deal with me, they will have to consider the person behind me, or the organisation backing me up. What if this background organisation is a group of people, a super clan, or a super sect? Nobody knows. Any person would want to investigate the unknown, to use all means to learn about their enemies."

"Before they investigate clearly, as long as I hide inside Hu Immortal blessed land and do not do anything overbearing, they will only try to probe me but would not truly go all-out."

Fang Yuan's thoughts moved like waves, sparked like flint rocks as he evaluated his current situation.

"Of course, this is only temporary. Paper cannot cover up a fire, once they find out the truth, or lose their patience, my trouble would come."

The moment Immortal Crane Sect attacks Hu Immortal blessed land, the best outcome for Fang Yuan is to self-detonate the blessed land and make both sides suffer a huge loss, nobody will obtain Dang Hun mountain in that case.

After losing the protection of his blessed land, Fang Yuan would be hunted down by everyone.

Thus, he was using the identity of Chang Shan Yin as a future back-up plan, to leave a way out for himself.

A crafty rabbit makes three homes, as a demonic lord in his time, Fang Yuan understood this clearly.

After collecting his thought, Fang Yuan sighed.

He had to cultivate quickly, it would be best if he reached Gu Immortal stage once again before Immortal Crane Sect and the mysterious force struck. But even so, it would still be a great danger. If he could not survive it, he would be smashed to bits, and end up in the pitiful state of eternal rest.

"The pressure is great..."

Even though Fang Yuan obtained the greatest benefits back at three kings blessed land, because of his actions, he lost the initiative.

Spring Autumn Cicada, Immortal Crane Sect, Dang Hun mountain, mysterious force, earthly calamity of the blessed land...

Even though he obtained Hu Immortal blessed land and his strength soared because of it, he was in even greater danger now.

All the intense and precarious situations, are pressuring him step-by-step, like a whip or a scythe, driving him to move forward.

If he slows down for even a moment, the outcome would be unthinkable!

If it were others, they would have exhausted their mind and body, crushed into pulp by such despairing circumstances. Only Fang Yuan, by racking his brain and thinking out of the box, could manage to find a chance of survival amidst looming disaster.

But even though he tried so hard, the situation was not taking a turn for the better.

Like now, he was facing a new problem.

Immortal essence stones were running out!

He had first sold large numbers of Immortal Gu recipes and obtained twenty-eight immortal essence stones. But after some purchases, especially the current bulk purchase, his spending was too high and his funds were running out.

Right now, Fang Yuan had four immortal essence stones left. But there were too many areas he needed to invest in.

Helpless, he had to stop investing in the wolf groups.

But Fang Yuan's original plan was to dual cultivate strength and enslavement path. Now that he had a second aperture, this plan was taking form.

Three things dictated an enslavement path Gu Master's strength.

Firstly, it was the size of the enslaved beast group.

Secondly, it was the enslavement path Gu worms that the Gu Master had.

The third was the enslavement path Gu Master's soul. The deeper the foundation of their soul, the more beasts they could enslave, and the stronger beast kings they could control. The time that they could manipulate beast groups to battle would lengthen as well.

"After my purchase, my wolf group's size is already second-rate in northern plains' mortal plane. The first-rate enslavement masters are still the three of them — Ma Zun, Jiang Bao Ya, and Yang Po Ying."

"But my enslavement path Gu worms were all from Chang Shan Yin. They are only rank four, I have to get them to rank five so as to deal with the great battle in northern plains."

"Thankfully, despite Dang Hun mountain's slow death, it can still be used. With guts Gu, my expenditure is greatly reduced, but other than that, I still need large numbers of wolf soul Gu to improve my wolfman soul."

Facing his cultivation requirements, the immortal essence stones in Fang Yuan's possession seemed lacking. Bulking purchasing wolves only fulfilled one of the three aspects in Fang Yuan's enslavement cultivation.

Next, he bought a few more Gu recipes in treasure yellow heaven, as well as many refinement materials and the rank five wolf soul Gu that he desperately needed, getting a total of eighteen.

This way, he spent another immortal essence stone, he only had three left.

Fang Yuan placed his sights on relic Gu next.

His second aperture Gu was just formed, it is only rank one initial stage, it had to cultivate from the beginning.

But where would Fang Yuan get the time to cultivate? By using relic Gu to boost the cultivation level, he could bring out this second aperture's usefulness in the short run.

Even though he had such intentions, the immortal essence stones were almost used up already, Fang Yuan could only buy the green copper, red steel, white silver, and yellow gold relic Gu.

Next, he chose the body modification Gu worm.

The body is like a sack, it holds the soul. When the soul is strong, while the body is unable to hold it, it would form a bottleneck, and the soul's growth would be halted.

Similarly, if the body was not strong enough, the one had to be careful when using strength path Gu worms. If they overexerted themselves, they might break their own bones and tear their flesh before even hitting the enemy.

After Fang Yuan finished his transaction, he had only two immortal essence stones left.

These two stones were kept to deal with emergency situations.

For the next two days, Fang Yuan did not leave Hu Immortal blessed land, he cultivated on Dang Hun mountain.

"This is the final guts Gu." On a cliff, Fang Yuan grabbed this Gu.

Splat.

With a crisp sound, yellow-brown mud flowed out.

This was a rotten Gu, its body was corroded by the gruel mud Immortal Gu, it lost the ability to enhance souls.

"Dang Hun mountain's vitality is falling, the number of intact guts Gu is dropping as well... but, after these few days of strengthening, due to the huge number, my soul still managed to reach thousand man soul."

Fang Yuan closed his eyes, feeling the soul in his body.

This thousand man soul was much more solid than before, it gave off a dense feeling. Almost as if it was stuffed inside Fang Yuan's body, it gave a feeling of almost bursting out.

Thousand man soul was the signature trademark of an enslavement expert. Back then, Chang Shan Yin had thousand man soul.

Fang Yuan opened his eyes, with a thought, he called little Hu Immortal, and teleported himself into Dang Hun palace.

Sitting on his cushion, he took out a white silver relic Gu.

Through his earlier tests, there was no problems with this relic Gu, thus Fang Yuan injected his primeval essence into it.

A moment later, he opened his eyes, after inspecting the second aperture, he nodded in satisfaction.

"Second aperture has reached rank three peak stage too."

This way, Fang Yuan's first aperture was rank five peak stage, having crystal purple primeval essence. Second aperture was rank three peak stage, having snow silver primeval essence.

Although snow silver primeval essence could not compare to crystal purple primeval essence, it could still provide some help to Fang Yuan.

After all, in the northern plains contest for the Imperial Court, rank three Gu Masters were the absolute vital force.

"After I use the yellow gold relic Gu, I will reach rank four peak stage, that would be the best. Of course, the happiest thing is that the second aperture gives me the option for another vital Gu. This way, I alone can have two vital Gu."

Chapter 494: All of you, get lost!

Throwing aside expendable Gu, a Gu Master's first choice of a Gu worm would become their vital Gu.

The relation between vital Gu and a Gu Master were very close; one could even say their lives were connected.

No matter which side was injured, the other side would also be implicated.

Vital Gu had one advantage which other Gu did not have — that was no matter how severe the backlash was after Gu refinement failure, the vital Gu would still preserved.

Thus, most Gu Masters would regard the vital Gu as their core Gu. Generally, the Gu Master's strongest Gu worm is their vital Gu.

Once a vital Gu forms, it would be difficult to change it.

But that was not absolute.

If the Gu Master found an extremely good Gu worm and wanted to cultivate it as their vital Gu, they could destroy their original vital Gu.

But this type of action was extremely dangerous.

Once the vital Gu was destroyed, the Gu Master would suffer enormous backlash; at the least, they would suffer heavy injuries, and the worst outcome meant death.

After rebirth, Fang Yuan's vital Gu was Spring Autumn Cicada which had been hibernating in the center of his first aperture with no movement.

Now, he had a second aperture and had a chance to choose a second vital Gu.

He had been able to guess this from the Gu recipe, but Fang Yuan was still happy after truly finding that it gave him this chance to choose.

'Which Gu should I choose as my second vital Gu?'

Immortal Gu could be taken out of the equation.

Fang Yuan's second aperture was only a rank three mortal aperture, unable to store Immortal Gu. Spring Autumn Cicada was a special situation.

Besides Spring Autumn Cicada, Fang Yuan also had two other Immortal Gu - Fixed Immortal Travel and Gruel Mud.

But Immortal Gu Gruel Mud was an expendable Gu; if he made it his vital Gu, after it is used up, Fang Yuan will suffer heavy backlash. Fang Yuan naturally would not do such a stupid thing.

As for Fixed Immortal Travel, it was far away at the poisonous grassland so there was no need to mention it.

Without much hesitation, Fang Yuan made his decision.

It was rank three all-out effort Gu!

He was cultivating strength path and enslavement path. All-out effort Gu was a must and was also the most ideal core of the strength path.

Previously, Fang Yuan intended to use undefeated hundred battles Gu to ensure the safety of the all-out effort Gu during Gu refinement.

But due to many reasons and because of the situation, Fang Yuan had no choice but to use undefeated hundred battles Gu to refine Immortal Gu Fixed Immortal Travel.

As long as all-out effort Gu became his second vital Gu, Fang Yuan would no longer need to worry losing this precious Gu worm after Gu refinement failure.

Two days passed in an instant.

Fang Yuan returned to the northern plains through stargate Gu.

The time flow in Hu Immortal blessed land was five times faster than the outside world. Fang Yuan had spent two days in the blessed land but only a night had passed in northern plains.

It was crack of dawn.

From the edge of the sky, gentle purple and white colors started to appear.

As the sun started to rise, the grass started to gradually look glossy green from the previously dark color.

The crescent lake reflected the dazzling sunlight and sparkled.

The light of dawn shone upon Fang Yuan's face, he smiled and looked at the side.

The sparse wolf group was once again replenished with many white wolf figures.

These were water wolves with a size that crossed ten thousand; a water wolf myriad beast king led them along with 6 thousand wolf kings under it.

As for the vermillion flame wolf group, night wolf group, mutated beasts and so on, Fang Yuan did not bring them.

It would be too abrupt and conspicuous if he brought them all out at once.

Fang Yuan was disguising as Chang Shan Yin and wanted to properly manage this identity, thus he had to avoid such exposing actions.

Water wolves were different.

This action was proclaiming he was taking in wild water wolves. The water wolves' appearance was easily explained. But if night wolf beast emperor or those mutated wolves appeared, it would make no sense.

"I will have to continue taking in the wild water wolf groups." Fang Yuan rode on the hump wolf and with a thought, the whole wolf group again moved out majestically towards the next destination.

Three days later, on a certain area beside the crescent lake.

Gu Masters from two tribes were furiously looking at each other.

"Zhong Fei You, your Zhong tribe is too much of a bully, these five black skin fat beetles are clearly our tribe's goods, but you actually dare to seize it out in the open!" One tribe's tribe leader Chai Zhang shouted.

"Bullshit! We have already agreed to our territories with this water wolf nest as the boundary. And this is our Chai tribe's territory. As these five black skin fat beetles have come to our Zhong tribe's territory, they naturally become ours!" Zhong tribe leader Zhong Fei You sneered.

Chai tribe's Gu Masters were furious at such words.

Chai Zhang's face even flushed with anger as he lashed out: "Shameless! Our Chai tribe is moving out our camp to hurry to the heroes assembly, and naturally we need to pass through this place."

Zhong Fei You's eyes shone with a chilly light as he grinned: "So this is your Chai tribe's mistake. You could have detoured this place, why would you walk into my tribe's campground?"

Chai tribe's Gu Masters were raging. Zhong tribe camp was placed at a tricky position, occupying the main road. It would be even more troublesome if Chai tribe was to take a detour; the way around had at least three myriad beast groups. Zhong tribe's action was intentionally extorting them.

"Zhong Fei You, aren't your actions too unsightly?" Chai Zhang gnashed his teeth.

Zhong Fei You shrugged his shoulders without concern, laughing coldly: "If your Chai tribe doesn't accept it, we can fight it out."

Cha tribe's Gu Masters' momentum slowed down.

Chai tribe was a small scale tribe while Zhong tribe had expanded into a mid-scale tribe two years ago.

Zhong tribe was strong; if they fought, Chai tribe would definitely suffer!

As the Chai tribe's leader, Chai Zhang was naturally clear of this. He had thought of retreating but three of these black skin fat beetles were holding their tribe's most precious goods.

These goods had been meticulously gathered and were what the Chai tribe wanted to use with, to side with Liu Wen Wu. If he had to give them up, Chai Zhang was of course very unwilling.

In the end, should he fight or retreat?

Just as the two sides were in a stalemate and Chai Zhang was hesitating, from far away wolf howls resounded.

Howl... Howl...

Wolf howls came one after another, endlessly. At the same time, the sounds of a large number of beasts rushing forward were also transmitted to everyone.

"This lineup..."

"Wolf group!"

"It is noon right now and the water wolves' nest is nearby, how could a wild wolf group come here?"

Zhong tribe and Chai tribe's people shifted their gaze towards the location of the sound, as if they were facing a great enemy.

They soon saw the majestic wolf army rushing towards them like a river, through the sparse jungle.

In this wolf group, there were strong night wolves, the defensive turtleback wolves, outstanding wind wolves and the white fur water wolves, which were the majority.

Different from other wolf groups, they were moving harmoniously like an army. There was only one reason for this.

Chai Zhang's heart thumped as he immediately thought of a person - Chang Shan Yin!

Zhong Fei You's expression became extremely unsightly.

Their Zhong tribe also wanted to side with Lord Liu Wen Wu, thus they were coveting after these goods of Chai tribe, but they had never thought someone would upset the whole situation at the crucial moment.

As the wolf group approached closer, the Gu Masters of the two tribes became restless.

"Such a large wolf group!" Someone could not help exclaiming in shock.

"Gasp... this scale, there are at least twenty eight thousand turtleback wolves, fifteen thousand night wolves, and the wind wolves are even more than the night wolves. The water wolves are the largest with about thirty two thousand." Someone drew in a cold breath and calculated the numbers with his rich experience.

The wolf group's size was really too big. They spread open grandly, forming a half-moon shaped formation and covering the two tribes.

Zhong tribe and Chai tribe's Gu Masters were instantly surrounded; and with the crescent lake behind them, they were in an unfavorable situation.

"Didn't they say Chang Shan Yin suffered huge losses after attacking Pei, Bei and Zheng tribes? Why does he still have so many wolves left?!" Chai Zhang's lips turned dry; the dense wolf group not only covered them, there were still many of them left who were hiding in the forest, their figures indistinct.

Zhong Fei You could not keep up his relaxed attitude from before. He looked at the large numbers of thousand beast kings and myriad beast kings among the wolf group; his heart stuck in his throat.

Enslavement path was different from other paths; they could change the situation with just a lone force.Normal enslavement path Gu Masters were already people who should not be underestimated, let alone Chang Shan Yin!

Zhong Fei You understood clearly that these wolf groups were enough to annihilate their Zhong tribe two-three times over and still have enough strength left!

Simply because they were in the wild with no obstacles to rely on. They did not have the walls of their camp, they were not in formation, they did not have time to rest and also no time to recover their primeval essence.

One hump wolf carrying Fang Yuan on its back leisurely walked out of the thin forest.

"Chang Shan Yin!" Zhong Fei You and Chai Zhang similarly called out.

In an instant, countless eyes gathered on Fang Yuan's face.

Fang Yuan expressionlessly rode on the hump wolf with his back upright just like Chang Shan Yin's habit.

His sharp gaze swept through everyone. He did not speak, but his closed lips was sufficient to display Chang Shan Yin's proud and aloof aura vividly.

Zhong tribe and Chai tribe's Gu Masters were silent. They only felt an enormous rock pressing down on their heart; the atmosphere seemed to freeze and made it difficult for them to breathe.

Especially when they thought of the Wolf King Chang Shan Yin challenging three tribes in one night, many started to shiver.

Pei, Bei and Zheng tribe had been mid-scale tribe for long time. While Chai tribe was only a small scale tribe and Zhong tribe had only advanced to mid-scale tribe not long ago.

Zhong Fei You and Chai Zhang glanced at each other, seeing the graveness and the intent to cooperate in each other's eyes.

The two were similarly agonized: Just now, they were both about to fight, and now they had the hearts to ally. This play of fate really made one not know whether to cry or laugh.

"Lord Chang Shan Yin, your fame is well known to me, Zhong Fei You..." Zhong Fei You gritted his teeth and bowed deeply towards Fang Yuan.

No one felt that the grand tribe leader Zhong Fei You's action was inappropriate. The other was Chang Shan Yin!

But Zhong Fei You had yet to finish speaking when Fang Yuan waved his hand and indifferently said: "All of you get lost, don't block me."

Zhong Fei You's eyes widened, his eyes showing an unconcealable humiliation.

But he did not retort and instead lowered his head, bowing towards Fang Yuan again before turning around to his Zhong tribesmen: "Retreat."

Chai Zhang discerned the situation and also immediately shouted: "We are also retreating."

Immediately, both the tribes started retreating far away.

Soon, the crowded lakeside only had the wolf groups and Fang Yuan, one person.

Of course, there were also those three slow moving black skin fat beetles.

Fang Yuan glanced at these three black skin fat beetles without interest. The things the two tribes were fighting for, did not have enough attractive force towards him.

He waved his hand and the water wolf group immediately rushed into the water, circling and attacking the water wolf nest here.

Chapter 495: Grey-white Stone Slab

The water wolf den here had four thousand water wolves, it was a thousand beast group.

Although water wolves rarely stepped foot on land, when their homes were invaded, that would be another issue.

After sensing Fang Yuan's wolf group approaching, this group of wild water wolves attacked together, engaging with Fang Yuan's wolves.

Facing obstruction, Fang Yuan's wolf group stopped their movement.

But he snorted, activating wolf howl Gu, sending three groups of reinforcements to help.

The wild water wolves only managed to hold on for a moment before being unable to hold the pressure, immediately overwhelmed as they lost completely.

Far away.

"Tribe leader, our things are still there." A Chai tribe elder looked indignantly.

Chai tribe leader sighed deeply: "Nevermind, let it be, it is better than losing our lives."

"Shouldn't we stay and watch? A person like Chang Shan Yin, he might not be interested in these three black skin fat armor worms." Another Chai tribe elder was still hopeful.

But Chai Zhang understood the truth, he snorted: "If you are not worried about offending Chang Shan Yin and attracting his slaughter, then stay."

This Chai tribe elder's face froze.

"Hmph, this idea, do you think Zhong tribe can't think of it? Even if Chang Shan Yin doesn't want them, we will not be able to take these resources! Sigh, with such an expert like Chang Shan Yin here, we can't stay in crescent lake any longer, we should set off now, and leave quickly." Chai Zhang waved his hand, his tone filled with helplessness, but also anger and weakness.

Chai tribe was only a small size tribe, they were weak. Especially with the ten year blizzard approaching, as well as the fight for the Imperial Court, it will be an era of turmoil where northern plains is engulfed in battles and chaos.

A tribe like Chai tribe was like a tiny boat amidst the chaos, being blown by the winds and waves, they can only ride on weakly. Only by clinging onto a stronger force can they increase their chance of survival.

Chai tribe left after packing up, without a bit of delay.

A moment later, Zhong tribe's investigative Gu Master reported to Zhong Fei You with some afterfear: "Lord, Wolf King was victorious, with just a wave of his hand, he exterminated that wolf den. Out of the four thousand water wolves, he recruited three thousand, yet he only lost three hundred."

Zhong Fei You and the Zhong tribe higher-ups shuddered upon hearing this.

Such loss to gain ratio was terrifying! No wonder this Wolf King's wolf group could be replenished so quickly.

"Lord tribe leader, you did not see personally, Chang Shan Yin's manipulation was otherworldly, he is truly skilled!" Investigative Gu Master wiped the sweat off his forehead as he added.

Zhong Fei You snorted, refusing to put his own tribe down, shamelessly saying: "Chang Shan Yin has a water wolf myriad beast king. The leader of this group of wild wolves is only a thousand beast king. Once they battle, the water wolf group would face great suppression, their battle strength would be weakened. It is easy to recruit them because of them. What about those three black skin fat armor beetles?"

The investigative Gu Master answered: "They were all taken by Chang Shan Yin."

Zhong Fei You's expression turned ugly.

He tried to steal a chicken only to end up losing the rice used to lure it[1], not only did he fail to get the resources, he even made an enemy out of Chai tribe.

Speaking of which, Chai tribe and Zhong tribe were in-laws, they had a close relationship. Otherwise, they would not have moved together, and when they set up camp, they chose to live closely to each other, to look out for one another.

But, the world is cruel.

Right now, the Imperial Court competition was not just about benefits for Zhong tribe and Chai tribe, it was about their survival.

Their relationship was only a method to defend their interests. When it was time to abandon the other, they would do so without hesitation.

In the main tent, there was a pressurizing silence.

Long after, Zhong Fei You sighed: "A person like Chang Shan Yin, even if we gather all our strength, we cannot compete against him. But northern plains is not his alone, there are three enslavement master stronger than him! We will note down this battle, and after we go to Lord Liu Wen Wu, one day, we will take revenge!"

Zhong tribe elders nodded in agreement.

Not long after, Zhong tribe set off as well.

Using a total of nine days, Fang Yuan led the wolf group that had expanded drastically in size back to Ge tribe camp.

Ge Guang led the Ge tribe higher-ups as he went out to welcome Fang Yuan back.

"Lord supreme elder, your cultivation recovered?!" When Ge Guang felt Fang Yuan's rank four peak stage aura, he was shocked and delighted.

Fang Yuan nodded, replying plainly: "It recovered, it was about time anyway."

Back then, Chang Shan Yin's cultivation was rank four peak stage. Later, he fought a grand battle with Ha Tu Gu and was injured to the point of nearing death, going into hibernation.

But now, Fang Yuan's first aperture had reached rank five peak stage. Even with northern plains' suppression, he still had rank five initial stage aura.

His current rank four peak stage aura was only due to the effect of breath concealment Gu.

As for his second aperture, because it first appeared in northern plains, there was no suppression and it was still rank three peak stage.

Keeping it secret for now, and then slowly releasing the aura, not only could be keep it as a trump card, he could even allow others to gradually accept his improvement without suspicion.

Fang Yuan followed the Ge tribe higher-ups back to camp.

Ge tribe camp was expanding, along the way, construction could be seen everywhere. Large numbers of mortal slaves or even Gu Master slaves were being mercilessly utilized.

Winner takes all, this was the cruelty of war, and also the beauty of it.

Ge tribe higher-ups were cheerful and joyous, after Ge tribe took down Bei tribe and Zheng tribe, they expanded greatly, as they tried to digest this new found force, the entire tribe's strength had increased greatly.

The biggest problem now is the lack of slavery Gu. If we had large numbers of slavery Gu, we could send these slave Gu Masters into battle. This will greatly increase our battle strength!" Ge Guang exclaimed.

Slavery Gu was a Gu worm that could control people.

But man is the spirit of all being, they were much harder to manipulate than beasts. The burden on the soul was greater, especially when enslaving Gu Masters with strong soul.

Thus, in general, a Gu Master rarely controlled more than five slaves. As for slave Gu Masters, the numbers were fewer. Normally, a Gu Master could only control one slave Gu Master, any more and the burden on their soul would be too much.

As for those slave Gu Masters with strong souls, to control them, one's soul had to be even stronger.

Fang Yuan naturally had the ability to get lots of slavery Gu.

But if he did so, he would expose many things. Ge tribe was only a chess piece in his plans, he did not need to worry for them to that extent.

"Next, I need to continue cultivating in seclusion. You will help me feed this wolf group." Fang Yuan spoke.

"Yes." Ge Guang quickly replied, but his heart was crying out.

Now that Ge tribe was expanding, they were facing a huge lack of manpower. The wolf group was too huge, the burden of feeding them would be great, this would expend a lot of labour for Ge tribe!

But Fang Yuan's next sentence made this young Ge tribe leader joyous —

"I brought a lot of resources back this time, they were obtained when I was hunting wolves. Use them as you wish, but remember, the things on those three black skin fat armor beetles are mine, safeguard them for me properly."

"Yes, Lord Supreme Elder!"

For the next few days, Fang Yuan stayed inside Ge tribe camp, cultivating bitterly in seclusion.

His second aperture's cultivation level needed to increase. Although he had thousand man soul, he still needed wolf soul Gu to strength himself, becoming a thousand man soul level wolfman soul.

At the same time, his strength path also needed improvement, he needed to continue using jun strength Gu.

When he needed to relax, he would take out the items on those three black skin fat armor beetles and inspect them.

These resources that Chai tribe painstakingly gathered were very strange, they were all grey-white stone slabs.

But the surface of these stone slabs were filled with black ink lines. Some were straight while others were curled, there were thin and thick lines. The lines were drawn over one another, some looked like letters while others looked like drawings of scenery.

If these stone slabs were real, that would be a huge deal. Tracing their source, they were from the immemorial era, Ren Zu's ninth daughter, Carefree Wisdom Heart.

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> states that in order to save wisdom Gu, Carefree Wisdom Heart came to the Qian Kun Crystal Wall.

Qian Kun Crystal Wall was straight from top to bottom, it floated in mid air like a giant mirror.

In the mirror, there was a book mountain.

On the book mountain, there was a ink waterfall, landing on the mountain rocks to form a literature spring.

The ink waterfall continued to flow, as it landed on the literature spring, water splashed about. These black color splashes flew in the air as the water droplets formed into words.

This was the origin of the hundred clan writing system in the Gu Master world.

After Qian Kun Crystal Wall was broken, it turned into numerous grey-white stone slabs.

Legends say that if one gathered all of the stone slabs, they could piece back Qian Kun Crystal Wall and the Gu Master would be able to enter book mountain again.

If one looked at the history of humanity, they would find that generations of Gu Masters, Gu Immortals, or even Immortal and Demon Venerables collected these stone slabs before.

Precisely so, large numbers of counterfeit stone slabs appeared quickly.

These fake stone slabs were indistinguishable to real stone slabs, unless the Gu Master was an experienced appraiser.

In history, the most authoritative and accomplished appraiser Gu Immortal was treasure yellow heaven's owner, Daoist Countless Treasure who owned treasure light Gu.

But even he could only identify them with an accuracy of seventy to eighty percent.

There were simply too many fake stone slabs, too many Gu Masters tried making fakes, even Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable himself.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable purposely created many fakes and scammed many Gu Immortals. The fakes that he made were very convincing, they could even surpass the real deal.

Fang Yuan had never thought of collecting all the stone slabs and restoring book mountain.

Even a rank nine Gu Venerable did not succeed, Fang Yuan had no such drive to waste his effort.

He was only resting now, and tried appraising these stone slabs.

In his previous life, he had trained his eyes to be discerning, he had also once sold and created these fake stone slabs.

Right now, he tried appraising these stone slabs, removing the fakes, it was a form of relaxation.

But unexpectedly, just when he was playing with one of the stone slabs, something happened.

This stone slab that he had evaluated to be a fake, after Fang Yuan injected his primeval essence, the ink lines started to move mystically.

[1] Lit meaning: Fail to achieve his aims while being even worse off than before. Back

Chapter 496: Di Qiu Inheritance

The ink lines changed and morphed randomly, after a long while, it settled and formed a terrain map.

At the center of the map, there was a heightened land. There were no cliffs as the slope was very gentle, there was an opening that resembled a tunnel.

On this place, two words were indicated — Di Qiu.

All around Di Qiu, there were swamps and forests, at the southwest corner, there was a river.

At the lower area of the map, there were four lines — "light in the soil, shine up to a hundred thousand feet high, swimming in the sky for a hundred li, praising plum fragrant snow."

Fang Yuan muttered it silently, but after a long time, he had no idea what it was saying[1].

These four lines were like poems, or not. They sounded like Gu recipes, but unlikely.

But Fang Yuan was sure about one thing, these four riddle-like lines were definitely clues left behind on purpose.

More amazingly, after the map formed for a while, it faded from the grey-white stone slab.

Soon, this stone slab in Fang Yuan's hands turned white, there was nothing left on it.

But when Fang Yuan closed his eyes, he could easily recall every detail on this map, at an extreme clarity.

This was not his outstanding memory, instead —

"Painting idea Gu. A painting idea Gu was once used on this stone slab. This Gu can turn into scenery images and etch itself into a Gu Master's memory, so that they will never forget it."

Light of comprehension flashed across Fang Yuan's eyes.

Evidently, this was an inheritance that a Gu Master left behind.

In order to appraise these stone slabs, Fang Yuan had taken many crystal clear Gu, sunshine Gu, moonshine Gu etc from Ge tribe's inventory.

Just earlier, he had used these Gu worms and injected his primeval essence skillfully to test them.

These methods were unique ways to appraise grey-white stone slabs.

In the end, these methods became the key to activating the secret of this stone slab.

"The Gu Master who created this stone slab counterfeit not only used painting idea Gu, he also used other Gu worms to form this effect. This is an inheritance from a Gu Master, in order to find the inheritor, he spent quite a bit of effort."

Fang Yuan smiled, to think that under such a situation, he obtained the clues to a Gu Master's inheritance.

Inheritance was one of the cultural identity of this world.

Be it righteous or demonic Gu Masters, they would choose to create an inheritance, to leave behind an imprint unique to them in this world.

Although he was lucky to receive clues about this inheritance, Fang Yuan did not show much joy.

In his previous five hundred years, he had encountered many of such situations, he was used to it.

Most Gu Masters would leave their inheritances behind.

Therefore, inheritances were always in ample numbers. There were Gu Immortal inheritances, rank four or rank five Gu Master inheritances, these were the truly valuable ones. But there were also many rank two or three inheritances, even those made by rank one Gu Masters.

With the passing of time and natural or man-made disasters, many Gu Masters often leave disappointed when exploring an inheritance.

Some inheritances were destroyed long ago. Others were already taken by the time someone found it. For some inheritances, they were demonic inheritances, traps created by someone meticulously, those mentally twisted Gu Masters who wanted to take revenge on the world before dying.

"I am too busy right now, I cannot abandon my plans for such a vague inheritance. Moreover, with just this map, where am I going to find that 'Di Qiu' place anyway."

Getting Di Qiu inheritance map was only a tiny accident, Fang Yuan quickly forgot about it.

In the following days, he continued cultivating while refining Gu.

From what he gained from the two tribes, he saw an improved recipe and found it interesting.

Taking out a few Gu worms from Ge tribe's warehouse, he spent a few days, and after failing twice, he refined the rank three eagle wings to the rank four eagle rise Gu.

Speaking of which, this eagle wings Gu was nearly unused in his hands. After Fang Yuan left poison grassland, he came to Hong Yan valley and reached Ge tribe camp. When he walked around the few markets that were set up during his stay, he bought it.

Wolf King Chang Shan Yin was not a flying expert. Fang Yuan would not use this master level technique easily.

This was a trump card, once he used it, it would shock the world.

Chang Shan Yin went missing for more than ten years, it was easy to make an excuse. Who knows what opportunities and inheritances he came across during the years, why couldn't he become a flying expert?

A few days after refining eagle rise Gu, Ge Guang visited Fang Yuan personally and brought the latest news with him.

"Ma tribe had completely absorbed Fei tribe, and became Tian Chuan heroes assembly's main character..."

"At Meng Qiu heroes assembly, Nu Er tribe's representative is a rank five Gu Master Nu Er Tu."

"Cao Fu's Zhao tribe? Mm, that Zhao Lian Yun, Ma Hong Yun's wife, the wondrous woman who became a wisdom path Gu immortal in the future, is only a young innocent girl now."

"No matter what, Ma tribe gained so much attention now, they definitely planning something big, to fight for the coveted throne of the Lord of the Imperial Court. This is the same as in my previous life's memories. But will Ma Hong Yun appear?"

Fang Yuan thought about it as he recalled.

He could vaguely remember that during this contest, Ma tribe showed outstanding strength, especially during the start, they had strong troops and high morale, they defeated many strong foes.

But a tall tree is the first to face destruction, soil that is nearest to the water will be the first to be swept away by the currents.

Ma tribe gained too much attention, they were targeted by experienced tribes of the Huang Jin family, after several tough battles, although they won, they had great losses and were weakened.

Eventually, Ma tribe was forced by Hei Lou Lan, facing encirclement. Hei tribe had a great number of people, but Ma tribe had fortified defense, they were able to protect themselves.

Hei Lou Lan brought his troops personally but was unable to gain victory, seeing the approaching blizzard, he had to relent.

After Ma tribe submitted to Hei tribe, they gained the rights to enter the Imperial Court. Ma Hong Yun, with his absurd luck, also managed to get in.

Precisely because he used this opportunity, he obtained the partial inheritance of an Immortal Venerable inside the Eighty-Eight Edge Treasure Building, which became the foundation for his rise in the future.

At this moment, Ge Guang spoke, asking Fang Yuan: "Lord Supreme Elder, most of the heroes assembly are taking place fervently now. Our Yu Tian heroes assembly also has many experts and competitors, engaging in fierce competition. Among them, Liu Wen Wu and Hei Lou Lan are the two tribes with the greatest strength, the other forces cannot compete with them."

"Right now, only our tribe is still left in crescent lake. Even the large-sized tribes have set off for Yu Tian, to attend the heroes assembly. After these days of recuperating, we have already digested most of our battle spoils, and stabilized the situation. If we don't set off now, we might not make it in time."

Fang Yuan nodded.

The heroes assembly was a place where forces probed each other and created powerful alliances.

Although Ge tribe gained strength quickly, they were only a mid-sized tribe. If they did not attend the heroes assembly, and detached themselves from the rules of the game, they would be ostracised, that had a huge impact on them.

Although Ge tribe leader was Ge Guang, every since Fang Yuan took the role of supreme elder, his decision was already the number one priority of Ge tribe.

During these days, Ge Guang and the other higher-ups were starting to get anxious.

They did not have Fang Yuan's memories, they did not know that during this Yu Tian heroes assembly, there would be a huge contest, and thus it ended the latest.

Fang Yuan had made his arrangements in light of this.

He waved his hand, saying to Ge Guang: "Although the tribe has stabilized, that is only on the surface. In the dark, there are still many people whose hearts are not with us. If we really went to battle, even with a mid-sized tribe's scale, we would not be able to unleash the corresponding strength."

Ge Guang lowered his head, listening to Fang Yuan's teachings patiently.

Fang Yuan continued: "Yu Tian heroes assembly's contest has just entered the climax. We are in no rush to get there. For now, we are going to onion valley."

"Onion valley?" Ge Guang showed some confusion.

Onion valley was a place like crescent lake, it was a wide valley overgrown with green onions, it was a unique habitat.

There, large numbers of beast groups lived, at a larger scale than crescent lake. of course, there were countless wild Gu worms.

Among them, there was the extremely famous rank two Gu, onion explosion Gu.

This Gu looked like an onion, but it was not green or white, instead it was red like fire. Once activated, it would emit an intense odor.

When wild beasts smell it, they would turn irascible, showing their wild nature, they would be more likely to attack people.

Thus, onion valley was much more dangerous than crescent lake.

Why did he want to go to such a dangerous place instead of attending the heroes assembly?

But soon, Fang Yuan said his reason: "Very long ago, I bred some wolves in onion valley, after these years of growing, they should've matured and expanded."

"So that's it!" Ge Guang's eyes shone.

It was very resource expending to nurture an enslavement path Gu Master, just the food needed to feed their wild beasts daily was an astronomical figure.

These days, in order to take care of Fang Yuan's wolves, Ge tribe had expended a lot of their resources, causing Ge Guang to wince in pain and have a clear understanding of this.

Thus, many enslavement path Gu Master would choose to let beast groups grow on their own.

They would choose some appropriate locations and leave some beasts behind as the seeds.

Once in a while, they would go to check their growth, if the beast group expanded, they would have profited.

Of course, the chances of having gains was low, in most situations, the beast groups would shrivel, or even get exterminated.

But even so, most enslavement path Gu Masters would choose to do so.

After all, enslavement path was a huge burden on resources. How many mortal Gu Master could be like Fang Yuan, sending their beast groups into the blessed land?

After Fang Yuan said that, Ge Guang immediately understood.

"After so many years, the wolf king is still around, but I do not know how many wolves there are left. But this time when we attend the heroes assembly, the more wolves there are, the better it is for us. We will have greater authority and voice if our wolf group is larger."

Hearing Fang Yuan's words, Ge Guang nodded, agreeing: "Lord Supreme Elder is right, then when do we set off?"

"Today." Fang Yuan said.

[1] Neither did I honestly. Back

Chapter 497: Mo Shi Kuang

The sky was pure and azure, and the ground was like a sea of jade.

The soil here was especially fertile with water plants growing lushly, reaching up to a man's knee.

This was the famous Yu Tian of Northern Plains, reputed as one of the most abundant pasturelands. Now, people were gathering here with their banners fluttering in the wind.

Yu Tian's heroes assembly had already lasted for half a month.

In the first week, every tribe was shouting their own slogans, causing clamor and disturbance. But gradually, all the forces began to join up through alliances. And now, the two strongest forces remained.

One side was Liu tribe's Liu Wen Wu and another was Hei tribe's Hei Lou Lan.

At this moment, the two sides were valiantly confronting each other.

In the center of the people was built a spacious battle stage.

In the battle stage, two Northern Plains' Gu Masters were having an intense battle; both of them with rank four cultivation.

Outside the stage, everyone was looking at the battle intensely. Battles at tribe leader levels were not something they normally had a chance to observe.

Especially the two people on the stage; one righteous and another demonic, both were famous characters and had deep hatred against each other!

"Water Demon, hand over your life!" The middle aged Gu Master in the battle stage shouted and stamped his foot, jumping into the air.

In the air, he took a deep breath then breathed out a basket-sized dark flame towards his opponent.

Water Demon Hao Ji Liu's heart gave warning signs.

His eyes flashed with blue light as he crazily poured his yellow gold primeval essence into water wall Gu.

"Rise!"

He raised his two palms from bottom to top; his movement looked heavy as if he was lifting a weight of ten thousand catties.

Following his movement, boundless water vapor formed into a blue waterfall that rose up from the ground.

The waterfall charged up in reverse and then came down, forming an arch of thick water wall.

The dark flames slowly fell onto the water wall and was immediately extinguished.

"Huh?" The spectators were stunned. They were just about to ridicule Water Demon for making a big fuss over nothing, when suddenly the spark with only a bit of light left in it suddenly exploded!

BOOM!!!

The deafening explosion was like the crackling of the thunder.

Great amounts of flames rushed forth and evaporated the thick water wall into water vapor.

The strong impact created a frantic wind that rapidly spread everywhere.

But the storm could not get out of the stage. There were Gu Masters standing around the battle stage, activating their defensive Gu to form a round barrier that firmly guarded the stage.

"Such terrifying skill!"

"Such intense explosion has already neared the effect of a rank five Gu. This killer move has all along been concealed by Fire Prodigal Chai Ming!"

"Although Water Demon detected it, he still underestimated Lord Chai Ming's attack."

As the shocks from the explosion started to dull down, everyone started discussing and making a din with their gaze concentrating on the battle stage.

Even Hei Lou Lan and Liu Wen Wu were unable to take their eyes off.

But within the round light barrier, water vapor caused the stage to become a scene of white, making people unable to see clearly.

Everyone patiently waited and when the water vapor dispersed, Chai Ming was still standing tall on the stage while gasping and looking at the body under his foot: "Water Demon, did you think a day like this would come when you killed my father that year?!"

Water Demon Hao Ji Liu spurted out mouthfuls of blood showing a pained expression under Chai Ming's step.

"Hahaha, it is our win!"

"Lord Chai Ming is mighty!"

The spectators were dazed for a while before the side belonging to Liu Wen Wu burst out with extremely loud cheers.

On the other hand, on Hei Lou Lan's side, some onlookers were silent, while others had twitching mouths.

"Brother Lou Lan, you let me win[1]." Liu Wen Wu stood up from his seat and cupped his fists towards Hei Lou Lan with a smile, showing an elegant demeanour.

Hei Lou Lan looked like he had not expected this result as he coldly snorted. Just as he was about to say few words to keep up with the formalities...

Whoosh!

A soft sound sounded out, and Chai Ming looked towards his chest in shock.

A sharp water blade protruded out of his heart.

He looked back slowly to see his enemy Hao Ji Liu malevolently smiling towards him with his face full of blisters from the fire.

"This is the real body, then under my foot is...." Chai Ming was full of doubts.

Bang.

Coincidentally at this time, the 'Hao Ji Liu' under his feet turned into a pool of water and dispersed.

"It is water image Gu!" someone exclaimed.

"Water image Gu is a rare rank four Gu, but Water Demon clearly used many other methods to make his water image look so lifelike."

The sounds beside his ears allowed Chai Ming to understand the reason for his defeat.

"Despicable...." He said the last word of his life and died with an extremely indignant heart.

"Lord Chai Ming!" Many people cried out in sorrow.

"Brother!!" Chai tribe leader cried out with tears rapidly flowing down his eyes.

"Hahaha..." Hei Lou Lan threw his head back and laughed loudly without concealing his joy in the slightest. He raised his thumb towards the Water Demon, "Hao Ji Liu, you did great! Come, drink this wine!"

"Many thanks for lord's reward." Water Demon walked off the stage while grimacing in pain from the burns that were all over his body, but still accepted the cup of wine and drank it in one shot.

"Great wine!" He gave a flattering smile and returned the wine cup to Hei Lou Lan.

Although everyone disdained his shamelessness, his strength was displayed in front of them and with adding in his evil reputation, no one ridiculed or mocked him.

Hei Lou Lan waved his hand and spoke with his coarse and boorish voice: "Take this cup as a reward too. Yan Cui Er, come, bring me a new cup and pour me the best wine!"

Following his beckoning, a beautiful young girl in gorgeous attire obediently walked forward and places several wine cups in the table in front of Hei Lou Lan, then gracefully poured wine.

She was the eldest daughter of Yan tribe, Liu Wen Wu's fiancee; kidnapped by Water Demon Hao Ji Liu, she was offered to Hei Lou Lan as a meeting gift.

Hei Lou Lan hurriedly brought Yan Cui Er with him to the heroes assembly as an attack against Liu Wen Wu.

"Young master Liu, you can't win against me. Why not admit defeat and I shall return your fiancee to you?" Hei Lou Lan drank the wine in one shot and boorishly wiped off the wine that dropped to his beard.

"Hehehe, why does a man have to worry about having no wife? This girl is beautiful, but how could she replace the ambition inside my heart? Brother Lou Lan, haven't you heard of the old saying that women are like clothes while brothers are like our hands and feet? Since brother Lou Lan likes her, feel free to have her." Liu Wen Wu chuckled, showing not even a bit of anger.

"Young master Liu is really ambitious!"

"Young master Liu Wen Wu is a true man of our Northern Plains."

"Right, only such a person is worthy for us to follow!"

Liu tribe's side spoke one after another in support of Liu Wen Wu. Since it was a woman, they were not moved and did not have any thoughts of retorting.

This was the tradition of Northern Plains, regarding men as superior to women; w**omen are like clothes and brothers are like hands and feet — this saying was said by none other than Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

The bloodlines that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had passed on was collectively called as Huang Jin family.

Huang Jin family held the supreme authority in Northern Plains and also followed the old ancestor's tradition.

Since Liu Wen Wu could compete with Hei Lou Lan on equal terms, he was naturally not somebody easy to deal with. His words were instead secretly ridiculing Hei Lou Lan's lustful and unambitious nature, giving him an appearance that he was not infatuated with the mortal affairs.

Hei Lou Lan furiously snorted: "Your Liu tribe has always been able to talk well. But so what? Come come come, we will send our people on the stage and have a match!"

Liu Wen Wu's expression immediately changed a little.

Rather than Yan Cui Er, this was his greatest weak spot.

In the previous nine matches, he only won three matches and lost many experts. In the battle just before, he even lost the rank four expert Fire Prodigal Chai Ming.

Now, Hei Lou Lan was inviting him for battle again, and he had no choice but to accept.

If he did not accept, it would show his cowardice. The men of the Northern Plains despised a cowardly master the most.

But if he accepted, he was sure to lose more than win.

"Damn it, this bastard is intentionally challenging me to weaken my elite battle forces. But I cannot show weakness in the heroes assembly. Who should I send this time?"

Liu Wen Wu inwardly gritted his teeth, his gaze sweeping beside him.

There were people from both righteous and demonic path who had sided with him, with no lack of famous characters. But at this moment, they did not dare to meet Liu Wen Wu's gaze and either lowered their head or gazed far away.

Right as Liu Wen Wu's subordinates were feeling awkward, a loud voice came from a distance: "Big brother, no need to worry, send me!"

"Third brother has come." Liu Wen Wu was very happy at the voice.

The crowd parted and created a passage. The person who walked through the path caused everyone to be surprised.

This person was tall with a beefed up body, a fierce mouth and wide nose, skin as dark as ink, with snowy white lush hair and beard that seemed to blend together like a lion's mane.

The white hair and black skin was such an unusual appearance that caused the crowd to be dazed for a while before someone exclaimed, revealing this person's identity - "This person — is an inkman!"

Rockman, eggman, hairy man and inkman were not Ren Zu's descendants but variant men.

Inkman was also recorded in the Legends of Ren Zu. Their homeland was the Book Mountain.

The book mountain had an Ink Waterfall which would crash down on the Literature Spring, and the raging ink would fall on the rocks, forming inkmen.

"Big brother, little brother is late!" This inkman walked to the center of the site and bowed deeply towards Liu Wen Wu.

"Not late, not late. You came at a good time." Liu Wen Wu patted the inkman's shoulder and introduced him to everyone, "Everyone, this is Mo Shi Kuang, whom I have sworn brotherhood to at my early years."

"Mo Shi Kuang.... Young master Liu really has good vision, fooling around with an insignificant variant man. Alright, let my Viper Prince exchange moves with your brother."

From Hei Lou Lan's side, a male Gu Master with triangular eyes walked out.

"Come." Viper Prince walked to the battle stage and beckoned Mo Shi Kuang with his finger.

Mo Shi Kuang was provoked by this action and immediately jumped to the stage in fury: "Die!"

He clapped his two palms.

BOOM!

An invisible force swept everything, crushing towards viper prince without any obstacle.

"What? Qi path!? Rank four peak stage!! Shit..." Viper Prince could not even finish speaking before he was crushed into minced meat which then splattered everywhere.

The result was decided with one move.

Gasp...

The sounds of sucking in cold breath resounded in the air.

[1] It is polite in such culture to say 'thanks for let me have the victory', but it sounds like complete BM in English. Back

Chapter 498: Wolf Howl

Hei Lou Lan looked at Mo Shi Kuang with a gloomy face.

He had a bad premonition when Mo Shi Kuang stepped on the stage, but when Mo Shi Kuang smashed Viper Prince into minced meat with one move, Hei Lou Lan's heart turned heavy.

Mo Shi Kuang was a rank four peak stage expert and cultivated the Qi path.

Humans were the spirit of all living beings and could awaken their aperture through hope Gu.

Since variant men had the 'man' word on them, they naturally had higher spirituality than beasts. But this spirituality was much less than humans. Thus, only a few variant men could achieve such accomplishments in cultivating.

The absolute majority of the variant men would never awaken their aperture in their whole life, only a few fortunate ones could.

Only the fortunate among these fortunate ones could achieve success in cultivation.

This Mo Shi Kuang was one such special case.

"No wonder Liu Wen Wu made friends with Mo Shi Kuang, if it were me, I will also be willing to make friends with such a rank four peak stage expert." Realization dawned upon many people.

"Hey, the black-skinned fatty over there, is it you who wants to oppose my big brother? Come come, send your experts, let me slap your lackeys flat!" Mo Shi Kuang patted his chest and shouted loudly, a heroic aura showed in his boorish manner.

"Black-skinned fatty..." Hei Lou Lan's eyelids twitched and was extremely angry, 'Although I am fat, am I as black as you? This black boor is really hateful!"

"Hei Xiu Yi." Hei Lou Lan lightly called, his calm voice holding within a burning rage.

"Here!" A thin man immediately responded.

"Go teach this guy a lesson."

"Yes, lord tribe leader." Hei Xiu Yi agreed expressionlessly and unhurriedly walked.

His gaze was as indifferent as ice. As he walked, a black light blossomed over his whole light. The black light condensed and formed an armor that firmly covered him.

Next, a dim green halo flew over his head.

Fifty-six flying bone shields flew out and hovered beside him, completely shielding him.

Similarly, nine greyish-blue ghost faces whimpered and hovered around him.

By the time he stepped on the stage, he was completely armed and protected.

The crowd was in a clamor, Hei Lou Lan's words were very imposing but he actually sent a defensive Gu Master to bring out Mo Shi Kuang's trump cards.

"Ahahahaha." Mo Shi Kuang was instead very happy, "You are a guy asking for a beating, come, eat my punch!"

The moment he finished speaking, his right hand clenched into a fist and fiercely punched at Hei Xiu Yi.

Instantly, his fist strength condensed into a thick fist qi which fiercely slammed at Hei Xiu Yi who was dozens of steps away.

If it was someone else, just this punch would leave them handicapped if not dead.

But Hei Xiu Yi forcibly took on this punch; his upper body shook a bit, but his lower body did not move in the slightest.

"Good!" Mo Shi Kuang was very happy at this. He was different from ordinary inkmen, and was extremely addicted to fighting. He became thrilled at this moment and shouted, "Again!"

He slowly took off to the air, his snow-white hair swaying loosely with the air. After pulling open a distance from Hei Xiu Yi, he started to punch rapidly.

The punch shadows rained down like a torrential rain, the translucent fist qi shooting towards Hei Xiu Yi.

ORA ORA ORA!!!!

The fist qi exploded on Hei Xiu Yi's armor, producing a sound like that of thunder crackling.

But Hei Xiu Yi was like a giant reef that would stand tall no matter how many sea waves struck it.

The fifty six flying bone shields dispelled most of the force on him.

Some bits and pieces of fist qi struck at his black iron like armor, but it was of no use.

The scattered qi flow was absorbed completely by the nine ghost faces.

When Mo Shi Kuang's crazed attacks stopped, the halo above Hei Xiu Yi let out a dim green light and shone down upon the flying bone shield, completely repairing the cracks in the shields.

"Let me return this to you." Hei Xiu Yi sneered; the nine ghost faces opened their mouths together and spurted out dozens of fist qi.

Shockingly, Mo Shi Kuang's attack was returned back to him in full.

Mo Shi Kuang was dazed at the dozens of fist qi; the fist qi exploded on him one after another and he crashed down to the ground.

"Hahaha, rank four peak stage is nothing outstanding." Immediately, someone shouted outside the stage.

"Young master!" A person beside Liu Wen Wu nervously shouted, "Hei Xiu Yi is one of the three commanders of the black banner troops; a rank four upper stage Gu Master specialized in defense. Should we call Mo Shi Kuang back?"

"Don't worry." Liu Wen Wu was not worried and instead had a joyful smile as he looked at Hei Lou Lan then at Hei Xiu Yi at the stage, "My third brother is extremely addicted to fighting. The stronger the opponent is, the more excited he becomes. Hehe, watch the show unfold now."

"Hahaha... refreshing, so refreshing." Mo Shi Kuang suddenly let out a crazed laughter and jumped up from the ground.

His eyes turned as red as fire and he looked at Hei Xiu Yi with a burning gaze.

"You are somewhat interesting, worthy of me using half my strength." Mo Shi Kuang said earnestly.

Hei Xiu Yi was naturally not happy: "Hmph, boastful guy, give me all you've got!"

"HAAAAAAH!" Mo Shi Kuang's body shook, an intense inhuman aura like that of lions or bears erupted from his body, oppressing everyone's hearts.

Whoosh!

He rushed to the sky with overflowing might like that of a demon god, and lifted his right leg.

"Here it comes!" He excitedly shouted and kicked his right leg towards Hei Xiu Yi.

Whoosh!

The sound of the wind suddenly whirled and boundless air condensed into an enormous foot.

This foot was nearly transparent and was as big as a small hill. It crashed down rapidly with an incomparably violent momentum.

"Such an attack!" For a moment, not only Hei Xiu Yi, but Hei Lou Lan and others all stared with their eyes wide open.

"Defend, use all your strength!!" The several rank three Gu Masters who were in charge of defending the site, shouted one after another.

The enormous foot stamped down; Hei Xiu Yi gritted his teeth and immediately sent his fifty-six flying bone shields to take it on.

But the flying bone shields could not last for even a second and were smashed by the foot!

Next, the enormous foot smashed down like a mountain.

The green halo was instantly broken, the nine ghost faces did their best to absorb the force but could only weaken one-tenth of it before dispersing.

The chaotic air flow could not even scatter before it was suppressed by the enormous foot.

Hei Xiu Yi felt an irresistible force heavily pressing down on his spine. He wanted to resist, but was powerless and within a few breaths of time, was pressed down to the ground.

The black iron armor which had made him famous was crushed to pieces by the huge force.

Crack...

The sounds of his bones breaking continuously entered his ears and large amounts of blood flowed out of his seven facial orifices.

The huge force was still spreading towards the surroundings. Several defensive Gu Masters had to sacrifice their lives to maintain the light barrier and not let it collapse.

After the dust dispersed, Hei Xiu Yi was lying on the ground like a dead dog, motionless and at his last breath.

Hei Lou Lan's expression paled as he stood up immediately. Hei Xiu Yi was part of his direct family line and was one of the three commanders of the black banner troops; without him, black banner troop's battle strength would fall by at least twenty percent. At the same time, Hei Xiu Yi was Hei tribe's supreme elder's grand-nephew's son, so this was a matter of utmost concern.

Hei Lou Lan had never expected Mo Shi Kuang to be so strong; his strike could almost jump realms and challenge rank five Gu Masters.

Hei Xiu Yi could not be lost, Hei Lou Lan immediately sent orders: "Bring back Hei Xiu Yi!"

Immediately, two rank three Gu Masters rushed forward.

The defensive Gu Masters hesitated but not wanting to offend Hei Lou Lan, they did not block the way, instead loosening up the barrier.

"Lord, this Hei Lou Lan is extremely shameless, actually is trying to break the rules! Let me go too!" A Liu tribe elder shouted in indignation.

Liu Wen Wu, however, just chuckled: "Nothing to worry, let them experience the power of my sworn brother."

"A group of scoundrels!" Mo Shi Kuang shouted in fury before waving forward with his right fist.

He seemed to be dragging a thousand jun of weight as he moved his hand, giving a feeling of slow exertion of power.

An enormous arm made of qi - fifty feet in length and ten feet wide - rapidly formed under everyone's dumbstruck gaze.

Whoosh...

The qi arm produced a sound like that of a roaring dragon or tiger and also seemed like a hurricane that would blow away everything.

The enormous qi arm fiercely swept across in a wild and unrestrained manner; if it came across mountains, it would break them, and if it came across seas, it would split them!

The two rank three Gu Masters that came to rescue Hei Xiu Yi were like flies as they were swept flying by the enormous qi arm.

The qi arm then swept outside the stage, causing sounds of shocks and screams to resound.

Many spectating Gu Masters who were not able to dodge in time were smashed into minced meat by the qi arm. Hei Lou Lan and his group hurriedly retreated to avoid the brunt of the attack.

"Courting death!"

"Kill him!"

"He actually attacked us, let's attack him together!!"

Hei Lou Lan and his group who avoided the brunt of the attack, made their moves one after another and immediately shattered the qi arm.

"Hahaha, more!" Mo Shi Kuang did not show a hint of fear in facing so many Gu Masters, and instead became even more happy, his battle intent burning high.

He advanced instead of retreating like a tiger that had come out of the mountain, his beard fluttering as he charged towards Hei Lou Lan and the group.

"Not good, third brother has gone berserk again." Liu Wen Wu could not remain calm anymore, he waved his hand, "Everyone, follow me to reinforce Third Brother!"

Liu tribe's side also entered the battle; the heroes' assembly immediately turned into a chaotic mess, and an unprecedented large chaotic battle suddenly unfolded.

Mo Shi Kuang rampaged here and there in the battlefield, and Hei Lou Lan along with his group smoothly grabbed Hei Xiu Yi and retreated. Chai tribe's Gu Masters charged towards Water Demon Hao Ji Liu, and the heavily injured Hao Ji Liu could only flee here and there...

It was chaos.

"Shit! This is only the heroes' assembly, we absolutely cannot have such a battle and suffer huge losses, if so how will we vie for the Imperial Court?"

"What to do? Even if our side wins, it will be a miserable victory!"

Liu Wen Wu and Hei Lou Lan felt the situation was far from good, they tried to stop it but it was in vain.

Howl!

Right at this moment, an intensely desolate wolf howl spread from far away, manifesting the presence of a beast emperor.

Howl!

Countless wolf howls followed soon after. The howling merged into a grand and majestic howl that resounded all over heaven and earth!

Chapter 499: Turtle Jade Wolf Skin Gu

"What happened?"

"Is there a wolf tide coming?!"

"So many wolves! There are night wolves, wind wolves, turtleback wolves, wait! There are water wolves and vermillion flame wolves!"

The shocked voices called out as the people stopped fighting, turning around and focusing their attention on the wolves.

But what they saw was a grand wolf army approaching from all directions. All sorts of northern plains wolves gathered together, and charged over collectively.

The black and nimble night wolves, the elegant wind wolves, the defensive turtleback wolves, the pure as snow water wolves, and the ones coated in blazing flames, vermillion flame wolves...

These wolf groups came together, each had at least several tens of thousands in number. At once, the grand wolf army filled everyone's field of vision, causing people to feel suffocated as a chill grew in their hearts.

A group of people moved slowly under the protection of the wolf groups. Large numbers of farm slug Gu, black skin fat armor beetles carried huge amounts of resources, while lizard house Gu moved their four limbs forward. There was a grand tribe flag carried by one of them, symbolizing the main tent's location. On the blue flag, there was a huge word written as 'Ge'.

"It's Ge tribe..."

"That means, this is Chang Shan Yin's wolf army?"

"Didn't Chang Shan Yin battle three tribes consecutively, how did his wolf groups expand by so much?"

Suspicion and questions filled everyone's hearts.

"According to our intel, the Wolf King has night wolves, wind wolves, and turtleback wolves. But where did he get all these water wolves and vermillion flame wolves?" Liu Wen Wu's face was grim.

"Big brother." Mo Shi Kuang returned to Liu Wen Wu's side, the huge wolf groups caused his heart to jump secretly.

"The water wolves can be explained, after all Ge tribe stayed in crescent lake for such a long time, and water wolves are most common there. But can anyone tell me where these eighty thousand vermillion flame wolves came from?"

"Vermillion flame wolves are much rarer than wind wolves, water wolves, and night wolves, they have the strongest attack power among wild wolves. We have to check clearly, where did Chang Shan Yin get such a powerful force suddenly? Can anyone tell me?!"

At once, countless tribe leaders and elders cursed the intel gathering Gu Masters in their tribes.

"Forget the vermillion flame wolves, look at that largest night wolf, is it a wolf emperor?!" Zhong Fei You pointed as he shouted.

The truth is, once the night wolf emperor appeared, numerous gazes were already assessing it.

"It truly is... a night wolf emperor." The authority of a wolf emperor was absolute, after Bei Cao Chuan clarified it, he said dryly.

Everyone gasped.

Wolf emperor!

This was equivalent to the strength of a rank five Gu Master!!

Chang Shan Yin was only a rank four Gu Master, he actually had control of a wolf emperor?

As expected of an established character, the hero of northern plains, the one who had once single handedly taken down Ha Tu Gu and his band of bandits, this legend!

"Damn it! How did his strength rise so much? With the wolf emperor, he is already on par with Ma Zun, Jiang Bao Ya, and Yang Po Tian!" Pei Yan Fei who wanted to take revenge clenched his fists, the grand wolf army made him feel a strong sense of helplessness and defeat.

Seeing the wolf army approaching them, everyone showed a grim and fearful expression.

The chaotic battle had stopped, everyone was gathering around Liu Wen Wu and Hei Lou Lan's side, getting into their formations.

Soon after, under everyone's gaze, Fang Yuan rode the white-eyes wolf as he followed Ge Guang and the rest and came to Hei Lou Lan.

"Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, I've long heard of your name!" Hei Lou Lan first greeted him.

Hei Lou Lan's body was bulky like an angry bear, his uneven shiny white teeth were like daggers giving people a ruthless feeling. His triangular eyes shone with threatening brilliance.

This person was extremely lecherous, it was a well known fact in northern plains.

Fang Yuan laughed lightly as he turned to look at Liu Wen Wu.

Liu Wen Wu wore white clothes, having a scholarly aura, looking like a perfect young master. His eyes were mild and his face was like jade. Beside him, there was a nine feet tall ink man, his body was black and he had white hair, standing like a guardian, he was the number one fierce general in this Imperial Court competition — Mo Shi Kuang.

Liu Wen Wu's heart jumped, Fang Yuan's deep gaze made him feel amiss.

Chang Shan Yin and Chang tribe's enmity had already been spread to the world by Ge tribe during the battle in crescent lake.

Right now, Chang tribe had already submitted to Liu Wen Wu, if Chang Shan Yin wants revenge on Chang tribe, he would first have to deal with Liu Wen Wu.

Fang Yuan retracted his gaze, looking at Hei Lou Lan, he said with a plain tone but his voice resounded in everyone's ears: "The reason why I have returned is to exact revenge. Coincidentally, the competition for the Imperial Court was undergoing, this will also allow me to meet all the grand heroes in northern plains. Brother Lou Lan, why don't we team up?"

Hei Lou Lan's pupils shrunk, as he happily stood up, walking towards Fang Yuan, grabbing his shoulders as he laughed: "Gaining Wolf King's help, it would be my greatest honor!"

At Hei tribe, the people suddenly exploded as their cheered loudly.

"Your defeated opponent, Hao Ji Liu, pays respect to Lord Wolf King." Water Demon paid respects to Fang Yuan with trepidation.

Hei Lou Lan frowned, immediately turning around, although Hao Ji Liu had gained some merits, if he offended Chang Shan Yin, Hei Lou Lan would have to kill him to express goodwill towards Chang Shan Yin.

But Fang Yuan nodded at Hao Ji Liu: "No matter, just do your best from now on."

Hao Ji Liu breathed a huge sigh of relief.

"Hahaha, the Wolf King truly has a big heart, such magnanimity, I am in awe!" Hei Lou Lan's laughter became louder, Hao Ji Liu was a rank four upper stage Gu aster, an absolute expert. Now that he got the best of both worlds, he was overjoyed.

While Hei tribe rejoiced, Liu tribe sank into solemness.

Although Liu Wen Wu had predicted this, his mood still turned terrible.

"If I had known this, I would not have agreed to Chang tribe's request. How can a Chang tribe compare to Chang Shan Yin? Sigh, but now that the deed has been done, I cannot salvage it further."

He sighed in his heart.

Yan Cui Er was his wife-to-be, but he could discard her. Not just because of the patriarchal traditions, but also because Yan tribe had been exterminated.

But Chang tribe's strength was still intact.

If he really gave up on Chang tribe, it would make all the tribes that subdued to him feel disheartened and fearful, he, Liu Wen Wu, could not do such a thing.

"Hei tribe leader, my Wang tribe would like to join you, what do you think?"

"Hei Lou Lan, my Fang tribe will be betting on you this time."

"Ye tribe is willing to submit to Hei tribe."

At once, several of the undecided large tribes immediately chose to side with Hei Lou Lan.

Although Liu Wen Wu had fierce generals like Mo Shi Kuang, Wolf King Chang Shan Yin had allied with Hei Lou Lan.

With such a huge wolf group as the vanguard, who knows how many people's lives would be saved in the future.

This way, all of the tribes at Yu Tian heroes assembly made their choices. A large portion joined Hei Lou Lan, while the rest went to Liu Wen Wu.

"Hahaha, Liu tribe's lad, we will meet on the battlefield next time!"

"Brother Lou Lan, till we meet again."

Now was not the time to fight, there were still several powerful forces outside of Yu Tian. The two groups were vigilant as they moved away from each other, towards their main camp.

On the way back, Liu Wen Wu called the intel tribe elder and chided him in public: "Where did Chang Shan Yin's wolves come from? Investigate, investigate it clearly!"

"Yes young master! I will definitely make up for my mistake..." The tribe elder left with a forehead full of sweat.

"Brother, don't worry. Regardless of how many wolves he has, I can directly attack and kill that Chang Shan Yin." Mo Shi Kuang consoled him with a fearless tone.

But Liu Wen Wu was deep in thoughts.

Against an enslavement path master, one would definitely choose the beheading leader tactic. But now that Chang Shan Yin has gone to Hei Lou Lan, when they meet in battle again, Hei tribe would definitely keep him protected.

By then, it would be extremely difficult to kill him!

But, he could not ignore the concern of his sworn brother.

Liu Wen Wu smiled lightly, patting Mo Shi Kuang's shoulder: "Hehehe, third brother, you are an unparalleled warrior that can easily take the enemy's head, of course I trust you."

"Big brother, you forgot about second brother. As long as he comes out of his closed cultivation, us three brothers would be able to work together, what's there to fear in the entire northern plains?" Mo Shi Kuang laughed.

"Second brother?" Liu Wen Wu's eyes shone, the pressure lifting in his heart: "That's right, when second brother comes out, Chang Shan Yin is not our match when we work together. but now, we should not bother with Hei tribe, this is a troublesome tribe. We should take down the west area and gather our strength, and strengthen ourselves."

"Just do what you want brother, I will follow behind you."

At the same time, at another group, Hei Lou Lan laughed loudly: "Hahaha, after today, Yu Tian heroes assembly's news will spread, all the forces around here will feel a great headache. Brother Shan Yin, your wolf army will definitely make them suspicious and scared."

Fang Yuan had great strength, Hei Lou Lan had paid attention to him long ago. Now that he joined him willingly, this Hei tribe leader definitely had to build a relationship with him.

Not only did he treat Chang Shan Yin as an equal, when they talked, he even started calling him brother.

Fang Yuan heard Hei Lou Lan's words and knew this was a secretive inquisition, thus he laughed plainly: "To speak the truth, I did not expect such gains. Back then at onion valley, I left some wolves behind. To think that after these years, they would expand to this extent."

Ge Guang beside him also said: "That's right, when Lord Supreme Elder came out of onion valley, the endless number of wolves stunned us all."

The truth was, after Fang Yuan went into onion valley alone, he opened the stargate and connected it to Hu Immortal blessed land, bringing out most of the wolves inside.

When he led the wolf group back to Ge tribe, almost everyone was speechless. This way, the entire Ge tribe was his witness.

At the same time, he covered up his tracks on onion valley.

Right now, the evidences were solid as a mountain.

"Hahaha, brother Shan Yin's luck is truly admirable. Letting the wolf groups develop on their own is a helpless measure, one rarely gained anything. Brother managed to get some gains, you truly are a fated individual, even heaven wants you to come out of seclusion once more. To speak the truth, after you disappeared, the entire northern plain went silent. Heaven did not want to see this, it did not want a grand character like brother to end up being secluded in the mountains."

Hei Lou Lan's words were all flattery, it sounded like the entire northern plains only had Chang Shan Yin.

But Fang Yuan gave a mild smile purposely, laughing arrogantly: "This time, I want to exact revenge, but I also want to spar with Ma Zun, Yang Po Ying, and Jiang Bao Ya. Finally, I want to make use of Imperial Court blessed land and improve my cultivation further."

Saying so, he acted as if the entire Imperial Court was his own.

Hearing such arrogant words, even Water Demon Hao Ji Liu bit his tongue.

"Good, this is the aspiration of a true northern plains man!" Hei Lou Lan praised, giving a thumbs up to Fang Yuan, taking out a Gu worm as he handed it to him: "Good Gu belongs to heroes, since brother Shan Yin came to me, that is my honor. This rank five Gu is our meeting gift, please accept it."

Fang Yuan took a look, this was a turtle jade wolf skin Gu, it had great defense. Fang Yuan had heard of this Gu's recipe back in his previous life, the rank five turtle jade wolf skin Gu was made using a living turtleback wolf emperor.

If there really was a turtleback wolf emperor, Fang Yuan would rather it be part of his force, than sacrifice it and turn it into a Gu.

Although Fang Yuan could use treasure yellow heaven to get rank five Gu as well, this turtle jade wolf skin Gu suited his enslavement path. It would take him a lot of time, effort, and most importantly, immortal essence stones, to get such a Gu.

After all, Fang Yuan only had two immortal essence stones left.

Now that this Gu was given to him for free, that would be the best.

"Alright then, I will happily receive it." Fang Yuan said, as he really grabbed this Gu without hesitation.

Chapter 500: Trapped inside and outside, slashing thorns and vines

Twelve days later.

In the secret room, Fang Yuan was seated above a cushion with both eyes closed, his whole body was tense, and his mind was in placid tranquility. His attention was solely focused on the turtle jade wolf skin Gu that was within his aperture.

Currently, the Gu floated atop his primeval sea within his first aperture; primeval essence was continuously poured onto it, which caused the Gu to emit a jade colored light.

The light radiated from his aperture, and illuminated Fang Yuan's entire body.

Gradually, the rays of light dimmed. The entire turtle jade wolf skin Gu dissipated into tiny fluorescent particles, thoroughly destroyed.

Fang Yuan was already mentally prepared. Turtle jade wolf skin Gu needed to be consumed, and would leave imprints on the Gu Master's body, similar to the bronze skin Gu and iron bone Gu.

"These past few days I've been in constant seclusion, my body has finally been refined to turtle jade wolf skin."

Fang Yuan slowly opened his eyes, and pulled back the cuffs of his sleeves to examine the skin on his arms.

His skin still retained the natural color of flesh, but when Fang Yuan took out a dagger and ruthlessly slashed at his arm, immediately, the effects of the turtle jade wolf skin Gu activated.

When the dagger made contact with his skin, the skin immediately turned to a jadish-green, while the faint lines of turtle shells pulsated outwards.

Cutting the skin was similar to a collision with iron, or possibly jade, but the skin still retained a degree of flexibility.

Fang Yuan gave a satisfied nod: "The turtle jade wolf skin Gu is rank five, its defensive power is truly remarkable. Most importantly, it does not require active use; as long as one is attacked, the defensive properties would activate, it is extremely practical as no primeval essence is expended in the process."

It wasn't difficult for a Gu Immortal to acquire rank five Gu, though for mortal Gu Masters, they were quite rare.

For a large number of rank five Gu Masters, they only possess one rank five Gu. Some do not even possess rank five Gu, but instead resorted to rank four Gu as substitute.

Upon meeting Fang Yuan, Hei Lou Lan immediately used turtle jade wolf skin Gu to entice him, which, in the eyes of bystanders, was a huge investment.

In the eyes of Fang Yuan, a rank five Gu wasn't much, but it allowed him to sense the sincerity from Hei Lou Lan.

"Turtle jade wolf skin's modification is done. The next step is to improve my strength." Fang Yuan sat still upon his cushion, seizing the most of every minute, diligently improving his strength.

He sent out a strength of ten jun Gu.

This Gu was like an iron weight. After being infused with primeval essence, it suspended itself above Fang Yuan's head, and afterwards blossomed with a glorifying radiance, covering his entire body while engraving a particular strength path Dao mark onto his body.

As time passed, the strength of Fang Yuan slowly and steadily grew.

For quite some time, he cultivated his strength non-stop.

He had already used up the five strength of ten jun Gu he purchased earlier. Now, he would have to use Hei tribe's inventory to acquire more strength of ten jun Gu.

By now, Fang Yuan's body contained the strength of sixty jun, stored in the very depths of his body.

Ten jun was the strength of three hundred jin, sixty jun was equal to one thousand eight hundred jin of strength.

On Earth, Green Dragon Crescent Blade[1] weighed merely eighty-two jin.

"I have already refined this body with turtle jade wolf skin, thus, it can hold about a hundred jun of strength. One hundred jun of strength or more would be the within the range of rank five realm."

Jin strength Gu and jun strength Gu's recipes were the invention of a rank seven Gu Immortal. Compared to traditional beast strength Gu, they were easier to refine, while simultaneously costing less, and thus were widespread in the north.

Fang Yuan abandoned his beast phantom Gu, and picked up the jun strength Gu, not only to keep up with current developments, but also to make his path more convenient, allowing him to disguise his own identity.

However, jun strength Gu could not solve the fundamental problem of strength path.

Fang Yuan had sixty jun of strength within him, but in practice could only exert a small portion of it.

To solve the problem, he would have to rely on all-out effort Gu.

All-out effort Gu could allow a Gu Master to make use of their whole body's strength, allowing them complete liberty to exert strength, it was truly the core Gu of strength path.

Therefore, Fang Yuan decided it would be his second aperture's vital Gu.

But this all-out effort Gu was a mere rank three Gu, and being in a foreign land resulted in it being suppressed to rank two.

Fang Yuan had the recipe for rank four all-out effort Gu, thus, so long as he is in northern plains when he refines the Gu to rank four, it will not be affected by the suppression.

"But... it would be hard to continue accumulating. Turtle jade wolf skin helps in bearing the weight of my strength, but does not benefit enslavement path. Although I have two apertures, I merely have one body."

In this world, there were few things that could satisfy all of one's needs.

While advancing strength path, he could not simultaneously advance enslavement path.

If he wanted to advance enslavement path, Fang Yuan should not have employed turtle jade wolf skin Gu, but rather a different rank five Gu, known as wolf totem Gu.

This Gu could be used to store wolf packs. They would be stored in his skin, and for every wild wolf he keeps, a wolf tattoo would also form on Fang Yuan's skin.

Many enslavement path Gu Masters would choose their corresponding totem Gu, and keep their elite troops in their own bodies.

In critical moments, Gu Masters would reveal the power of their elites, summoning them and making them fight.

Like before, Fang Yuan used rank four impermanence bone Gu, which allowed him to further strengthen his soul.

But impermanence bone Gu did not benefit strength path.

Fang Yuan may be a Gu Master of both the strength and enslavement path, but it was not simple. It was easy to cause a disaster for both paths.

Fang Yuan's problems were far from just this.

Spring Autumn Cicada was gradually recovering, once again putting him under the pressure of death.

His frequent entering and exiting of Hu Immortal blessed land caused his supply of starlight firefly Gu to dwindle.

Immortal Crane Sect's great desire towards Hu Immortal blessed land, the mysterious force's attention due to the fixed immortal travel Gu, the problem of recovering fixed immortal travel and gruel mud Immortal Gu, Hu Immortal blessed land's earthly calamity, the crisis concerning the death of Dang Hun mountain, and constantly pretending to be Chang Shan Yin, and the mental pressure of making sure I do not show any weakness or flaws...

His situation was terrible, it could even be said that he was beset on all sides.

"But because of the crisis , I can look forward to the moment when I cut through the thistles and thorns and break free of worries."

Fang Yuan let out a cold laugh, organizing his state of mind, and left his secret room.

Outside the secret room stood two rank three Gu Masters, standing like guardians.

The Wolf King's identity was the main reason for this situation; after arriving at Hei tribe camp, they immediately decided to strictly protect him.

"Greetings, Lord Wolf King." When the two Gu Masters saw Fang Yuan come out, they immediately saluted and reported to him, "Lord Hei Lou Lan invited the other lords to attend the banquet to conduct important business."

After returning to Hei tribe's compound, Hei Lou Lan one large feast for almost three days, and spent five days at a smaller feast. Several invitations were sent to Fang Yuan, but he was busy cultivating; every sent invitation was completely rejected by him.

Fang Yuan was in a race against time to increase his strength, which was also in accordance with Chang Shan Yin's haught and lofty disposition.

Though this time, the banquet was extraordinary.

"There are important matters to discuss?" Fang Yuan's footsteps halted, and he changed his usual attitude towards banquets: "Let's go".

The secret room was built underground.

Fang Yuan exited his secret room and arrived above the ground, the curtain of night already enveloped the sky, stars scattered about.

Rushing to the banquet, as he had expected, it was the matter of the blood oath.

These days, the banquet did not have Hei Lou Lan's usual decadence, rather it focused on talks between leaders negotiating the contracts of an alliance.

This heroes assembly was only the preliminary stage to establishing the genuine union, which would unite the forces of all parties into one alliance.

The contract of the alliance already agreed on various things, and the leaders were now working on their individual tribes' interests. Fang Yuan looked at the contents and saw no issues, so along with everyone else, he used the poison vow Gu.

poison vow Gu had the power to restriction, and was also the foundation of building mutual trust.

But Fang Yuan was the exception.

He possessed eating one's words Gu. In two hundred years, this Gu would be developed by a western desert chief. When he was in Shang clan city, he used it to break his poison vow with Bai Ning Bing.

And now that he could link with treasure yellow heaven, if he wanted to remove the poison vow, he would merely have to refine it again.

The main tent was brightly lit, with each tribe having their own seat.

Hei Lou Lan held the central seat, and the first to his left was Fang Yuan, with Ge Guang standing behind him.

It was difficult for the young tribe leader to hide his happy expression, holding second seat in the alliance was a result of clinging to Fang Yuan, their benefits surpassed that of any ordinary medium-sized tribe.

Sitting after Fang Yuan were the leaders of the large tribes: Wang tribe, Fang tribe, and Ye tribe.

While down the line were the leaders of the medium-sized tribes, and finally the small scale tribe leaders, as well as the rank four demonic path experts.

Now, the alliance began its preliminary aggregation, before they were merely like loose sand.

"Hahaha, now everyone is family. According to conventional tradition, after having established our alliance, we need to hold a large feast. But these traditions and conventions are total bullshit! I've already thought of something better, rather than annexing those weaker powers, we should instead collect wild wolves." Hei Lou Lan began his speech.

Soon, all eyes concentrated on Fang Yuan's face.

Fang Yuan's complexion was indifferent, his eyes darted across the room, within his heart he understood that by joining in, he had already altered history.

He vaguely remembered, five hundred years ago in his previous life, after Hei Lou Lan's alliance was formed, he immediately assaulted the east, launching a bloody war with the Dong Fang tribe.

"But this is good, although Hei Lou Lan prevailed over Dong Fang tribe, he suffered huge losses in the process. Hei Lou Lan is obviously taking consideration of my night wolf emperor, which was expected. With the night wolf emperor, he could incorporate myriad beast groups into his army. The expansion of the wolf group will be a great thing for me.

Fang Yuan thought about it for a moment, and gave everyone a nod: "Since this is the case, I will do my part."

No one in the camp gave an objection.

The larger the number of wolves, the more they would benefit, while suffering fewer casualties, preserving the strength of their tribes as much as possible.

Hei Lou Lan was relying heavily on Chang Shan Yin, everyone understood and agreed.

It would be a shame to have such a great master of the enslavement path and not put him to use!

As for the sharp rise in strength of the Wolf King, they did not have to be too concerned.

They were not aware of the eating one's words Gu, and had complete trust in the poison vow Gu. Since the covenant had already been formed, they did not have to worry that the Wolf King would take advantage of their interests.

Soon after their discussion, the entire Hei tribe alliance began to work actively. Gu Masters from tribes both large and small dedicated themselves to expanding Fang Yuan's wolf pack.

[1] Legendary weapon wielded by the Chinese General Guan Yu in the 14th-century historical novel Romance of the Three Kingdoms. Back

Chapter 501: Five hundred thousand wolves start a war

In the grassland shrouded by the night, Sang Yi was running for his life.

The bone-chilling wind pounced on him, but he, however, was perspiring greatly.

"Fast, faster!" He screamed in his heart, pouring his primeval essence frantically into his movement Gu.

Howl!

Behind him, a night wolf group was charging towards him. The reason for that was the corpse of a night wolf's cub in Sang Yi's hand; leading to this pursuit that had continued for several minutes.

If it was before, these few minutes would be gone in a blink of an eye to Sang Yi. But with the myriad wolf group closely chasing him, Sang Yi felt every second of time passing very slowly and unendurably.

"Finally, I've arrived!" Seeing the small ravine in front of him, Sang Yi burst forth with newfound strength, rushing towards the ravine.

Rumble...

Close to twenty thousand night wolves followed him into the ravine like a dark flood.

"They have entered!" The Gu Masters lying low in the ravine shouted in joy.

"Collect the net quickly, don't miss it." A rank three Gu Master who was the leader of this group, sent the command immediately.

"Earth wall, rise up!" A group of rank two Gu Masters simultaneously activated rank two earth mound Gu.

With so many earth mound Gu activated together caused the stones on the entrance of this narrow ravine to rapidly rise up, forming into a barrier like that of a rank three earth wall Gu.

At the same time, on another side of the ravine were dozens of Gu Masters who activated falling stones Gu.

Large numbers of stones fell down and firmly blocked the entrance.

The exit to this ravine was already sealed before. Now with the entrance blocked as well, the night wolf group that had entered was like a turtle trapped in a jar.

The night wolf myriad beast king saw the situation turn bad and immediately led the wolf group to climb up the ravine and cross over it.

However, at this time, a desolate and magnificent wolf howl resounded through the skies.

Fang Yuan was riding on a night wolf emperor, commanding large numbers of night wolves to attack from above.

The wild night wolf group's eyes turned red and howled furiously, but they hesitated because of the wolf emperor's presence.

Clear mind Gu!

With a thought, Fang Yuan summoned a clear mind Gu. This was a rank four Gu; after the primeval essence poured into it, it immediately changed into a cool wind.

The cool wind blew gently over the area.

The night wolf group that was starting to turn frenzied due to the effect of onion explosion Gu immediately came to their senses when this cool wind blew over them.

The wolf emperor howled again, turning this wild night wolf group to fall into a chaotic mess; their formation crumbled and their will to fight received a huge impact.

Fang Yuan laughed and commanded his wolf group to attack for real.

There were already Gu Masters who were tangling up the wild myriad wolf king.

Fang Yuan first mobilized his wolf group to divide the wild night wolves before nibbling away at them; the whole situation was in his firm control. Then he approached the wild myriad wolf king and then at the opportune time, used rank four wolf enslavement Gu.

In the end, he only had to pay the lives of few hundred night wolves to smoothly take in this myriad wolf king and close to twenty thousand wolves.

After this great success, the Gu Masters remained behind to clean up the battlefield while Fang Yuan led the increased wolf group towards the next destination.

There, another large group of wild night wolf group was waiting for him.

"You did good." A rank three leader patted Sang Yi's shoulder and gave him five hundred primeval stones along with a rank three Gu, "This is your well deserved reward."

Sang Yi wiped off the sweat off his forehead and looked at these primeval stones and the Gu while breathing heavily.

He then looked at the distance, looking at Fang Yuan's receding figure with envy and admiration.

"Although I am a rank three Gu Master and have some fame in the demonic path, I cannot be compared to Wolf King. This is a true big shot. When will I have such an accomplishment?"

In this night, Fang Yuan wandered thousands of li and took in seventy thousand wild night wolves.

Only by dawn when night wolves would not go out to hunt and had all returned to their nest, did Fang Yuan lead the wolf group back to Hei tribe camp.

After Hei Lou Lan established the alliance, with the concept of safety in numbers, five enormous camps were stationed nearby.

Fang Yuan's wolf group was divided among these five camps for the specialized people to feed them.

These few days, he had taken in large numbers of night wolves; the night wolf group that was only about thirty thousand originally, had now expanded to three hundred twenty thousand!

The night wolf group had become the greatest force in Fang Yuan's troops in one go.

Adding in the vermillion flame wolves, wind wolves, water wolves and others, Fang Yuan's wolf group had reached a huge size of five hundred and thirty thousand!

"It is thanks to the night wolf emperor that I could incorporate the night wolves so easily." Settling down the wolf group, Fang Yuan brought his exhausted body back to the secret room to rest.

With the increase in the night wolf group, the numbers of myriad wolf kings Fang Yuan had to control also increased by several times.

These large numbers of night wolf myriad beast kings created a burden on his soul, causing him to feel an increasingly heavy feeling in the depths of his soul.

After sleeping for hours, Fang Yuan opened his eyes and sat cross-legged on a cushion and continued to cultivate.

Wolf soul Gu.

He used the wolf soul Gu, slowly converting his thousand man soul into wolfman soul.

Previously, he had hundred soul level wolfman soul which had a human body, wolf ears, wolf tail and wolf claws. But afterwards, he used large numbers of guts Gu in Dang Hun mountain and his soul rapidly expanded to thousand man soul; this instead caused the wolf soul Gu's effect to thin out and his soul recovered the appearance of a normal soul.

The wolf soul Gu's effect was not clear at all, after more than two hours, it only slightly lengthened the wolf ears on Fang Yuan's human soul.

But to Fang Yuan, the heavy feeling in the depths of his soul had lifted by a lot.

With wolfman soul, controlling wolf groups would become much easier because the wolves would acknowledge the Gu Master as one of their own kind from the depths of their soul.

"Unfortunately, I do not have rank five wolf soul Gu and can only use the rank four wolf soul Gu; its effects are clear on hundred man soul, but the effects have great weakened as I progress through thousand man soul."

After using it for a long time, Fang Yuan stopped it while feeling some regret in his heart.

However, rank five Gu were never easy to obtain.

Refining rank four wolf soul Gu required an intact soul of a myriad wolf king. But to refine rank five wolf soul Gu required the soul of a wolf emperor.

Moreover, even a refinement master would only have about fifty percent chance to successfully refine rank five wolf soul Gu.

Fang Yuan had thought of purchasing it in treasure yellow heaven, but when he recalled he only had two immortal essence stones left and the mysterious force hiding in the dark, he dispelled this plan for safety purposes.

"Although I can't directly buy it in treasure yellow heaven, I have already mentioned this request to Hei Lou Lan. Hei tribe is part of the Huang Jin family and their supreme elders are Gu Immortals, thus they have extremely deep foundations. Two-three days have already gone by, I might as well ask him now."

With this thought, Fang Yuan walked out of the secret room and met Hei Lou Lan, but he expressed that his hands were tied.

"Brother Shan Yin, truth be told, I have already written a letter to request it from the supreme elders. But they thought it would be better to give a live wolf emperor instead of rank five wolf soul Gu. And the wolf emperor cannot be given casually as well, their intention is to use battle merits to exchange for it. After all, I need to convince the masses as well."

Hei Lou Lan was very cunning, ever since Fang Yuan took the poison vow, his attitude was no longer as cordial as before.

Together with the fact that he had used large amounts of manpower and physical resources over these days to help Fang Yuan incorporate the night wolf group, he felt he had done more than enough for Fang Yuan.

Simultaneously, Fang Yuan's wolf group had expanded to over five hundred thousand in number. Such a large force also caused him to inwardly feel fear. Despite the restriction from poison vow, Hei Lou Lan was subconsciously guarded.

Fang Yuan nodded and expressed his understanding.

He had also commanded Little Hu Immortal to keep a close watch on treasure yellow heaven to get any wolf emperors native to northern plains.

Unfortunately, beast emperors were rarely sold. A beast emperor had been put for sale in these days, but it was a boar emperor and not a wolf emperor.

Fang Yuan realized from Hei Lou Lan's words that he was already unable to hold back and was already preparing to start a war campaign.

Over these days, Tian Chuan, Meng Qiu, Cao Fu and every other region of northern plains were already engaging in battle. Among the popular candidates for the ownership of Imperial Court this time, only Hei tribe had been holding back and growing the wolf group.

Now, they had already accumulated enough wolves, Hei Lou Lan who was full of hope had already been impatient.

"Then brother Lou Lan, which force do you want to attack first?" Fang Yuan asked.

Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily and patted Fang Yuan's shoulder: "Little brother is really sharp. I won't hide it from brother, I want to attack Cao Fu and eradicate Dong Fang tribe. Dong Fang tribe has lot of beauties, especially that Dong Fang Qing Yu who is a famous beauty in northern plains. I want to kill all their men and capture all their women! Hahaha..."

Fang Yuan was slightly stupefied, history was still steering in the same direction, after making a detour, the focus still returned to Dong Fang tribe.

"But with my five hundred thousand wolf group, it is different from my previous life. Dong Fang tribe... Hehe." Fang Yuan sneered inwardly.

Reaching this stage, he could already influence the development of the future.

But so what?

Let history be completely changed.

As long as there are profits in front of him, so what if the sky and earth collapses, or if the floods reach heaven! Who cares if his reputation stinks for ten thousand years!

The next day, Hei tribe completely pulled out the camp and began a majestic expedition towards Cao Fu.

This news immediately attracted the attention of all kinds of forces.

The situation was changing crazily and Cao Fu was preparing for a great battle.

Different from Yu Tian's heroes assembly where Liu tribe and Hei tribe were evenly matched, Dong Fang tribe occupied the greatest dominance in Cao Fu's heroes assembly, suppressing the heroes and incorporating large numbers of tribes. Only Zhao tribe was barely resisting the pressure, not willing to agree to Dong Fang tribe's harsh alliance conditions.

The news of Hei tribe large expedition attracted almost all the attention of Dong Fang tribe. Zhao tribe got space for a breather and showed signs of moving their tribe towards a corner.

Dong Fang tribe's current tribe leader was a rank five wisdom path Gu Master Dong Fang Yu Liang.

After making deductions and forecasts over a night without resting, he immediately changed the stiff stance and changed the conditions for joining the alliance to become extremely lenient and generous.

Dong Fang Yu Liang personally travelled to invite Zhao tribe to join the alliance!

Zhao tribe leader hesitated.

Zhao tribe and Dong Fang tribe had enmities between them, and this enmity had gotten deeper over the years. But Dong Fang tribe's sincerity could be clearly seen right now and the conditions they offered were also very attractive.

Maybe, this was a rare opportunity to resolve the old hatred and grudges with Dong Fang tribe?

Chapter 502: Zhao Lian Yun

In the study room, Zhao tribe leader placed down the document wearily.

Sunlight passed through the window and shone on his face.

Due to handling the tribe affairs for a long time, this fifty year old rank five initial stage Gu Master already had white hair and a face filled with wrinkles.

These days, because of Hei tribe's large scale expedition and the personal invitation from Dong Fang Yu Liang, the tribe was divided into two factions.

These two factions argued endlessly; one side wanted to side with Dong Fang tribe and resolve the old grudges, while another side wanted to side with Hei tribe as Hei tribe was much bigger.

Could siding with Dong Fang tribe really resolve the old grudges? When he thought of the deep hatred that had accumulated over the generations between their tribe and Dong Fang tribe, Zhao tribe leader could not speak with certainty.

And siding with Hei tribe was also not right.

Zhao tribe's main headquarters was after all in this Cao Fu region while Hei tribe represented Yu Tian's tyrants and had already gone through the vow with their allies. As a tribe who joined later, Zhao tribe would unavoidably be bullied and how much profits could they even obtain? They might even be treated as cannon fodder.

Thus, Zhao tribe leader was deeply conflicted. Especially these days, the tribe higher-ups were always busy arguing; Zhao tribe leader had to guard against that cunning Dong Fang Yu Liang's scheme, while also needing to suppress the internal situation and lead the tribe. He was already very exhausted.

"Sigh..."

He heaved a deep sigh and leaned back on the chair, gazing at the dust that was floating in the sunlight.

In this dazzling sunlight, the tiny dust could be clearly seen and Zhao tribe leader felt he was like one of these dust, hesitating back and forth; now it was floating in the air, but who is to say that it will not fall down to the ground when wind blows over.

The battle between Hei tribe and Dong Fang tribe was precisely a violent wind that would sweep away everything.

Facing such a wind, what path should his tribe take?

Right as Zhao tribe leader was feeling frantic, a weeping sound suddenly came from outside the window.

Hearing this familiar sound, Zhao tribe leader's brows slightly furrowed and revealed a concerned look as he immediately asked: "What's the matter?"

The guard outside the door immediately replied: "Lord tribe leader, big missy slipped on the stairs and knocked her head while running here."

"Ahh!" Zhao tribe leader stood up with a pained expression, "How could my little darling fall? How much blood did she lose? Quick, bring her here."

Zhao tribe leader had several sons but they were all schemed and killed by Dong Fang Yu Liang, leaving behind only a daughter.

His daughter was only about five or six with a very mischievous nature, but her appearance was extremely similar to his late wife and so Zhao tribe leader doted on her very much.

Soon, the door to the study room was pushed open.

The guard supported a little girl to the room.

The girl looked like she was carved out of jade and looked extremely cute with her embroidered clothing. Right now, she, however, was sobbing, covering her forehead with her hand.

"My little darling, my little Yunyun, where did you get hurt?" Zhao tribe leader quickly walked over and hugged the little girl, asking her with concern.

'Father, did you go blind? The injury is on my forehead...' The little girl furiously shouted inwardly, but on the surface, she smoothly leaned on Zhao tribe leader's chest and acted like a spoiled child, "Father, Yunyun's head hurts..."

"Oh oh, let father take a look." Zhao tribe leader softly parted the hair that covered the little girl's forehead and saw a small scrape on her forehead, the scrape had slightly reddened but was still far from bleeding.

But even so, Zhao tribe leader's heart hurt very much.

He comforted his daughter with warm words before berating the old caretaker that had hurried over: "Nanny Wu, what are you doing? I told you to look after her closely and protect her at all times, look, her forehead is wounded!"

'This old lady should die! Please forgive me lord tribe leader." The old caretaker immediately kneeled with fear, cold sweat filling her face. But her heart was full of grievances, this child was the most crafty child she had seen in her whole life, and the most troublesome little demon. Normally, if she lost her concentration even a bit, the child would disappeared somewhere bizarrely. The child was extremely crafty, toying with this adult women until she wished she was dead. But in front of the tribe leader, the child showed an obedient and pitiful expression, her acting was so brilliant that it seemed she was innately born with it. The old caretaker could not find the least bit of evidence on this little demon!

"Father, don't blame nanny, it is Yunyun's fault for carelessly running around." The little girl said in a soft voice.

Adding in a sentence inwardly: 'This old woman is too annoying, always following me the whole day. I had to self-harm myself to enter this study room, was it easy for me huh!'

Zhao tribe leader heaved a sigh and stroked the little girl's soft dark hair with a gratified expression: "Daughter, you are as kind-hearted as your mother."

The old caretaker however roared inwardly: 'Tribe leader, you have been deceived, your daughter is absolutely a demon...'

But she could only shout in her mind because she knew, very few people apart from her would be willing to believe this fact. She naturally did not dare to tell it, if she said it, who knew how this girl would tease and abuse her later on.

"Useless thing, if it were not for Yunyun asking for leniency... hmph, leave." Zhao tribe leader waved his hand towards the old caretaker to order her to leave before looking at his daughter with a gentle expression, "Little darling, why did you come here to play?"

"Father, Yunyun was worried about you, I heard others say those elders were arguing with father these days and that you were upset and locked yourself in the study." The little girl looked concernedly at Zhao tribe leader with her large gleaming black eyes.

But in truth, she was shouting in her mind: 'Rubbish, if I did not come, my life would be in danger. Convenient dad you are too indecisive, with the situation as it is now, you are still not immediately escaping? What on earth are you dilly-dallying for?!'

Zhao tribe leader felt a twinge in his nose, his eyes reddened, almost letting out tears: "Good girl, you finally know to care for your father, father's love for you all this time was not in vain. Don't worry, father's health is quite good and my mood is much better now after I saw you."

'Convenient dad, it is a matter of life and death now and you are still so optimistic, so intolerable! For my future happy life, I need to show off a bit regardless of consequences!'

The girl roared in her mind and said with a 'couldn't care less' expression while waving her small delicate hands: "Father, Yunyun thinks those people who quarreled with you are idiots. Our Zheng tribe is like a sheep, Dong Fang tribe is a wolf while the tiger from Yu Tian is coming over. Wolf can't beat tiger, so it wants to find the sheep to help, but whichever side the sheep helps, the tiger or the wolf won't let it go in the end."

The little girl's words shocked Zhao tribe leader's mind. The person on the spot is baffled, while the onlooker sees clearly; sometimes the person involved needs to be enlightened by such words from the onlookers.

'That's right, whether we side with Dong Fang tribe or Hei tribe, it will be like taking favors from a tiger. But can our Zhao tribe stay out of this?'

'No, the blizzard disaster every ten years has already decided there is no utopia in northern plains. The struggle for the Imperial Court is very significant, as long as one can enter Imperial Court blessed land, they can receive astonishing benefits. But which side should Zhao tribe take?'

The little girl had been observing the tribe leader's expression all this while and when she felt the time was right, she added: "Father, I heard Ma[1] tribe is very strong and also treats its people well. Sheep and horse are both vegetarians but tiger and wolf are carnivorous, it will be better for us to ally with Ma tribe!"

Zhao tribe leader's body shuddered.

'Right, why not?'

Ma tribe was different from Hei tribe and Dong Fang tribe, the latter two had Gu Immortal ancestors and the support of blessed lands. They had long lasting history and were super tribes with deep foundations.

Ma tribe was also part of the Huang Jin family, but they did not have a Gu Immortal's support and was advancing towards the level of a super tribe currently. Ma tribe leader and its young tribe leader were outstanding heroes, they would definitely welcome Zhao tribe. Except that to go to Tian Chuan, it would be a long journey...

'Convenient dad, why on earth are you still hesitating? Decide quickly!' The little girl who had been observing her father's expression changing frequently, felt very anxious inwardly.

But Zhao tribe leader was thinking of the long distance they had to travel to Tian Chuan to side with Ma tribe. This distance was filled with danger which caused him to hesitate.

Helplessly, the little girl could only add on: "Father, we should leave right away. This is the best time to leave, tiger and wolf are confronting each other, they don't have any spare strength to care about us."

Zhao tribe leader's heart trembled.

"Right, why am I still hesitating? If I hesitate any longer, even the best chance to escape will be lost! Whether it is Hei tribe or Dong Fang tribe, they are both not kind. If my tribe wants to get some profits in the battle for the Imperial Court, laying a bet on them is not a good thing!"

"Good girl, you are extremely correct. Our Zhao tribe cannot meddle in such a huge battle, also cannot throw ourselves in this whirlpool. Right, we shall leave!" Zhao tribe leader made the decision.

The little girl leaning on his chest was almost sobbing tears of joy at this moment, as she sighed inwardly: 'Old man, you finally opened your eyes. Ah, it was not in vain that I took so much trouble to run over here to persuade you...'

"But Yunyun, did you think up all these things? Did someone tell you to say so? Who was it, tell father." Zhao tribe leader finally sensed something amiss and gazed at his daughter.

The little girl's heart thumped, she promptly blinked her large eyes and showed an innocent expression: "No one taught me. Father, this was all thought by Yunyun. Father works so hard every day, Yunyun does not want father to be so exhausted, so Yunyun wanted to help father."

She then carefully said with a pitiful expression: "Father, was Yunyun wrong?"

Zhao tribe leader's eyes flashed with a pleasantly surprised look. He did not think this little angel before him would deceive him.

How old was this child?

And he had watched her grow up!

Since she was so intelligent at such a young age, her cultivation talent might also be extraordinary.

Seeing his daughter afraid of being scolded, an affectionate feeling rose in Zhao tribe leader's heart.

He stroked the little girl's hair: "Yunyun, thankfully I have you. Father is really happy to have such a good daughter!"

'Sigh, it has to be like this, since I've transmigrated here already. In life, friends can be chosen, but parents are predestined. Seeing how you have treated me well, I will naturally return the favor...'

The little girl said so inwardly, but on the surface, she hugged Zhao tribe leader's neck and kissed this convenient dad's cheek: "Father, daughter likes you the most."

"Hahaha, good girl, you are really father's darling." Zhao tribe leader laughed loudly.

[1] Also read as horse in chinese. Back

Chapter 503: Dong Fang Yu Liang

"Zhao tribe tore down their camp and left?" Hei Lou Lan glanced at the information report before casually throwing it on the table.

Zhao tribe might be a large scale tribe but it did not have elite troops and not even a decent Gu Master expert. Although Zhao tribe leader was at rank five initial stage, he was challenged and defeated by Dong Po Kong with his rank four peak stage cultivation three years ago. Thus, he did not have high prestige and also did not make too big of a contribution in his long years of being in power.

If Zhao tribe had sided with Dong Fang tribe, he might have given them some attention; after all, even a weak rank five Gu Master could not be underestimated.

However, Zhao tribe had fled in a sorry figure which caused Hei Lou Lan to be filled with contempt towards them.

Northern plains men admired the brave and looked down upon such cowardly conducts of escaping before even fighting.

"Congratulations to alliance leader, we have not even truly attacked and yet we managed to scare off a large scale tribe of the other side."

"Dong Fang Yu Liang should be bursting with rage, he had personally invited Zhao tribe but the other directly ran away, hahaha."

"In my opinion, Zhao tribe might be a large scale tribe, but they are nothing outstanding, they were actually such cowards. Hmph..."

The Gu Masters in the main tent commented one after another, not concerned about Zhao tribe's stance.

Fang Yuan who was sitting by the side swept his eyes through the information report on the table.

Zhao Lian Yun.

He remembered this name. A mysterious woman who would become one of Ma Hong Yun's wives, and also a wisdom path Gu Immortal. Now, however, she was only a little girl.

"Looks like the famous persuasion of tiger, wolf and sheep has already utilized..."

Fang Yuan sneered inwardly.

In his past life, after Zhao Lian Yun became wisdom path Gu Immortal, someone made a biography on her.

This cultural tradition could be traced back to \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>. This first classic of Gu was polished by many Gu Masters spending their effort and time. For many outstanding Gu Masters and Gu Immortals, people would write and spread their biography to remember and praise them.

In the contents of the biography of Zhao Lian Yun: Zhao Lian Yun displayed extraordinary intelligence and wisdom since she was young. In the huge battle where 'Black Tyrant Hei Lou Lan' fought for the ownership of the Imperial court, Zhao tribe was sandwiched between Dong Fang tribe and Hei tribe.

When Zhao tribe leader was hesitating, Zhao Lian Yun used the comparison between tiger, wolf and sheep to persuade her father and made him decide to travel far away to side with Ma tribe. In the end, this allowed Zhao tribe to not only be protected, but also received extremely high importance and cordial welcome.

His five hundred years of memories of his past life was all in disorder, but this information was still fresh in Fang Yuan's memories.

Simply because in the battle of five regions, Ma Hong Yun, Sheng Ling Er and Zhao Lian Yun would not only become Gu Immortals but also become the symbols and cornerstones of Northern Plains in resisting the invasion of Heavenly Court.

In the five regions, the biographies of such people would be widely spread and reviewed.

"Hmph, people like Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun, I will send them to their deaths before they grow sooner or later. But there's no hurry at the moment..." Fang Yuan restrained the killing intent in his heart while showing a tranquil expression on the surface.

Whether it was Ma Hong Yun or Zhao Lian Yun, these people who rode the tides of the five regions battle, right now they were still a long distance away from becoming Gu Immortals. Fang Yuan had plenty of time to deal with them.

But Ma Hong Yun, Fang Yuan had to keep him around to deal with the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. As for Zhao Lian Yun, although he wanted to kill her, he was hindered by his identity and the situation.

After all, Fang Yuan was currently playing the role of Chang Shan Yin. The great Chang Shan Yin, how could he attach such importance to a girl that was only a few years old, to the point of wanting to kill her?

"Moreover, the matter of importance right now is to handle Dong Fang tribe!" Fang Yuan collected his thoughts and concentrated on the discussions again.

After having ridiculed Zhao tribe for a while, everyone put their attention on their opponent this time.

Dong Fang tribe was the same as Hei tribe, a super tribe with deep foundations and was preeminently a huge force in Cao Fu region.

Dong Fang Yu Liang was this generation's tribe leader for Dong Fang tribe, young and promising. Relying on his wisdom path cultivation, he not only handled all the tribe affairs cleanly, the tribe was even showing the trend of becoming more prosperous.

Although Hei tribe's military strength was superior, their opponent was a wisdom path Gu Master who was an expert in planning and deductions, such strength could absolutely not be underestimated!

"If we talk of the greatest threat in this battle, it definitely is Dong Fang Yu Liang!"

"Right, this kid is young but has great experience and knowledge, accomplished in the four arts as well as astronomy and geology. He lost his parents at eleven, and he had to not only maintain his livelihood but also care for his then six year old little sister Dong Fang Qing Yu. His parents had left him an enormous inheritance, but this kid knew clearly about the nature of men and that he could not protect the inheritance, so he gave these family assets to an authoritative elder, leaving only a small portion for himself."

"He performed extremely well during his time at the academy. After graduating, he became that elder's trusted aide. Afterwards, he made many contributions which got him the appreciation and recommendation from the elder, unexpectedly obtaining pointers from their Gu Immortal ancestor, finally obtaining his current status and power."

Everyone knew about Dong Fang Yu Liang in detail, each of them said a few words about his origins.

Fang Yuan carefully listened.

He had not heard of these in-depth things in his past life. Now that he was experiencing this, he immediately realized this Dong Fang Yu Liang was not simple and needed to be given importance.

"History is vast and profound, great waves sweep away the sand, who knows how many heroes it will sweep away."

At the same time as everyone was discussing, their focal point — Dong Fang Yu Liang was also planning for this extremely important battle, in the study room.

Dong dong dong.

Three soft knocking sounds were heard.

"You can come in, sister." Dong Fang Yu Liang knew who was it without even raising his head.

The door was pushed open and a gentle, graceful and extremely beautiful girl wearing a light yellow dress came in with a bright appearance.

She had soft and glossy skin with eyes that were clear and transparent, her soft voice was full of concern: "Big brother, the jade apricot blossom we got from central continent should have blossomed. Big brother, accompany me to go look at them."

Dong Fang Yu Liang smiled, he knew he had worried his little sister by sitting in the study for a day and a night, and she was using this excuse to let him loosen up.

"Alright, let's go, Qing Yu."

The brother and sister walked out of the study together and arrived at the courtyard.

Right now, light rain was falling down and dark clouds covered the sky.

Far away, the rainy curtain and the horizon had merged into one forming a gloomy green color. Coming closer, from the courtyard walls, one could see countless banners and the densely packed tents of Dong Fang tribe.

People moved to and fro in the camp, it was a clamorous scene as they were preparing for the coming battle.

In the small courtyard, there were only the Dong Fang siblings.

The outside clamorous sounds were separated by the rainy curtain, making the small courtyard appear serene and quiet.

Especially that jade apricot blossom with its delicate and exquisite petals which appeared moist and glossy from the rain, and its soft yellow color, gave a comforting feeling to the siblings.

"Big brother, I heard Zhao tribe has moved?" After a while of silence, Dong Fang Qing Yu cautiously asked.

"Don't worry, little sister, big brother had already anticipated this." Dong Fang Yu Liang smiled and softly held his little sister's hand.

Dong Fang Qing Yu slightly raised her head and looked at her big brother standing in this light rain with his white clothing, jade-like face, deep eyes along with his strategizing aura, carrying gracefulness and calmness.

Dong Fang Yu Liang continued: "The reason I invited Zhao tribe was to gather all the strength I could. But them leaving is also of no great matter. With my current force, we can still win against Hei tribe army."

Dong Fang Qing Yu's worries disappeared by over half: "Nothing can escape big brother's deductions. But the opponent this time is not a small character. Not only is there Hei Lou Lan, I heard the previous hero of northern plains, Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, has also sided with him. Big brother, you need to be careful."

"Hehehe, little sister, do you still not believe your big brother? But..." Dong Fang Yu Liang softly comforted his little sister, a radiant light flashing in the depths of his pupils, "We first met Hei Lou Lan when we went to adventure, this person harbored unkind thoughts towards you and was taught a good lesson by me. But now, it seems this person has still not given up. This time, big brother will teach him a lesson that he will never forget in all his life. As for Chang Shan Yin, big brother has a plan to deal with him. All these are within my plans, you just need to recuperate at ease. Your body has been weak since young, don't worry too much. If you become ill, it will only distract me."

Dong Fang Qing Yu lightly nodded with her mind completely relieved.

Since young, it was big brother who cared for her, worried for her and looked out for her.

She was like a young, delicate flower that was sheltered by this big tree, her big brother.

All these years, she and her brother had gone through all kinds of difficulties together, this time too would be the same.

'Because since young till now, big brother has always been calm and collected like this. It is only that... if I didn't have this illness, if I had the aptitude to cultivate, it would have been much better.' Dong Fang Qing Yu heaved a deep sigh in her heart.

The siblings quietly stood there, looking at the jade apricot blossom.

"Little sister, standing in the rain for too long is not good for health, you should go back to rest." After a while, Dong Fang Yu Liang spoke.

"Mm, big brother don't work too much." Dong Fang Qing Yu answered with her lovable voice.

Looking at his little sister leaving and disappearing at the corner, Dong Fang Yu Liang could finally not hide his expression, his brows furrowed and revealed a worried expression.

This battle was absolutely not as easy as he made it out to be.

"Hei Lou Lan himself is not an easy opponent, now there is Chang Shan Yin as well. Five hundred thousand wolves, really worthy of being an enslavement path master, just him alone can change the situation, causing this slightly superior Hei tribe to jump far ahead of my tribe."

"For this coming battle, our side must first deal with these five hundred thousand wolves. Otherwise, the hopes for victory will be extremely uncertain."

"I cannot lose! It was not easy for me to make Gu Immortal Old Ancestor agree; if I can complete this secret mission, the old ancestor will personally solve the source of the illness in my little sister. For my little sister, I must become the master of Imperial Court and enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!"

"Before this, anyone who dares to block my path must die! So, Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, why don't you die in this rain before the battle?"

Dong Fang Yu Liang looked at the dense dark clouds in the sky, his handsome face showing a very cold expression.

Chapter 504: Assassination (Long Chapter)

The weights-like strength of ten jun Gu was quietly hovering above Fang Yuan's head.

Fang Yuan was sitting cross-legged with his eyes closed, his body shrouded by the light from strength of ten jun Gu.

A long time passed.

Fang Yuan opened his eyes, the light slowly dispersed and the strength of ten jun Gu only was half of its original size.

"I can still use it twice." Fang Yuan silently evaluated.

Strength of ten jun Gu was an expendable Gu; after completely using this one, Fang Yuan would possess seventy jun of strength. This strength could only be said to be just passable even among rank four initial stage strength path Gu Masters.

All-out effort Gu was suppressed to rank two and if it was not resolved, there would be no possibility for a qualitative change in Fang Yuan's strength path cultivation. That is to say, his strength path battle strength was not useful in this short period of time.

He checked his first aperture and second aperture again.

The vital Gu of the first aperture was Spring Autumn Cicada which was still in a concealed state and was recuperating.

The ninety percent purple crystal primeval sea was gleaming with light, dying the rank five peak stage crystal walls with purple color.

Above the sea was wolf smoke Gu which looked a lump of dark clouds in the shape of a wolf.

The completely repaired battle bone wheel was afloat on the surface along with the spotless white willow leaf-like snow wash Gu.

Rank five hints and clues Gu was diving like a cuttlefish, playing occasionally with the wolf swallow Gu.

At the bottom was large numbers of wolf enslavement Gu, many strength of ten jun Gu and some wolf soul Gu.

At the same, the most important Gu to Fang Yuan currently - stargate Gu, moving perspective cup Gu, east window Gu, soul burial Gu and instant success Gu - were lurking around.

As for wolf howl Gu, wolf care Gu, eagle rise Gu, wolf sprint Gu and breath concealment Gu, they were residing in different places on his body.

As the time Fang Yuan spent in northern plains increased, his body was also gradually adapting to the northern plains' environment. His first aperture's cultivation had already recovered to rank five middle stage but Fang Yuan had all along been using breath concealment Gu to suppress his aura to rank four peak stage.

It was a different scene in the second aperture.

The crystal membrane of the second aperture shone brightly.

Ninety percent true gold primeval sea rippled and gleamed.

After these days of cultivating, Fang Yuan's second aperture had grown to rank four peak stage from rank three peak stage.

At the center of the aperture was the rank three all-out effort Gu.

Besides this, there were rank three strength qi Gu which could condense beast phantoms into solid form, rank four bitter strength Gu which could increase strength the more one got injured.

Rank four charging crash Gu, rank three tusita flower, primeval elder Gu, rank four expend strength Gu and the healing Gu rank three self-reliance Gu.

As for vajra stare Gu, turn gold Gu, pitch black Gu, blood skull Gu, bone flesh unity Gu, yin yang rotation Gu and others, they could not be used at the moment and were thus left behind in Hu Immortal blessed land.

Because Fang Yuan appeared in northern plains first from Lang Ya blessed land, his second aperture was approved by northern plains and its rank four peak stage cultivation did not receive any suppression.

Second aperture's cultivation could increase so rapidly because of those relic Gu Fang Yuan bought before.

But due to the limited immortal essence stones he had, he was unable to buy purple crystal relic Gu, so now the second aperture's cultivation would depend on Fang Yuan's own effort.

"Rank four to rank five is a process of qualitative change, there is a huge gap between them. I might as well raise my second aperture's cultivation to rank five initial stage tonight!" Seeing there was enough time, Fang Yuan continued to sit cross-legged, deciding to breakthrough to rank five realm.

Second aperture's cultivation was already at rank four peak stage and already had sufficient foundation, its aptitude could not be higher than the first aperture but with Lang Ya land spirit personally refining it, its aptitude also reached ninety percent.

For normal Gu Masters who fulfilled these two conditions, they had enough capital to breakthrough to rank five realm.

Normally, they would gain enough experience after some failures and then successfully advance.

But experience had always been a strong point of Fang Yuan and this obstacle did not exist for him.

More importantly, first aperture and second aperture's primeval essence could be mutually used!

There were no two leaves that were completely the same in this world; similarly primeval essence was unique to each Gu Master. If Gu Masters transferred primeval essence to each other without the use of Gu like bone flesh unity Gu, the foreign primeval essence would mix together and the aperture would explode eventually.

However, whether it was the first or second aperture, they both belonged to Fang Yuan; their essence was the same so the primeval essence could be mutually transferred.

"Rise."

Fang Yuan silently willed and the purple crystal primeval essence in his first aperture charged towards the second aperture in the center of his chest.

A rank five peak stage primeval essence charging at rank four crystal membrane was bound to cause an intense reaction.

At the crack of dawn, Fang Yuan had successfully broken through to rank five initial stage.

The breakthrough to rank five this time was the easiest one in all the attempts he had ever tried.

"But because I used first aperture's primeval essence, the second aperture has also received the region's suppression now." Fang Yuan could perceive that the second aperture right now had light purple primeval essence but activating it would only give the effect of the previous true gold primeval essence.

"In just over half a month, the suppression on the second aperture will fade while the first aperture will completely blend into northern plains' environment in three months and will no longer receive suppression! It will also be the time when the struggle for the Imperial Court reaches the climax...."

Fang Yuan let out a breath of turbid air and stood up to stretch his body.

A night of cultivation without rest gave him a slight feeling of tiredness.

He pushed open the secret room's door. The two rank three Gu Masters guarding in front of the door immediately greeted him.

One of the Gu Masters gave good news to Fang Yuan: "Lord Wolf King, our Gu Masters were fortunate enough to capture a shark fin wolf in the wild. We have locked it within a cage, tribe leader has told me to inform lord, when you finish your cultivation, to go to the supply camp to subdue it.

This news was an unexpected surprise to Fang Yuan.

Shark fin wolf was a mutated beast with the battle strength of a rank four Gu Master. Although Fang Yuan had purchased a batch of mutated wolves in treasure yellow heaven, he did not bring them out due to the lack of a clear explanation.

If there was a shark fin wolf by his side guarding him, Fang Yuan would no doubt be much safer while battling.

After a while, Fang Yuan entered the supply camp.

"Tu Bo greets Lord Wolf King." A rank three Gu Master hurried over to welcome Fang Yuan.

He was short and fat, his chubby face shining with a glossy light. He spoke with a flattering voice: "Lord Wolf King, I have already been waiting for a long time to receive you."

At Tu Bo's lead, Fang Yuan and others soon saw that shark fin wolf in a wooden cage.

The shark fin wolf was as huge as an elephant and was lying in the cage at this moment. Its whole body was covered with firm carapace like a crocodile's. On its back, a row of shark fins extended from its head to tail.

The light of dawn shone on its body. This shark fin wolf was closing its eyes, its consciousness lost under the effect of slumber Gu.

"Congratulations to lord. Shark fin wolf is the mutated wolf with the strongest defense. With this wolf's protection, lord will be like a tiger that has grown wings."

"What's rarer is that shark fin wolf can not only fight on land, but has even more battle strength underwater!"

The two rank three Gu Master guards looked at this divine steed shark fin wolf and commented while congratulating Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan smiled and looked at this shark fin wolf, his eyes slightly narrowed as he absent-mindedly asked: "How many people were sacrificed to capture this mutated wolf?"

Tu Bo knew Fang Yuan was asking him, immediately replying: "We had to sacrifice four rank three Gu Masters and at least over two hundred rank two Gu Masters. If not for Wang tribe leader and Fang tribe leader's timely reinforcement, this shark fin wolf would have escaped."

Fang Yuan nodded, his eyes squinting to a slit: "This shark fin wolf is riddled with injuries but it looks like it had old injuries?"

"Yes. If not for its old injuries, the investigative Gu Master might not have been able to escape alive and hurry back to report. I can see that Lord Wolf King has obtained the blessing of Longevity Heaven, sending you an injured shark fin wolf before the great battle." Tu Bo flattered.

"Fortunate..." Fang Yuan muttered, a feeling of uneasiness becoming ever stronger in his heart.

He was not clear on how this feeling arose, but it gave him an indescribable sense of danger.

He asked several questions but did not find anything wrong.

Shark fin wolf was a mutated beast, having battle strength of a rank four Gu Master. Because it had old injuries, it could be held back and captured alive.

Everything was reasonable.

The only unreasonable thing was the uneasy feeling in Fang Yuan's heart.

But Fang Yuan placed utmost importance on this instinct.

He did not have this feeling when he had just crossed over in his previous life. It was an intuition that was born from the accumulation of his plentiful experience after enduring hundreds of years of trials and countless deadly situations.

People became astute as they aged. No matter how stupid someone was, after experiencing many losses and trials, and seeing many things, they would naturally gain some wisdom.

In truth, not only humans, even ordinary beasts would have a type of intuition and sensitivity towards danger.

Under the surrounding Gu Masters' anticipating looks, Fang Yuan took out a rank four wolf enslavement Gu.

"Here take it, subdue this mutated wolf." What was unexpected was Fang Yuan did not personally make a move, instead gave the wolf enslavement Gu to Tu Bo.

"Lord wants me to use it?" Tu Bo was astonished, "But I am only at rank three..."

"Speak less nonsense and use it quickly." Fang Yuan impatiently shouted, forcibly handing the wolf enslavement Gu to Tu Bo.

Tu Bo was helpless, he did not know what eccentric temperament a lord like Wolf King had, but due to Fang Yuan's prestige, he could only start pouring primeval essence into the wolf enslavement Gu.

He poured his primeval essence for a long time and only when he was starting to sweat profusely from the exhaustion, did the rank four wolf enslavement Gu slowly activate.

Wolf enslavement Gu turned into a mystical light and descended on the shark fin wolf's body while flickering.

"Sigh..." A regretful sigh of a female suddenly resounded in everyone's ears.

At that instant, the warning sign in Fang Yuan's heart suddenly soared and he immediately retreated without thinking!

A trembling feeling instantly engulfed the souls of everyone present.

Almost at the same moment, Tu Bo suddenly opened his mouth and let out a miserable cry before dying on the spot!

The two rank three Gu Master guards were overwhelmed with shock, they simply did not know how Tu Bo lost his life. Subconsciously, they followed Fang Yuan and quickly flew back.

But soon, one of them suddenly shuddered, losing all life while still in mid-air.

"Soul explosion..." A light flashed past Fang Yuan's mind as he blurted out.

"Lord Wolf King sure enough has extraordinary insights." A woman's soft sound echoed beside his ear followed by surging shadows.

The shadows were like swords, overlapping over one another and suddenly opened up like a peacock fanning its feathers before binding Fang Yuan's body incisively.

Rank four — multiple sword shadow Gu!

Cling Clang!

Immediately, concentrated sounds echoed, blending into one.

Multiple sword shadows struck Fang Yuan's body, producing dazzling sparks like gold colliding with iron.

Fang Yuan's skin turned dark-green and if one carefully observed it, they would see patterns over his body like that on a turtle shell.

Rank five — turtle jade wolf skin Gu!

"Female scoundrel!" The remaining rank three Gu Master roared when he saw Fang Yuan being attacked, and changed his direction to help out.

The female Gu Master who was mounting a sneak attack on Fang Yuan snorted, ignoring him as she made the multiple sword shadows go more berserk.

At the same time, she spat out a thin snake.

The snake was like a black thread that passed by the sword shadows and directly moved towards Fang Yuan's ear.

Fang Yuan was expressionless, his gaze as cold as an icy mountain. He suddenly moved his right hand and grabbed the rank three Gu Master guard who came to assist him.

"Lord Wolf King!" The rank three Gu Master was startled, he had come to protect Fang Yuan and had never imagined Fang Yuan would actually grab him.

While he was astonished and dazed, Fang Yuan pulled him towards his right side, right in between Fang Yuan and shark fin wolf.

Almost at the same time, the rank three Gu Master gave a short pained groan, his whole body twitched, his eyes rolled and he foamed from his mouth!

The thread-like snake took this chance to slitter into Fang Yuan's ear.

Fang Yuan gave a stuffed snort, he then let go of the rank three Gu Master and started to pound the sword shadows.

The female Gu Master could perceive the enormous strength contained within these punches. She softly chuckled and did not receive the punches forcibly, instead called back the multiple sword shadow Gu, her body then turned into a black shadow as she swiftly retreated twenty steps away.

The black shadow landed on the shadow of a tent and turned back into a woman.

This woman looked exquisite, she wore black clothing and her face was covered with a black gauze, only revealing a pair of narrow red phoenix eyes.

From top to bottom, her body let out a gloomy and solitary aura, adding a demonic charm to her beauty; one look at her and it would be hard to forget.

"Junior Shadowless Sword Bian Si Xuan greets Lord Wolf King." The woman slightly bowed towards Fang Yuan. She was in the enemy camp with enemies surrounding her, but she looked calm and at ease.

Fang Yuan snorted and questioned: "What Gu did you assault me with?"

Bian Si Xuan smiled: "When junior went on an expedition once, in a certain ruins, I unexpectedly discovered a strange Gu worm. When activated, it would pierce into the ear and enter the brain. As long as the person thinks faster for even a bit, this Gu will rapidly expand till the brain bursts. Thus junior has named it brain explosion Gu."

Fang Yuan's expression sank.

Bian Si Xuan bowed once more, her tone full of sincere admiration: "Senior could actually perceive Lord Dong Fang's meticulously planned fatal trap and even avoid most of the force of soul explosion, junior is truly in admiration. Taking senior's life will be junior's greatest honor, farewell."

Immediately afterwards, she turned into a black shadow and ran through the shadows of the buildings.

"She's shadow sword expert!"

"Damn it, block her."

Many Gu Masters who had hurried because of the noise, shouted furiously and attacked at the shadows, but Bian Si Xuan's black shadow had already disappeared.

She left, or was she still here? For a moment, no one dared to be certain.

"We came late, we ask for Lord Wolf King's forgiveness!"

"Lord Wolf King, are you alright?"

The worried crowd quickly surrounded Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's body did not suffer heavy injuries but his skin and hair were slashed by the sword shadows, making him look quite miserable.

"What could happen to me? A group of incompetent trash, no one realized that the other party had infiltrated the camp! All of you get lost!" Fang Yuan shouted in anger, but he was secretly joyful.

He had not thought that in this assasination attempt, a clue to one of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritances would become his!

Brain explosion Gu?

Did you really think I could not have blocked it?

Hmph, inexperienced junior...

In Fang Yuan's past life's memories, this shadow sword expert Bian Si Xuan was an important character.

She was one of Ma Hong Yun's wives and would become rank six Gu Immortal in the future. It was because of her 'brain explosion Gu', that Ma Hong Yun could obtain one of Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritances.

It was only that Ma Hong Yun had always avoided mentioning what this inheritance was or the concrete details of it, so Fang Yuan was also not clear.

He only knew how to properly activate this 'brain explosion Gu'.

"Ma Hong Yun always avoided talking about it, one could see how big of a harvest he had gained from this inheritance and was afraid of others coveting it if he told the truth." Fang Yuan looked extremely furious on the surface, but his heart was calmly analyzing the event.

Chapter 505: Star Thought Gu

"We did not succeed after all..." Dong Fang Yu Liang looked at the rain outside the window with his arms behind his back, sighing.

This shark fin wolf was captured from the wild intentionally, he paid a hefty price.

After that, he made some secret markings on the shark fin wolf, and as he was afraid of his enemy finding out, he purposely chose a rank five soul explosion Gu and planted it inside the shark fin wolf.

Finally, he sent an assassin in the demonic path who was famous in northern plains, Shadow Sword Expert, and gave the corresponding Gu needed to activate the soul explosion to her, instructing carefully.

This assassination that he planned meticulously, in order to not waste his efforts, he made several simulations, until all the flaws and loopholes were removed.

Be it the shark fin wolf's body, the location or time it appeared, even the attitude of the Gu Master who discovered the shark fin wolf was considered by him.

But even so, he did not succeed.

At the crucial moment, Wolf King Chang Shan Yin found something amiss and ordered someone else to strike. Seeing that the chance was slipping away, Shadow Sword Expert had to activate soul explosion Gu.

The power of soul explosion was formless and colorless, it could not be seen with the naked eye, but Chang Shan Yin was able to escape at the first moment and reveal the truth.

As he was restricted by Bian Si Xuan's attacks, he only managed to get to the furthest range of the soul explosion, but in the moment of crisis, he was extremely calm, using the reinforcements as a shield and blocked most of the soul explosion's strength.

"His reputation matches his abilities, as expected of the Wolf King who shook northern plains." Dong Fang Yu Liang heard Bian Si Xuan's report and raised his evaluation of Fang Yuan.

With a mutated beast before him, he managed to control the temptation. With his vigilant nature, he made the correct judgement in the face of danger, and immediately spotted the soul explosion's range, the callousness of using his own alliance mate as a shield, as well as the calmness to not chase after the perpetrator after being assassinated.

"Wolf King..." Dong Fang Yu Liang muttered, his heart becoming heavier.

"Dong Fang alliance leader does not need to worry. Although Chang Shan Yin used a meat shield at the last moment, he was still obstructed by me and was within range of the soul explosion. Furthermore, he was afflicted by my brain explosion Gu, even if this Gu didn't take his life, his battle strength would be greatly affected. We can say that Wolf King is basically crippled now."

At a corner of the study room, Bian Si Xuan wore black clothes as she stood among the shadow, saying in a cold voice.

"Brain explosion Gu?" Dong Fang Yu Liang was stunned, this was the first time he had heard of this Gu.

Bian Si Xuan laughed lightly, explaining to him the origin of this Gu.

"So that's it..." Dong Fang Yu Liang heard this and his eyes shone, he sighed as he thanked Bian Si Xuan: "It was all thanks to Shadow Sword Expert's help this time, but you lost a great trump card in the progress."

Bian Si Xuan did not speak.

Actually, her heart was bleeding too.

Ever since she had tested the effects of brain explosion Gu, she had kept it as one of her trump cards. Many of her assassinations succeeded because of it.

But when she assassinated Chang Shan Yin, the situation was urgent and she could not kill Chang Shan Yin on the spot, thus she could not retrieve it. When the enemy forces came, she had to retreat to protect herself.

"This is the reward that you were promised earlier." Dong Fang Yu Liang took out a Gu worm from his aperture.

This Gu's body was black, it had a horn and square shell. It was fist-sized but gave people a heavy feeling.

This was the rank four overlapping shadow Gu.

Bian Si Xuan's gaze landed on overlapping shadow Gu, showing some desire and anxious emotion. Although she had multiple sword shadow Gu, the attacks were dispersed and she would face a tough battle when fighting against a defensive opponent.

If she could have overlapping shadow Gu, she could overlap the sword shadows together, and form a strong attack. It would be a huge boost to her battle strength.

But quickly, Bian Si Xuan retracted her gaze, not taking the overlapping shadow Gu.

In the shadows, her cold voice could be heard carrying some arrogance: "This overlapping shadow Gu will be kept by alliance leader for now, after the Wolf King dies, I will come and take it."

Saying so, she fused into the shadows, vanishing.

Dong Fang Yu Liang was slightly stunned, he kept the overlapping shadow Gu back into his aperture.

"This Shadow Sword Expert is truly a person of her word, no wonder she can gain such success among the large tribes despite being a demonic path Gu cultivator. Many righteous path Gu Masters would spend a heavy sum to hire her. It seems that she is very confident in brain explosion Gu... if this can really get rid of Wolf King, then I will have one less threat to worry about, that is the best case."

"But what if she fails? What if brain explosion Gu was successfully resolved by Chang Shan Yin? At the crucial moment, he had chosen to deal with the soul explosion Gu and instead allowed the brain explosion Gu to enter his ear, that shows he had some confidence and countermeasure for this problem..."

Dong Fang Yu Liang's gaze dimmed: "But Wolf King was indeed affected by the soul explosion... there are more variables now, I have to make new deductions."

Thinking of this, he moved beside the book shelf and turned the incense holder, opening up a secret tunnel.

Walking in the secret tunnel, he came to a deep area.

Here, he had planted an earth bacteria king Gu.

This Gu was a type of Gu house, the space was cramped inside but it was enough for a person to cultivate. Most importantly, the earth bacteria king Gu had strong defense, it could ensure Dong Fang Yu Liang's safety.

After he entered the Gu house, Dong Fang Yu Liang closed the exit. The entire earth bacteria king Gu curled into a ball and went further down by a few meters before stopping.

The earth bacteria king Gu's internal walls were soft and thick, like a carpet. Dong Fang Yu Liang sat down and closed his eyes.

His mind entered his aperture, activating his rank five primeval essence and injected it into his star thought Gu.

He started to think —

"If Wolf King manages to deal with brain explosion, how do I deal with him?"

The moment this question emerged in his mind, under the effect of star thought Gu, it formed into a thought.

Ordinary thoughts were formless and without matter, it could exist in the brain.

But this thought gave off a blue starlight, not only could it be seen with the naked eye, it could also leave his brain and head, flying above Dong Fang Yu Liang.

Dong Fang Yu Liang quickly thought: "To deal with an enslavement path Gu Master, there are three ways."

"The first is the supreme method, pitting enslavement path master against enslavement path master." The second thought shining with starlight flew out of Dong Fang Yu Liang's brain, flying together with the first star thought.

"The second is the domination method, using the beheading leader tactic, charging forward and taking his life from within the army of defense." The third star thought spun around the first star thought as well.

"This third is the peculiar method, assassinating Chang Shan Yin, using bribes or kinship against him." The fourth star thought flew out as well, coiling together with the previous thoughts and collided at times. But no matter how they clashed, the four thoughts remained as four, there were no changes.

Soon after, Dong Fang Yu Liang recalled: Our side's military force, the enemy's military force, both side's rations, Chang Shan Yin's personality and motive, all of our expert Gu Masters' information, all of the enemy's expert Gu Masters' information, the recent weather prediction and changes, the terrain of the battlefield, how many mounds, lakes, how many beast groups nearby, whether any forces will intervene...

Poof.

In an instant, thousands of star thoughts formed at once, gushing out of his brain towards Dong Fang Yu Liang's head.

At once, starlight was shining brightly!

Dong Fang Yu Liang's expression paled as his primeval sea level fell drastically.

He manipulated these star thoughts proficiently.

Orbs of star thoughts, big and small, the biggest were toe-sized while the smallest were thumb-sized. Within this crowded space, these star thoughts collided with each other.

Some star thoughts collided and formed into three or four, even five or six new star thoughts.

Some fused instead, while others split themselves into smaller orbs.

Hundreds and thousands of thoughts filled the air, they were densely packed, circulating around Dong Fang Yu Liang.

The primeval sea level continued to fall, Dong Fang Yu Liang's mind was completely focused, manipulating these star thoughts to fuse and collide, or split into new ones.

Due to his hard work, or through the help of his other wisdom path Gu worms, the star thoughts continued to decrease in number.

After four hours, from the hundreds and thousands of star thoughts, only eight were left.

But these eight star thoughts were fist-sized, shining with starlight as they contained a complicated thought.

As these star thoughts entered Dong Fang Yu Liang's brain, his eyes shone with the light of wisdom.

He had successfully deduced several methods to deal with Wolf King. These methods were organized and clear, with proper steps to be taken.

If it was a normal person, they would have to think for a month or two to clear out these thoughts, in fact, it would be difficult to get the solution from among these messy thoughts.

But using his wisdom path method, Dong Fang Yu Liang spent only four hours and got his answer.

But these answers were not the only ones.

Taking out primeval stones to recover his primeval essence, Dong Fang Yu Liang rested for a while before starting to analyze the same question again.

This time, he only spent an hour and obtained seven star thoughts.

The star thoughts entered his brain, and he got some answers after reading them. These answers were very similar to the ones before, but there were minute details that were different.

Dong Fang Yu Liang breathed a sigh of relief, finally stopping.

After a while, he relied on his primeval stones to recover his primeval essence back to its peak condition.

But in the depths of his soul, there was a strong sense of fatigue circulating around him, he could not get rid of it.

The deductions of wisdom path not only expended primeval essence when activating Gu worms, it also expended the soul's energy. The more deductions made, or the grander the scale of the thoughts, the longer the deduction would take, and the greater the burden on the soul.

Feeling a sense of weakness was normal, if the difficulty of the deduction was higher, the soul might get damaged, or he might even die!

Of course, as a rank five wisdom path Gu Master, Dong Fang Yu Liang who had received guidance from a Gu Immortal naturally had a complete set of Gu worms.

Rank four, refine essence spirit Gu!

Dong Fang Yu Liang's body became thinner immediately, as the vitality in his body was converted by the refine essence spirit Gu into resources for his soul.

The soul was nourished, and his fatigue faded quickly.

But a strong sense of hunger soon assaulted him.

Dong Fang Yu Liang rubbed his tummy, laughing bitterly in his heart: "Refine essence spirit Gu, a secretly passed down Gu in my Dong Fang tribe, it can heal the soul well but it does not treat the core of the issue. Soul path and wisdom path are closely related, if I can get the legendary guts Gu, I would be able to make deductions as I wish. Even if my soul gets damaged, I can easily heal it. What a pity that guts Gu can only be found on Dang Hun mountain..."

Chapter 506: Three Hearts Combination Soul

After a few days of ominous rain, it finally stopped.

The dark clouds dispersed in the sky, as pillars of light shone through the clouds, landing on the wet grassland.

The sky was wide and huge, a truly grand sight.

Hei alliance army formed into a current as they flowed towards Cao Fu.

Looking ahead, there were people all around; looking back, the dark troops looked like a tail, extending beyond where one could see, but this was only the middle troops, other than this, there were the vanguards, support troops, left and right defense troops, this displayed Hei alliance's grand army perfectly.

A huge twin-headed rhino's body was covered in steel armor as it moved like a small astle. With sixteen pairs of pillar-like legs, it moved forward, stepping on the grass causing a dent in it.

This was the rank four strength huge beast twin-headed steel rhino, it was being manipulated by an enslavement path Gu Master as it gave off an imposing aura. Hei tribe's main tent was on its back, as Hei Lou Lan sat at the center of the main tent, the tent was propped up highly and their field of vision was very wide.

He was black and fat, his face was full of hair, he laid down on the tiger skin chair, raising his head to gulp some wine in one mouthful.

"Hahaha, looking at my army's formation, there is no reason to fear that Dong Fang Yu Liang lad." He looked around, the flames of ambition burning in him, as his laughter revealed a brutal and violent aura.

"Lord alliance leader is right!"

"I'm afraid that Dong Fang lad is already peeing his pants in fear already?"

"Haha, with all the heroes present here, our army can definitely take down the opponent swiftly in this battle."

In the main tent, the higher-ups present were mostly rank four experts, there were few rank three peak stage Gu Masters, they were laughing and optimistic, agreeing with Hei Lou Lan's words.

Only one person was seated right beside the main seat, he was expressionlessly resting his eyes, like an outsider, paying no heed to the conversations.

But this did not make anyone unhappy, in fact, this felt natural to them.

Hei Lou Lan filled his wine cup as he toasted this person: "Brother Shan Yin, let's have a drink!"

Fang Yuan opened his eyes, raising his cup as he toasted Hei Lou Lan, drinking the delicious wine together.

"Brother Shan Yin, still thinking about that assassination? Hahahaha, that Shadow Sword Expert is indeed a beauty, I have sent my men to deal with her already. That Dong Fang lad is shameless, he dared to carry out an assassination, but we cannot show any weakness! After we win this battle and capture that woman, she will be yours to deal with!" Hei Lou Lan urged with his rough voice.

Everyone laughed.

"With Lord Wolf King's assistance, any defense line can be broken!" A Gu Master immediately bootlicked.

"Extremely true, I heard that Shadow Sword Expert is beauty as a flower, she would definitely be fun in bed!" A male Gu Master winked, showing an expression that all men can understand.

"What assassination can take our Lord Wolf King's life? Hmph, it is but that Dong Fang lad's wishful thinking, no matter how many assassinations they carry out, we are not afraid." The Gu Master in charge of the camp's defenses laughed.

Fang Yuan snorted, looking at this person coldly: "How many assassinations do you want? Letting someone sneak in here and leave as they wish, aren't you ashamed at all?"

The tent turned quiet.

Hei Lou Lan quickly soothed the atmosphere: "Sigh, don't be angry brother Shan Yin..."

But before he finished, Fang Yuan interrupted him: "Never mind the rest, but Hei tribe leader, where are the materials and Gu worms that I wanted?"

Using the opportunity of the assassination, Fang Yuan flew into a rage and demanded some 'fright recovery fees'.

Hei Lou Lan's eyes flashed with unhappiness for a moment, as he laughed: "I have sent them to your tent, brother."

Fang Yuan nodded in satisfaction, standing up: "In that case, I shall go and cultivate, when the battle begins, call me."

Saying so, he did not wait for Hei Lou Lan's reply before jumping off the twin-headed rhino, leaving everyone's vision.

"Hmph!" Hei Lou Lan snorted with his nose, slamming his wine cup on the table.

After he succeeded in making the alliance, he became the alliance leader, the authority of controlling tens of thousands of people made him feel great satisfaction, he could not tolerate Fang Yuan's arrogant attitude.

The tent was still silent.

But quickly, an ominous voice spoke: "This Lord Wolf King... I understand now why Chang tribe could not tolerate him back then."

Everyone heard this and did not say anything, but agreement could be seen on their expressions.

Chang Shan Yin was arrogant, but any organisation had its chain of commands, any person in power would not allow a subordinate's disregard for the system.

"Oh, it is Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han." Hei Lou Lan turned his gaze over and saw the person speaking, he pointed at Fang Yuan's seat: "Come, since Chang Shan Yin left already, you shall sit here."

Sun Shi Han was overjoyed, he made bad remarks about Fang Yuan in order to please Hei Lou Lan after all.

Hei Lou Lan accepted his goodwill, after all, Fang Yuan's seat was the closest to Hei Lou Lan, but this was the reason why not anyone could sit there.

Sun Shi Han was called Cunning Gentleman, he was a cunning and devious person, adept at using schemes and plots, but he always had a good excuse for what he did, using the banner of righteousness to abide by the rules of the game, although he was extremely shameless, no one could do anything to him.

Sun Shi Han had rank four initial stage cultivation, he knew he had no qualifications to sit on Fang Yuan's seat.

But he had a plan, he stood up from his seat and bowed to Hei Lou Lan: "Thank you alliance leader, but there cannot be reward without hard work, for this battle, I have thought about it for seven days and seven nights, I have twenty-three ideas to offer to you."

"Oh?"

Sun Shi Han immediately said his twenty-three ideas, each sentence cut to the point, he was extremely familiar with Dong Fang alliance army, especially all the expert Gu Masters that they had, he evidently put in great efforts for this.

At once, everyone's attention was on him.

After he finished, Hei Lou Lan clapped as he laughed: "As expected of Cunning Gentleman, that is a good plan."

Sun Shi Han laughed as he continued: "Reporting to alliance leader, just earlier, I have thought of a new plan, it is called expression weakness to the enemy. That Dong Fang Yu Liang assassinated Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, the Wolf King was affected by soul explosion Gu but did not die. Dong Fang Yu Liang would definitely plan again and make many moves against Lord Wolf King. Why don't we make do with this, and order the Wolf King to stay put, only after we tear down Dong Fang Yu Liang's methods in battle will we call the Wolf King to strike, to put an end to the enemy. What do you think about this, alliance leader?"

Everyone heard this and raised their brows, some were silent.

Hei Lou Lan's gaze shone for a bit, he thought about it and said solemnly: "Sun Shi Han's plan is not bad, we will see about it."

This answer was very vague, but Sun Shi Han showed a happy expression.

"Sit." Hei Lou Lan pointed at the seat again.

"Thank you lord for the seat, I am honored." Saying so, Sun Shi Han really kneeled on the ground and kowtowed to Hei Lou Lan.

Many of the Gu Masters present showed a look of disdain, while some old tribe leaders had an expression deep in thought.

　　...

"E Xuan Ming, Jiang Wan Shang, and Wei Xin pays respect to Dong Fang alliance leader."

In the study room, three enslavement path Gu Masters, two males and one female, greeted Dong Fang Yu Liang together.

Although there were no enslavement masters like Fang Yuan in Dong Fang alliance army, there were quite a number of enslavement Gu Masters from the different tribes, and among them, these three were the most outstanding.

Dong Fang Yu Liang sat as he moved his head slightly at the three, immediately getting to the point: "The reason why I called you three here today is to discuss how to deal with Wolf King Chang Shan Yin."

Wolf King Chang Shan Yin!

Hearing this, their expressions changed.

A person's name was like the shadow of a tree.

This was an enslavement path master, having shook northern plains decades ago, now that he had returned, he challenged three mid-sized tribes in one night, not only did his strength increase, he even had the night wolf emperor. With the help of Hei tribe, he controlled half a million wolves, and could affect the entire battle single-handedly!

Such an expert, how could they be his match?

These three enslavement path Gu Masters looked at each other and saw the solemn fear they all had.

But at this point, there was no use being afraid, the three said collectively: "We will listen to Dong Fang alliance leader's instructions."

Dong Fang Yu Liang laughed, but he changed the topic, asking them about the details of enslavement path cultivation.

"Enslavement path requires the most resources, although we have our tribe's support, my crocodile group is only about fifty thousand in numbers. I am ashamed." E Xuan Ming said.

"I'm sure alliance leader knows my circumstances, I was not an enslavement path Gu master from the start, I started halfway when I found Blood Sea Ancestor's small inheritance during an expedition, and obtained quite a number of the bladewing blood bats group. These years, I have been gathering the relevant enslavement path Gu worms, but my progress is slow." Jiang Wan Shan sighed.

Wei Xin sighed too: "In my opinion, the hardest part about enslavement path cultivation is the soul. Using ordinary Gu worms to strengthen and refine the soul has too low efficiency. I worked hard for twenty years, almost cultivating daily, but now I have only reached eight hundred man crabman soul."

Among the three, the oldest and strongest person was Wei Xin.

Soul path, enslavement path, and wisdom path, the three paths had a deep relationship, after Dong Fang Yu Liang heard Wei Xin's words, he thought about his own cultivation, and he showed an understanding expression.

He slowly spoke: "Soul cultivation is very difficult indeed, ample patience is needed to accumulate your growth. Although I used the coptis rhizome Gu, and slow slicing Gu to gain a thousand man soul, it expended ten years of my precious time."

The three heard this and their expression changed when they looked at Dong Fang Yu Liang, turning into a look of admiration.

Coptis rhizome Gu and slow slicing Gu, the former could strengthen the soul, but once a Gu Master uses it, they would experience the most bitter taste in the world, eating anything would be a painful torture to them, if they used this Gu for a long time, they would be unable to eat anything, and the Gu Master would became extremely thin and weak.

Meanwhile, slow slicing Gu could refine the soul, and get rid of the impurities in the soul, but in the process, the Gu Master would feel extreme pain, like their flesh was being sliced away piece by piece.

Dong Fang Yu Liang had outstanding talent, reaching rank five at this young age, but this was also due to his hard work, achieved through an uncountable amount of tears, blood and sweat.

Dong Fang Yu Liang's expression turned serious: "Do you know about our Dong Fang tribe's combination killer move used by three people, called three hearts combination soul?"

Killer move — Three Hearts Combination Soul!

The three's pupils shrunk, Dong Fang tribe's famous triple combination killer move, who in the world would not know about it?

Chapter 507: Surprising Thieving Heaven Inheritance

Red, green, and black, three colors intertwined in the air violently.

A flickering light was reflecting in Fang Yuan's eyes, he was extremely focused as he concentrated on the half finished product in front of him, trying to stabilize the situation.

Chiiii!

Suddenly, a shrill buzzing erupted.

The sound waves vibrated in the air, forming a violent wind as it overturned the table and chairs in the room, even the flower vase fell and smashed on the ground, ink on the table fell on the ground as writing paper flew in the air.

The three colors vanished, and the half finished product exploded into a pool of blue blood traces, splattering on the surrounding walls.

"Failed again..." Fang Yuan sighed lightly.

These days, he had been refining Gu, this Gu was called nauseous crying baby Gu, used mainly to deal with three hearts combination soul.

Three hearts combination soul was a famous killer move of Dong Fang tribe, it could allow three Gu Master's soul to fuse into one temporarily, going into a state where all three work as one, regardless of defending, attacking, or retreating.

With Fang Yuan's experience these few days, his unclear memories started to become more vivid as well.

He vaguely remembered that Hei Lou Lan suffered greatly in this battle against Dong Fang Yu Liang, only winning by a margin. Because of three hearts combination soul, Hei Lou Lan's side suffered great losses.

After that, Ma Hong Yun rose up, and when he was dealing with Dong Fang tribe, three hearts combination soul caused great problems for him.

Once, he was set up by some people, and lost terribly against this killer move, getting captured alive by Dong Fang tribe.

Ma Hong Yun thus became a prisoner, and met with Dong Fang Qing Yu by accident, gaining her affection. Not only did Dong Fang Qing Yu let him escape secretly, she even told him all the secrets regarding this killer move.

Ma Hong Yun returned safely, and together with his wife, Sheng Ling Er, who was a refinement path master, created the nauseous crying baby Gu, specifically to deal with three hearts combination soul.

Nauseous crying baby Gu had great effects on the battle, using this, Ma Hong Yun obtained a great victory, while Dong Fang tribe lost consecutively.

After they failed too many times, the killer move three hearts combination soul was slowly phased out of use.

During the battle of the five regions, chaos was everywhere and three hearts combination soul was stolen by central continent Gu Masters, they improved upon it and it became a powerful move again. Ma Hong Yun thus released the recipe of nauseous crying baby and after everyone learnt it, they modified it based on the original Gu recipe, to deal with the improved three hearts combination soul.

Thereafter, three hearts combination soul finally lost its use, and was left behind in history.

Fang Yuan rebirthed, with five hundred years of memories, he naturally knew the recipe of nauseous crying baby Gu.

But nauseous crying baby Gu was rank four, while the refinement materials were not rare, the refinement difficulty was extremely high. Even with Fang Yuan's near refinement master level skills, he attempted it more than ten times but failed them all.

Sighing, Fang Yuan got up and walked to the window.

This window was destroyed by the Gu refinement failure, the air blast broke the glass, as a huge hole was created. The wind from outside carried the smell of the grass as it flowed into the room through the hole.

Fang Yuan pressed his hand on the window as he sent his primeval essence over.

Quickly, the new window panel started growing, forming and blocking all the wind outside.

The walls moved like intestines, the earlier crevices and holes created were all filled, while the broken vase fragments on the ground as well as the blood traces were devoured.

This was the convenience of the large lizard house Gu.

Large lizard house Gu was rank three, advanced from the rank two lizard house Gu.

The lizard house Gu was already large as a bus, it looked like a four-legged lizard on the outside, with a pathway inside the lizard that splits into rooms on both sides.

The large lizard house Gu was like a two-storey building, its body was five times the size of a lizard house Gu.

It was split into two storeys, there were more rooms and a larger space within,. This was given to Fang Yuan by Hei Lou Lan personally after he joined Hei tribe.

His daily cultivation was all done inside this room.

Aside from Fang Yuan, there were six rank three Gu Masters guarding the surroundings.

They took turns as sentries, paired with their investigative Gu that could deal with all hiding and lurking Gu Masters.

If shadow sword expert attacks again, before she even gets close to a hundred steps, she would be discovered by Gu Masters, and her traces would be exposed. This was a measure set up after Fang Yuan's assassination.

At this moment, Fang Yuan looked down from the window, seeing large numbers of mortals and Gu masters anxiously setting up their defenses.

Some of them were digging canals, some were growing trees, erecting arrow towers, or building mud walls... a tight defensive line was starting to form.

This was the third line of defense.

Northern plains' terrain was mostly flat grassland, there were little obstacles and horses could run freely. Thus, since long ago, when two forces in northern plains engage in battle, the moment one side loses, they would not be able to escape, the winner would definitely be able to chase them down.

Once a battle is lost, it would mean that it was the end, a tribe would quickly weaken or even face its demise.

But with a defensive line, the results would be different.

Once a battle is lost, be it retreating and escaping, or avoiding the enemy temporarily, waiting for a chance to counterattack, these defensive lines would have great use.

Battles were a matter of life and death, it decided the fate of the tribes, it was dangerous and hard to predict, one tiny accident or a mistake from either side could result in failure.

At this time, when a tribe retreats and defends according to their defensive line, they would stabilize their footing and would be able to regroup.

This was the world of Gu. An individual had mysterious powers, it was not difficult to construct a long defensive line that was longer than the great wall on Earth.

People soon realized the benefits of these defensive lines.

Because battles in northern plains were not decided quickly, defense battles were much more advantageous than offensive assault.

"According to our intel, Dong Fang tribe is already starting on the growth defensive line, there are still about three thousand li of distance between us. According to their habits, every eight hundred to one thousand li would have a new defensive line." Fang Yuan recalled from his memories.

These days, he had been cultivating in closed doors, but he had a firm grasp of the outside information. He was a higher-up of Hei alliance army, everyday there would be Gu Masters coming to give him information.

"Looking at the time, tomorrow our vanguards will meet and begin the battle. But there is still some time before I strike."

Fang Yuan was guarding the central camp now with Hei Lou Lan.

A few days ago, Hei Lou Lan had sent someone to convey the message of the showing weakness tactic. In all, they wanted to make use of the opportunity to lure Dong Fang Yu Liang to make arrangements that he had prepared so that Fang Yuan could deal with him.

Fang Yuan laughed coldly towards this.

He had the night wolf emperor, the night wolf group was easy to replenish. But Hei Lou Lan refused to use these cannon fodder, while he wanted to deal with Dong Fang Yu Liang, he also wanted to suppress Wolf King Chang Shan Yin.

Fang Yuan had displayed Chang Shan Yin's arrogance perfectly, this made Hei Lou Lan unhappy, as the alliance was newly formed, all the different tribes were contesting against each other secretly, especially when the current situation was Hei tribe's dominance. thus, all the Gu Masters were competing for battle merit, suppressing others to vie for more benefits.

Water Demon Hao Ji Liu stood in front of the main tent for three days without moving in order to compete for the vanguard's general position. He blocked the door for three days and made a din requesting to participate in battle, and after defeating over a dozen competitors, he got his wish.

Cunning Gentleman used his schemes to emerge victorious, gaining Hei Lou Lan's favor by showing his allegiance, now he was the number one strategist in the alliance army.

This was the internal strife.

Any organisation or political system had no lack of internal strifes.

Chang Shan Yin was a loner, and also had five hundred thousand wolves, thus he was ostracised by everyone — since he is so strong, if he strikes, all the battle merits will be his, what would become of our benefits then?

Hei Lou Lan agreed to Cunning Gentleman's plan because he had to stabilize his position as the leader, and also to defend the hierarchy — Wolf King is way too strong now, it gives me great pressure, there has to be balance, he has to be suppressed.

Towards these issues and these people's thoughts, Fang Yuan was clear as day.

His situation was different, the fight for the Imperial Court was just a jumping board, his motive was greater, much more than anyone could imagine, with the blessed land in his possession, he had little need for these battle gains.

"Since they do not want me to strike, I would use this time to cultivate, isn't that more advantageous for me?"

What Fang Yuan lacked now was not these ordinary resources, but precious resources and large amounts of time.

A day later, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu led the vanguard troops and engaged in battle with Dong Fang alliance army.

When the generals were fighting, Hao Ji Liu displayed great strength as he killed the enemy's general as well as three sub-generals.

The enemy troops were without a leader, they lost their morale and were overwhelmed by Hao Ji Liu's army, allowing him to gain a great victory. But in the process of chasing them, he was attacked by shadow sword expert Bian Si Xuan, and got heavily injured.

Hao Ji Liu had to stop the attack and make a base there, nursing his wounds while waiting for the main troops to arrive.

Three days later, Hei Lou Lan led the central army and entered the frontlines.

Five days later, the two armies converged.

The two camps were only several hundred li apart, the tribe flags were erected all around the camp as battle was around the corner, the atmosphere was heavy.

Late at night, the bright moon shines in the sky with few stars.

In the room, Fang Yuan sat on the cushion as his eyes were shut, activating space thought Gu.

Space thought Gu, rank five, was bought in treasure yellow heaven. Using moving perspective cup Gu, Fang Yuan obtained it from Hu Immortal blessed land.

Under the effect of space thought Gu, Fang Yuan had half-transparent thoughts that appeared like bubbles, getting closer to the brain explosion Gu in his skull.

Brain explosion Gu was only rank four, Fang Yuan used Spring Autumn Cicada's aura to forcefully subdue it back then.

But the brain explosion Gu still remained in his head.

These days, the brain explosion Gu had been absorbing his brain matter, while being corroded by space thought Gu, it had finally reached a qualitative change!

In an instant, the brain explosion Gu scattered into a lump of black light, a lump of white smoke, and a fist-sized space thought.

"The reverse refinement succeeded." Seeing this, Fang Yuan breathed out heavily as his heart was filled with joy.

He moved the black light and white smoke out of his head, as they formed into two rank three Gu.

These Gu were ordinary, Fang Yuan casually placed them at the side.

The important thing was that space thought.

Fang Yuan placed the space thought into his brain and read the details in it.

Soon, his body shuddered as his pupils expanded, his face showing an undeniable joy that could not be concealed.

"This particular Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable's inheritance leads to Luo Po valley?!"

Chapter 508: Challenging Wolf King

The pioneer of soul path — the legendary Gu Master at the apex of rank nine, Spectral Soul Demon Venerable once said:

"In this huge world, the best option for soul strengthening is Dang Hun mountain, and for soul refinement, the best choice is Luo Po valley. One mountain and one valley, with both, one can obtain great success in soul path and sweep every obstacle in this world!"

Thus, Dang Hun mountain and Luo Po valley became known as the soul cultivator's sacred lands.

Fang Yuan was well aware of how huge a help these two sacred lands could provide since obtaining Dang Hun mountain.

His thousand man soul was cultivated through the guts Gu on Dang Hun mountain.

Guts Gu was the number one Gu in increasing the foundation of the soul; it had no side-effects and its efficiency was extremely high as well.

Normal Gu Masters would usually require about twenty years to cultivate their soul to thousand man soul level. Some geniuses with the help of their clans or the guidance of their seniors could cut down this twenty years by half.

But for Fang Yuan?

He used the guts Gu on Dang Hun mountain to strengthen his soul to thousand man level in less than half a year.

This was coupled with the fact that Dang Hun mountain was slowly dying from the Immortal Gu Gruel Mud's corrosion.

With Dang Hun mountain, the speed at which Fang Yuan was able to raise his soul to thousand man soul level was like charging to the sky with a rocket. But apart from strengthening soul, the cultivation of soul required tempering to purify it.

In this aspect, Fang Yuan's progress was much slower.

Compared to the speed of soul strengthening, his soul tempering speed was as slow as a tortoise climbing.

Fang Yuan was using wolf soul Gu to temper his soul, to transform his soul to wolfman soul.

But none of the wolf soul Gu he was using were rank five, the most he used was rank four. Using a rank four wolf soul Gu to purify thousand man soul was like pouring a bottle of ink in a lake; the efficiency of dying the whole lake was way too low.

Fang Yuan had been searching for rank five wolf soul Gu, but it was in vain.

But even without rank five wolf soul Gu, there was still one method.

That was to use second watch Gu or third watch Gu to increase the timeflow of his body, or enter the blessed land, to increase the speed of his cultivation.

These methods could be used by others, but Fang Yuan could not.

Fang Yuan's first vital Gu Spring Autumn Cicada was slowly recovering with time. Before he becomes a Gu Immortal, this Gu would be like an executioner's blade hovering above his neck.

"My thousand man soul was accomplished using Dang Hun mountain, Luo Po valley is on par with Dang Hun mountain, if I could obtain it..."

For a moment, Fang Yuan had an impulse to change to soul path.

"If I can save Dang Hun mountain and obtain Luo Po Valley, with the huge foundation of two sacred lands of the soul path, cultivating soul path would truly be a wise choice, even having much more prospects than the blood path I cultivated in my past life!"

But soon, Fang Yuan calmed down.

"According to the directions given by space thought, Luo Po Valley is quite far away, the matter of importance right now is saving Dang Hun mountain, now is not the time to go to Luo Po Valley. The battle is approaching, I also cannot casually abandon my current strength path and enslavement path foundation."

Fang Yuan was relying on enslavement path and strength path to become an influential figure in northern plains.

But his current strength was still far from allowing him to roam unhindered and invincible in the mortal world.

One shadow sword expert was able to obstruct him.

Although he had second aperture, cultivated strength and enslavement path, had rank five peak stage cultivation, Fang Yuan was involved in the fight for the Imperial Court, he still appeared insignificant.

This was a whirlpool of war that involved the whole northern plains; if one was just a bit careless, even a rank five Gu Master had the danger of dying.

"My enslavement path cultivation has achieved some success and can influence the whole situation, but it is clear that my attack is strong but defense is weak. On strength path aspect, it is still not enough for defending myself. It will be trouble once people like Mo Shi Kuang and Bian Si Xuan get near to me. I have to be much more careful in this battle with Dong Fang tribe."

Thinking of the imminent great battle, Fang Yuan did not have raging battle intent like others.

It could be said that Cunning Gentleman was doing him a small favor, letting him stay behind the scenes and have more time to cultivate and increase his battle strength.

In the following days, Fang Yuan nurtured his second aperture while trying to refine nauseous crying baby Gu. At the same time, he communicated with Little Hu Immortal to handle all kinds of matters in the blessed land.

In Hu Immortal blessed land, Dang Hun mountain's situation continued to worsen, the whole mountain was shrinking day by day. Little Hu Immortal disposed of large amounts of Gruel Mud from Dang Hun mountain every day to prolong Dang Hun mountain's vitality as much as possible.

Starry clouds covered the eastern part of the blessed land, the scale of starlight fireflies had expanded by three times of before, and there were even fifty to sixty more starlight firefly Gu than Little Hu Immortal's initial assessment.

Being able to get this many starlight firefly Gu in this short period of time was all thanks to air bubble fish.

These air bubble fish were gradually showing their effects.

Previously, Fang Yuan had frequently entered and exited Hu Immortal blessed land, using stargate Gu for a long time which caused the amount of starlight firefly Gu to dwindle. Now, starlight firefly Gu expanded in numbers once more, alleviating his pressure.

At the western part of the blessed land, large numbers of pink rabbits were reproducing.

Since Fang Yuan had transferred the wolf groups to northern plains, the pressure on the pink rabbits had decreased, thus their numbers were quickly expanding.

After Little Hu Immortal reported these news, Fang Yuan immediately made her transfer large amounts of water wolves from the eastern lakes to the western parts to fill the gap in the food chain, but even so, the rabbits were still expanding wildly.

To prevent a rabbit calamity, Little Hu Immortal had put up a large group of pink rabbits for sale in treasure yellow heaven, a few days ago.

Fang Yuan was most concerned about the hairy men who were momentarily placed at the southern part of the blessed land.

This was originally the rockmen's home grounds, now there was a group of hairy men who suddenly appeared out of nowhere. The two sides fought for their territories causing several small scale conflicts.

Under Fang Yuan's instructions, Little Hu Immortal secretly helped the hairy men win against a stoneman tribe, and sold the stoneman captives to Immortal Crane Sect.

Immortal Crane Sect kept on trying to make transactions for the guts Gu, but were always refused by Little Hu Immortal. Fang Zheng requested to see Fang Yuan several times as a negotiation representative, but was also refused.

As for treasure yellow heaven, another batch of Gruel Mud was sold, gaining another remnant recipe of Immortal Gu Gruel Mud.

The remnant recipes of Immortal Gu Fang Yuan had sold before was once again resold by Little Hu Immortal after a gap of some time, obtaining eleven immortal essence stones.

When the same Gu recipe is sold multiple times in treasure yellow heaven and more Gu Immortals obtain it, its treasure light will decrease. Thus, this method could not be treated as a long term source of income.

This was like a gold mine which was already mostly mined. The profits in the future would continue to decrease and not be worthy of too much expectations.

After another three days of confrontation, Dong Fang Yu Liang personally wrote a war challenge and sent it to Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan was shocked and asked his subordinates: "Has the rear army of Dong Fang tribe arrived already?"

Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han answered: "Their rear army is still five thousand li away, building the fifth defensive line."

Hei Lou Lan gave a sinister smile: "Dong Fang tribe's military strength was originally lower than ours and they still dare to split their forces!"

Sun Shi Han also smiled: "Dong Fang Yu Liang is playing with fire. We might as well wait until our rear army converges, our military strength will greatly surpass theirs and at that time, we can crush through their whole army in one move."

Baleful light flickered in Hei Lou Lan's eyes. He had a personal grudge with Dong Fang Yu Liang; when he went adventuring to gain experience in his youth, he saw Dong Fang Qing Yu and drooled over her beauty, but he was taught a lesson by Dong Fang Yu Liang and had suffered quite a bit.

He really wanted to take revenge, but he was not someone who was easily controlled by emotions.

"Even a fool can see through this Dong Fang lad's intention. He wants to battle but I won't give him the chance. How long till my rear army arrives?" Hei Lou Lan asked.

"Approximated three days." Wang tribe leader answered from the side.

"Good. I will write a letter to Dong Fang Yu Liang to change the date to four days later!" Hei Lou Lan laughed loudly.

Dong Fang Yu Liang received the letter and skimmed through it.

Dong Fang alliance's higher-ups were filled with fury.

Hei Lou Lan had written nonsense, proclaiming he was giving three days of time to Dong Fang Yu Liang in magnanimity, and hoped Dong Fang Yu Liang would live up to this good intent and enjoy the last days of his life.

The crowd shouted for war one after another, but Dong Fang Yu Liang calmly smiled: "Everyone, do not be impatient. This letter was already within my expectations. I have deduced many times over these days and have come up with a plan, please listen to the details..."

Four days were gone in an instant.

In this day of battle, it was a day of fine weather with blue sky spreading to the distant horizon.

Knee-length grass grew lushly, the two sides moved in formation that reached hundred li, raising banners with tightly packed troops.

A twin-headed hill sized rhino carried the main tent on its back. On the main tent was Hei Lou Lan, Fang Yuan, Hao Ji Liu, Wang tribe leader, Fang tribe leader, Ye tribe leader and other experts.

Fang Yuan's position was naturally at the topmost left side of the main seat.

Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han was standing behind Hei Lou Lan with a loyal expression; he had already become Hei Lou Lan's trusted aide.

The wind whistled, causing the banners to flutter wildly. Fang Yuan looked into the distance from his seat, seeing the tight and disciplined formation of Dong Fang tribe with their main tent resting on a white cloud, floating in mid-air.

One could vaguely see Dong Fang Yu Liang sitting on the central seat in the main tent with officials and fierce experts sitting on his left and right. Just from their disposition, they did not appear any weaker than Hei Lou Lan's side.

At this moment, Hei Lou Lan's loud laughter rang in Fang Yuan's ears: "Hahaha, this battle will signify the first step my Hei tribe takes towards the ownership of the Imperial court and ruling the northern plains. Everyone, who wants to go forward and make the first challenge?"

His words had just landed when a group of Gu Masters rose one after another, shouting or vouching for themselves to request to be sent to battle.

Hei Lou Lan's gaze travelled through the group and landed on one of them: "Pan Ping, you shall go."

Pan Ping was tall and buff, his hair was reddish-yellow, on his waist was a scimitar with gold edge and silver handle. He laughed heartily when chosen and just as he was about to agree, a loud shout came from the enemy: "Junior Tang Miao Ming has heard of the awe-inspiring name of the grand Wolf King for a long time, I have specifically come to get a pointer or two."

"Dong Fang Yu Liang has guts, he actually chose to challenge us first!"

"That is little fox commander Tang Miao Ming, a rank four middle stage Gu Master, she actually directly challenged Lord Wolf King, they must be planning something."

For a moment, everyone's gaze landed on Fang Yuan, waiting for the Wolf King's response.

Chapter 509: A wave of his hand

The two armies were poised for battle. Hei tribe had been about to send Pan Ping to challenge, but Dong Fang Yu Liang was the first to send Tang Miao Ming.

Tang Miao Ming was Tang tribe's specially cultivated enslavement path female Gu Master with rank four middle stage cultivation. She liked foxes and had exquisite control over them, but she did not have any notable achievements in history.

However, Dong Fang Yu Liang specially sent her to directly challenge Wolf King, so it was clear he had a specific plan against Fang Yuan and Tang Miao Ming was one part of it.

Wisdom path Gu Masters were like this with plans within plans. The people fighting against wisdom path Gu Masters would not sense it at the start, but by the time they realised it, they would be deep under already.

Tang Miao Ming's public challenge attracted everyone's gazes towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was at leisure as he drank wine and slowly placed down the wine cup, then looked at Hei Lou Lan: "Alliance leader, then should I take the challenge?"

Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily, pleased at Fang Yuan asking him before the battle: "Let these experts look at brother Shan Yin's might and be awed!"

Fang Yuan slowly stood up and used a Gu worm to transmit his voice outside: "Little girl, your bravery in challenging me deserves praises, but you are not my match. Moreover... it is getting late."

In front of the formation, Tang Miao Ming clenched her hands which were soaked with sweat. Her lovely body shuddered at Fang Yuan's words, and her thoughts began to unfold at a rapid speed: 'Wolf King replied! He is truly arrogant, just like alliance leader Dong Fang expected. Now I should act according to his plan and use words to force him to battle with only a hundred beast group against my similar-sized fox group . But... what is the meaning of his last sentence?'

Dong Fang Yu Liang who was sitting in the main tent had been observing the situation.

Tang Miao Ming was an enslavement path expert he accidentally discovered not long ago. After Dong Fang Yu Liang learned the details, he found that Tang Miao Ming was very good at fighting with small scale fox groups. Her skill at this aspect was quite deep, and adding in her set of supporting Gu worms, she could even match an enslavement path master!

Dong Fang Yu Liang immediately thought of using Tang Miao Ming to openly scheme against Wolf King Chang Shan Yin.

The Wolf King's prestige was deeply set in people's hearts. If he was beaten under everyone's gaze, it would definitely greatly raise their morale.

What was even more matching was that Wolf King Chang Shan Yin was very arrogant; Tang Miao Ming was his junior and a female. As long as she was putting herself in a lower position, even Chang Shan Yin would also find it embarrassing to bully a junior in front of everyone.

'Chang Shan Yin, you are really as arrogant as the rumors say. Hehehe, as long as you come out to fight, Tang Miao Ming will definitely give you a great surprise.'

Dong Fang Yu Liang was inwardly excited but also had a doubt: "It is getting late? What is he talking about?"

Not only Dong Fang Yu Liang, but others also had doubts.

But Fang Yuan's next sentence immediately answered their doubts: "It is getting late, quickly start the battle. I still need to eat my lunch after it. Come, those who want to challenge me, all of you come out!"

After he finished speaking, he stood and then waved his hand from the main tent.

Howl—!

Five hundred thousand wolves howled together.

The explosive wolf howls resounded through the skies. Their vigor was so majestic that even the wind stopped for a moment and all the experts shocked.

"Brother Shan Yin, what are you..." Hei Lou Lan's hand slipped and the fine wine in his cup spilled down on his robe.

"Could it be, the Wolf King is thinking...?!" Dong Fang Yu Liang's pupils shrunk, his expression paling.

Following, five hundred thousand wolf group rushed forward like a majestic tide towards the opposite army.

"My... my god!"

"Wolf tide, this is a wolf tide..."

"Chang Shan Yin, he is making a direct attack, he has sent all his wolves!"

Dong Fang alliance army was in a chaos, the enormous momentum from the wolf group shook them. Many people screamed in fear, and countless defensive Gu worms were activated.

For a moment, countless light barriers with all kinds of color shone among Dong Fang alliance army. Some just shielded one person while some shielded a large patch of land. Some formed into armors while some caused the earth to bulge and form into earth walls.

Tang Miao Ming's face was as pale as paper!

She was standing between the two armies, and with the wolf group rushing forward, she would be the first they would charge into.

Facing the endless wolf tide, she felt like she was a small wooden boat in a vast sea about to be swallowed by a shocking tide.

"Damn it, the Wolf King is not abiding by the rules! I came forward to challenge him and only brought a thousand beast group!!" Tang Miao Ming was shocked and also furious.

Normally speaking, before a battle began, there would be a battle between experts in between the armies.

This was an old practice in northern plains.

In the battle between Gu Master experts, not only would the winner's side's morale greatly increase, they could also understand the strength of the other side and be more prepared later. At the same time, this expert challenge could also build friendship. Once the battle ended, the losing side's Gu Masters would have a way out when they surrendered.

The challenge between experts?!

The moment Fang Yuan raised his hand, he used all his wolf groups and directly cut apart the round of expert challenging.

Wolf King, do you know the rules!?

For a moment, countless people from both sides roared and questioned in their mind.

The two armies were not too far apart; the wolf group's rush was quick and soon crossed this distance and unfolded an intense battle against Dong Fang army.

"Attack, don't be in a daze, the wolf group has attacked!"

"Kill, slaughter these damned wolves!!"

"Brothers, move together, fight alongside each other!"

A clamor erupted within Dong Fang army. All kinds of colorful lights, rolling stones, golden lights, wooden spikes, water steam, wind blades and so on landed among the wolf group, causing enormous casualties in Fang Yuan's wolf group instantly.

Hei tribe army was still standing on their spot, looking dumbfoundedly at the frenzied battle situation in the other side.

"Brother Shan Yin!" Hei Lou Lan stared with wide eyes at Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan smiled at fatty Hei: "Dong Fang Yu Liang is a rank five wisdom path Gu Master. Since he initiated the expert challenge, he must definitely have had gathered a lot of intel to help him in making deductions. And it was the talented alliance leader who directly told me to make my move."

Hei Lou Lan's eyes widened even more.

He had commanded Fang Yuan to make a move, but it was not to make such a big move! Clearly, Fang Yuan had intentionally distorted his intention, but he could not bicker with Fang Yuan at this critical juncture.

"Move! All army charge, attack, attack!!" Hei Lou Lan swallowed his resentment and turned around towards the front, fiercely waving his hand and giving his command.

"Orders from alliance leader, all army charge!"

"Orders from alliance leader, all army charge!"

The command was conveyed from top to bottom. The great army began to move slowly; hundreds of thousands of soldiers followed the wolf group in charging towards the other side.

Tang Miao Ming manipulated her fox group, changing the formation again and again to firmly protect herself.

She was worthy of being the person Dong Fang Yu Liang had chosen. Under the charge of the wolf tide, with just a thousand beast group, she continuously changed the formation to keep on resisting the charge.

Her fox group surrounded her, forming a round formation. The formation kept on rotating with a natural flow to it, like a millstone or a reef. The incoming wolf group was like a tide, attacking wave after wave, but it could not break through the round formation of the fox group.

However, Tang Miao Ming did not have the least bit of joy on her face; she was even shouting madly in her mind —

'This damned Wolf King is simply a lunatic!'

'Damn it, I might be able to hold on for now, but with this, I cannot move a single step.'

'Someone save me, save me... eh!'

Suddenly, Tang Miao Ming's body stiffened; her complexion went completely white, her eyes showing fear and despair.

In front of her, the Hei tribe army was gradually starting to move before her, quickly increasing their speed. Under the cover of the wolf group, they showed an earth-shattering influence and power of violence!

Tang Miao Ming momentarily lost her senses and the round formation of the fox group immediately collapsed.

The two-headed rhinoceros came rushing over with explosive sounds; as Hei Lou Lan looked on from above, his heart received a slight jolt at Tang Miao Ming's beauty.

"Who will capture this woman for me?" He had just spoken when Pan Ping shot out.

Pan Ping made a few jumps and fiercely charged to Tang Miao Ming's side, moving rapidly; in a short few moments, he smoothly captured Tang Miao Ming.

Hei Lou Lan nodded with satisfaction at this scene, then turned his gaze towards the front.

"Dong Fang lad..." He gave a malevolent smile, his eyes burning with the flame of revenge.

After a short time, the two armies officially started the battle. A large chaotic battle had begun.

With Fang Yuan's one move, this great battle that had just started had entered its climax.

"Beast!"

Facing the incoming night wolves, Tang Fang furiously shouted and poured his primeval essence into fire pellet Gu.

Whoosh!

A fist-sized fireball shot forward, bringing a gale with it.

This orange pellet fire struck the night wolf.

The night wolf whimpered and rolled around the ground, but its whole body burned with the fire before shortly dying.

"Kill!" Tang Fang breathed roughly and was about to charge forward when he was blocked by a Tang tribe elder.

"Third young master, don't rush ahead, the tribe leader has commanded you to return back quickly!"

"But big sister has been captured!" Tang Fang stared wide, he did not want to turn back. His big sister was Tang Miao Ming.

"Third young master, rushing forward like this will only lead to your death!" The elder hastily persuaded.

"Damn it!" Tang Fang gnashed his teeth and clenched his fists, feeling his powerlessness.

He was Tang tribe's genius, and he was only twenty two but had already reached rank three. Yet this rank three battle strength that could have controlled the situation in the past was now so minute in this great battle.

The rank three battle strength that was normally hard to be seen were all present in this battlefield.

Rank three Gu Masters were reduced to mid level strength; above them were those rank four Gu Master experts and even more higher were the rank five experts.

"Big sister, wait for me, I will definitely rescue you." Tang Fang calmed down and swore in his mind as he retreated.

"Hmph, leaving whenever you want? Leave behind your life!" Right at this time, a rank three Gu Master of Wang tribe rushed over.

"It is Wang Jiang! Third young master, leave quickly, I will hold him back." The Tang tribe elder instantly recognized the enemy.

Wang Jiang's fiance Luo Yu Feng had been snatched by Tang tribe, so he had deep hatred towards them. And now in this large battle, he naturally would not let this chance for revenge go.

Such situations were not few.

In this world, people would have gratitude, grudges and hatred.

Now, those with grudges could let out their grudges and those with hatred could repay their hatred!

Chapter 510: Great Battle

"Tang tribe! The humiliation back then, I will repay it double today!!" Wang Jiang had a malevolent expression on his face as he gave a deep shout, his whole body inflated like a black bear as he violently smashed towards Tang Fang.

Tang Fang was startled and furious at Wang Jiang's fierce momentum, and had the intention to battle with his life.

Pellet fire Gu!

He pushed his right palm and an orange fire shot towards Wang Jiang.

The fire made an arc in the air, quickly approaching Wang Jiang's face. Wang Jiang felt the burning heat before the fire even struck him.

But he just laughed nastily and actually opened his mouth, without any intent to dodge.

Gulp!

He swallowed the pellet fire!

"This is rank four swallow fire Gu!" Tang Fang was shocked.

Swallow fire Gu was not an offensive Gu but a storage Gu. But using Gu always relied on a Gu Master's wits. Who was to say storage Gu could not be used for battle?

Tang tribe always prioritized fire path Gu worms. Wang Jiang spent a huge price to purchase a rank four swallow fire Gu, so he could use it against Tang tribe sometime in the future.

"Wang Jiang, we will help you." At this time, two Gu Masters rushed over, both with rank three cultivation.

Tang Fang and the Tang tribe elder's expression turned pale. The swallow fire Gu could already restrict them, now the other side had three people, occupying a huge advantage.

"Third young master, leave quickly, I will hold them back!" The Tang tribe elder saw the critical situation and stood up to fight to give Tang Fang an opportunity to escape.

Tang Fang was not a conceited man, he gnashed his teeth and turned around to leave: "Elder hold on, I will quickly come back with reinforcements!"

"Chase!" Wang Jiang and the two others naturally were not willing to let Tang Fang escape safely, but who could have thought the Tang tribe elder that remained was a defensive Gu Master and moreover had a rank three rare Gu 'slow steps'.

As this Gu's name implied, it could slow down Gu Masters' speed for a period of time.

Wang Jiang and the two others were slowed down and could only give up on Tang Fang, then with a belly filled with anger, attacked the Tang tribe elder.

The Tang tribe elder could not fend off against the numbers although he had slow steps Gu. First, he was struck by Wang Jiang's punch, then his arm was severed by wind blade. Finally, a snowball turned him into an ice sculpture, killing him.

"Elder!!" Tang Fang watched with tearful red eyes; when he came back with reinforcements, he could only collect the corpse of this elder.

The flames of hatred raged in his heart, but he could not find his enemies.

The battlefield was in chaos. Large numbers of wolves rushed forward and created a havor. Besides them, there were fox groups, war crabs, bats and other beasts. Metal, wood, water, fire, earth, wind, lightning, light, darkness... All kinds of attacks streaked through the sky and landed on the ground; rocks were smashed, flames ablazed, ice spread, lightning dazzled the eyes...

Gu Masters shouted and screamed; some attacked while some retreated; some were rushing to reinforce while some were defending.

A great chaotic battle between hundreds of thousands of people was enough to fill a range of thousands of miles.

Rumble...

Suddenly, an enormous blue wave with the momentum of covering the sky, descended like an evil flood dragon.

Large numbers of wolves and Gu Masters were swept by the enormous wave.

This part of the battlefield was instantly cleared up, several large puddles forming in this cleared grassland. A Gu Master arrogantly stood in this center of the battlefield while laughing wildly.

"It is Water Demon Hao Ji Liu!" Tang Fang's pupils shrunk as he recognized this man.

"Retreat, this person is a rank four upper stage expert, he is a demon." Many surviving rank three Gu Masters wisely chose to retreat.

Water Demon's fierce gaze swept through the battlefield and landed on Tang Fang's side who had the highest numbers.

These rank three Gu Masters were moving battle merits to Water Demon, representing a bountiful reward after the war.

Water Demon licked his dried lips with his scarlet tongue, a bloodthirsty killing intent filling his face.

"Consider it your bad luck to have ran into me!" Water Demon laughed loudly as he fiercely pushed forward his two palms.

Rank four waterfall Gu!

BOOM!

In an instant, an enormous torrent bubbled and charged towards Tang Fang and his group with an immense momentum.

Facing such a majestic attack, Tang Fang felt he was like a single person facing a tsunami, feeling he was facing a great catastrophe alone.

"Third young master, we will hold it back, retreat quickly!" Several elders who had been accompanying Tang Fang, gnashed their teeth and stood in front of Tang Fang.

They combined their strength and were finally able to hold back this waterfall.

"Leave!!!" The elders' urging caused Tang Fang to feel stifled.

"Hold on, I will get father to come rescue you!" He gnashed his teeth and finally chose to leave.

Gagaga...

Water Demon laughed wildly and engaged in the battle with the several Tang tribe elders. His offense surged forward, his water abilities charged forward with huge momentum as he used his power to overwhelm the elders, and although the Tang tribe elders had many people, they were falling into a disadvantage and it was becoming difficult for them to hold back Water Demon.

After several moves, an elder lost his life at Water Demon's hands.

After dozen or so moves, only one elder remained, with the rest dead.

Water Demon laughed sinisterly and was just about to make the final move when suddenly a cold killing intent pounced on him.

His plentiful battle experience had given Hao Ji Liu an intuitive feeling towards danger. He did not even look and immediately retreated backwards, giving up the battle contribution that was within his reach without any hesitation.

Whoosh!

A soft ripping sound echoed and right at the instant of his retreat, a four-leaf wind blade crossed through the air and brushed past him.

The wind blade kept on rotating, making a long arc through the battlefield, everything that it passed through, whether it were humans or beasts, were cut through; blood flew and limbs scattered.

The light green wind blade spiralled a long arc in the air before flying back to its master.

"It is you? Wind Demon Tan Wu Feng!" The sinister smile on Water Demon gradually disappeared and a solemn look appeared in his eyes.

Tan Wu Feng and him were called wind and water demons, both having rank four upper stage cultivation.

Previously, Water Demon rampaged in the eastern areas of Northern Plains while Wind Demon wreaked havoc in the western areas, their fame echoing with each other. But later, Dong Fang Yu Liang devised three escapements scheme to subdue Wind Demon. Tan Wu Feng became Dong Fang Yu Liang's subordinate and sided with Dong Fang tribe.

"Water Demon, your laughter is too ear-piercing. Lord has ordered me to bring an end to your life." Wind Demon Tan Wu Feng was clothed in green clothes, hovering in midair, grasping the wind blade that had returned.

The wind blade only had three sides remaining from the consumption in the way, but with Wind Demon pouring in primeval essence again, it gradually began to recover back to the previous four-leaf wind blade.

Normally speaking, wind blades could not be retrieved once they were sent. Wind Demon played with the wind blade like some toy, he clearly had extraordinary wind manipulation skill.

"Hmph, it seems you have been taught pretty well by your master over these years, seeing nothing worthwhile around you." Water Demon laughed sinisterly, gazing at Wind Demon like a falcon.

Wind Demon's expression suddenly turned gloomy. He swung his palm and shot out the four-leaf wind blade, and at the same time, he also charged towards Water Demon.

"Come!" Water Demon was at ease, a huge wave rising from below his feet. He stepped on the wave and charged towards Wind Demon.

BOOM!

A huge explosion echoed, wind screamed madly and water wave surged high, unfolding an intense battle of rank four level experts.

Surrounding Gu Masters hurriedly retreated and soon a special battlefield was formed for the battle of wind and water demons.

As time passed by, not only these two, other rank four Gu Master experts also found their opponents.

Dozen or so battle rings emerged one after another in the chaotic battlefield. These battle rings were not set in place, but instead moved with the battle between the experts.

With the battle of higher level forces, the whole battlefield began to become clear.

First of all was the large battle rings for the fight of the rank four experts. Surrounding these large battle rings were small scale battle rings where rank three Gu Masters fought. And beyond that were the fights between groups of rank two and rank one Gu Masters.

Fang Yuan took this chance to assemble his wolf group.

The two armies faced off against each other, creating a deadlock.

Usually, the side which broke through this balance would obtain the initiative which would accumulate into advantage. After their dominance was accumulated enough, it would change into victory momentum.

Both Hei Lou Lan and Dong Fang Yu Liang knew this.

Thus, their gaze landed on their elite troop.

These elite troops that were either made of three-four hundred soldiers, or five-six hundred, had received strict training to deploy their Gu worm together and create a formidable attack in an instant. They were the weapons to rampage the battlefield, the trump cards of their commander.

Not every tribe had the ability to form elite troops.

Hei Lou Lan's side had five divisions of elite troops while Dong Fang Yu Liang had six.

Dong Fang Yu Liang first deployed hundred blossoms elite troop.

This was Hua tribe's elite troop who were quite weak at attacking and defending, but were specialized at healing.

With this division of elite troop moving out, they immediately healed large groups of wounded and stabilized the situation, providing a great assistance to Dong Fang side's base level Gu Masters.

Hei Lou Lan looked at this scene from the main tent and snorted, commanding blue butterfly elite troop to attack hundred blossoms elite troop.

The blue butterfly elite troop that contained five hundred soldiers who detoured the rank four Gu Masters battle rings and easily pierced through the battlefield, charging towards hundred blossoms elite troop.

Just when it looked like they were about to succeed, three elite troops charged in separately from east, south and west, surrounding the blue butterfly elite troop.

Dong Fang Yu Liang had already planned for this and sent hundred blossoms elite troop as the bait while making these three elite troops lie in ambush.

Hei Lou Lan naturally was not willing to see the annihilation of blue butterfly elite troop, immediately sending other elite troop divisions as reinforcements.

Each elite troops of the two sides quickly converged and formed into several lines of encirclement; the situation once again entered a deadlock.

"Lord tribe leader, let me go forward and crush them!" Dong Fang She could not restrain anymore as he requested to be sent to battle.

Dong Fang Yu Liang slowly shook his head and did not permit him.

Dong Fang She was Dong Fang tribe's feather arrow elite troop's commander with rank four upper stage cultivation.

But as long as Hei tribe's black banner elite troop did not move, this flower feather elite troop could not be sent out.

Dong Fang Yu Liang slowly swept his gaze through the battlefield and placated Dong Fang She: "Elder She does not need to be impatient, this is not the time for you to take the stage. The current situation is already within my expectations."

Saying so, he calmly smiled and turned towards the three enslavement path Gu Masters: "It is time for you to show your strength."

These three were precisely E Xuan Ming, Wei Xin, and Jiang Wan Shan.

Chapter 511: Dark Vortex and Cloud Whirlpool

At Dong Fang Yu Liang's words, E Xuan Ming, Jiang Wan Shan and Wan Xin glanced at each other before nodding and activating their Gu.

Rank three, djinn heart Gu, to enhance the spirit.

Rank two, heart sound Gu, to strengthen the voice of one's heart.

Rank two, harmony Gu, the harmonization of one's heart and voice.

Rank three, flying soul Gu, the soul can leave the body.

Rank three, soul chain Gu, souls can be interlinked.

Rank four, soul combination Gu, three souls can be linked and fused as one.

Killer move — Three Hearts Combination Soul!

BOOM...

A soundless explosion burst out, as the three Gu Masters' souls flew out of their bodies and merged together into a complete entity in the air.

For a moment, in the radius of two hundred li, all Gu Masters with at least five hundred man soul could feel a strong pressure spreading and weighing down on their souls.

The Gu Masters with less than five hundred man soul, however, could not sense anything.

"This pressure... it is already at the level of one thousand four hundred man soul, as expected of three hearts combination soul!" Fang Yuan immediately reacted and gazed towards Dong Fang tribe's main tent.

He had a thousand man soul originally, but there was injuries from the soul explosion though he was able to escape from most of its force. His soul strength had fell to eight hundred man soul and after these days of recuperation, it had recovered to nine hundred man soul level.

Nine hundred man soul naturally was not able to match against the other side's one thousand four hundred man soul.

"Unfortunately, there are many eyes within the alliance army, I cannot get rid of them, otherwise I would have gone to Dang Hun mountain and used guts Gu to easily heal all the injuries on my soul."

Fang Yuan inwardly sighed while mobilizing the wolf group.

Large numbers of night wolves, water wolves, wind wolves and turtleback wolves formed into a enormous force that charged towards the enemy army like a raging river.

"Wolf King, let us experience your brilliance today!" Wan Xin, E Xuan Ming and Jiang Wan Shan simultaneous spoke. Because their souls were temporarily merged together, their every movement was done simultaneously and was completely in sync.

Under their command, large numbers steel pincers crabs, crystal drilling crabs and big qi crabs flocked together, forming into a firm defensive line within several breaths of time.

The wolf group fiercely smashed into this defensive line, like a flood striking the dam.

Sharp wolf fangs and claws collided intensely against the firm crab shells.

Fang Yuan snorted and gazed afar while standing on the twin-headed rhino. Under his exquisite control, the whole wolf group formed into waves after waves of offense; the defensive formation formed by the crabs soon was on the verge of collapsing.

"This is... the nine layered wave charge! Quick, reinforce me, my crab group won't be able to persist longer." Wan Xin had just thought of this when the other two felt it.

Under the effect of three hearts combination soul, they were just like one person, any thought would be immediately known by the others.

"No need to worry, my crocodile group is coming." E Xuan Ming's expression was unshaken as an excited battle intent emerged in his concentrated gaze.

'The enemy is the famous Wolf King, being able to fight with such an existence, this life was really not in vain!'

Under his control, large numbers of six legs crocodile, lava crocodiles, rock crocodiles and shadow plunder crocodiles soon rushed to the frontline.

After the addition of these new forces, the defensive line that was on the brink of collapsing showed a sign of being indestructible.

"Whether it be crabs or crocodiles, they are both beasts excelling in defense. At the same time, under the three hearts combination soul, they are like three people merged together, increasing their beast commanding skills greatly, directly reaching master level."

Fang Yuan squinted his eyes, there was no signs of irritation due to not getting any results.

Suddenly, he stopped the fierce attacks and wisely chose to slow down the offense.

He was not wholeheartedly controlling the beast group, instead he divided half of his concentration to observe the battlefield.

His enemies were not these three people, neither Jiang, Wei nor E. As a person of importance who could influence the whole battlefield, he was extremely likely to encounter another assassination attempt from shadow sword expert Bian Si Xuan.

Since the battle started, shadow sword expert was nowhere to be seen and was likely observing Fang Yuan from the darkness, looking for a good opportunity to kill him.

It was only that beside Fang Yuan was the rank five Gu Master Hei Lou Lan. Maybe because of this, shadow sword expert had not revealed herself.

Right at this time, a large group of blood colored bats emerged above the wolf group.

These bats possessed four wings; the wings were sharp and firm like knives. Under the attack of the bat group, large numbers of casualties started appearing among the wolf group.

The crocodile and crab groups took this chance to attack pushing forward their battleline by a hundred steps.

"Sure enough, it is Jiang Wan Shan's bladewing blood bats group." Fang Yuan's gaze flashed, he was not a bit surprised.

With the intel from Hei tribe, he had a rather good understanding of the enemy Gu Master experts. Dong Fang Yu Liang did not have any enslavement path masters under him, so Fang Yuan had guessed Dong Fang Yu Liang would use three hearts combination soul to deal with him.

And the candidates to use this killer move were extremely likely to be the strongest three enslavement path Gu Masters.

Now, under Fang Yuan's probe, these three were sure enough Jiang Wan Shan, Wan Xin and E Xuan Ming.

Bladewing blood bats' offense were extremely violent, changing the direction of this part of the battlefield the moment they joined the fray.

The wolf group that had been occupying the upper hand was being defeated bit by bit, while crocodile group and crab group seized the chance to attack. Mud crabs, small qi crabs, big qi crabs, steel pincers crabs, crystal drilling crabs, six legs crocodiles, lava crocodiles, rock crocodiles and shadow plunder crocodiles formed into a large mixed army that stretched out like an opened steel fist, defeating the wolves in its way and charging straight towards Hei tribe's main tent.

According to logic, enslavement path Gu Masters would find it hard-pressed to cooperate with each other. A mixed beast group would usually impede each other, making one plus one less than two.

But Wei, Jiang and E, these three merged their souls with three hearts combination soul and were like one person, forming a qualitative effect of having one plus one greater than two.

"Brother Shan Yin." Facing the mixed beast group's strong charge, Hei Lou Lan could not help feeling some pressure and his expression turned dark.

If they let this group of beasts charge over, he would have to use black banner elite troop earlier than scheduled. But if he did so, they would not be able to contain Dong Fang Yu Liang's feather arrow elite troop.

The scales of victory was slowly inclining towards the other side.

Fang Yuan said to Hei Lou Lan in a low voice: "The other has bladewing blood bats group which has very sharp offensive power, and my wolf group is unable to do aerial attacks. More importantly, the other side has used three hearts combination soul to achieve thousand man soul and are able to lead this mixed beast group as if they were one person. If we can break through this killer move, the mixed group will disperse without even putting up any fight."

Hei Lou Lan frowned deeply, an ominous glint flashing rapidly in his eyes as he made a decision.

"Brother Shan Yin, concentrate on the battle, I will resolve this quickly!"

He suddenly extended his arm that was the size of an ordinary person's thigh, his right palm formed a claw while his palm faced upward. Rank five aura rose fiercely while the primeval essence in his aperture fell rapidly, pouring into four different Gu.

"Dong Fang tribe has three hearts combination soul, while my Hei tribe has dark vortex!" Hei Lou Lan smiled sinisterly, an intense killing intent raging in his heart.

Whoosh...

A pitch black stream rose in the air and rotated once before flowing towards Hei Lou Lan's palm.

Following, the second stream, third stream, fourth stream...

In a blink of an eye, large numbers of dark streams were created one after another and converged in Hei Lou Lan's right claw.

Whoosh Whoosh Whoosh....

Countless dark streams rose and merged with each other, creating a wild gale.

These finger sized dark streams pressed at each other and formed a dark speck of light.

As large numbers of dark streams continued to pour into it, the dark speck of light gradually inflated, forming a fist sized dark sphere.

The dark sphere seemed to have immeasurable depth in it as if the night was condensed into it, even absorbing the light around it, causing a terrified feeling to grow in people.

Hei Lou Lan, however, revealed an extremely excitement and a mad killing intent when he looked at this dark sphere.

"Dong Fang lad! Take this!!" Hei Lou Lan suddenly shouted and disappeared from his place.

The next moment, he appeared above the enemy main tent.

"Go and die!" Hei Lou Lan let out a crazed laughter and flipped over his wrist; as if he was holding a thousand jun of weight, he exerted all his strength to slowly push the dark sphere towards Dong Fang Yu Liang.

Following his movement, that small dark sphere madly expanded and in several breaths of time, had expanded to size of a small hill.

The pitch black giant sphere pressed down with a seemingly slow speed but was actually very fast. It covered the light of the sun and casted a giant darkness on the ground.

Before the giant sphere even struck, all the Gu Master experts in the main tent felt terror like they were facing a calamity.

They looked at the pressing giant sphere, and felt heaviness as if lead was poured into their body. They wanted to retreat but were barely able to move!

"Damn it, it is Hei tribe's killer move dark vortex!"

"Retreat, retreat!!"

Gu Masters exclaimed in shock, not having even a trace of intent to resist. Wei Xin and the other two had a despairing look on their face. They were under three hearts combination soul state, and would require at least two-three minutes to get rid of this killer move.

The corners of Dong Fang Yu Liang's lips, however, curled up.

He looked towards the sky, the dark sphere growing bigger and bigger in his sight, but his expression was a scene of calmness: "Sure enough like I expected, Hei Lou Lan, I have been waiting so long for your move."

He slightly raised his right foot and lightly pressed on the white cloud below his feet.

The originally tranquil white cloud crazily surged as clouds and mists burst out in blink of an eye like boiling water, and formed into an enormous whirlpool.

The whirlpool slowly rose up like a giant opened mouth and swallowed the dark sphere.

"This is?!" Hei Lou Lan was shocked and furious. At this moment, he realized he had fallen for Dong Fang Yu Liang's scheme.

Dong Fang Yu Liang had meticulously arranged this trap, waiting for Hei Lou Lan to come crashing in.

"Let me teach you, this is the killer move I spent three years of my life to plan meticulously, cloud whirlpool, it was specially created to deal with your dark vortex. Hei Lou Lan, you have lost just like many years back." Dong Fang Yu Liang proclaimed his victory.

"Damn it..." Hei Lou Lan gnashed his teeth, his forehead filled with sweat. He wanted to pull back but the cloud whirlpool was firmly sucking in his dark vortex.

The smile on Dong Fang Yu Liang's lips became even bigger as he summoned: "Dong Po Kong, Bian Si Xuan."

His voice was not loud, but under the effect of Gu worm, it could be clearly heard by everyone.

Hearing his command, the shadow sword expert who had been concealing herself for a long time, turned into a dark shadow, and moved while wriggling in the shadows on the ground; in a blink of an eye, she was in front of the twin-headed rhino.

And at the same time, a flash of lightning broke through the air and crossed the battlefield, instantly arriving in front of the twin-headed rhino.

The lightning dispersed and turned into a valiant man, who then pounced towards Fang Yuan.

Flying Lightning Dong Po Kong, Shadow Sword Expert Bian Si Xuan!

In an instant, both Hei Lou Lan and Fang Yuan had fallen into danger!

Chapter 512: Reliable Alliance Mate

Dong Fang Yu Liang lived up to his name as the wisdom path Gu Master, accurately calculating Hei Lou Lan's reaction.

Three hearts combination soul killer move was only bait to lure Hei Lou Lan into attacking. Then, Dong Fang Yu Liang was able to leisurely unfold his trump card - a killer move that was specially designed to restrict dark vortex and trap Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan had been at the main tent but now he was trapped; the defense around Fang Yuan had suddenly decreased by a very large amount.

Taking this chance, Shadow Sword Expert Bian Si Xuan appeared and charged into the main tent to once again assassinate Fang Yuan.

As long as Fang Yuan died, the wolf group would immediately disperse and the scales of victory would greatly incline towards Dong Fang alliance army.

To make sure this beheading the leader tactic succeeded, Dong Fang Yu Liang had not only arranged Shadow Sword Expert, but also an even stronger Gu Master.

He was Dong Po Kuang known as 'Flying Lightning'! One of the few flying masters of northern plains, a lightning path Gu Master with rank four upper stage cultivation. He had not made a move even in the chaotic battle earlier, patiently waiting till now to shock the world with one move!

"Protect Wolf King!"

"Sneaky bastards, don't think you can have your way!!"

"Wolf King, leave quickly!"

Six rank three Gu Masters around the main tent jumped up one after another, trying to hold off Dong Po Kuang and Bian Si Xuan.

"Scram!!" Dong Po Kuang coldly shouted, lightning suddenly crackling around him.

The three Gu Masters who were blocking him were struck by the lightning; their defensive Gu worms were instantly destroyed, two instantly died while one was heavily injured.

"Hehehe." Bian Si Xuan chuckled softly, her body turned into a shadow and quickly moved like a poisonous snake through the Gu Masters blocking her, and moved past them.

"What?"

"Such speed..."

"Is this Shadow Sword Expert's true strength?"

The three Gu Masters were shocked, they gazed back only to see Bian Si Xuan's seductive back figure.

They wanted to chase, but found they could not move at all. Their hands and feet were tied up by a dark shadow, firmly binding them to the spot.

Facing the above and under pincer attack from Dong Po Kuang and Shadow Sword Expert, Fang Yuan paled, his gaze revealing a frantic look as he retreated in panic and shouted: "Quick, someone come protect me!"

"Wolf King, no need to worry, Hei Xiu Yi will guard you." One person stood behind Fang Yuan, clothed in black and had unshaken expression. He walked forward few steps and stood in front of Fang Yuan.

"Courting death!" Dong Po Kuang shouted, the lightning over his body crackled violently and turned into a battle spear which he then stabbed towards Hei Xiu Yi.

Bian Si Xuan snorted and flicked her wrist lightly, immediately throwing out a torrent of shadow swords.

Hei Xiu Yi's expression did not change at this combined attack from two experts. He put together his palms in front of his chest and transferred his primeval essence.

BOOM!

Next instant, his defense was fully activated.

Fifty-six flying bone shields flew together and blocked in front of him.

A green halo flew above his head and illuminated a range of a hundred steps.

Black iron-like metallic light formed a set of thick armor which then covered him from top to bottom.

Nine ghost faces whimpered and wept as they revolved around him.

At the same time, a dark brown oil wind breezed in between the flying bone shields.

Dong Po Kuang's lightning spear pierced through seven flying shields and made a hole through the dark-brown oil wind, but was blocked by the black armor.

Bian Si Xuan's shadow swords bombarded upon the shields, shattering eighteen shields but were thwarted by the oil wind; the shadow swords seemed to have fallen into a swamp as their momentum dispersed and were no longer a threat.

Hei Xiu Yi was Hei Lou Lan's expert and also one of the three commanders of black banner elite troop, an expert in defense.

Facing the defense specialized Hei Xiu Yi, Dong Po Kuang and Bian Si Xuan were actually delayed for a while, unable to break through.

Hei Xiu Yi had suffered a terrible defeat during the battle with Mo Shi Kuang; it did not mean he was weak but the enemy was too strong, a top expert in the whole of northern plains in this struggle for Imperial Court.

Now, facing the combined strength of Flying Lightning and Shadow Sword Expert, Hei Xiu Yi shielded here and there, firmly protecting Fang Yuan who was behind him for dozen moves.

His Gu set had complementing Gu worms focused on defense and had been carefully chosen.

Dong Po Kuang and Bian Si Xuan tried to break through multiple times, but it was all a failure.

The aftermath of this battle caused severe pain to the twin-headed rhino. The giant rhinoceros screamed in pain and stamped its feet, recklessly charging in the battlefield without considering allies or enemies.

Hei Xiu Yi's expression turned heavier.

His primeval essence was quickly depleting because of this intense battle, already reaching the bottom. While the other side had two people and their primeval essence consumption was half that of Hei Xiu Yi.

Hei Xiu Yi was now confronted with a difficult choice.

The first choice was to continue to defend to death without caring about his primeval essence expenditure and hoping Hei Lou Lan or others would come in time to support him. But now the twin-headed rhino was crazily rampaging and had already travelled far away; how high was the possibility for the reinforcements to cross the battlefield and arrive in time?

Second option was to conserve his primeval essence. But with this, his defense would fall and the chance for the enemies to breakthrough would increase dramatically. In case, they were able to move past him, Fang Yuan who was behind him would be in grave danger.

'What should I choose?'

A hesitating look flashed in Hei Xiu Yi's eyes, but was soon replaced by resolve.

He began to slowly cut down on defense and was no longer very active in facing the enemies' attacks. Dong Po Kuang and Bian Si Xuan immediately sensed the change in Hei Xiu Yi; they attacked several times and took some risks, and were about to succeed.

Even if Wolf King had an important identity that concerned the whole situation, even if Hei Xiu Yi was appointed by Hei Lou Lan to defend Chang Shan Yin, but at this critical juncture when he was at risk, Hei Xiu Yi was not able to give up his own life.

"If it was Lord Hei Lou Lan behind me, I would definitely risk my life to protect him. But Chang Shan Yin is just an outsider, always acting so arrogant and looking down on me, why should I sacrifice my life for such a person? Even if Wolf King dies, we still have the black banner army and are still a match for the enemy. Yes, I need to save myself and continue to render my service to the tribe."

Hei Xiu Yi's thoughts surged rapidly to justify himself and gradually began to have a clear conscience.

He was originally guarding Fang Yuan, but now was only looking after himself, thus his primeval essence consumption immediately slowed.

"Now is the time, overlapping shadow Gu!" Suddenly, Bian Si Xuan noticed a gap in the defense, her eyes flashed with a sharp light as she grabbed this chance and activated the Gu worm Dong Fang Yu Liang had lent her.

This overlapping shadow Gu was a rank four rare Gu which was very difficult to find in the market and its price was comparable to many rank five Gu.

Initially, Bian Si Xuan had agreed with Dong Fang Yu Liang for this Gu to be her reward once she assassinated Fang Yuan.

But Bian Si Xuan's assassination failed and the brain explosion Gu she had struck with was also dealt with by Fang Yuan; with her proud nature, she would naturally not accept this overlapping shadow Gu. But before this battle, Dong Fang Yu Liang had lent her this Gu of his own initiative, just to be on the safe side.

Overlapping shadow Gu might only be a rank four Gu to others, but to Bian Si Xuan, it could raise her battle strength explosively and was even more precious than rank five Gu to her.

Under the use of overlapping shadow Gu, Bian Si Xuan's multiple shadow swords overlaid upon each other and in just a second, only one sword remained of the overflowing shadow swords.

This shadow sword was as dark as the abyss and was like a solid object; all the offensive power of the shadow swords had been overlaid together in it.

Bian Si Xuan pierced the sword forward; the sword easily broke through Hei Xiu Yi's defense like a knife cutting through tofu, and pierced towards Wolf King.

The defense that had lasted for a long time was finally broken!

Dong Po Kuang let out a breath of relief at this scene; he continued to hold back Hei Xiu Yi to provide a chance to Bian Si Xuan.

But Hei Xiu Yi could not care about this as he already had an intent to retreat. Now that Shadow Sword Expert was charging towards Chang Shan Yin, this was the chance for him to retreat, why would he not take this chance? Thus, he quickly retreated and directly jumped off from twin-headed rhino's back.

Dong Po Kuang looked at Hei Xiu Yi's fleeing figure in shock, he hesitated for a moment before thinking that it was better to quickly kill Wolf King, so he did not chase Hei Xiu Yi.

But when he gazed back, he saw Bian Si Xuan's shadow sword had already pierced into Chang Shan Yin's chest.

Bian Si Xuan pierced it so deep that only the hilt of the shadow sword remained on the outside; the sword had pierced through Fang Yuan's chest and large part of it stuck out through his back.

"Wolf King, remember, the one who killed you is Shadow Sword Expert Bian Si Xuan!" Bian Si Xuan's eyes turned red, excitement filling her face.

The famous Wolf King whose name had spread throughout the northern plains died by her hands. This glory, this brilliant battle achievement, caused her whole body to shudder in happiness.

"It's over!" Dong Po Kuang also raised his brows in joy.

"Wolf King has died, my army has now the upper hand and victory is within grasp." Far away, Dong Fang Yu Liang who was observing the battle with a detective Gu, clenched his fists in excitement.

He raised his head and smiled calmly at Hei Lou Lan who was competing with the cloud whirlpool: "Hei Lou Lan, Chang Shan Yin has been beheaded. Now stop and admit your defeat, I will give you the position of a general and also an opportunity to enter the Imperial Court."

But what made him surprised was Hei Lou Lan not only did not fly into a rage but instead revealed a malevolent smile: "Dong Fang Yu Liang, look carefully with your dog eyes!"

Right at this time, Bian Si Xuan and Dong Po Kuang's shocked exclamations rose from the twin-headed rhino's back.

"What?" Dong Fang Yu Liang had a very bad feeling and immediately used his investigative Gu to gaze ahead.

He saw 'Chang Shan Yin' had already turned into a puddle of water. Several Gu worms flew out with only a water image Gu remaining in the water which was almost pierced into two by the shadow sword with only a thin layer of skin holding its body.

This was the water image Gu of Water Demon Hao Ji Liu.

Previously, he had used water image Gu in the heroes assembly to deceive everyone by passing it off as the genuine body, and was able to kill Fire Prodigal Chai Ming.

Before this great battle, Fang Yuan had taken this method into consideration and made a plan with Hei Lou Lan. To prevent news from leaking out, this arrangement was only known to the three of them.

Fang Yuan's true body had never been in the main tent, but was instead hiding in a corner of the battlefield. With wolf care Gu, he had been observing the battlefield and commanding the wolf group to fight. The dialogues with Hei Lou Lan previously was also a facade prepared by using a series of Gu worms.

"Damn it, this is a fake."

"Where is the real Chang Shan Yin?"

Bian Si Xuan and Dong Po Kuang's expressions turned extremely unsightly; they had fought so hard for such a long time but the result was that they were tricked!

Chapter 513: Seven Star Light

From the back of the twin-headed rhino, Shadow Sword Expert and Flying Lightning looked around everywhere.

In the chaotic battlefield, dozen or so rank four Gu Masters had formed their own battle rings out of which three matches were finished; Hei tribe won two while Dong Fang tribe won one.

Several divisions of elite troops were still fighting against each other, and because of Dong Fang Yu Liang's scheme, Hei tribe was on the losing end in this aspect.

The battle of wolf group with crocodile, crab and bat group was also in a deadlock.

There was no sign of Fang Yuan, no one knew where he was hiding.

Bian Si Xuan and Dong Po Kong searched in vain, their expression turning several shades darker.

Dong Fang Yu Liang soon accepted the fact of this failure, he smiled brightly: "This is somewhat interesting, but still within my expectations. As long as Wolf King continues to command the wolf group, his soul fluctuations will be revealed and sooner or later, we will find his position. Hei Lou Lan, your loss has only been momentarily delayed."

"Hahaha." Hei Lou Lan threw his head back and laughed loudly, his laughter containing a disdainful intent, "Dong Fang child, you really think I was restrained by you?"

Saying so, the skin on his whole body turned pitch dark like the night. At the same time, endless black smoke oozed out of the pores on his body.

The black smoke surged and soon covered his whole body.

In just moments, Hei Lou Lan turned into a human shaped black smoke with smoke rising in spirals. When looked from outside, one would only see a pair of bloodthirsty eyes.

A very ominent feeling welled up in Dong Fang Yu Liang's heart.

A thought to retreat immediately crossed in his mind.

However, although the cloud whirlpool was restricting the dark vortex and restraining Hei Lou Lan, in another aspect, was it not same as the dark vortex restricting cloud whirlpool?

The next instant, Hei Lou Lan turned into black smoke and actually entered into the dark vortex.

"Not good!" Dong Fang Yu Liang immediately felt his blood run cold.

But it was already too late.

The dark giant sphere that was as big as a small hill, was originally being slowly swallowed bit by bit by the cloud whirlpool. But suddenly, the dark vortex rapidly shrunk.

The cloud vortex was unable to react in time and quickly contracted with the flow of the dark vortex.

But next instant, the dark vortex suddenly expanded violently.

"No, instead of saying expansion, it is better to call it — explosion!" Dong Fang Yu Liang was overwhelmed.

There was no sound, it was a soundless explosion.

The cloud whirlpool could only hold for three breaths before it was burst by the dark vortex. The dark giant sphere continually enlarged and swallowed everything, be it humans or beasts like a prehistoric giant monster.

Only when it covered a radius of ten li, did the semi-circular dark sphere disappear.

There was no sound wave like that of a normal explosion and also no windforce was generated. This strange tyrannical explosion had the nature of corrosion with the ability to melt everything.

After the dark vortex disappeared, ten li of battlefield was completely cleared, with only Hei Lou Lan remaining in the air and Dong Fang Yu Liang who was in a deep crater on the ground.

All the remaining humans or beasts within the radius of the explosion of the dark vortex were eroded into nothingness!

Hei Lou Lan looked down at Dong Fang Yu Liang with extreme exhaustion, he was gasping for breath and his whole body was soaked in dark red blood.

But the corners of his lips had curled up into a crazed, sinister smile.

"Hahaha, Dong Fang Yu Liang, since you can think of this cloud whirlpool killer move to restrict dark vortex, I can also improve on my killer move! How is it, how is the taste of the banquet I prepared for you meticulously? This is a trump card which I have been concealing all along, not even letting my kin know."

Hei Lou Lan laughed wildly, his laughter echoing throughout the whole battlefield.

For a moment, his aura pressed down on his surroundings, even the Gu Masters in the battle could not help but gaze towards him.

When they saw Hei Lou Lan occupying the upper hand, Hei tribe's Gu Masters' morale surged high while Dong Fang tribe's Gu Masters felt a heavy pressure on their heart.

The generals were the source of courage of the troops, the fight between Hei Lou Lan and Dong Fang Yu Liang was crucial to the soldiers, it was very important and was not only a matter that concerned an individual life or death, but would influence this great battlefield.

"Cough cough..."

Hei Lou Lan was laughing wildly, when suddenly he spurted out several mouthfuls of dark blood.

Although this move was very powerful, it would also cause self-harm. It was classified as a self-harming move and no matter what the result, once it was activated, most of the Gu worms that formed the dark vortex killer move would die.

Once Gu worms died, the Gu Masters would naturally suffer from backlash.

But this move was already very profitable.

In one move, Hei Lou Lan not only escaped from the trap, he was able to counter-pressure Dong Fang Yu Liang and also kill Wei Xin, Jiang Wan Shan and E Xuan Ming who were in three hearts combination soul state.

With these three people dead, the mixed beast group immediately began to fight against each other with there being no one to guide them. Just like Fang Yuan said before, they crumbled.

With this mixed beast group rushing everywhere and attacking recklessly, the battlefield turned even more chaotic.

Dong Fang Yu Liang rose up slowly with a solemn expression.

Hei Lou Lan had kept this move extremely confidential. Dong Fang Yu Liang did not even have a trace of any relevant clue, so he had not expected for the killer move to be improved with such terrifying destructive power.

As a matter of fact, he had secretly prepared a means of escape for E Xuan Ming, Wei Xin and Jiang Wang Shan, which could directly transfer these three to the rear of the battlefield.

However, when Hei Lou Lan was improving on his killer move, he added a space path Gu as well. Thus, when the dark vortex exploded, the surrounding space was locked and Dong Fang Yu Liang's methods lost their effectiveness.

"Dong Fang Yu Liang, it is still not late for you to accept your defeat. As long as you surrender, I can let bygones be bygones and forget all my past hatred, and appoint you as my first military advisor." Hei Lou Lan tried to make Dong Fang Yu Liang surrender in front of everyone.

Dong Fang Yu Liang coldly smiled.

Hei Lou Lan's lustful nature was widely known and had already been coveting after his sister Dong Fang Qing Yu. Dong Fang Yu Liang might surrender to other forces, but he would never choose to pledge allegiance to Hei Lou Lan.

"Hei Lou Lan, you are really too optimistic. Even if your side is occupying the upper hand, you are still a long way from victory. Come, let us fight. Seven Star Light!"

Dong Fang Yu Liang softly shouted, seven lights swiftly rose up beside him.

These seven lights had different colors, continually rotating around his body, drawing a beautiful light orbit.

This was Dong Fang Yu Liang's signature killer move. These seven lights had different effects and under their empowerment, Dong Fang Yu Liang activated star thought Gu.

Whooshh...

Countless thoughts gushed out as bright as starlight. The radiance of these star thoughts could not be covered even by the sunlight.

A sea of star thoughts rose up to the air and within few breaths of time, Dong Fang Yu Liang had tens of thousands of star thoughts.

In the air, starlights merged into one and formed a large patch of star cloud which surged forward with great momentum.

"Hei Lou Lan, take this!" Dong Fang Yu Liang shouted and shot the star thoughts beside him towards Hei Lou Lan.

Such an enormous scale of star thoughts burst through the wind with astonishing grandeur.

"Hmph!" A trace of fear flashed past the depths of Hei Lou Lan's pupils.

Wisdom path Gu Masters were not defenseless people. Each Gu Master path had its own attacking methods.

A path without any attacking methods would be eliminated and vanish in the passage of history.

Many years ago, Hei Lou Lan and Dong Fang Yu Liang had crossed swords. At that time, just a scale of several thousand star thoughts was enough to make Hei Lou Lan suffer greatly.

Star thoughts were very fast and would directly attack the enemy's mind from any direction possible, and were very difficult to guard against.

"So many star thoughts, it seems Dong Fang Yu Liang really intends to bet his life! Creating so many star thoughts without any restriction, it is already no longer as simple as injuring soul or body; no matter what the outcome of this battle is, Dong Fang Yu Liang will lose at least two years of his lifespan. My state is not good now, I had better avoid it first."

Hei Lou Lan had thoughts of retreating when he looked at such a large scale of star thoughts.

He disappeared from the spot, appearing thousand steps away.

But star thoughts were as fast as lightning as they chased after Hei Lou Lan without giving up.

Hei Lou Lan snorted, healing himself while continually dodging.

The enormous start cloud formed from the star thoughts, continued to chase after Hei Lou Lan, devastating everything in its path.

Some Gu Masters with weak willpower were directly struck into idiocy by the star thoughts.

Most of the Gu Masters whose minds were struck by star thoughts, immediately felt dizzy and could not keep standing stably.

Only few Gu Master experts with firm willpower, moved their thoughts to destroy the external star thoughts. But because of these Gu Masters resisting the star thoughts, the intense battle had slowed down.

Rank four Gu Masters could rampage through the battlefield, but once a rank five Gu Master moved, they could influence the whole situation.

Dong Fang Yu Liang made an all-out attack, pressing down Hei Lou Lan into disadvantage.The star cloud formed from the majestic star thoughts became the first force to dominate the battlefield.

Although star thoughts exhausted rapidly, the star thoughts Dong Fang Yu Liang created were extremely fast.

As time passed, the size of the star cloud did not decrease, but instead slightly increased.

Almost everyone in the battlefield were concentrating on the star cloud. When the star cloud neared, most of the Gu Masters would choose to flee, afraid of being struck into idiocy.

However, Dong Fang Yu Liang did not have the least bit of joy and was instead filled with worry.

Hei Lou Lan's movement Gu was outstanding, even star thoughts could not catch up. Dong Fang Yu Liang knew clearly there were two people who were the most significant in Hei alliance army - Hei Lou Lan and Chang Shan Yin.

Right now, Hei Lou Lan was escaping faster than a rabbit while Chang Shan Yin was hiding somewhere, meticulously suppressing his soul and only using a portion to control the wolf group. The chance of bringing him out in the light in this chaotic battlefield was extremely minute.

"Since it is so, I shall destroy your elite troops. I want to see if you can still keep on enduring!" A cold glint flashed in Dong Fang Yu Liang's eyes; the star thought cloud suddenly changed direction and charged towards the battle rings of the elite troops.

These elite troops were at least of rank two cultivation with rank three Gu Masters as their leaders.

They had numerical advantage but could never be Dong Fang Yu Liang's match. Under the special consideration of star thought cloud, Hei tribe's blue butterfly elite troop immediately collapsed with countless casualties.

"My elite troop!" At this sight, Ye tribe leader shouted in heartache.

"Still not coming out?" Dong Fang Yu Liang slightly raised his brows and mobilized star thought cloud to attack war dog elite troop.

War dog elite troop was immediately disrupted and the surrounding elite troops took this chance to besiege them, killing this elite troop quickly and easily.

"My war dog elite troop!" Wang tribe leader's body trembled in heartache. Who knew how much resources and energy Wang tribe had used to cultivate this elite troop.

Such precious battle force was destroyed within moments.

"Hm, still not coming out to rescue them?" Dong Fang Yu Liang's brows furrowed deeper. Killing two elite troops one after another had caused a huge consumption in the star thoughts, if not for him continually creating new star thoughts, the star thought cloud would have already been used up.

Despite the empowerment from seven star lights, Dong Fang Yu Liang still felt an intense weakness at this moment. Strands of white began to appear in his bluish-black hair.

"Kill, kill, i want to see how long you can maintain this killer move." Fang Yuan who was hiding in some corner enjoying this scene through wolf care Gu while smiling coldly.

To him, the more people that died, the more souls he would be able to collect after the battle.

Anyway, as long as they obtained victory at the end, he still held the qualification to enter Imperial Court.

Dong Fang Yu Liang was trying to force Fang Yuan out by slaughtering the elite troops; but it will only happen in his sweet dreams.

Chapter 514: Wolf King’s ruthlessness

The battle continued.

Because of Dong Fang Yu Liang using all his strength to attack and slaughtering three elite troops one after another, Dong Fang tribe began to occupy upper hand.

"Kill!"

"Let us kill all these Hei tribe thugs."

"Kill all the men, and take all the women to our camp!"

Dong Fang alliance army's morale surged high, their offense becoming fiercer as they beat back Hei tribe allied army without giving them room for breather.

However, the originator of this momentum, Dong Fang Yu Liang, was somewhat worried.

"Although we look to be moving towards victory, my side has already shown our trump cards. My killer move seven star lights won't last for long, if I still can't force Hei Lou Lan and Chang Shan Yin out, then..."

Dong Fang Yu Liang's eyes flashed with a cold light when he thought of this.

His clear and incisive eyes gazed towards the mid army of Hei tribe where black banner elite troop was stationed. This division of elite troop had formidable strength, far surpassing others; till now, this precious force had not made any move and was holding their position.

Next, Dong Fang Yu Liang's gaze moved towards a specific corner of the battlefield.

Ge tribe Gu Masters were gathered there with Ge Guang and the rest being blood-soaked and fighting bravely.

Dong Fang Yu Liang expressionlessly split the star thought cloud into two; one half moved towards black banner elite troop while the other half moved towards Ge tribe.

Seeing the invasion of the star cloud, black banner army's three commanders paled.

"Defend! All forces activate Gu together!"

The commanders sent the command and all the heads of the black banner elite troop put all their efforts in activating Gu.

Battle thought Gu was similar to star thought Gu and space thought Gu, and was also one of the wisdom path Gu worms. All the different ranking commanders of black banner elite troop coordinated to activate rank three to rank four Gu.

These battle thought Gu were meant to be used on black banner elite troop. During the battle, the battle thought Gu would enter their brain and surge their battle intent, making them fearless.

Star thought cloud pounced towards them. Red thoughts emerged above the black banner elite troop.

There were few of these battle thoughts, but with them guarding beside the black banner elite troop, the elite troop was able to forcibly resist the impact of the star thought cloud.

"Hei tribe is indeed worthy of being a super tribe, the quality of their elite troop is far beyond that of other tribe's elite troops." Fang Yuan inwardly praised at this sight.

These black banner elite troop belonged to Hei tribe completely and would keep on accumulating their strength during peaceful times. The Gu Masters in this troop were carefully selected elites, and with the large amounts of training and enormous resources invested in them, they were able to form into a trump card.

Each of them had firm willpower and possessed the ability to resist the thoughts impact by themselves. Now, with the protection of battle thoughts added, the devastation of star thought cloud was restrained for the first time.

Naturally, there was a crucial reason for this; Dong Fang Yu Liang had not used all his strength in this and had divided the star thought cloud into two, only using half of it to attack black banner elite troop.

Black banner elite troop's breathtaking performance shocked the people, forming a clear contrast with the other devastated elite troops.

While on the Ge tribe's side, miserable screams kept on ringing out; they were being slaughtered under the attack of the majestic star thoughts.

Fang Yuan watched this indifferently. He was able to use wolf care Gu very proficiently, allowing him to see Ge tribe's miserable condition clearly.

Ge tribe was no more than one of his chess pieces to disguise his identity. As the chessmaster, why would he put himself in danger because of a chess piece?

"Still not coming out?..." Dong Fang Yu Liang waited patiently for a while, secretly observing with his detection Gu; as long as Fang Yuan made any move to rescue the Ge tribe, he would be able to pinpoint Fang Yuan's exact location through the soul fluctuations.

But, no matter how long he waited, Fang Yuan did not make any move.

Such cold and heartless action of Wolf King made Dong Fang Yu Liang feel a chill down his spine.

On the contrary, when Hei Lou Lan saw his black banner elite troop showing signs of not being able to hold off anymore, he quickly made his move.

"Dong Fang Yu Liang, die!" He shouted with a grandeur that looked like he had already recovered from the backlash.

Dong Fang Yu Liang snorted, large numbers of new star thoughts emerged above his head and charged towards Hei Lou Lan.

The two collided in the mid-air, exchanging many moves; for a time, the victor or the loser could not be determined.

With Hei Lou Lan's interference, the star thought cloud that was causing troubles for black banner elite troop had no more support, and completely disappeared after causing mayhem for a while.

The battlefield that had turned chaotic for a while, again entered a deadlock.

A smaller part of the dozen or so rank four battle rings, had already ended with the result ending in death or injuries. Among them, Wind Demon and Water Demon were still fighting. Shadow Sword Expert Bian Si Xuan and Flying Lightning Dong Po Kong, however, were moving back and forth in the battlefield.

These two both had outstanding movement Gu, and even when they were blocked by rank four Gu Masters, they were able to easily get past them.

They were continuously searching for Fang Yuan's traces, but unfortunately Fang Yuan kept on hiding without making any moves, causing their search to be fruitless.

.........

At the same time, in Ni Yu blessed land, two Gu Immortals, a male and a female, were sipping tea while observing the smoke image on the center of the table.

The smoke image kept on surging, showing the scenes of the battle between Hei tribe and Dong Fang tribe. The scenes were extremely clear, showing minute details of every corner.

The female Gu Immortal Tan Bi Ya looked away and smiled towards the male Gu Immortal Dong Fang Chang Fan: "Looks like this battle will be determined by the battle between Dong Fang Yu Liang and Hei Lou Lan. Whichever side wins will be the side that will occupy the upper hand. Dong Fang Yu Liang, this young man is pretty good, being able to bring the battle into a stalemate while having weaker military forces than Hei tribe, it seems Brother Chang Fan's guidance is quite effective."

Dong Fang Chang Fan had an ancient noble appearance, with eyes that intermittently flashed with all kinds of colors. This sole wisdom path Gu Immortal of Dong Fang tribe indifferently shook his head and said with indifference:

"Actually I only said two to three sentences to Dong Fang Yu Liang. But this young lad is indeed good and quite interesting. After returning, he wantonly proclaimed this and rose up borrowing my prestige. He has some talent and also puts in great efforts. I have already promised him that as long as he can be the Lord of the Imperial Court, I will heal his little sister and nurture him as one of my successors."

"Become the Lord of Imperial Court?" Tan Bi Ya was slightly dazed before smiling, "Please forgive little sister for being blunt; in this round of the Imperial Court contest, I am afraid Dong Fang tribe does not have a high chance. Within the several popular candidates this year, Ye Lui tribe's Ye Lui Sang is thought to have a high chance by everyone. This time, Ye Lui tribe's Supreme Elder Ye Lui Lai has secretly entrusted an Immortal Gu to Ye Lui Sang. This is already an open secret in the circle."

"Ye Lui tribe might be part of the Huang Jin family and one of the super tribes of northern plains, but they haven't gained ownership of Imperial Court for the last eight rounds. Because of this, Ye Lui Lai has been made fun of by Hei Cheng of Hei tribe in these days. He is probably mobilizing Immortal Gu this time to regain face." Dong Fang Chang Fan chuckled after he finished speaking, his chuckle seemed to contain disdain.

Tan Bi Ya sipped tea and said: "Yes, speaking of Hei Cheng, Hei Lou Lan is his twenty-seventh concubine's child. This is his son, so he has been actively supporting from behind because of sentiment and principle. Thus, Hei Lou Lan is also one of the popular candidates. Historically speaking, the struggle for the Imperial Court is no more than a competition between several large Huang Jin family tribes. Those that are able to be the Lord of Imperial Court have immense support from behind. From what I see, Hei Lou Lan's chances are much higher than your tribe's Dong Fang Yu Liang."

Dong Fang Chang Fan, however, slowly shook his head.

Tan Bi Ya's eyes flashed with a trace of interest at this: "What is it? Could it be Brother Chang Fan also privately gave an Immortal Gu to Dong Fang Yu Liang? Or maybe you set up some arrangements to ensure Dong Fang Yu Liang becomes the Lord of Imperial Court?"

Wisdom path Gu Masters had the ability to scheme deeply and make deductions; most Gu Immortals have either experienced this personally or have heard of it. Wisdom path Gu Immortals were few in numbers, Dong Fang Chang Fan was a famous wisdom path Gu Master of northern plains; if he had secretly made arrangements and as long as it did not openly break the game rules for the fight for Imperial Court, Dong Fang Yu Liang would have a great probability of success.

However, Dong Fang Chang Fan negated Tan Bi Ya's conjecture: "No. During this round's competition for Imperial Court, Ma tribe has enormous momentum and could be said to have one foot on the throne of Imperial Court. Why would I Dong Fang Chang Fan do pointless work?"

He, Dong Fang Chang Fan, was already old and did not have much time left.

He had calculated that the time of his death was around the corner and thus for the tribe and also for his legacy to be continued, the matter of importance was to choose and nurture his successor. The fight for the Imperial Court was secondary.

Not all Gu Masters could become wisdom path Gu Masters by having a set of wisdom path Gu worms. Dong Fang Chang Fan was very pleased with Dong Fang Yu Liang's talents and even was slightly fearful. What made him even more pleased was Dong Fang Yu Liang had a weak and sick little sister who was unable to cultivate.

This was Dong Fang Yu Liang's weakness, and as long as he grasped this hold on him, he would not need to worry about Dong Fang Yu Liang's loyalty.

The fight for the imperial court was only a plan he set for Dong Fang Yu Liang.

After Dong Fang Yu Liang was defeated, he would definitely come to beg him to save his little sister. This was akin to him gaining a hold on Dong Fang Yu Liang of the latter's own initiative.

If Dong Fang Yu Liang succeeds by fluke, that would also be an unexpected surprise. Even though he had promised Dong Fang Yu Liang to heal his little sister, who is to say if she would be cured completely?

Tan Bi Ya was surprised: "What is this? Brother Chang Fan, you actually are optimistic about Ma tribe? Ma tribe might be a large scale tribe with quite extraordinary military strength, but they don't have an Gu Immortal supreme elder."

Dong Fang Chang Fan seemed to be waiting for this question as he leisurely replied: "Sister Bi Ya, you are unaware that snowy mountain blessed land has already secretly contacted Ma tribe to give them support."

"Snowy mountain blessed land, that group of demonic path Gu Immortals?" Tan Bi Ya's complexion sank as the news had quite a huge impact on her.

She closely looked at Dong Fang Chang Fan: "Brother Chang Fan, How did you know this?"

Dong Fang Chang Fan proudly smiled: "I personally deduced this, you are the first one to know of it."

Tan Bi Ya immediately believed most of it; Dong Fang Chang Fan was a wisdom path Gu Immortal, this deduction he made personally should be equal to the truth. She also knew his details and knew he did not have any reason to deceive her.

Moreover, snowy mountain blessed land's group of demonic path Gu Immortals had always been coveting after Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. This time, they were secretly supporting Ma tribe to get their hands on Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's inheritance, such things had happened many times in the past as well.

Thinking of this, she could not remain seated anymore.

She was Liu tribe's external supreme elder and was secretly supporting Liu Wen Wu. In case Liu Wen Wu obtained the throne of Imperial Court, it would be an extremely big help to her status in Liu tribe.

Ma tribe's existence had severely affected her arrangement. She naturally could not be tolerant and stood up: "Brother Chang Fan, this matter is of grave importance. Demonic path Gu Immortals are jackals and wolves, the others are still in the dark. Little sister will go inform them, please forgive little sister for taking her leave."

"Go, go." Dong Fang Chang Fan slowly nodded and opened the door of the blessed land.

After Tan Bi Ya left the blessed land, Dong Fang Chang Fan's face that had no change like an ancient well, showed a hint of a smile.

This discussion was a scheme he had made for Tan Bi Ya.

Tan Bi Ya was also an astute Gu Immortal, but since she was involved herself and also had her own expectations from this, she could be easily plotted against.

Dong Fang Chang Fan's gaze moved towards the smoke image where some changes had appeared in the battle.

After a long fight, Dong Fang Yu Liang was slowly unable to hold up and began to retreat. With the main chief commander retreating, the army morale instantly fell and under Dong Fang Yu Liang's command, also began to retreat.

The army was rattled but retreated without rushing, they had clearly received a lot of training.

Dong Fang Yu Liang had already expected this, thus he had spent a lot of care in planning the retreat prior to the battle.

Dong Fang army slowly retreated while counter attacking occasionally; many Gu Masters of Hei tribe were instead the ones to lose their lives due to carelessness.

"Wind Demon, you gutless rat, want to run?" Water Demon Hao Ji Liu shouted, his body was filled with injuries and was soaked in blood.

Wind Demon scoffed but did not reply, instead retreating silently, firmly acting on Dong Fang Yu Liang's command.

The defensive line the army had constructed before was several hundreds of li farther. As long as they could retreat to the defense line, they would have time to get some rest and recover their strength.

At that time, it would be Hei tribe army's turn to feel a headache, and this bad start would only be a small detail.

However, right at this time, wolf group suddenly howled and gathered together, once again forming into a wolf tide that unfolded a death charge towards Dong Fang army.

The wolf group was different from Gu Masters; Gu Masters cherished their lives while the wolf group could charge on without fearing death.

"Damn it!" Dong Fang Yu Liang's heart was tearing as he looked at this. Under the wolf group's charge, Dong Fang alliance army suffered countless casualties and panic soon spread in the army, continuing to show signs of crumbling.

Fang Yuan used eighty percent of his master level enslavement attainment. The people who looked at it were dazzled as the assault came in waves after waves, unceasingly; Dong Fang army was like mud which under the cleansing of the wolf tide, broke apart piece by piece.

The strong soul fluctuations revealed Fang Yuan's position.

But Fang Yuan was already in the open now; he was standing on the calm twin-headed rhino with many Gu Master experts gathering beside him.

"Wolf King Chang Shan Yin..." Dong Fang Yu Liang gnashed his teeth, his eyes seemingly breathing fire.

In this battle, he had thoroughly experienced the ruthlessness and the ferocity of Fang Yuan.

Don't forget, Fang Yuan had only acted twice in this battle!

The first time he moved, he directly created the all-out war, causing many of Dong Fang Yu Liang's arrangements to have no place to be used.

And now, the second time he moved, was the time when Dong Fang army was its weakest, throwing stones at them when they were having difficulties. Right now, the Gu Masters almost had no primeval essence in their aperture, having risked their lives for so long. Although they still had strength to battle, they were perishing together with the wolves.

Fang Yuan's wolf group also had severe losses. But this was already a great profit, his wolves could be easily replenished, there were many wolves in northern plains! But the sacrifice the other side had to make were precious Gu Masters!

Chapter 515: Dong Fang Yu Liang’s backup plan

Dong Fang army suffered huge losses within a short period of time, and they abandoned the large numbers of corpses as they retreated.

"Run!"

"Run, it will be too late if we don't go now!!"

The situation Dong Fang Yu Liang was most worried about finally happened - Dong Fang alliance army collapsed with no intent to battle, only concentrating on escaping. Hei tribe army took this chance to unfold a cruel massacre.

Dong Fang Yu Liang gnashed his teeth and promptly mobilized rank four Gu Master experts to hold back the enemy.

The experts turned around and dealt a heavy blow, restraining the momentum of Hei tribe army. But this did not last long as Hei tribe's rank four Gu Master experts took the stage and hindered the Dong Fang tribe's experts.

Dong Fang Yu Liang made a move again, but was pinned down by Hei Lou Lan.

Seeing his side troops chasing after the enemy and having the momentum in unfolding cruel massacre, Fang Yuan stopped and summoned the wolf group beside him.

This move immediately won favorable impression from the black banner elite troop's commander who was beside him.

In his view, this was a great chance for Wolf King to get battle contributions, but the latter instead gave these battle achievements to others. This commander praised Fang Yuan openly.

Fang Yuan knew the other party was trying to express goodwill. Hei Xiu Yi had been appointed as his bodyguard, but Xiu Yi deserted him in the face of danger, and if not for the water image Gu, he would have already been dead.

However, Fang Yuan never counted on someone else's protection; he only relied on himself. Moreover, Hei Xiu Yi was Hei Lou Lan's trusted general and because of this, he would not be able to do anything to Hei Xiu Yi if he raised this topic. Even if he could, Fang Yuan was not willing to be in such pointless internal friction.

He casually replied, secretly hinting the commander that he did not put this matter in heart.

Only then did the commander let out a breath of relief, secretly feeling: though Wolf King was arrogant, he was truly magnanimous and extraordinary.

Finally, Dong Fang army made a mad run to the first defense line, paying a disastrous price for this.

Twenty percent of the whole army had died during the first battle but fifty percent had died during the chase by the wolf group and the enemy. The remaining thirty percent who were injured and disabled managed to run to the defense line.

Among the rank four experts, two died in the process of holding back Hei tribe army.

The Hei tribe army chased without stopping, but they were shot through by the feather arrow elite troops who were standing on the defense walls, and lost hundreds of people before running away in sorry figures.

This was the elite troop that the Dong Fang tribe had cultivated by spending a lot of care and resources; they were not any weaker than the black banner elite troop.

Hei tribe's Gu Masters tried to charge through three times but were shot back into retreat by the feather arrow elite troop. Hei Lou Lan mobilized the rank four Gu Masters to charge forward, but they were trapped by Dong Fang Yu Liang's arrangement and lost three experts.

"Lord alliance leader, the enemy is relying on their location to defend and they occupy the geographical advantage. Our side has fought hard for long, we don't have sufficient primeval essence to keep on fighting, it would be better to retreat for now and make new plans." The group of experts returned to the main tent where cunning gentleman Sun Shi Han suggested this idea.

Fang Yuan's brows furrowed; he had his previous life memories and knew Dong Fang Yu Liang was very good at handling messy situations, winning against stronger opponents as the weaker side. If they delayed for long, the amount of intel he would receive would increase and it would be more unfavorable for Hei tribe.

This time, there was Fang Yuan's interference which led to the Hei tribe occupying a greater dominance than in his previous life, but Dong Fang Yu Liang who was in a good shape was an enormous threat. To deal with Dong Fang Yu Liang, the best way was to continue attacking, without giving him the chance to scheme and calculate.

Hei Lou Lan pondered on cunning gentleman's suggestion in silence. He had crossed hands with Dong Fang Yu Liang before and was well acquainted with Dong Fang Yu Liang's methods. He did not want to let go of this chance in front of him and thus his gaze moved towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan proudly smiled and said to Hei Lou Lan: "Hei tribe leader does not need to worry, I can guarantee you that I will break this defense line in just a quarter of an hour."

The crowd raised their eyebrows in surprise while cunning gentleman sneered, feeling Fang Yuan was boasting.

Hei Lou Lan, however, was joyous: "Then I shall see the Wolf King's ability."

The wolf group once again gathered together and unfolded an endless charge at Dong Fang tribe's first line of defense.

The Dong Fang tribe defended very tightly and in just moments, wolf corpses littered under the walls.

Hei tribe's troops were overwhelmed at this sight; Fang Yuan was simply sending the wolf group to their death, disregarding the sacrifices.

Especially the feather arrow elite troop; they were experts at long distance attacks and were with the direction of the wind from the walls. Rank four experts acted as emergency response group, moving everywhere; as long as an area showed signs of falling, they would move one after another to avert the disaster.

Dong Fang tribe's defense line was truly like a fortress.

Fang Yuan scoffed while continuously activating wolf howl Gu, and creating shocking variations in the assault. Every variation brought an enormous threat to the defense line.

This high intensity of battle caused enormous sacrifices in the wolf group; two hundred and eighty thousand wolves had died in a short period of time!

Fang Yuan was expressionless as he commanded the wolf group from the twin-headed rhinoceros's back. The gazes the crowd in the main tent looked at him quietly changed.

Wolf King's ruthlessness caused fear to emerged in these people.

Such a majestic and fierce wolf tide gave them a feeling of being insignificant.

"Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, such a ruthless heart you have, do you want to spare none!?" Dong Fang Yu Liang's expression was heavy. The large numbers of sacrifices in the wolf group were exchanged with intense consumption of primeval essence of Dong Fang army.

He was extremely regretful. If he had known this, he would rather give up on Hei Lou Lan, to take Chang Shan Yin's life!

Finally, Dong Fang tribe's Gu Masters could not hold up anymore, and the wolf group's offence made them so exhausted that they did not even have time to take a breather, much less recover their primeval essence.

"Retreat!" Helplessly, Dong Fang Yu Liang could only send down the command to retreat.

Just like Fang Yuan proclaimed, after a quarter of an hour, Dong Fang tribe's first line of defense was broken. Dong Fang Yu Liang left behind a group of crippled Gu Masters to cover their retreat, and led the remaining troops to escape towards the second defense line in the fastest speed possible.

"My wolf group is very exhausted and is not fit to chase them anymore." Fang Yuan withdrew his wolf group and made way to give Hei tribe army the chance to move.

This action won him almost everyone's good impressions.

"I have sustained some injuries in this battle, you guys chase them and kill them all. But be careful, that Dong Fang lad definitely has some arrangements." Hei Lou Lan did not move from the main tent, and instead sent Hao Ji Liu, Pan Ping, the Wang tribe leader and others to chase.

The crowd excitedly crossed over the broken defense line and moved in pursuit.

But the troops had just crossed over the defense line when an intense explosion suddenly burst out.

BOOM! Just like the crackling of a thunder, dozens of Gu Masters were instantly fried, leaving behind flesh and broken limbs on the ground.

BOOM BOOM BOOM...

Immediately after that, large numbers of explosions exploded in a chain-reaction, covering the whole defense line.

The troops who went to chase immediately suffered huge losses and fell into chaos.

"It is charred thunder potato Gu! Dong Fang Yu Liang buried large numbers of them under the defense line!" The investigative Gu Masters returned to report in the main tent.

"I can see it!" Hei Lou Lan's expression was extremely dark as he waved his hand for the investigative Gu Masters to take their leave.

He was not stupid and immediately realized he had been schemed by Dong Fang Yu Liang.

Setting up so many charred thunder potato Gu would require a long time. This time was actually given by Hei Lou Lan.

Before the battle, Dong Fang Yu Liang had purposely sent a challenge letter to start the war. In retaliation, Hei Lou Lan listened to cunning gentleman's words and delayed it for several days, only starting the battle after his rear army gathered. This gave Dong Fang Yu Liang the chance to put this plan in action.

The explosions continued without an end, inflicting many casualties among the Hei tribe army. The most crucial point was that their pursuit had stopped; the Hei tribe army could only watch as the Dong Fang tribe's remnant troops safely escaped.

Charred thunder potato Gu might only be a rank two Gu with limited power but there was just too many of it.

Besides this, there were also many rank three muffled thunder potato Gu and a few rank four thunderclap potato Gu mixed among them.

Even if Gu Masters were able to activate defensive Gu and preserve their life, their primeval essence would be greatly consumed. There were only a few Gu Masters who had flying Gu worms. Even if these people could catch up to the enemy, their strength was weak and would instead be giving Dong Fang tribe the opportunity to kill them.

The Gu Masters who had been worked up and excited to establish merits, finally returned to the camp in a sorry figure, full of injuries.

"We have already gained a huge victory today, Dong Fang lad is only delaying his death. I can still have the pleasure of killing him later!" Hei Lou Lan pacified himself and began to handle the postwar affairs.

Cleaning the battlefield, healing the injured, listing the battle merits; these were all complicated affairs that required energy and time.

Fang Yuan naturally was not willing to waste his precious time on this. He casually gave an excuse and left the main tent, returning to his large lizard house Gu to continue cultivating.

He had established huge contributions in this battle, and although he only moved a few times, each time was crucial. In front of his military success and position of strength, even cunning gentleman kept quiet, much less anyone else.

"The Wolf King was not injured by the blast?...." Dong Fang Yu Liang listened to the battle information from the detective Gu Master, and felt quite regretful.

Through this battle, he placed Fang Yuan as the number one enemy with threat even higher than Hei Lou Lan.

Chang Shan Yin was extremely cunning and vicious, not even caring about Ge tribe's life or death. Although he was only at rank four peak stage, he was much more troublesome than Hei Lou Lan.

Dong Fang Yu Liang had originally calculated that the chance for Chang Shan Yin to mobilize his wolf group to chase them was very high.

But his meticulously prepared trap did not even ensnare a single wolf, and instead killed large numbers of Hei tribe's Gu Masters.

A Gu Master's life was much much more precious than wild wolves. But Dong Fang Yu Liang was not happy.

To a wisdom path Gu Master who were experts at deductions and schemes, a strong and powerful enemy was not troublesome. But even though the Wolf King was strong, he was not conceited, and instead was a very calm opponent; such opponents were a thorn in the neck.

It was precisely because of Fang Yuan's few times of making a move that caused Dong Fang army to fall from slightly losing position to utter defeat. From this, a gap appeared in the two sides where the Hei tribe was in a clear superiority and Dong Fang army was in a disadvantage, in a worsening situation.

Looking at this battle coming to an end, in Ni Yu blessed land, Dong Fang Chang Fan retracted his gaze and collected the smoke on the table into his sleeves.

Even without a need to deduce, he could tell that Dong Fang Yu Liang was already in an absolute disadvantage after this battle. Unless Hei Lou Lan made a great mistake, Dong Fang Yu Liang's hopes of advancing to Imperial Court had become very minute.

However, Dong Fang Yu Liang had performed remarkably in the battle, even creating a stalemate with his comparatively weaker military force. He had made full use of all the cards available to him.

"Especially his move in protecting the tribe's strength, which caused there to not be a single loss in feather arrow elite troop. This is his loyalty towards the tribe. Now, it is a test to see how well he deals with this messy situation." Dong Fang Chang Fan slowly closed his eyes, very pleased with this point.

Other tribe's casualties were their matters, it was okay as long as Dong Fang tribe's losses were not large.

The struggle for the Imperial Court by itself was an arrangement set by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable; one of the objectives was to preserve his bloodline while weakening the other tribes!

Chapter 516: Battle Merit Board

The red cloud surged in the air, giving Fang Yuan a burning hot feeling.

Fang Yuan was sitting cross-legged on a mat with his eyes closed, his mind holding the fire cloud together.

"It is time." He inwardly calculated the time and slowly opened his eyes, after which he took out a wine vat.

The wine vat was filled with dark blue liquid, giving off a shine like the reflection of the moon on the sea.

"Descend." Fang Yuan softly spoke and the fire cloud in the air slowly fell down, pouring completely into the wine vat.

For a moment, the contact of fire and water along with their merging produced thick black smoke.

The black smoke rapidly pervaded the whole room.

Fang Yuan could not even see his own fingers as if he was in a dark night.

With a shift of his mind, the wine vat suddenly let out an attraction force that completely absorbed all the black smoke within a few breaths of time.

The room was bright once again with a vague sweetness remaining in the air.

Fang Yuan repeatedly flicked his finger, throwing Gu worm after Gu worm into the wine vat. The wine vat kept on shaking for two-three minutes before finally calming down.

Fang Yuan gazed into the wine vat and only saw black mud inside. Those Gu worms he had thrown inside had completely merged together, forming a semi-finished product that was concealed in the center of the black mud.

"Rise." Fang Yuan cautiously poured his primeval essence.

The surface of the black mud broke open and a thin, delicate sprout grew out of it. The delicate sprout was glossy green and grew rapidly, already growing into a small sapling in an instant.

The sapling grew thicker with a visible speed, slowly growing upwards. Conversely, the black mud in the wine vat rapidly decreased.

When the black mud decreased to eighty percent, the small tree stopped growing. The crown of the tree had formed into a tight shape, like a clenched green fist.

"Open." Fang Yuan gave a light shout and simultaneously poured in large amounts of primeval essence into the tree.

The green fist slowly opened, revealing a Gu worm in its palm.

This Gu had a long oval body with a dark brown carapace. A majestic horn was on its head, which made it look thick and powerful.

It had four pairs of long strong legs and its whole body emitted a glossy metallic luster. One look at it was enough for anyone to know that it was not an ordinary Gu.

A trace of joy flashed in Fang Yuan's eyes.

This Gu was precisely the all-out effort Gu which he had failed to advance three times before, finally succeeding in this fourth try.

Fang Yuan carefully observed, examining the differences in before and after the refinement.

Rank three all-out effort Gu only had three pairs of legs and because it was from the Southern Border, it received the region's restriction and was suppressed to rank two.

Rank four all-out effort Gu had four pairs of legs and was larger in size, over two times bigger than its rank three counterpart. And because it was refined in Northern Plains, it became a Northern Plains Gu and did not suffer from suppression, thus letting out a genuine rank four aura.

"With this rank four Gu, my strength path battle strength has immediately recovered for the most part. I will have to make preparations for its rank five recipe. Fortunately, I now possess a blessed land and can connect to treasure yellow heaven, and also have some connection with Lang Ya blessed land. There is hope in getting hold of all-out effort Gu's rank five recipe."

Fang Yuan stored this new all-out effort Gu into his aperture and cleaned the room once before coming out of the large lizard house Gu.

Outside was a bright and beautiful scene.

Large numbers of Gu Masters were moving back and forth between countless tents, hurrying about their respective affairs. Some were going to supply camps to exchange for Gu worms, some were returning after cleaning up the battlefield and some were building up defensive structures.

Eight days had passed since the great battle with Dong Fang alliance army.

In these eight days, Hei tribe's army kept its patience, cleaning up the battlefield everyday, making details of battle merits and healing the injured.

These serious and diverse affairs caused the army higher ups to be extremely busy. A mountain of paperworks had piled up on Hei Lou Lan's table. Cunning gentleman was given heavy responsibilities and was so busy that he had not slept for three days and three nights, and his face had become pale as paper. Each of the tribe leaders were also very busy, rushing about to fight for the benefits of their respective tribes.

As people holding top positions, they naturally had their own duty and responsibility.

In this period of time, Ge Guang also looked for Fang Yuan several times, hoping Fang Yuan would come out for Ge tribe's benefits, but Fang Yuan ignored and refused to see him, only concentrating in cultivating.

In this time, they appeared to be free and unconstrained like those demonic path Gu Masters. For the most part, they did not receive any implications and only looked after themselves; apart from checking whether their battle merits had not been embezzled, they were either healing their injuries or using battle merits to exchange for new Gu worms, actively preparing for war.

The treatment abilities of this world was far above that on earth.

On Earth, amputated limbs would mean becoming a disabled. If fingers were cut off, the fingers would need to be preserved and transplanted within a set period of time. And this transplantation had a chance of failure.

But in this world, even if one's limbs were completely cut off, they could be directly grown under the healing effects of Gu worms.

Basically, as long as the Gu Masters were not inflicted with troublesome injuries, they could be healed.

Thus, although only a short period of eight days had passed, the number of injured in Hei tribe army had already decreased by eighty percent, among which most had recovered the ability to fight.

As one went nearer towards the supply camps, they would discover a bigger stream of people.

Over these days, large numbers of Gu Masters came here to exchange their battle merits for goods.

The supply camps became the most busy place in the whole camp. They opened fifteen large tents in a row with each tent occupying at least 3.25 acres, and over a thousand Gu Masters were working to serve people. But even so, the supply camp was packed with people and every tent was crowded and clamorous.

"Subordinate greets Lord Wolf King, please come this way lord." When Fang Yuan arrived at the supply camp, a professional female Gu Master led him to a Gu house with a smile on her face.

As long as there was an organization, there would be hierarchy, upper and lower levels and also difference in treatments.

Fang Yuan belonged to the upper layer in the whole army and the treatment he received would naturally be different from ordinary people.

"Lord Wolf King is mighty, you are the first in the battle merit list in this battle!" The young and beautiful female Gu Master handed a scroll to Fang Yuan with a look of worship.

Fang Yuan gently pulled apart the two ends of the scroll and saw Chang Shan Yin at the very start. After his name was the amount of battle merit, which was a series of numbers written in Northern Plains' language, denoting over a hundred thousand characters. Fang Yuan only roughly glanced at it.

In this world, battle merits were easy to calculate.

Because there were large numbers of Gu worms that could monitor or capture images. In every large battle, every tribe would use large numbers of Gu worms to record the whole process of the battle. Besides the purpose of calculating the battle merits, it was more importantly for assimilating experience, gathering intel, probing the enemy's real details and understanding one's own side's deficiencies.

Besides this, many Gu Masters would also use their own Gu worms to record their own battle.

With all these details and images of every corner, the battle merits would be calculated again and again to verify the correct statistic.

Fang Yuan opened the scroll further; under his name was Hei Lou Lan. His battle merit was over eighty thousand.

Hei Lou Lan fought and pinned down Dong Fang Yu Liang who was the strongest expert in the enemy's side. At the same time, he killed Wei Xin, E Xuan Ming and Wan Shan who were under three hearts combination soul, getting rid of the mixed beast group; this was an enormous battle contribution.

Under Hei Lou Lan was Water Demon Hao Ji Liu, Wang tribe leader, Pan Ping and so on with tens of thousands as their battle merits.

As Fang Yuan went further down, the battle merits became less and less. After the top ten, the battle merits fell down to over nine thousand. After the top twenty, the battle merits fell down to around seven to eight thousand.

The scroll recorded one hundred and six people altogether, with most having around three thousand battle merits.

It was clear this scroll was the list of the highest battle merits achiever. The complete battle merit list was erected in the fifteen large tents and was as large as defense walls, with large numbers of swimword Gu used on them. Thus, the characters on the surface of the large list would flicker time to time, showing the change in the battle merits.

The battle merits statistics had started from the moment the battle started, and would keep on being maintained.

Some Gu Masters would exchange their battle merits for Gu worms, thus their battle merits would fall. Some Gu Masters' battle merits would instead continue to rise. Especially healing Gu Masters, they would have considerable gains in the postwar.

Fang Yuan placed the scroll to the side. The female Gu Master had been observing his expression and at this moment, she handed over a Gu worm.

This Gu worm looked like a ladybug with square carapace, protruding edges while the middle part was sunken like a window frame.

This was rank four east window Gu, an information path Gu, used to store information.

Previously at Lang Ya blessed land, when Fang Yuan asked for the information on Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the Lang Ya land spirit had given him an east window Gu.

Fang Yuan took the east window Gu and held it in his hand, pouring primeval essence into it.

East window Gu gave off a glimmer, and an enormous amount of information poured into Fang Yuan's mind.

There was a large number of goods including Gu worms from every path, beasts, vegetation, primeval stones, variant men, Gu recipes and so on.

These goods were put up by all tribes, and according to rules, as the alliance leader, Hei tribe put forward the maximum number of goods, no less than half of all these goods.

Soon, Fang Yuan discovered many things he wanted to purchase from these goods.

Although Fang Yuan could connect to treasure yellow heaven through Little Hu Immortal, the transactions in treasure yellow heaven was the transactions between great sects and clans, which used immortal essence stones as the currency. It was not suitable for Fang Yuan's current state.

At the same time there was also the mysterious force represented by Old Man Yan Shi who was coveting after Fang Yuan's fixed immortal travel Gu. If Fang Yuan wanted to buy rank five Gu to raise his strength, he would need to buy Northern Plains' Gu worms. If he did that, it would definitely provide an important evidence to this wisdom path Gu Immortal.

Thus, the supply camp was much more suitable to the current Fang Yuan than treasure yellow heaven.

"Among my strength path Gu worms, all-out effort Gu has been raised to rank four and has adapted to Northern Plains. But I still have rank three strength qi Gu, tusita flower, primeval elder Gu, self-reliance Gu as well as rank four bitter strength, expend strength Gu and charging crash Gu. These Gu are all from Southern Border and is under region suppression in the Northern Plains."

"To remove the region's suppression, I would need to advance these Gu to higher rank in Northern Plains. But to do so would mean too much investment."

There was a probability of failure in Gu refinement.

Even though Fang Yuan had close to master level skill in refinement path, he was not exempted from this probability.

The rank four all-out effort Gu he refined had failed several times before succeeding. The refinement of nauseous crying baby Gu failed for over ten times, yet it still did not succeed in the end.

The higher the rank of the Gu, the higher the probability of failing the refinement. This was especially so for rank five Gu as those were very challenging and difficult to refine, with the probability of success usually being less than one in a thousand.

Chapter 517: Lurking Soul Coat Gu

Advancing bitter strength Gu, expend strength Gu and charging crash Gu to rank five was a huge project; Fang Yuan would need to use large amounts of materials and Gu worms.

Thus, often only the Gu Immortals who had blessed lands had the capital to gather a complete set of rank five Gu.

It was very hard for mortals to bear such a price.

Thus, in the mortal world, a lot of rank five Gu Masters did not even have one rank five Gu. Only people like Hei Lou Lan and Dong Fang Yu Liang who had the support of a large force behind them had one or two rank five Gu.

In the information provided by east window Gu, there was only a dark path rank five Gu that could be exchanged with battle merits.

"My enslavement path Gu originated from Chang Shan Yin, almost all are rank four and it will be extremely difficult to raise them to rank five in a short period of time. Thus, I need to concentrate on gathering Gu recipes, just in case."

"As for my strength path Gu, those originate from Southern Border; rather than refining them, it might be better to make direct purchases. After all, these Gu are not my vital Gu, so if the refinement fails, they will perish. And if I want to refine again, I will have to accumulate them again.'

Fang Yuan's plan was the same as the choice many foreign region Gu Masters sensibly made in the troubled times that were to come in the future.

He made his choice.

There was only one rank five Gu among the goods, but there were many rank four Gu including bitter strength Gu, tusita flower and primeval elder Gu.

But there was no charging crash Gu.

Fang Yuan could only opt for the next best choice and choose two pairs of rank three horizontal charge Gu and vertical crash Gu, intending to fuse them himself.

Self-reliance Gu was a perfect match for strength path Gu Masters, and a rare Gu at that. In Hei tribe's enormous list of goods, there was one self-reliance Gu, but unfortunately it was only at rank two, even lower than Fang Yuan's.

Rank three self-reliance Gu could reach a price of forty-five thousand primeval stones which corresponded to forty-five hundred battle merits.

A rank four self-reliance Gu's price could be compared to a rank five Gu, and had a very low possibility of appearing in the exchange list.

Fang Yuan pondered and bought this rank two self-reliance Gu as well. If there was truly no other way, he could only try to refine it.

If the self-reliance Gu was like this, then there was no need to even mention strength qi Gu.

Strength qi Gu was already extinct in the mortal markets, and Fang Yuan's strength qi Gu was obtained by reverse refining rank four atmosphere Gu.

But the atmosphere Gu was rank four, and was not a mainstream Gu, and was also very rare on top of that.

If Fang Yuan wanted to obtain strength qi Gu, he could only use Northern Plains' atmosphere Gu and reverse refine it to rank three strength qi Gu.

He had rank five cultivation now; rank three strength qi Gu was not suitable for him anymore, rank three Gu's help to him now was extremely small.

"Since there is no expend strength Gu, then so be it. After all, this Gu is used for restricting strength path and has few applications. If I don't have strength qi Gu, it will truly be miserable; I will be lacking long range attack methods and land in the most common predicament of present age strength path Gu Masters."

Strength qi Gu might not be treated as a core Gu, but it was extremely important to strength path Gu Masters.

"So I can only try to gather rank four and rank five recipes of strength qi Gu for now. Qi path has already died out, treasure yellow heaven has them but the prices are definitely high. Perhaps my greatest hope is in Lang Ya blessed land. But Lang Ya land spirit is not easy to deal with, I will have to pay a huge price if I want to obtain the recipe."

Just when Fang Yuan was inwardly vexed about this problem, he suddenly had a realization.

"Eh? Wrong." His mind received a slight jolt.

"Even if my strength path doesn't have long ranged attack methods, my enslavement path can make up for it! My situation is no longer the same now, I have two apertures, I cultivate enslavement and strength path, they can complement each other."

Fang Yuan's view suddenly cleared up.

Although he was someone who had been reborn and was meticulous, it was unavoidable for even him to have times of habitual thinking.

He only had one aperture in his previous life and even though he had touched upon other paths, it was mostly after he became a Gu Immortal. But now, he was already cultivating two paths as a mortal.

"Enslavement path Gu Masters are most afraid of beheading the leader tactics, I can use strength path to defend. On the contrary, strength path's weakness can be filled by using enslavement path. Strength qi Gu, there is no need for it."

Because he cultivated two paths, this problem that troubled strength path Gu Masters was easily resolved.

Following after this, Fang Yuan used his battle merits to exchange for many space path Gu and large numbers of Gu refinement materials.

These space path Gu and materials were preparations to enter Luo Po Valley later on.

Thieving Heaven Demon Venerable had sealed Luo Po Valley back then. If one wanted to enter, normal methods wouldn't work; one must have a rank five open door Gu.

Open door Gu could let the fated ones enter Luo Po valley. But to close the passage would require refining a rank five close door Gu, to prevent the exposure of the passage and others entering in.

'Lord Wolf King actually exchanged for so many strength path Gu and space path Gu, and there are also huge amounts of Gu refinement materials.' The goods Fang Yuan wanted to exchange for, caused this female Gu Master to be inwardly surprised.

Exchanging for strength path Gu was still reasonable, after all strength path might be declining but it consumed less primeval essence. In case primeval essence was about to be exhausted, it could act as a Gu Master's last support.

Thus, in Northern Plains where battles occurred frequently, almost all the Gu Masters cultivated some strength path Gu.

'But what is Lord Wolf King going to do with these space path Gu?'

'Maybe he wants to use space path Gu to protect himself? After all, enslavement path Gu Masters are often restrained by beheading leader tactics.'

'There are also these astonishing amounts of Gu refinement materials, is Lord Wolf King interested towards refinement path? Or maybe he is researching a completely new enslavement path Gu?'

The female Gu Master was full of doubts but did not express them.

She was very aware that rashly inquiring about these secrets was an extremely great offense to the Gu Master.

Thus, she did not reveal any curiosity on her face, concentrating only on handling these exchanges.

Fang Yuan soon saw his battle merits decreased by over half on the battle list, immediately falling down from first position.

"Lord Wolf King, these goods you exchanged for will be sent to you one by one today and will be completely delivered by dawn." The female Gu Master informed in a soft voice.

Fang Yuan nodded and was just about to leave when this female Gu Master said in a low voice: "Lord Wolf King, please wait a moment. Here is a Gu recipe which is extremely suitable for you, Lord tribe leader specifically told me to hold it for you."

"Hmm?" Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with a bright light.

There was no need to even guess, the female Gu Master before him was definitely Hei tribe's Gu Master.

In such an important place like the supply camp, Hei Lou Lan could only be at ease if he placed his men inside.

Listening to the female Gu Master's words, Fang Yuan realized this was Hei Lou Lan's goodwill towards him. It was extremely likely that it was because of Hei Xiu Yi deserting in the face of danger, and that Fang Yuan let the bygones be bygones, so Hei Lou Lan was secretly reciprocating for it.

Fang Yuan immediately felt some interest and after understanding about the details, he found that this Gu recipe was truly very suitable for him.

This was a Gu recipe of lurking soul coat Gu.

Lurking soul coat Gu had only one ability, and that was to cover soul fluctuations.

Previously, Fang Yuan was hiding in a corner of the battlefield and had to mobilize the wolf group without being able to use his full strength to prevent being discovered. But with this Gu, he could completely cover his soul fluctuations and mobilize the wolf group with his whole strength while hiding.

This Gu recipe went all the way from rank one to rank five, thus it had very high price.

Fang Yuan used all his remaining battle merits and barely obtained it.

He skimmed through the Gu recipe once and saw the difficulty in refining this Gu was not high, but there were monumental amount of refinement procedures. Moreover, the cost involved was not low, especially one procedure among them required a large number of fresh beast skins as Gu refinement materials.

"Tribe leader has said himself that if Lord Wolf King feels like the Gu refinement is too complicated, you can ask the refinement path Gu Masters to do it. You only need to pay equivalent battle merits to them. If Lord Wolf King has insufficient battle merits, you can borrow five hundred thousand." The female Gu Master timely suggested.

Primeval stones were the currency during normal times.

But during battles, because of Gu Masters using a large number of primeval stones to restore their primeval essence, refine new Gu or so on, primeval stones were in scarcity.

At such times, battle merits were often used as currency.

This was not only in Northern Plains, it was also the same in Southern Border and other regions.

Borrowing battle merits naturally was not a treatment given to ordinary people. Fang Yuan, however, was a crucial battle strength as he could directly raise the strength of the whole Hei tribe army by himself, thus Hei Lou Lan was happy to actively promote such actions secretly.

Fang Yuan nodded and borrowed five hundred thousand battle merits on the spot.

With this, his battle merits went into negative, falling down to the last position on the large battle merit list.

The Gu Masters who saw this scene in the fifteen large tents exclaimed in surprise.

In the enormous battle merit list that was as large as defense walls, the negative five hundred thousand which was written in scarlet was exceptionally dazzling.

From first to last, such a huge discrepancy caused people to be greatly taken aback.

Clamorous discussions rose before gradually quieting down.

The Wolf King's strength and status made them involuntarily accept this fact.

Soon after, several assignments that came from the Wolf King caused the quietened discussions to again turn into a clamor.

The assignments were capturing wolves, gathering souls, peeling off wolf skins and processing them, along with large numbers of Gu refinement assignments; once completed, could give them a lot of battle merits.

These assignments quickly stimulated everyone's enthusiasm.

In the next few days, Fang Yuan continued to cultivate, concentrating mainly on strength path.

Because of turtle jade wolf skin Gu, his body could bear even more strength.

Several days later, Fang Yuan's strength path broke through the hundred jun strength barrier, and he had already successively received ten thousand rank one lurking soul coat Gu.

But to push to rank five, this amount was still far from enough.

Hei tribe army rested and reorganized for a week more before pulling up the camp and pushing forward towards Dong Fang tribe's defense line.

The battle began once more.

Dong Fang Yu Liang relied on tall and firm defense walls to defend tightly, and along with repeated clever plans, he was able to push off the battle to the limit, causing great trouble to Hei tribe.

But it was still very difficult for him to make up for the large gap created by the first battle.

The five defense lines Dong Fang army had built, was broken through by Hei tribe in a row.

In the end, the Dong Fang army had retreated to the final defense line - in the central zone of Cao Fu - and were firmly surrounded by Hei tribe.

"Dong Fang Yu Liang, you are surrounded, your loss is already determined. A wise man submits to fate; as long as you surrender, my army's main military advisor position will still be yours."

Hei Lou Lan stood high on his twin-headed rhino, his voice echoing throughout the battlefield.

Chapter 518: Famous

Facing Hei Lou Lan's offer of submission, Dong Fang Yu Liang went silent.

He was standing on the walls, looking at the black enemy troops, the wind blew his hair and his clothes fluttered lightly in the air.

He sighed lightly.

Even though he had many brilliant schemes and always held the initiative with his predictions, the difference between the two sides was just too overwhelming, in the end, they reached this stage.

Wisdom path was not invincible.

Throughout history, there were a great number of Gu Master path and styles, even qi path and strength path which were dominant in a point in time, did not manage to cause other paths to go into extinction, becoming the sole path of the Gu Master world.

Every path had its strengths and weaknesses.

Especially when Gu Master paths were established on the basis of resources. As times changed, and environments changed, when the resources that Gu Masters needed to cultivate dwindled, that particular path's vitality would go down.

Any Gu Master familiar with history would know that throughout the long river of time, countless paths were buried.

Speaking of which, wisdom path had been popular since the immemorial era, until this day. Even though they were always low on numbers, such an established path could be said to be independent already.

In this world, there were no invincible paths, only invincible Gu Masters.

But to be truly invincible, there were only ten in history.

Dong Fang Yu Liang was only a rank five wisdom path Gu Master, although he was at the peak of the mortal realm, he was far from invincible.

Even though he had his self created killer move, Seven Star Light, the primeval essence expenditure of it was too great, it could not be sustained. Against a huge force like Hei tribe, he was already feeling overpowered and outnumbered.

"If I was an enslavement path Gu Master, there might be a chance of salvaging it. But even enslavement path would need to be worried of beheading the leader tactic. Even Wolf King Chang Shan Yin does not dare to venture out alone, leading his wolves to leave the main troops. Thus, only by ascending to Gu Immortal can one rule above the mortal world." Dong Fang Yu Liang sighed in his heart.

At this time, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu came forward to battle.

"Wind Demon, come out and die!" He shouted out his enemy's name.

Wind Demon was furious, growling: "Hao Ji Liu, don't be arrogant!"

Saying so, he leapt from the defense walls, activating his Gu while in mid air, as two four-leaf wind blades formed, shooting out.

"All you can use are old tricks!" Water Demon laughed, not dodging as he charged head on.

Bam bam bam!

The water and wind demons had battled for dozens of rounds, they were very familiar with each other, thus, the moment they fought, it reached the climax.

Wind blades and water bullets flew on both sides, colliding in mid air as they exploded.

Wind Demon's attacks were sharp and focused on penetrating and kiting, while Water Demon engaged in frontal assault, overwhelming the enemy.

The two were established characters, now that they were engaging with each other, they were displaying great strength as the battle could not be decided easily.

The Gu Masters from both armies focused their attention on these two people.

The strength of a rank four Gu Master was well known by all, but now, it still gave them a great sense of fear and trepidation.

After a while, Water Demon gradually gained the upper hand.

Wind Demon's condition was not good, there were times where a Gu Master's strength fluctuated.

Like now, the conclusion had already been decided, being surrounded by Hei tribe heavily, Dong Fang tribe's warriors had low morale, Wind Demon was affected too.

Seeing his rival of equal strength suppressed by himself, Water Demon shouted in joy as he attacked even more fiercely.

The general was the courage of the soldiers, seeing this, Hei tribe army's morale surged, as Dong Fang alliance army sank into silence on the defense wall.

In the main tent, Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily as he sent another rank four expert into battle.

Dong Fang Yu Liang sent a person to deal with him.

But the battle between these two Gu Masters was not as intense as the battle between demons.

Not only was the commotion smaller, they even talked in the middle of battle, talking about their ancestor's time and their alliance marriage.

Dong Fang Yu Liang's expression became uglier as Hei Lou Lan's smile became deeper.

Dong Fang alliance army had low morale, the troops had lost their sense of belonging. All the forces in the alliance were starting to find a way out of their predicament.

Hei tribe army's morale was high, all the rank four experts requested to battle.

Hei Lou Lan laughed as he approved all their requests.

Quickly, before the two armies, twelve battle rings were created.

"I am Pan Ping, who will battle me?" Pan Ping carried a fierce aura as he became the thirteenth person to enter the battlefield after getting Hei Lou Lan's permission.

Dong Fang Yu Liang was silent.

By now, the rank four experts under him had mostly perished. Many experts were worried for the present and future, they were no longer giving it their all, but instead hiding their strength.

Although when the alliance was made, all the leaders and experts used the poison vow Gu, the content of the vow was not strict, there were many loopholes that could be exploited.

As the alliance leader, although they would want to tie the large tribes closely to them, other forces were not idiots. Thus the content of the poison vow had been passed down for numerous generations, created through many collective agreements.

As Pan Ping requested for battle, Dong Fang Yu Liang found that he had no one to summon already.

He thought about it before sending an order.

"What? Dong Fang alliance leader is ordering my father to battle?!" In the camp behind the defense walls, Tang Fang saw this messenger and his expression turned ugly, his eyes almost blowing fire.

In the earlier battle, in order to protect his tribesmen, Tang tribe leader was attacked by two Hei tribe Gu masters and suffered grave injuries. After that, he had been bedridden, he had not even recovered now.

"This is the alliance leader's orders, are you trying to defy it? I know your tribe leader is injured and bedridden. But there are so many bedridden tribe leaders, after getting the alliance leader's orders, didn't they participate too?" The messenger's words were rigid as he looked at Tang Fang with disdain.

"You!" Tang Fang was furious, shouting: "They are pretending to be injured, my father is truly heavily injured!"

"Alright, son, enough. As the Tang tribe leader, I have to participate in this battle." At this time, the pale Tang tribe leader walked out.

"Hmph, as long as you obey the orders." Dong Fang tribe's messenger snorted as he walked away.

"But father, your body..." Tang Fang was extremely worried.

"No matter." Tang tribe leader patted his son's shoulders: "I have been recuperating these days, my injures are mostly healed. Today's battle might be the last. If I do not participate, it would be detrimental to our tribe, and our reputation."

Tang Fang gritted his teeth: "Then you have to be careful father, sister is still with them, if there is a chance..."

"Mm, I will do my best." Tang tribe leader frowned as he walked out of the tent.

He came to the defense walls as he met Dong Fang Yu Liang, before going to the battlefield, starting the battle with Pan Ping.

Tang Fang stood at the edge of the wall, staring at his father.

"Young tribe leader, we will be fine. Although lord tribe leader still has some poison in him, today's battle is different, everyone will not go all out." A Tang tribe elder consoled.

Tang Fang looked at his father battling on par with Pan Ping, with neither giving it their all, and the worry in his heart dissipated.

But at this moment, Pan Ping burst out and drew the scimitar by his waist.

Everyone saw a bright white light flash past quickly.

The next moment, Tang tribe leader was beheaded!

"Ah, father!" Tang Fang was stunned before crying out painfully.

This had occurred too suddenly, both sides were shocked for a few breaths' time before starting to discuss fervently.

"Tang tribe leader Tang You has been taken down by me Pan Ping!" Pan Ping's eyes were shining with a bloodthirsty light as he raised Tang tribe leader's head and shouted.

Tang Fang's vision turned dark as he fainted on the spot.

"What was that?"

"I only saw a flash of light, it was too fast! I could not see anything clearly."

"I wonder what Gu or killer move Pan Ping used?"

Pan Ping killed an expert on the same level as him, he gained great fame as even the resting Fang Yuan opened his eyes slightly to give him a glance.

Northern plains was huge, it was a land of battles. Countless wars and battles created numerous experts. These experts might have some unknown trump cards that they had been hiding forever.

Although Pan Ping was a rank four Gu Master, his reputation was not very high, among the rank four Gu Master, he was not outstanding. But after this battle, he rose to fame by stepping on Tang tribe leader's corpse.

Pan Ping's expression was shining like flowers as he returned victorious.

Hei Lou Lan laughed loudly, ordering his men to bring his wine cup and gave the delicious wine to Pan Ping as a reward.

"Thank you lord alliance leader for the reward!" Pan Ping stood in the main tent, drinking the wine in one gulp, his gaze was full of anticipation as his expression was lively.

He got this Gu by accident. Once, there was a market set up by a few tribes, he saw this scimitar and thought it was beautiful, thus he bought it out of interest.

But to think that when he was toying with it, he found the secret in this scimitar.

On the blade of this scimitar, there was a cold light. This cold light was actually a mysterious Gu worm.

Pan Ping spent a lot of effort before finally refining this Gu. Although he did not know the name of this Gu, it had executed many strong foes for him, it had an extremely sharp attack.

He had great expectations for this Imperial Court contest.

Originally, during Hei tribe and Dong Fang army's first battle, he had requested to be the first to battle. At that time, he was planning on using this Gu to slay a strong enemy, gaining fame immediately.

But Tang Miao Ming called out the Wolf King Chang Shan Yin and challenged him, it obstructed his plans.

What's worse was, Fang Yuan did not go with the norm, he attacked directly and skipped the challenge, directly causing the war between both sides.

The chance that Pan Ping was looking for was gone like that. Although there were battles later, it was not the environment that Pan Ping was hoping for.

"But today's battle was a huge chance, Tang tribe leader, Tang You, is an established character. After this battle, my status will rise and I would become Hei tribe's number one general. After all, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu had greater reputation, but he had not taken down Wind Demon yet. As for Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, he is an enslavement path Gu Master, there is no point competing with him..."

Pan Ping looked around, feeling that everyone's gaze towards him had changed, the happiness in his heart rose again.

"This is the feeling of a top dog[1]. Hehe, one day, I, Pan Ping, will have my name resound all over Northern Plains!" He shouted in his heart.

[1] man above man Back

Chapter 519: Just a game

Ni Yu blessed land.

A long jade-layered walkway led the way along the lake surface towards a pavilion.

Outside the pavilion, there was a light rain and soothing wind.

Different from the outside world, the rain here fell from bottom to top. The name of Ni Yu[1], came from this.

After the female Gu immortal Tan Bi Ya, there was a new guest in the blessed land.

"Junior Hei Bai pays respect to senior Dong Fang." The person who came looked like an ordinary middle aged man, but he was a true rank six Gu Immortal.

"It has been seventy years since we last met. Back then, you were still Hei tribe leader, a step away from entering the Imperial Court."

Hei Bai stood on the stone bench, bowing slightly: "I am ashamed, back then I was greatly supported by my tribe, but I lost by one move and Liu tribe emerged victorious."

"Hehehe." Dong Fang Chang Fan laughed: "That's right, the Liu tribe leader back then, Liu Yi Feng, had unprecedented talent, he was a genius barely seen in a hundred years."

"Senior has good memory, junior is full of admiration."

Dong Fang Chang Fan shook his head: "Us wisdom path Gu Masters will always collect every single information we can get in order to make our deductions. Although Liu Yi Feng was glaringly talented, he failed when charging towards Gu Immortal realm. Among the people of that generation, the one who remained standing at the end was you, commonly known as 'Hei tribe rockman'."

"Senior is too kind, this junior was lucky."

"No need to put yourself down, becoming a Gu Immortal is as hard as ascending to heaven, out of ten thousand rank five Gu Masters, not even one might succeed. Sigh, to speak the truth, I have observed many juniors these years, and now my hopes are on this child." Dong Fang Chang Fan pointed with his right index finger, and a colorful smoke rose from the stone bench, reflecting the real-time battle situation in northern plains, Cao Fu.

Coincidentally, the two Gu Immortals saw Pan Ping flash his scimitar as he beheaded Tang tribe leader.

Hei Bai frowned, lightly gasping: "This is interesting, if I did not see wrongly, this is the sole blade Gu. Sole blade Gu is unique, once activated, it can ignore all defenses of the same level. This was created by the Gu Immortal Blade Demon, it has a strange form, merely a flash of blade light, and has to be kept on a blade. This Gu eats blades as food, and the blade it resides in will gradually shrink and turn into dust."

Dong Fang Chang Fan nodded: "That's right, sole blade Gu can reach rank six at most. Back then, Blade Demon used the rank six sole blade Gu to hold his own, no one dared to trifle with him. But eventually, he lost to Butterfly Sword Immortal. Blade Demon died in battle, and his blessed land was consumed by Butterfly Sword Immortal. The recipe of sole blade Gu was not passed down, but now there are still many sole blade Gu in the mortal realm, these were handed out when Blade Demon disguised as a mortal and travelled the world back then. It seems this lucky lad obtained one of the gifts from Blade Demon back then."

"Senior is wise, I have learnt much today." Hei Bai said with admiration.

Dong Fang Chang Fan was a famous wisdom path Gu Immortal in northern plains, he had glorious battle results his whole life, numerous Gu Immortal suffered from his schemes.

When he was born, Dong Fang tribe was already declining like the setting sun. When he became a Gu Immortal, he single handedly held them up as he made many schemes against his enemies, he had great methods and eventually caused Dong Fang tribe to rise up again.

He was a rank seven Gu Immortal, a great power in northern plains undoubtedly, and the pillar of support for Dong Fang tribe.

But now, his lifespan was at its end, he was eager to leave his inheritance. In the past, Dong Fang Chang Fan had high expectations, and many did not meet his requirements. Now, Dong Fang Yu Liang might not have met all his expectations, but he was the best candidate out of them all.

Lifespan Gu were hard to find, even for Dong Fang tribe which was a super tribe, one of the largest force in northern plains.

Of course, a part of the reason was that the righteous path Gu Immortal secretly colluded to restrict the selling of lifespan Gu to Dong Fang Chang Fan. Similarly, demonic Gu Immortals who were schemed against by Dong Fang Chang Fan hated him to the bones.

Dong Fang Chang Fan schemed against numerous people, but at the end of his life, he was ganged up on collectively by his enemies.

He was clear about this, he had offended too many Gu Immortals. Even the righteous path did not want to see him live longer.

Hei Bai understood, this meeting with Dong Fang Chang Fan would be the last time he could see this legendary Gu Immortal in northern plains.

The rainbow smoke on the stone bench displayed the battle situation perfectly, showing it to them without any lack of clarity.

Dong Fang army, while already weaker in terms of power, got into an even worse situation after Tang tribe leader was killed by Pan Ping.

Eventually, Dong Fang Yu Liang challenged Hei Lou Lan, entering the battle himself.

He wanted to use his own strength to fight for a bit of chance and hope.

But eventually, he could not emerge victorious as he and Hei Lou Lan ended in a draw.

When night descended, Hei Lou Lan ordered a collective attack.

At night, night wolves surge in battle strength. The wolf tide came waves after waves, under Fang Yuan's manipulation, they broke through Dong Fang army's final line of defense.

Dong Fang army had low morale and the troops were not united, even though Dong Fang Yu Liang made many preparations, the defensive line only lasted for seven minutes before being taken down.

Helpless, Dong Fang Yu Liang could only surrender.

At this point, Hei tribe and Dong Fang tribe's battle ended, as Hei Lou Lan and Dong Fang Yu Liang's personal grudge ended in Hei Lou Lan's victory.

"This young man, Dong Fang Yu Liang, has few flaws, except that he cares too much for his sister. In order to protect her safety, he made a portion of the troops stay at the back to protect his sister. Thus, Dong Fang army became far weaker than Hei tribe, even though they were already disadvantaged to begin with. If not for this, the first battle's victory might not have been like this. Hehehe, this is embarrassing to show you, Hei Bai."

Dong Fang Chang Fan smile lightly at this rainbow smoke.

After Hei tribe army stabilized the battle situation, they entered the camp and starting to take over captives and clean up the battlefield.

"Winning and losing is part of battle, if we failed this time, there is always next time. In my opinion, Dong Fang Yu Liang is already very outstanding. He preserved the strength of his tribe well, he did it even better than I would. His affection and protective nature towards this tribe is very precious." Hei Bai said.

"That's right." Dong Fang Chang Fan's tone was rueful: "So be it if other tribe members die, but we are all descendants of Ancestor Giant Sun. Back then when ancestor set up the Imperial Court, he had one motive, that was to weaken other tribes and preserve our bloodline. Unfortunately, even a grand existence like Giant Sun Immortal Venerable passed away when his lifespan was expended. In this world, what can truly be immortal and indestructible..."

Hei Bai did not speak, he only listened silently.

Dong Fang Chang Fan soothed his emotions, laughing softly as he stretched out his palm towards Hei Bai: "Alright, let's get to business."

"Yes." Hei Bai took out a list from his storage Gu and handed it over to Dong Fang Chang Fan.

There was a great amount of content on the list, there was a huge amount of resources listed.

Dong Fang tribe lost in this Imperial Court contest, and became Hei tribe's captive. According to Giang Sun Immortal Venerable's rules, Dong Fang tribe could pay a certain amount of resources to redeem themselves.

Dong Fang tribe and Hei tribe were super tribes, they had more than one Gu Immortal.

The contest between two giant forces, this 'Imperial Court contest' was merely a game. Most importantly, these battles would weaken other tribes and expand one's own tribe, recruiting and choosing new talents.

This grand scheme engulfing all of northern plains was naturally not created by Dong Fang tribe or Hei tribe's Gu Immortals. It was created by one of the ten supreme invincible beings, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Dong Fang Chang Fan received the list and started browsing through.

The resources on this list were not only a great amount, there were also many aspects that it touched on, like some specialty Gu worms that only Dong Fang tribe had, or some newly created Gu recipes.

But Dong Fang Chang Fan did not show any indignance, he nodded lightly and agreed: "Winner takes all, since we failed, a small price is but fair, we will go with this."

Loser pays the price, this was the rule that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable set.

In history, there were some times when tribes were unwilling to pay this price, but they all ended up being wiped out.

But now, not a single tribe dared to violate the rule.

This was the rule of northern plains' righteous path, if any tribe refused to obey it, they would be ostracized, and become the target of all others.

A giant light ring suddenly appeared in the night sky of the battlefield.

After the light ring stabilized, a giant light door of about 60 meters was formed.

The light shone across a thousand li, as it opened, a jade light path was formed.

From the door, a young female Gu Master walked out. She held a token as she landed before Hei Lou Lan under everyone's gaze.

"I am the envoy, I am here to bring back Dong Fang tribe." She said expressionlessly with a cold tone.

The two finished their business on the spot.

After checking the battle reparation, Hei Lou Lan's brows were uplifted, he had earned a fortune! Using so much resources, he could equip more Gu Masters and especially the tribes that surrendered, after taking them in, his military strength would surge by at least fifty percent of the original!

"We will meet again." Since the results were decided, Dong Fang Yu Liang had no lingering emotions, he bid farewell to Hei Lou Lan calmly and led his tribesmen on the light road, entering the door.

Because they absorbed a lot of tribes, Dong Fang tribe's size expanded by thirty percent.

"How great, even if they lost, they can still hide from the blizzard inside the blessed land!"

"There's no choice, they are a super clan, there are Gu Immortals shielding them."

"Alright, concentrate, it is a turning point for us after submitting to Hei tribe. As long as we win a few battles, our losses would be recuperated. If we are fortunate enough to enter Imperial Court blessed land and obtain those inheritances, we would have a chance of striking it rich!"

Everyone looked at the light ring on the air as they discussed.

Fang Yuan watched this silently.

This ten year blizzard involves the entire northern plains, causing numerous homes to be destroyed and countless people to rise up from battle. It was a contest of the top predators, a game that they engage in together.

Some people immerse themselves in it and chase after fame. Some cry and grief, feeling extreme pain. As for Fang Yuan, as a person within this giant game, he would watch coldly as he make his own plans.

Hehe.

Such is life.

The law of the jungle, it is truly fantastic!

[1] Reverse Rain Back

Chapter 520: Stealing Shoes (1/2)

In the camp, there was silence.

On a bright red table, books were stacked highly into a pile.

At times, wind would blow through the window and carry the fragrance of the grass with it, as it flips the top few pages of the documents.

It was a bright and sunny day outside, at times, sounds of battle horses or hump wolves could be heard from far away.

This in fact, intensified the silence in the camp.

As Ma tribe's young tribe leader, Ma Ying Jie was sitting on his cushion as he lowered his head, helping his father settle the administrative matters of the alliance army.

Ever since Ma tribe unleashed a sneak attack and exterminated Fei tribe, their largest obstacle in the heroes assembly had been removed.

Thereafter, at Tian Chuan heroes assembly, Ma tribe suppressed Cheng tribe to become the alliance leader. After taking the poison vow, Ma tribe's military force rose to six hundred thousand, they were at the peak of their strength.

After that, Ma tribe ventured west, going southwest from Tian Chuan. Along the way, they found beast groups or stubborn forces to train their troops, sharpening their battle strength. Because of the continuous battles and the absorption of defeated tribes, they expanded once more and their morale was surging.

Right now, Ma tribe had arrived at mirror lake and found an equal — Song tribe alliance army.

At the moment, Ma tribe was building their first line of defense.

"Report!" At this moment, the investigative Gu Master from outside the tent reported.

Ma Ying Jie's eyes shone with brilliance, he knew that this would definitely be some important military information, thus, he placed down his documents and called: "Come in."

The exhausted investigative Gu Master heard the call and was about to enter, but the guard outside stopped him: "Do you know the rules? Change your shoes, don't dirty the carpet inside."

The investigative Gu Master apologised profusely, after changing his shoes, he entered the tent. Upon seeing Ma Ying Jie, he kneeled down on one knee: "Subordinate greets young tribe leader. I have brought important information regarding Yu Tian."

He reported a summary of the events that happened, and after Ma Ying Jie made some inquiries, about fifteen minutes later, he left.

"Hei tribe defeated Dong Fang tribe, that is the first crucial victory they had." Ma Ying Jie's heart was slightly heavy.

The Imperial Court contest had occurred for many times, at his level, he was already clear of the rules of this game.

He knew the importance of victory, after Hei tribe defeated Dong Fang tribe, they would receive a huge amount of compensation. These compensation would include Dong Fang tribe's newest Gu recipes, as well as an ocean of battle resources. As long as they make good use of these gains, and take in the captives, Hei tribe army's battle strength would rise by five times!

"In all the past Imperial Court contests, the first battle is the most crucial. Once the first fight is won, the foundations would be earned. Those who lost the first fight would almost certainly be eliminated, very few could reverse the situation. Hei tribe has already won their first battle, while we Ma tribe and Song tribe are still at a stalemate..."

Fei Cai carefully came to the tent entrance, trying not to make any noise.

The two guarding Gu Masters gave him a look before diverting their gaze.

After Fei tribe was wiped out, the confused Fei Cai was chosen by Ma Ying Jie and luckily became his personal servant, avoiding the terrible fates of his tribesmen.

His daily job was to manage the shoes outside the tent.

Ma Ying Jie was a clean freak, every guest that entered his tent would need to change their shoes, so as to not dirty his elegant and beautiful carpet.

After every guest wears the shoes provided, Fei Cai would need to wash it before placing it back in.

But this time, it was different.

Fei Cai held the shoes worn by the investigative Gu Master and hesitated for a moment before stuffing the other pair of shoes in front of his chest.

No one noticed this tiny action of his, Fei Cai managed to leave without any problems, and after ten tents, he came to the water pond.

He squatted beside the pond as he started washing the worn shoes, he was extremely focused and did not even notice that there was one person behind him.

"Hey, big dummy, why are you so serious in washing shoes!" A small hand patted Fei Cai's shoulders roughly.

Fei Cai was shocked, turning around, he saw a girl that resembled jade with pinkish skin, and a pair of crystal clear eyes. It was Zhao Lian Yun.

Zhao Lian Yun used her 'tiger-wolf-sheep' analogy and convinced Zhao tribe leader to leave, after some hurdles, they arrived at Ma tribe camp without casualties, and were welcomed by Ma tribe leader.

Zhao tribe managed to join Ma tribe army and was highly regarded by Ma tribe higher-ups and received warm hospitality.

"It is you, Lady Xiao Yun." Fei Cai saw Zhao Lian Yun and showed an innocent smile. After his father was killed, he sunk into endless grief. By chance, he became Ma Ying Jie's personal servant, and was ostracized by the old servants, thus he did not have a single friend.

After Zhao Lian Yun made fun of him many times, but he acknowledged her as his only friend. Thus when he saw her, he was overjoyed.

"Lady Xiao Yun, I have something for you." Fei Cai lowered his volume, moving his head towards Zhao Lian Yun's ears.

Zhao Lian Yun pushed his head away, muttering unhappily: "Hey blockhead, don't come so close, do you know that there should be prudency between sexes."

Fei Cai almost fell into the water after being pushed, but he did not mind it, he secretly pulled his shirt and exposed the shoes that he were hiding, asking as if he was looking for praise: "Look, what is this?"

Zhao Lian Yun gave him a look of disdain: "A pair of stinky shoes, they've obviously been worn before. Stupid blockhead, why are you so dumb, you actually gave me something like this. It doesn't even fit me, and I wouldn't wear this pair of stinky shoes anyway!"

Fei Cai said: "Lady Xiao Yun, didn't you say you were lacking primeval stones earlier. This pair of shoes is exquisite and beautiful, we can sell it in the black market and exchange it for primeval stones."

Zhao Lian Yun's brows lifted, looking at Fei Cai in another light: "Oh wow, blockhead, you actually thought of abusing your position and smuggling public property? Amazing, I never thought you would think of this. But how much can this pair of shoes sell for? My daily pocket money is ten times of the shoes. I appreciate it, but you should sell it. Change your tattered and dirty clothes."

Fei Cai rubbed his nose, shaking his head: "No need, my clothes are still wearable. Actually, I did not think of this. Those old servants always do this, since there is a large number of shoes constantly worn by different Gu Masters, and lord young tribe leader loves cleanliness so much, he always changes the shoes together at set intervals."

Zhao Lian Yun nodded.

Snakes and rats have their own way of living. Servants might have low statuses, but they also have their own way of living.

Especially someone like Fei Cai, although he is a servant and lost his freedom, he got close to Ma Ying Jie and was most likely the first person to receive information from Ma tribe higher-ups.

Zhao tribe had entered Ma tribe's army, Zhao Lian Yun purposely got close to Fei Cai because she also had the intentions of gathering intel.

At this time, a commotion could be heard.

"Where is Fei Cai? Get out here now!"

"Fei Cai, you're in trouble now, you dared to take young tribe leader's shoes."

"Young tribe leader wanted to walk around the camp, but realized his shoes were gone. Fei Cai, you are too daring, you are unforgivable!"

A bunch of old servants shouted arrogantly, coming out of the entrance as they searched for Fei Cai's whereabouts.

Fei cai's expression paled: "Oh no, I have been discovered. Lady Xiao Yun, quickly leave, this has nothing to do with you. I cannot implicate you, I will go ask for forgiveness from young tribe leader."

"Forgiveness my ass!" Zhao Lian Yun shouted, her expression turning ugly: "You fool, you have been plotted against and you don't even know it! Quickly follow me and run."

"Ah?" Fei Cai had no idea what's going on, but as Zhao Lian Yun pulled him, they entered a narrow alley.

"Damn it, this path has been blocked off." Zhao Lian Yun relied on her familiarity of the area and brought Fei Cai around, finding four exits, but three were blocked.

"Lady Xiao Yun, quickly go, it will be too late otherwise!" Fei Cai was getting dizzy from moving around, he had lost his sense of direction. He was anxious as he did not want to get his only friend into trouble.

Zhao Lian Yun stomped her feet in anger, howling in her heart: "Was it easy for me to find an insider to provide information?! In this day and age, where can I find such a dummy like Fei Cai? These old servants are all shrewd snakes, they will request for money when I want a bit of information, and they would even give half-truth information. Hmph! They are jealous of this newcomer Fei Cai and wants to get rid of him. As expected, any place with humans will have conflicts, and thus schemes. No way! I cannot take this lying down, you are courting death if you want to harm my informant!"

Zhao Lian Yun's expression was full of uncertainty as she tried her best to think of a solution, while the old servants' voices could be heard.

"He's not here, I've searched the water pond, he's not there either!"

"Did he leave?"

"How can that be, we were following him, I'm sure he came here."

"We have not searched there yet, go."

Hearing the old servants' footsteps, Zhao Lian Yun thought of a solution amidst the anxiety.

"Big dummy, you are truly lucky, I just bought some silk from the market." Zhao Lian Yun said as she took out some high grade silk from her pockets.

This silk was meant to be made into clothes for her.

"Big dummy, listen to my instructions and do as I say, this might benefit you greatly!" Zhao Lian Yun placed the silk into Fei Cai's hands.

"Ah?" Fei Cai was dumbstruck.

Zhao Lian Yun quickly told him about her plans.

After a dozen breaths' time, Fei Cai walked out and was discovered by the servants.

They were overjoyed, encircling him as Fei Cai clenched his fists, beating them to a pulp like he was crazy.

"He's revolting, revolting, this dog slave dared to attack us seniors!"

"Fei Cai, you are in huge trouble, young tribe leader is looking for you, we came to arrest you but you dared to resist!"

Fei Cai shouted: "Young tribe leader is looking for me, I will go on my own. Don't touch me with your filthy hands you lowly scum!"

Chapter 521: Stealing Shoes (2/2)

The slaves were old while Fei Cai was acting like a crazed man; for the moment, the slaves could only surround Fei Cai without daring to go forward.

Fei Cai stared with wide, furious eyes as he kicked an old slave in front of him: "Filthy bastard, I am going to pay respects to young tribe leader, don't block my way."

The old slaves felt ashamed and furious, sinister glint flashed past their eyes but they still did not dare to go forward.

They had already noticed a bulge in Fei Cai's clothes. Many sneered in disdain in their hearts: 'This stupid kid really has the courage to steal! It doesn't matter if he stole shoes, but he actually stole the young tribe leader's shoes, hahaha, his luck is truly bad. I originally wanted him to be relocated to cleaning the latrine, but now this kid might even lose his little life. Serves him right! Is it so easy to become young tribe leader's personal servant?'

Fei Cai walked towards young tribe leader's tent while being surrounded by the old slaves.

The two Gu Masters guarding the tent saw Fei Cai and looked at him as if he was a dead person.

Ma Ying Jie stood at the entrance of the tent with a solemn expression. He had been tired of handling the various affairs and wanted to take a walk outside, but he found that his shoes had disappeared.

He called for his old personal servant, and the old slave told him the shoes were very possibly stolen by the new young slave to possibly sell them for money. The old slave also informed Ma Ying Jie that this was not the first time Fei Cai had stolen.

Ma Ying Jie was naturally furious. He had never expected that his kindness would bring in a thief.

Fei Cai was extremely anxious with panic already filling his mind, but he firmly remembered Zhao Lian Yun's instructions, and walked towards Ma Ying Jie with his head high like a valiant hero.

Ma Ying Jie was secretly amazed at this sight.

Those old slaves that were following Fei Cai to keep an eye on him, instead looked like they were escorting him. More importantly, Fei Cai did not appear panicked, was it not him who stole the shoes?

Unwittingly, the fury in Ma Ying Jie was replaced by curiosity and doubts.

"Subordinate greets young tribe leader." Fei Cai kneeled on the ground and greeted with a clear voice.

Ma Ying Jie looked at Fei Cai and shouted in an displeased voice: "My shoes, did you steal them?"

"I would never dare to steal lord's shoes even if I had a hundred guts." Fei Cai denied flatly.

"He is lying, his clothes are bulging, he has something there, we will know once we look at it!" The old slaves immediately shouted from behind.

Fei Cai snorted and opened his shirt, revealing a ball of snowy-white, high grade silk.

He carefully took out the silk and opened it, revealing the shoes inside.

Ma Ying Jie looked at this pair of shoes and knew it was the pair which he wore, and he couldn't help but coldly smiled: "Great, great, the proof is here, a thief having such confidence is really hard to come by."

"I implore young tribe leader to investigate clearly." Fei Cai did not refute and placed the shoes on the ground respectfully. He then placed his forehead on the ground like he was willing to take on any punishment.

"Lord young tribe leader, there is clear evidence, please punish this vile bastard fiercely!"

"Yes, he actually dared to steal young tribe leader's shoes. He might steal many more things later on."

"He is such a thief, we should just cut off his hands!"

The old slaves continued to speak extremely sinister words; Fei Cai's heart trembled but remembering Zhao Lian Yun's words, he did not retort.

This scene caused Ma Ying Jie to be somewhat interested.

Killing a slave was nothing, but Ma Ying Jie had always praised himself as 'wise and benevolent' to restrict himself so that when he took over the tribe in the future, he could become a wise ruler of the generation.

Especially now that Ma tribe had become the head of a huge army, their every move was being paid attention to by others. Rashly killing a slave just because of a small matter like stealing shoes, would it not be spread as brutal?

Ma Ying Jie had such misgivings in his heart.

A good reputation was easy to build but difficult to maintain.

Thereupon, he asked: "I have always dealt with things fairly. Fei Cai, I will give you a chance to explain yourself."

Fei Cai immediately let out a breath of relief, he had been waiting for these words just like Zhao Lian Yun instructed him. This gave him a huge confidence and he decided he would reply exactly according to Zhao Lian Yun's instructions.

"My father died because of the internal strife in the tribe, so young tribe leader obliterating Fei tribe can be said to have taken revenge for me. Young tribe leader is so wise and benevolent, how could I do a thing like returning benevolence with enmity?"

When Ma Ying Jie heard the words 'wise and benevolent', his mood immediately took a turn for the better as he asked in a gentle voice: "Hmm, then do you have some ulterior motives?"

Fei Cai, however, shook his head: "No ulterior motives, it is just that I wanted to repay young tribe leader. But what can I do? I am only a mortal, I have no ways to break through the enemy defense lines for young tribe leader. I am very stupid, I cannot bring forward any plans to young tribe leader. I am only your personal servant who can only clean shoes and place them properly. I thought in young tribe leader's place — these shoes have been put outside for so long that young tribe leader's feet might become cold when you wear them, right? So I used all my savings to buy this real silk to cover young tribe leader's shoes and held it in my clothes. With this, young tribe leader won't feel cold when you wear them."

"Eh? So it was like that!" Ma Ying Jie was greatly surprised.

He was obsessed with cleanliness and if Fei Cai had directly held the shoes in his clothes, he would instead be disgusted.

But covering the shoes with silk was different.

Moreover this was a genuine high grade silk. There should not be anyone who used such materials to cover shoes, right?

'This Fei Cai is really a good servant, he is actually so considerate.' Ma Ying Jie's thoughts moved and the gaze he looked at Fei Cai quietly changed.

If what Fei Cai said was true, his devotion was really overwhelming!

At this moment, Fei Cai suddenly kowtowed: "Young tribe leader, I have sinned!"

"Eh? What sin have you committed?" Ma Ying Jie looked at Fei Cai with a clear smile on his face.

Fei Cai replied: "I only thought of keeping the shoes warm for young tribe leader, but forgot it would be extremely inconvenient for you when you go out. I have sinned, please punish me!"

Ma Ying Jie heaved a sigh: "It is not like I only have one pair of shoes, but because I saw that the pair I usually wore had disappeared, I called you over. It is fortunate, I nearly blamed my loyal servant."

"Lord young tribe leader, don't listen to his words!"

"Lord young tribe leader, this kid is deceiving you, he is very crafty and is lying to you!!"

The old slaves experienced a reversal of fortune when they saw the normally stupid Fei Cai speak with such a glib tongue, and thus they began to hurriedly shout.

Fei Cai spoke again at this moment: "Young tribe leader, please inspect clearly. There is indeed a matter of stealing shoes, but I have never done it. Instead, it was these old slaves who did it many times. After I was appointed to this post, these old slaves incited me many times, but I never listened, thus they resent me. I am not afraid of being investigated and also not afraid of punishment. I earnestly request young tribe leader to investigate clearly and give me justice!"

Fei Cai was naturally not afraid of investigation as this was the first time he had stolen shoes!

He had heard the old slaves 'carelessly' speaking that a pair of the finest shoes could sell for a high price.

Fei Cai was ignorant; he had followed the young tribe leader for so long but had not paid attention to the look of the shoes young tribe leader wore, and thus was easily plotted against by the old slaves.

Fortunately, he met a crucial person during the crucial time. Zhao Lian Yun became his savior, and under her instructions, Fei Cai made a comeback and averted danger.

When the old slaves heard the request for investigation, their face turned as pale as paper.

Gu Masters had plenty of methods and could easily get to the bottom of this trivial affair.

These old slaves were already regretting their actions, never having expected for them to be the ones landing in deep trouble!

Ma Ying Jie noticed the change in the expressions of the old slaves, and became seventy-eighty percent convinced in Fei Cai. But since his resolve was to become a 'wise ruler', he naturally could not rashly decide based on his thoughts.

Immediately, he summoned an investigative Gu Master and commanded him to get to the bottom of this affair.

Receiving Ma Ying Jie's personal order, the investigative Gu Master investigated enthusiastically. In only five minutes of time, the truth of the matter was brought to light.

As the facts were disclosed, the old slaves kneeled on the ground and began weeping and howling with their bodies trembling in fear, asking the young tribe leader to forgive them.

Ma Ying Jie snorted: "Fawning upon your superiors and bullying your subordinates, you slaves actually dared to deceive me! You should all be put to death, but considering the many years you have served me, and that some of you even having served me since I was a child and also served my subordinates, I will forgive your cheap lives and send you to the supply camp to serve my army. Clean the faeces and latrine!"

"Thank you young tribe leader for showing mercy!" The old slaves kowtowed like they were pounding garlic, extremely thankful for this.

"As for you..." Ma Ying Jie looked at Fei Cai and smiled playfully, "You dared to steal my shoes, you truly are extremely daring! From now on, you shall be punished to be the head of the slaves and redeem yourself by serving me properly!"

Fei Cai was stumped for a long time before he came to his senses; Ma Ying Jie's punishment was actually a promotion!

He immediately kowtowed and expressed his thanks.

Ma Ying Jie laughed heartily and waved his hand: "Alright, now get lost, think properly on the ways to serve me!"

"Yes, my lord." Fei Cai left with a dazed expression the whole way.

Only after a long while did he become clear, he had profited from the disaster and became the head of the slaves!

"This is all thanks to Lady Xiao Yun... ah, right, Lady Xiao Yun told me to report to her quickly if everything went alright." Fei Cai shook his head and promptly change direction towards the secret place.

"What, you actually became the head of the slaves?" Zhao Lian Yun's eyes involuntarily widened when she heard this news, and looked at Fei Cai with surprise.

Her plan might have been ingenious but also carried risks in that it depended completely on Ma Ying Jie's mood.

If Ma Ying Jie was in a bad mood, he would only need to issue a death command and Fei Cai would be done for. But clearly, this big dummy was quite lucky and not only were there no accidents, he even got appointed as the head of the slaves.

Chapter 522: Rank Five Amplify Effect Gu

Although servants were servants, the one tasked to take care of Ma tribe's young tribe leader was definitely a crucial person that was closely related to the tribe in many ways. Having such a role, if the low rank Gu Masters want to find out information about the higher-ups, they would need to go through the servant leader.

"What a huge profit, he became the servant leader, I am truly a genius!" Zhao Lian Yun laughed furiously in her heart, she did not waste her efforts after all.

She stared at Fei Cai with shining eyes, saying gently: "Big dummy, after you become the servant leader, you have to work hard."

Fei Cai shuddered at once, replying truthfully: "Lady Xiao Yun, I don't know why, but that tone of yours made me really nervous."

Zhao Lian Yun immediately changed her expression, kicking Fei Cai's leg as she screamed: "You idiot, now that you are the servant leader, your situation is more precarious than before. I wonder how many people will target you, and among them, there might even be vile and evil Gu Masters."

Fei Cai was shocked: "Then what should I do?"

"Hmph, you're lucky to have a friend like me. As long as you listen to what I say, I assure you, you will live blissfully." Zhao Lian Yun stretched out her hand, wanting to pat Fei Cai's shoulders, but found out that she was too short.

She immediately opened her mouth: "Quick, squat down now."

Fei Cai squatted down obediently, and Zhao Lian Yun succeeded in patting his shoulder, she nodded her tiny head in satisfaction, speaking in an old and experienced tone: "Do you know what to do next?"

Fei Cai naturally shook his head.

"Hmph, you idiot." Zhao Lian Yun snorted: "Since you are the servant leader now, and those old servants have already been sent away, you have to recruit new subordinates first. Otherwise, how can you handle everything alone?"

"Oh? You are extremely right!" Fei Cai realized at once, nodding in agreement.

Zhao Lian Yun snorted again: "But just this is not enough. You need to learn about the young tribe leader's likes, dislikes, and lifestyle habits. You have to ask those old servants for these information."

"What? Ask them? Will they tell me?" Fei Cai stared with wide opened eyes.

Zhao Lian Yun snickered: "You are now the servant leader, your status is different already. They are the lowest of slaves, I'm sure they are afraid of you taking revenge now. If you ask them, they are sure to tell you everything. Of course, if they do not know what is good for them, I have my ways of making them spill everything obediently!"

"Oh."

Zhao Lian Yun looked at Fei Cai's blank expression and rolled her eyes uncontrollably.

Her thoughts had already drifted far away: 'I am not a person of this world, hmph, there are simply too many ways to make these stinking men talk. As long as we learn about Ma Ying Jie's habits and please him accordingly, Fei Cai's current position would definitely be stable. Hehe...'

Cao Fu, Hei tribe camp.

All sorts of tents and Gu houses covered the wide grassland, as tribe flags fluttered in the wind, large numbers of Gu Masters entered and exited. If one looked from above, they would resemble a nest of ants.

In the supply camp, Fang Yuan held the east window Gu as he checked the resources silently.

The female Gu Master in charge of attending to him stayed focused as she stood at one side, waiting for Fang Yuan to make his decision at any moment.

Ever since they received Dong Fang tribe's reparations, the resources that could be exchanged for using battle merits had increased by more than ten times.

Of course, among these resources, not all of them were the compensation from war, other than Hei tribe's previous accumulation, there were also the resources offered by tribes who surrendered and joined the Hei tribe alliance army.

Just a few days ago, Hei Lou Lan organised another alliance meeting, and ordered the newly joined tribe leaders to make the poison vow.

To prevent the good things from being exchanged by others, once the resources were collated, Fang Yuan entered the supply camp at once.

Even Shadow Sword Expert and others, after they joined Hei tribe army, could not affect Fang Yuan's status of being second to only Hei Lou Lan.

Fang Yuan had such authority, the others definitely had issues with it, but no one dared to reprimand him in public.

"Oh? There's a rank four self-reliance Gu?" Fang Yuan's heart was moved, among these resources, he found the Gu that he had greatly desired.

Self-reliance Gu was rather precious, Fang Yuan had a rank three version of it in Southern Border, but after coming to Northern Plains, it was suppressed to rank two. Fang Yuan did not have the relevant Gu recipe, he could not advance it further.

Earlier, he had found a self-reliance Gu in Hei tribe's resources, but it was rank two. Without a choice, he planned to collect the Gu recipe and use these two Gu as the foundation to refine the higher rank Gu.

But this way, it would take eons for him to get a high rank self-reliance Gu. If his luck was bad and he failed the refinement several times, the duration would be prolonged further.

Now, he found this rank four self-reliance Gu, without doubt, he had to get it!

Other than rank four self-reliance Gu, he also found the rank four charging crash Gu. But he had already bought the rank three vertical charge and horizontal crash Gu earlier, and had succeeded in refining them into a rank four charging crash Gu.

Diverting his attention from charging crash Gu, Fang Yuan found several good things, especially Dong Fang tribe's unique Gu worms.

Even with his five hundred years of experience, Fang Yuan was still very interested upon seeing these things.

What attracted him the most was the refine essence spirit Gu.

If it was categorised, this should be a healing Gu worm.

Refine essence spirit Gu could convert the essence of a Gu Master's physical flesh into a mysterious form of energy that could nurture and heal the soul.

There were many Gu worms that could heal the soul, but this refine essence spirit Gu was far superior to its peers. Dong Fang Yu Liang had such a Gu worm, and it was a huge support to his wisdom path deductions.

As for Fang Yuan, this Gu suited him even more.

Different from Dong Fang Yu Liang, Fang Yuan was a dual enslavement and strength path cultivator, his body was strong and his mind was sharp, his soul often felt weakness and exhaustion from commanding the beast groups. The refine essence spirit Gu could be the perfect bridge between his two paths!

Among the resources, other than refine essence spirit Gu, there was also the recipe for it, Fang Yuan took them all.

According to rumors, this Gu recipe was especially created by Dong Fang tribe's Gu Immortal Dong Fang Chang Fan in order to cultivate wisdom path. This meant that Dong Fang tribe had much greater attainments in wisdom path than others.

After Fang Yuan obtains this recipe, as well as the refine essence spirit Gu, it would be the same as obtaining Dong Fang tribe's experimental results for himself.

Gu worms only need one thought from the Gu Master to self-detonate. If this was during normal times, it would not be so easy for Fang Yuan to obtain refine essence spirit Gu.

The Imperial Court competition every ten years was not only a purification and refinement process to weed out the weak, it also assisted in the interactions between all the large forces.

The way of Gu originated from the Immemorial Antiquity era, and Ren Zu was the first Gu Master who used Gu worms. After that, there was the Remote Antiquity era, Olden Antiquity era, Medieval Antiquity era, followed by the Late Antiquity era.

Until today, the way of Gu prospered, in fact it was blooming all over the world, countless paths were created from all the eras like ripples in the river of time, numerous paths flourished at times while vanishing at others.

But because of the harsh living environment, the concept of trading was not very popular with people, all the large forces liked to do their own research and treasured their findings, keeping it from others.

Back then, one of the invincible venerables, Giant Sun, felt this and set up this huge arena. Because of the battle reparations, the Huang Jin family could pass on their learning throughout the ages, grasping the overlord position of Northern Plains throughout history without declining.

After countless Imperial Court battles, Northern Plains became the publicly acclaimed strongest region out of the five in terms of fighting strength.

"But if we look at total power, Central Continent is the strongest, followed by Northern Plains." Fang Yuan had his previous life's memories, he understood clearly the strength of the five regions.

During the battle of the five regions, Northern Plains was the region which resisted Central Continent most fiercely. The other three regions, although having the same terrain advantage as Northern Plains, were suppressed fiercely by Central Continent.

Only Northern Plains managed to organise troops to fight back, invading Central Continent in return.

"Northern Plains has such great strength all thanks to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's setup. Because he used battles and war, while restricting it to a certain level, it allowed Northern Plains to hone the greatest fighting strength. Unfortunately, his plans were still too restricted, he only cared about his bloodline's benefits. In contrast, Central Continent was strong due to their systemic reforms, it was an advantage that stemmed from their core."

Fang Yuan came from Earth, he had a unique perspective, together with his five hundred years of experience, he had a clear understanding towards the true nature of society.

"Eh, there are over a dozen amplify effect Gu?" Fang Yuan collected his scattered thoughts as he continued looking at the list, finding a new surprise.

Amplify effect Gu was from the rule path, it was used to supplement other Gu worms, to amplify the effects of the chosen Gu worm.

As for the amplification level, it would depend on the rank of the amplify effect Gu. The higher the rank, the greater the effect. Of course, the drawback was that the Gu Master's primeval essence expenditure would be relatively higher.

Amplify effect Gu was very popular among Gu Masters, because it could be used in any path.

Fire path Gu Masters could use it, water path Gu Masters could use it, and for Fang Yuan, both his enslavement and strength paths could use amplify effect Gu.

Among Hei tribe's resources, there was only one rank five amplify effect Gu! There were also one rank four, three rank three, and the rest of the amplify effect Gu were rank two.

Fang Yuan had to pick the best one, he chose the rank five amplify effect Gu, it would boost the effectiveness of a Gu worm by five times!

But this way, a new problem occurred.

"Lord Wolf King, you want to take so many Gu, your battle merits might not be enough..." The female Gu Master in charge reminded him as she chose her words carefully.

"Ah, I know. After all one of the rank five Gu is amplify effect Gu. That refine essence spirit Gu is also Dong Fang tribe's specialty Gu worm." Fang Yuan's words were very understanding and accommodating.

But his next sentence was not like this: "Never mind if I do not have enough battle merits, just credit another five hundred thousand."

"Ah?" The female Gu Master was shocked, she carefully said: "Lord, you still owe around three hundred thousand of the previous five hundred thousand battle merits you borrowed. According to the rules, you have to pay them first before borrowing again."

Fang Yuan raised his brows, saying nonchalantly: "So what, rules are made by men, since they can be made, they can be altered. I'll borrow another five hundred thousand, no, eight hundred thousand! I will explain to Hei Lou Lan personally, now give me the goods!"

Chapter 523: Tai Bai Yun Sheng

The weather was gradually starting to get cold and gales started blowing over the grassland causing the beast groups to become fretful.

The aura of the ten year blizzard was already manifesting.

And in the majestic northern plains, heroes were rising and vying for supremacy causing the flames of war to burn everywhere.

Mirror lake.

Ma tribe and Song tribe had officially started their battle.

Both of them had erected three to four defense lines before starting this confrontation.

In Ma tribe's main tent, Ma tribe leader Ma Shang Feng was in the main seat looking with a heavy gaze at Song tribe's dense battle formation that was surging battle intent; Ma tribe's military force was stronger than theirs, but it would not be easy getting the victory.

"Lord alliance leader, please send me out to challenge enemy general and raise our army's prestige!"

"Alliance leader, Fei Sheng requests to be sent to battle."

"The first battle belongs to me, no one shall compete with me!"

Gu Masters were very impatient and eager as they requested to be sent to battle one after another,

Ma Shang Feng looked around him before hesitating at Fei Sheng and Cheng Hu.

The two were both rank four Gu Masters. Fei Sheng cultivated wood path and had been taken in by Ma tribe after they annexed Fei tribe. Cheng Hu cultivation transformation path and came from Cheng tribe. Cheng tribe was subjugated by Ma tribe during heroes assembly and was now the second most influential force in Ma tribe army.

Ma Shang Feng pondered and then smiled towards Cheng Hu: "Cheng Hu, you shall go first and stimulate my army's morale."

Cheng Hu was overjoyed as he hurriedly bowed and rushed towards the frontline.

"Hah, I am Cheng Hu, who dares to approach their death?" Cheng Hu challenged loudly.

"Arrogant! Let me Su Yi teach you a lesson!" A rank four expert flew out of Song tribe army.

Cheng Hu did not say anything else but directly pounced towards the other person.

Bam bam bam...

The two were incomparably valiant and attacked with grand momentum. For a moment, the stronger and the weaker side could not be determined; the two continued to exchange moves, sending rocks, grass and mud flying around in their battle ring.

The two armies concentrated on the battle with all their attention.

Lower ranked Gu Masters felt their heart shaking, while the upper ranked Gu Master experts were fired up.

Northern plains was filled with many brave heroes and the blood of warriors permeated the bones of their Gu Master!

"Alliance leader, Fei Sheng requests to be sent to battle!" Fei Sheng shouted with a fierce glint in his eyes. He was a newly subjugated person and was filled with enthusiasm to show his loyalty.

Ma Shang Feng nodded with a smile.

Fei Sheng went to the battlefield and Song tribe army also sent their expert to battle him.

The two had just exchanged three moves when at the other battle ring, Cheng Hu suddenly roared, his whole body giving off dazzling orange light.

After the orange light dispersed, he had unexpectedly transformed into a striped tiger king, the size of an elephant!

Cheng Hu was a transformation path Gu Master and could change parts of his body into a tiger tail, tiger claws, tiger skin and so on. The complete transformation was a killer move!

This was also the superiority of transformation path — every transformation path Gu Master possessed at least one killer move as long as they collected the respective Gu worms!

Su Yi turned pale with fright and started to retreat in panic.

The tiger king pounced on him; Su Yi frantically activated his movement Gu and narrowly dodged this attack.

The tiger king swung his tail without turning around; the tail lashed through the air like a steel whip, producing an explosive sound through the air.

Su Yi quickly activated his defense Gu which created a light barrier over his whole body.

But the tiger whip was very powerful and as it fell on the light barrier, the barrier was broken in an instant.

The defense Gu died and Su Yi spurted out a large mouthful of blood due to the backlash. He hurriedly tried to retreat, but it was too late.

An intense bloody wind pounced on his face and the next moment he only saw a huge tiger mouth shrouding over his head.

Crack!

The tiger king directly bit apart Su Yi's head.

Cheng Hu won, obtaining the first victory for Ma tribe!

Song tribe's higher ups were slightly moved while Ma tribe's troops rejoiced.

'Victory! A great start means half the success! Today, my army will definitely win!' In the main tent, Ma Ying Jie clenched his fists, an extraordinary light flashing past his eyes as his spirits roused to the limit.

And on another battlefield...

In the vast battlefield, one side was shouting in high spirits with their banners fluttering grandly in the air. While the other side's army formation was shaking, their morale low and was already showing signs of defeat.

"Alliance leader Luo, the enemy's momentum is too fierce, we can't hold them back!"

"We need to retreat..."

"A commander needs to be able to judge the situation properly. Right now, Liu tribe's experts are like tigers, our army truly cannot match them."

The several higher ranked Gu Masters shouted hurriedly, all of them panicked.

Luo Bo Jun looked around him and smiled bitterly: "Retreat? Tell me, where can we still retreat to? This is already our last defense line. Sigh... forget it, since the battle with Liu Wen Wu started, which of our defense lines could hold for more than three days? They are way too strong, we might as well surrender!"

In the first battle, Luo Bo Jun was heavily injured by Liu Wen Wu, Mo Shi Kuang and others; he had yet to recover from it.

These days, Luo tribe army kept on being defeated again and again, no matter how much efforts he made, he was unable to reverse the situation. Now, as he completely realized the enormous gap between the two sides, he became disheartened and had already lost any intent to battle.

The higher ranked Gu Masters let out a sigh of relief at this. Because of poison vow, they could not easily say it, but since Luo Bo Jun himself mentioned surrendering, there was no problem.

The command to surrender was quickly spread and the battle also soon calmed down.

"Hahaha, didn't I say it, as long as we three brothers join hands, we can rule the world!" Mo Shi Kuang laughed heartily, extremely proud of himself.

Liu Wen Wu also laughed, his heart filled with huge joy.

Liu tribe alliance had won their first battle!

Now, they would annex the enemy army, take in the captives and increase their strength before continuing forward!

　　...

Meng Qiu.

The leopard group hissed and growled as they fought a bloody battle with rat group.

The great army of Gu Masters of the both sides instead became a background.

Nu Er Tu held his hands behind his back with his head high; mutated leopards moved beside him, showing their dignity and prestige.

By contrast, his opponent Jiang Bao Ya - who was publicly proclaimed as one of the enslavement path masters of northern plains - was sweating greatly and was as pale as paper.

"Jiang Bao Ya, you have already lost. Do you know how you lost? Your rat group's scale is too large, reaching six hundred and fifty thousand in numbers. Troops are valued for their quality not for their numbers, it is the same with beast groups as well. Now, quietly become a stepping stone for my name to spread in northern plains!" Nu Er Tu lightly spoke but his tranquil voice resounded within everyone's ears.

"No, I haven't lost yet, I still have my trump card!" Jiang Bao Ya let out a hysterical shout, "I will let you gain a first hand experience in my enslavement path killer move which I have never displayed before — Rat Epidemic!"

The moment he finished speaking, hundreds of thousands of rats self-destructed at the same time.

The leopard group suffered disastrous casualties in this chain explosion.

The ground slightly shook, turfs were flipped over, soil and stones splattered everywhere, and huge amount of yellow poison gas started appearing.

The surviving leopard group was covered by this poison gas, immediately becoming sickly with their movement slowed down; their battle strength had sharply fallen.

By contrast, Jiang Bao Ya's rat group moved around in this yellow poison gas without being affected.

"Hahaha, the final winner is me, Jiang Bao Ya! Young man, you want to step on my position, keep on training for five hundred years more!" Jiang Bao Ya howled with laughter.

"Hmph! I had intended to keep on hiding it, but since you want to die, don't blame me." Nu Er Tu snorted, a sinister smile appearing on his face.

He suddenly shouted: "Killer move — Leopard Dash!"

Howl!

Leopard group howled and unfolded an unmatchable mad charge.

"This?!" Jiang Bao Ya's eyes opened wide, the leopard group's battle strength had surged by over two times, furthermore their speed increased by an astonishing eight times!

Under everyone's dumbfounded look, the leopard group quickly charged out of the area covered by the yellow poison gas and breathed in fresh air, before charging forward like a terrifying tsunami, swallowing and engulfing everything!

　　...

Du Jiao.

A large battle had already ended.

Fire blazed towards the sky, the whole battlefield covered by raging inferno.

A Gu Master stood loftily in the inferno like a fire deity.

He played with the fire in his hand, changing it into all kinds of shapes as he looked at the surrounding Gu Masters with his narrow eyes and spoke, his voice appearing extremely cruel and cold in the blazing inferno: "It is your honor to be defeated by my supreme fire path. Surrender, otherwise... all of you and this lowly grass shall turn into ashes."

The surrounding Gu Masters looked dejectedly at each other.

After few breaths of time, they kneeled one after another.

"I... we... surrender..."

　

　...

After Hei tribe obtained the first victory against Dong Fang tribe, the curtains to many large battles, that had started over Northern Plains, also fell one after another.

The defeated did not lose everything; some surrendered and some ran away choosing to side with another force. This was only the initial stage of the struggle for Imperial Court, they still had hope and chance.

The winners swallowed the weak, obtaining huge amounts of war reparations and expanding themself.

The countless corpses of beast groups, Gu Masters and ordinary mortals instead became nourishments for the grassland, and in the future would sink down under the snowy land, doomed for eternity.

Winner takes all!

After resting and reorganizing for over ten days at Cao Fu, Hei Lou Lan finished absorbing the captives, expanding his military strength by sixty percent and resumed the expedition.

This time, his target was Guan Xi.

The Gu tribe[1] army stationed there had weak military strength and thus became the optimum target for Hei Lou Lan to expand his force.

Seven days later, Hei tribe army confronted Gu tribe army.

Gu tribe suffered a huge defeat at the first battle. Gu tribe alliance leader Gu Guo Long resolutely gave the order to abandon their three defense lines without using them and retreated to their tribe's main camp.

Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily as he led his army with a crushing momentum.

But at the final battlefield, he was dumbstruck and asked his subordinates: "How is there a mountain here?"

Gu tribe army might be weak but they had their own ways. They built up a mountain by piling stones and garrisoned on the mountain, with countless traps set around the foot of the mountain. They occupied the high ground, having huge geographical advantage. Their intention to defend to the death was abundantly clear.

Hei tribe army attacked several times but were defeated every time, leaving behind large numbers of corpses.

Fang Yuan looked at the battlefield with indifference and did not use his full strength in mobilizing the wolf group, only doing it to show he was putting some effort. Adding in that there were many trees and undergrowth on the mountain, the wolf group could not show their strength properly and were instead separated and killed. Thus, the battle situation might be progressing but it was very slow.

Above all, Gu tribe army was still continuing to add in stones to the mountain, making this mountain become taller and taller.

Hei Lou Lan was furious: "Gu Guo Long is as obstinate as the rumors said. After I win, I will definitely step on him to death!"

However, the situation was still not optimistic.

Just the rocks dropped by mere mortals possessed the strength of a rank one Gu when dropped from such a height.

"If I had known this earlier, I would not have come here to chew on such a hard bone!" Hei Lou Lan had the intent to retreat, but right at this time, a person walked out of the camp.

This person held a letter as he came in front of Hei Lou Lan: "This old man Tai Bai Yun Sheng received benefactor's letter and came to lend you a hand."

Hei Lou Lan was joyous as he grabbed this person's hands: "With old sir helping us, we can definitely succeed!"

[1] Looks slightly confusing I know. Back

Chapter 524: Number one in prestige and merit

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was tall with a strangely ancient appearance. The hair near his temples had turned white and his face was filled with deep wrinkles.

He was already over eighty but his eyes were not dim and blurred, instead had a gentle look that seemed to pity the fate of mankind along with a calmness that had seen through the secular world.

Since he was seven, he had been determined to travel the northern plains to help common people.

His life was full of turmoil, as he was frequently toyed by fate. He became an enslaved Gu Master after his tribe was annihilated, then he was betrayed by his wife and became a captive of variant men. Then in a fortuitous encounter, he obtained a time path Gu Immortal's inheritance and was rescued by his brothers when he was at the verge of death...

Now, he had already become a living legend.

Although he was a loner, he was publicly accepted as a great righteous path Gu Master. His benevolence reputation had entered the depths of northern plains' people, the level of his prestige far surpassing people like Chang Shan Yin, Hei Lou Lan and Liu Wen Wu.

Right as Hei Lou Lan was at his wit's end considering the battle situation and had the thought of retreating, Tai Bai Yun Sheng came to the camp by himself, holding a letter in his hand.

Hei Lou Lan read the letter and immediately realized the reason.

Back then, Hei tribe's supreme elder Hei Bai took a fancy to Tai Bai Yun Sheng, guiding and rescuing him many times. Now that Hei tribe army had fallen into a predicament, Hei Bai who had been secretly observing all along sent a letter to Tai Bai Yun Sheng to provide assistance.

Hei Lou Lan knew the ability of Tai Bai Yun Sheng and was thus overjoyed. He arranged a banquet that night to serve Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

On the second day, the sky had just become bright; Hei Lou Lan impatiently arranged his army formation and requested Tai Bai Yun Sheng to make his move.

Under everyone's expectant gaze, Tai Bai Yun Sheng slowly walked to the front and looked at the tall mountain in front of him.

Gu tribe was specialized in earth path and were long famous for it in northern plains. Piling stones to form a mountain, this would be an unimaginable and impossible tactics in Earth. But in this world, this mountain formed in about ten days proved nothing was impossible.

The alliance leader Gu Guo Long looked at the foot of the mountain from the summit.

When a white clothed, white hair old man walked in front of the formation, the Gu Masters around him roared in laughter and made disdainful comments, but Gu Guo Long, however, had a bad feeling in his heart.

He was well aware this mountain that they had formed by piling stones was built on many foundations constructed by his tribe's earth path Gu Masters. Other tribes might find it hard to imitate, but it was not like there were no ways to break through it.

After being defeated repeatedly for several rounds by Hei tribe army, Gu Guo Long's military force had suffered damage and his ambition of vying for supremacy had dimmed down. He pondered over this and had decided to side with Liu tribe.

Liu tribe's Liu Wen Wu was wise and benevolent, treating his people leniently and being strict to himself; his reputation was much better than Hei Lou Lan's. Several days ago, Gu Guo Long had secretly sent a letter to Liu Wen Wu express his intent to side with Liu tribe.

"Lord Liu Wen Wu has already replied and agreed to my tribe's request to seek refuge, and is leading his army to reinforce us. As long as I defend for seven more days, this predicament before us will part like clouds and allow me to see the clear sky."

Just as Gu Guo Long was inwardly encouraging himself, Tai Bai Yun Sheng slowly extended his hands.

His large palms were covered with callus and wrinkles, just like an old tree bark.

He slowly transferred his primeval essence, a weak silver light blossomed forth from his hands. The silver light was weak at first but soon turned brighter and brighter, and in a few seconds, the silver light was so dazzling that people could not look at it directly.

"Mountain as before." Tai Bai Yun Sheng slowly chanted, his voice resonating in the air.

On the summit, Gu Guo Long heard this voice and a shocked expression appeared on his face: "Oh no, he is Tai Bai Yun Sheng!"

At the very same moment, silver light burst out, transforming into a straight light pillar that directly rammed into the mountain peak.

Countless Gu Masters saw the situation turning awry and immediately activated their defense Gu or attacked to intercept the light pillar.

But the silver light disregarded all interception and shone on the mountain peak.

Both humans and beasts were unscathed, but the mountain stones below Gu tribe - regardless of how enormous or thick they were - under the silver light, were like snow under scorching sun, as they turned into nothingness in a visible speed, seemingly like they had never even existed!

As Gu tribe army lost the support under their feet, they started falling down one after another. It was a crushing defeat, countless died as they crashed down to the ground from a height of five hundred to six hundred feet.

Even if Gu tribe masters were stupid, they would become aware of their crisis at this moment.

They exclaimed in shock one after another.

"Such strength, this is Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mountain as before!"

"Heaven, why is old sir Tai Bai helping Tyrant Hei Lou Lan?"

"Lord Tai Bai Yun Sheng helped us restore our tribe's spirit spring back then, he is our tribe's benefactor. Now, we need to fight with him?"

The mountain was the source of Gu tribe's army's confidence and now it was loudly crumbling apart. But even more than that was Tai Bai Yun Sheng's prestige that shook their will to battle.

"Hahaha, Tai Bai Yun Sheng is indeed worthy of his name; once he moves, it will be out of the ordinary." Hei Lou Lan laughed wildly as he looked at this scene from the main tent.

Even he had not expected there to be such a hidden expert in the tribe.　　

But each super tribes' supreme elders would occasionally fancy someone from demonic and righteous path's mortal Gu Masters, they would then select these seeds to cultivate.

In case these seeds were able to become Gu Immortals, they would often be taken in by the super tribes and become their external supreme elder.

This was one of the tactics the super tribes used to preserve their position and develop themselves.

Clearly, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a seed the rank six Gu Immortal Hei Bai thought highly of and believed he had hopes of advancing to Gu Immortal realm.

Seeing the sorry figure of the enemy army, Hei tribe army's morale surged; many started laughing loudly and there were even more who shouted of slaughtering everyone in the enemy faction even the old and the young.

The Gu Master experts in the main tent were also excited with only Fang Yuan having a calm expression. Tai Bai Yun Sheng's appearance was already within his expectation.

In his previous life's five hundred years of memories, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had joined Hei tribe army from this point onwards and provided an enormous assistance to Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan being able to become the winner in the end was mostly because of Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a benevolent character and during the expedition, he became deeply aware of Hei Lou Lan's savage and brutal nature. Thus, when he entered Imperial Court blessed land and advanced to Gu Immortal, he did not agree to Hei Bai's request to become Hei tribe's external supreme elder.

"Kill! Kill these bastards, they actually dared to pile stones into a mountain to make a stand!" Hei Lou Lan excitedly shouted.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng who was at the front of the troops, heard Hei Lou Lan's words and frowned; he heaved a deep sigh and did not continue to attack, instead transmitted his voice to Hei Lou Lan to persuade him: "Alliance leader, heaven care for every living thing, why the need to kill? Throughout history, the struggle for Imperial court has always been accompanied by blood dying the land and disastrous deaths. Since alliance leader wants to enter the Imperial Court, it might be better to take in Gu tribe army, I am willing to persuade them on your behalf!"

Gu tribe piled up stones to form into a mountain and used it to contend against Hei tribe, but against Tai Bai Yun Sheng, this mountain they created instead became a fatal trap to themselves.

The current situation was Hei tribe army tightly surrounding Gu tribe army.

If Tai Bai Yun Sheng just made a casual move, he could reduce Gu tribe by over half. Gu tribe would naturally not sit and wait for their death, but when the mountain was completely collapsed, they would have almost no battle strength left and their final charge would contain no threat.

However, Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not do this.

Hei Lou Lan's eyes flashed with an ominous glint, although his heart raged with killing intent, he needed to think about Tai Bai Yun Sheng's face.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was not an ordinary Gu Master.

He was one of the extremely rare time path Gu Masters, and had rank five peak stage cultivation. His prestige in northern plains was like the sun in daytime, his influence was spread throughout the entire region.

Hei Lou Lan thought to himself before replying: "Then I shall listen to old sir, but it is too dangerous for old sir to go up the mountain alone. I will send six rank four experts to escort old sir!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng nodded his head and climbed up the mountain under heavy protection.

He had great prestige and his benevolent reputation had spread into the depths of people; as he climbed up the mountain, the enemy troops spontaneously parted way to reveal a passage in middle.

"I did not think I would meet benefactor at such a time." Gu Guo Long laughed bitterly as he went forward and greeted.

Back then, Gu tribe's spirit spring had dried up and they were pushed aside by several large tribes. It was very dangerous for them to migrate and thus they requested Tai Bai Yun Sheng to help them. Tai Bai Yun Sheng helped them without taking any fees and became a benefactor to everyone in Gu tribe.

Under Tai Bai Yun Sheng's persuasion, although Gu Guo Long admired Liu Wen Wu - circumstances are more powerful than individuals - he had no choice but to lower his head.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had only been on the mountain for a quarter of an hour before he descended.

When he climbed up, there were six people with him. When he descended, there were over a hundred thousand!

Evidently, Tai Bai Yun Sheng's persuasion was successful; Gu tribe army pledged allegiance to Hei Lou Lan, thus Hei tribe army's military strength increased sharply.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng changed the battle situation by himself. And with his deep prestige, he saved over a hundred thousand lives and also established great merits for Hei tribe.

On the very first day Tai Bai Yun Sheng came to Hei tribe army, he reached the top position in battle merit list. And exactly opposite to him was Fang Yuan.

Wolf King Chang Shan Yin's name was listed at the last on the battle merit list, in scarlet red color and was negative, forming a stark contrast with Tai Bai Yun Sheng's battle merit.

That very night, Hei Lou Lan sent command for a celebratory banquet and also a welcoming reception for Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

The moon was bright and stars were few; as bonfire raged high.

It was a festive scene with cheerful sounds resounding throughout the place and beautiful young girls in northern plains' clothings embroidered with gold, silver and precious jewels, danced around the bonfire.

Hei Lou Lan repeatedly toasted towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng and praised: "With old sir assisting us, all defense lines are useless!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had two rank five Gu that were recognized by all northern plains' people.

One was 'mountain as before' and another was 'river as before', both were time path Gu worms.

The former could restore earth, hills, mountains, mounds and valleys to their original appearance; and the latter could restore rivers, lakes, streams, springs and waterfalls back to their original appearance.

Gu Guo Long created the mountain on a land that was originally a flat grassland. Thus, under the effect of mountain as before Gu, it returned to its original form.

Gu tribe's spirit spring had been restored to its original state by river as before Gu, being able to create primeval stones again.

In the battles between great armies, defense lines needed to be created and this usually relied on earth path Gu worms to create long and tall defense walls. These defense walls would be restored to flat grassland under the effect of mountain as before Gu. Thus Hei Lou Lan's words 'all defense lines are useless' had deep reasoning behind them!

Chapter 525: Rapid Changes and Fierce Experts

Northern plains calendar, middle of June.

It should have been summer, but the aura of ten year blizzard had already thickened. The sky would often be gloomy and cold wind blew with increasing condensed frost aura.

And the struggle for Imperial Court that covered northern plains was advancing forward like a wildfire.

At Mirror lake, Ma tribe army and Song tribe had started their battle. Ma tribe's dominance was huge and they broke through two of Song tribe's defense lines in a row.

Song tribe alliance leader Song Qing Yin led the army to counterattack and ambushed Ma tribe, causing them to give up a defense line.

But soon after, Ma tribe's enslavement master Ma Zun moved and mobilized his trump card pegasus group, surrounding and killing Song Qing Yin in the air. Song tribe army became a headless dragon, and after an internal discord caused by Ma tribe secretly, they finally crumbled apart.

Ma tribe annexed most of the tribes while some remnants managed to escape to all directions.

In this battle, one of the few flying masters of northern plains, rank five initial stage Water Fairy Song Qing Yin died and became a stepping stone for enslavement path master Ma Zun's fame.

The strength Ma Zun displayed shocked the people. Faintly, people were already calling him northern plains' number one enslavement path master.

----------------

Meng Qiu.

Nu Er Tu's battle with Jiang Bao Ya.

Nu Er Tu was originally not an enslavement path Gu Master and had switched to it midway. But the leopard group he led was unexpectedly able to overpower and defeat the veteran enslavement path master Jiang Bao Ya.

Just because of this battle achievement, Nu Er Tu rose to the ranks of enslavement path masters of northern plains; and together with Jiang Bao Ya, Yang Po Ying, Ma Zun and Chang Shan Yin, were called five beast kings.

However, although Nu Er Tu managed to become famous, the price he had to pay was very high.

Jiang Bao Ya's counterattack had inflicted disastrous damaged to Nu Er Tu's troops. Despite annexing the remnants of the enemy after the battle along with the war reparations, Nu Er Tu's army's momentum was hindered.

Rat King Jiang Bao Ya managed to escape with his life and gathered the remnant army. His original rat group of over six hundred thousand, now had less than three hundred thousand left.

But even as a defeated general, many large forces still showed interest towards him and over ten forces had already sent him an invitation letter.

--------------

Du Jiao.

Ye Lui Sang was empowered by the Immortal Gu and with his formidable rank five peak stage fire path strength, he suppressed all the heroes and swept through the last obstacle, succeeding in dominating Du Jiao region.

However, just as Ye Lui army was spreading towards all directions like an unstoppable wildfire, they were pincer attacked by alliance of seven armies.

Each of the seven armies had at least over a hundred thousand troops. Although none were super tribes, they had famous Gu Master experts.

The alliance of seven armies created an aggressive momentum. Ye Lui army who had just gotten a head start and were about to continue with great momentum, fell into a perilous situation.

At the same time, Hei tribe army was also confronted by a great enemy and did not have any time to relax.

Liu tribe, Liu Wen Wu personally led his army and was pressing closer to Hei tribe every passing day!

Previously, Gu Guo Long had seeked helped from Liu Wen Wu; Liu Wen Wu was quite excited at reading the letter, knowing this was a rare opportunity. As long as Gu Guo Long's side could hold on, Liu tribe army could pincer attack Hei tribe from behind and gain the upper hand, causing Hei tribe to land in a passive situation.

But the result was that the situation changed way too fast. Liu tribe army was just halfway on their way when they heard the report of Gu tribe's defeat and submitting to Hei tribe. And the crucial character that made this possible was Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Liu Wen Wu was shocked at this report.

A legendary character like Tai Bai Yun Sheng had actually taken the initiative to come out and help Hei Lou Lan. Obtaining this person was like adding a huge army to Hei Lou Lan's forces.

Liu Wen Wu soon realized this was the behind-the-scenes move of Hei tribe's Gu Immortal.

According to the rule Ancestor Giant Sun set, Gu Immortals could provide some help to mortals in the struggle for Imperial Court. Naturally, this type of help had its restrictions, at least the Gu Immortals absolutely could not move personally.

Whether it was the Immortal Gu on Ye Lui Sang or Tai Bai Yun Sheng who assisted Hei Lou Lan after receiving the letter, they were both Gu Immortals' pawn pieces.

Liu Wen Wu naturally also had the privilege to request help from the Gu Immortal supporting him.

Hei Lou Lan obtained Tai Bai Yun Sheng's assistance who in Liu Wen Wu's opinion was much more terrifying than Wolf King Chang Shan Yin!

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's reputation was extremely high, whether it was righteous path or demonic path, many had received his grace. If just a small portion of these people had the heart to repay gratitude, the force they could gather would be very terrifying.

Besides, once Hei tribe expanded, those scattered demonic Gu Masters who had been watching from the sidelines would see the hopes of entering the Imperial Court in Hei tribe, and would side with them of their own initiative.

And Tai Bai Yun Sheng's existence would cause them to be even more inclined to choose Hei Lou Lan.

With this, Hei tribe would continue to be stronger. And as time passed, they would throw all the other competitors behind.

"Hei Lou Lan defeated Dong Fang Yu Liang and obtained a super tribe's war reparations, this by itself is a great profit. By contrast, we might have defeated several allied armies, but they were all an alliance of large tribes, so the war reparations we received are lower than Hei tribe's. Now, Hei tribe has Tai Bai Yun Sheng, a living signboard with him, if we give him time to expand, it will be very difficult to deal with him later."

Liu Wen Wu contemplated for a while before resolutely sending a command. Liu tribe army continued along their original plan, pushing on towards Hei tribe.

Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily at this news: "Come, come!".

He then sent the command to set up defense lines around the area.

After constructing the first defense line properly, the large army slowly moved towards Liu tribe army. At every thousand li of distance, they would stop and garrison for several days to construct another defense line.

Twelve days later, Hei tribe army moved on from their fourth defense line and travelled five hundred li before coming face to face with Liu tribe army.

The two army parted a way for the experts challenging stage.

Hei tribe's expert Hao Ji Liu charged forward, not giving precedence to others.

Liu Wen Wu saw this and sent Pei Yan Fei.

Hao Ji Liu was at rank four upper stage and Pei Yan Fei was also the same. The two exchanged twenty moves, the situation was still neck and neck.

Hao Ji Liu's offense surged higher and higher, causing people's hearts to shake. While Pei Yan Fei used sharp and precise attacks, moving back and forth within the attacks, and sweeping everything before him.

As the battle continued on, both of their primeval essence were running low.

Gu Masters were not good at prolonged battled and once their primeval essence was exhausted, their battle strength would sharply fall.

"This cannot go on!" The two had similar thoughts at the same time.

Waterfall Gu!

Hao Ji Liu took the lead and pushed forward his palms; a giant waterfall fell from the air and crashed towards Pei Yan Fei with a rumbling sound.

Pei Yan Fei did not face it head on, instead using his movement Gu to soar to the sky, evading the waterfall.

Rank four golden coat Gu!

Rank four swallow wings Gu!

Rank four rainbow transformation Gu!

Killer move — Golden Rainbow Strike!

Pei Yan Fei staked it all, using his signature killer move.

At that instant, he turned into a golden rainbow and made an arc through the air as fast as lightning, cutting open the waterfall before bursting through Hao Ji Liu!

However, Hao Ji Liu turned into water after being burst; it was not his real body.

Water image Gu!

Hao Ji Liu had fought for a long time and already had the intel on Pei Yan Fei, and knew Pei Yan Fei did not have any powerful detection type Gu. Thus, when he sent the waterfall, he took the advantage of the giant current blocking Pei Yan Fei's line of sight to quietly use his water image Gu while his real body hid inside the waterfall. His actions were extremely secretive and most of the Gu Masters from both sides had been deceived.

Pei Yan Fei burst through the water image and immediately had warning signals going off in his heart. Without holding back, he transferred all his remaining primeval essence into his swallow wings Gu.

The two pairs of swallow wings on his back rapidly flapped and took him away from the battlefield.

Hao Ji Liu stood on the spot, his whole body soaked in water. Even though he won the battle, he was not happy. The enemy's killer move had astonishing power, this time he used water image Gu to deceive him, but what about the next time?

"Big brother, let me go out!" Pei Yan Fei returned in defeat, causing Mo Shi Kuang to fume with anger and impatiently requested to be sent to battle.

Liu Wen Wu had a smile on his face, but he did not agree.

"Third brother, no need to fret. You came forward in the previous battle, it is my turn now." An extremely tall and thin Gu Master with robust and shiny bald head stood out and patted Mo Shi Kuang's shoulder.

"Second brother!" Mo Shi Kuang helplessly shouted.

This person's name was Ouyang Bi Sang, a demonic Gu Master. In their early years, by chance encounter, he met Liu Wen Wu and Mo Shi Kuang in an inheritance site. The three combined their strength to tackle the obstacles and obtained the inheritance, and because they felt affinity with each other, they became sworn brothers.

"I am Ouyang Bi Sang, who wants to come spar with me?" Ouyang Bi Sang slowly walked towards the front of the troops and shouted in a soft voice.

Soon after, he looked at Hao Ji Liu: "If Water Demon wants to fight with me, you might as well get some rest first to recover your primeval essence."

Water Demon snickered but did not agree to the provocation: "No need to hurry, there will be many chances later on."

After saying that, he returned to the camp.

With the struggle for Imperial Court advancing to this stage, the intel on experts of every forces was widely spread.

Ouyang Bi Sang was Mo Shi Kuang's second brother, just this status alone made him someone who could not be underestimated. His performance was extremely glorious during the several large battles before.

He was a transformation path expert and the Gu Masters of this path possessed at least one killer move. With a cultivation of rank four peak stage, he was same as Mo Shi Kuang, possessing the battle strength comparable to a rank five Gu Master!

During his first battle, he had killed the enemy side's rank five alliance leader. A dazzling battle achievement like crossing realms to fight was something many people would look up to their whole lives.

Facing such an expert, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu might have small chance at victory even if he was at his peak stage. Let alone now, when his energy was already exhausted in the battle with Pei Yan Fei. A Gu Master's state did not just depend on the amount of primeval essence in their aperture.

Seeing Ouyang Bi Sang coming forward, Hei Lou Lan felt a slight headache.

In contrast to Liu Wen Wu, he currently found that he lacked fierce generals beside him.

After taking in Gu tribe army, Hei tribe army now had three rank five Gu Masters - Hei Lou Lan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and the just recently subdued Gu Guo Long.

Hei Lou Lan could not easily move because of his status as the alliance leader. Tai Bai Yun Sheng was a healing Gu Master and was not good at fighting. Gu Guo Long was a rank five earth path Gu Master but the other was at rank four peak stage; it would not conform to the rule of battle if he was sent out, and they would only be sneered upon.

He then looked at his rank four Gu Masters - Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu, Shadow Sword Expert Bian Si Xuan, Little Fox Commander Tang Miao Ming and Sole Blade Pan Ping.

Chang Shan Yin and Tang Miao Ming were enslavement path Gu Masters, so they could be excluded. Water Demon Hao Ji Liu had already went up, so Hei Lou Lan only had two choices left.

His gaze moved between Pan Ping and Bian Si Xuan.

Pan Ping knew he was not Ouyang Bi Sang's match by just relying on his trump card, so he looked uncomfortable. While Bian Si Xuan's face was covered with a black veil, revealing her cold and clear gaze.

Hei Lou Lan turned around towards Bian Si Xuan: "For this challenge, I will have to trouble Shadow Sword Expert to make a move."

"I can only ensure that I won't lose my life, but I can't guarantee a victory." Bian Si Xuan coldly replied.

Hei Lou Lan gave a hollow laugh, although he was alliance leader and Bian Si Xuan had taken the poison vow, Hei Lou Lan could not forcibly make Bian Si Xuan fight to the death.

Chapter 526: Asura Ouyang, Losses to both sides

Bian Si Xuan moved to the front of the troop and without saying much, quickly started the fight with Ouyang Bi Sang.

The battle between the two attracted the close attention of countless people.

If considering reputation, Shadow Sword Expert could throw Ouyang Bi Sang several streets away. But if considering cultivation and strength, Ouyang Bi Sang was a rank four peak stage Gu Master who was able to cross a great realm and kill a rank five expert, while Shadow Sword Expert was only at rank four upper stage.

Shadow Sword Expert's Gu worms complemented each other very well and there was no shortcomings. At the same time, she placed high importance on her movement ability.

Her figure turned into shadows and continuously circled around Ouyang Bi Sang, attacking with multiple sword shadows from time to time.

Ouyang Bi Sang stayed stationary on the spot as he defended, his body unmoving like the rocks on the shores of the sea.

The battle went on for a while, when this sworn brother of Liu Wen Wu slowly felt impatient: "If you are only of this standard, then go die!"

He gave a low shout, as great changes appeared over his whole body.

His teeth quickly grew longer and sharper like swords, and his two pairs of canine teeth protruded out of his mouth like fangs.

Green hair started growing out of his bald head. Not only on his head, the green hair grew all over his body.

His body made creaking noises and his blood flow instantly slowed down greatly. The originally tall and skinny body became even more thin, but the aura of danger coming from him grew thicker by ten times!

His eyes were no longer human eyes, but had transformed into a pair of eerie and cold green eyes, giving off a glossy jade light.

Rank five, asura zombie Gu!

This Gu was classified under the most classic zombie series of transformation path.

The series of zombie Gu were spread widely throughout the five regions. From rank two roaming zombie Gu to rank three hairy zombie Gu to rank four hopping zombie Gu till the rank five flying zombie Gu.

There were five great flying zombie Gu in the world - asura zombie, heavenly demon zombie, blood wight, nightmare zombie and plague zombie.

Many Gu Masters who did not have much lifespan left and had no lifespan Gu to increase their life, would often choose to turn into zombies to prolong their life, transforming into a monster that was neither human nor ghost.

Fang Yuan had already seen blood wight Gu before. At Qing Mao mountain, Gu Yue first generation ancestor had turned into blood wight to change his fate in defiance of heaven, but his plan was thwarted by Divine Investigator Tie Xue Leng and others.

This asura zombie Gu that Ouyang Bi Sang was using was a formidable Gu that was equally famous as blood wight Gu!

Clank clank clank...

Bian Si Xuan's sword shadows cut at Ouyang Bi Sang's body, but they actually produced sparks on contact, unable to injure his skin by even a fraction, only cutting several green hair.

Overlapping shadow Gu!

Bian Si Xuan's eyes flashed with a sharp light, multiple sword shadows overlaid on top of one another to transform into an abysmally dark and extremely condensed sword.

"Now this is something!" Green light blossomed in Ouyang Bi Sang's pupils as he looked at this sword shadow attack; he was not afraid, but instead was happy.

He stretched his right hand in a form of a claw and grabbed at the sword shadow like he was grabbing a rabbit.

"This!" Bian Si Xuan revealed shock, the sword shadow in her hand could not go an inch further.

"Gagaga..." Ouyang Bi Sang laughed in a haggard and unpleasant tone as he clenched his claw-shaped right palm.

Puff.

A soft sound echoed.

He actually forcibly burst apart the sword shadow. Bian Si Xuan quickly retreated, the shattered sword shadow burst into many sharp pieces that ruthlessly struck at Ouyang Bi Sang, inflicting several deep wounds on his body, and slashed apart the four fingers on his right hand and almost cut apart the whole right fist.

Bian Si Xuan had bitterly accumulated battle merits from several small battles before and exchanged them for overlapping shadow Gu from Hei tribe supply camp.

Under its effect, the multiple sword shadows' offense could merge and could match the offensive prowess of a rank five attack Gu!

Ouyang Bi Sang was slashed at by the sword shadow, but he did not feel any pain. He had transformed into a zombie which caused the feeling of pain to almost disappear. At the same time, large amounts of eerie green blood flowed out of the wounds.

The wounds were so deep that one could see the bone, but they healed within just few seconds of time. New hair grew on top of it and covered it.

His broken fingers also grew again and it looked like it did not take any effort.

Bian Si Xuan's complexion turned pale white at this sight.

Ouyang Bi Sang looked hot-headed when he forcibly grabbed the sword shadow, but it was actually a psychological tactic. After he transformed into asura zombie, his defense and recovery ability were raised by several folds. Bian Si Xuan's strongest attack could not affect him in any way.

This unavoidably weakened Bian Si Xuan's will to battle severely.

Gu Master's battle strength did not only rely on the amount of primeval essence in their aperture, it also depended on their determination and mental state.

"I am an assassin, an expert at movement and infiltrating secretly. These challenges between the two army are done out in the open and facing someone head-on is not my usual style..." Ouyang Bi Sang's performance greatly weakened the battle intent in Bian Si Xuan's heart.

In the next several rounds, she kept on attacking while moving around Ouyang Bi Sang, but it was clear her attacking frequency had decreased by a lot compared to before, and she was dodging most of the time.

After exchanging ten more moves, Bian Si Xuan shouted and quickly pulled open a distance from Ouyang Bi Sang, retreating towards Hei tribe camp.

At this sight, Liu tribe army's morale rose again, while Hei tribe's morale shook and the higher ups did not have good expressions.

"Bian Si Xuan lost..."

"Is Ouyang Bi Sang really so strong? His killer move is asura transformation, having killed a rank five expert with this killer move. Now, he has only used asura zombie Gu, not even using his full strength but was still able to defeat Shadow Sword Expert!"

"Shadow Sword Expert did not have a strong will to fight, but by continuously attacking while moving around, she has exhausted a considerable amount of Ouyang Bi Sang's primeval essence. We can send another person to fight with him!"

The discussions settled and Hei tribe army sent Pan Ping to battle.

But within only a short period of time, Pan Ping seemed unable to stall further and panickedly unsheathed the scimitar on his waist and used sole blade Gu.

A cold light flashed but it was in vain.

Sole blade Gu could ignore defense but it did not work always and had a certain probability. Moreover, once this rank four sole blade Gu was activated, it needed eight hours of rest before it could be used again.

Ouyang Bi Sang got quite a shock. Despite having read relevant intel, sole blade Gu's speed was way faster than what he imagined, making him unable to react in time!

"I can't leave him alive!" Ouyang Bi Sang's killing intent surged as he pounced towards Pan Ping.

Pan Ping already knew the situation was bad the moment he saw his attack did not succeed, so he hurriedly retreated. Ouyang Bi Sang pursued him closely, Hei tribe quickly sent three rank four experts to block Ouyang Bi Sang and rescue Pan Ping.

The three rank four experts surrounded Ouyang Bi Sang and attacked fiercely. Ouyang Bi Sang was about to use his killer move — Asura Transformation, when Mo Shi Kuang who was unable to endure anymore charged out of the main tent and shouted: "Second brother, I will lend you a hand!!"

Ouyang Bi Sang, alone, put Hei tribe army under great pressure, now adding Mo Shi Kuang on top of that and the situation turned way worse.

"Third brother, no need to interfere, what is the use even if there are more people? Look at my asura transformation!" Ouyang Bi Sang furiously roared under the three rank four experts' violent attacks, and used his killer move.

His aura suddenly increased sharply, his body grew bigger, becoming a giant of over ten feet.

The muscles in his whole body inflated like a balloon and quickly transforming into absurd rock-like bulging muscles. And under his pair of arms, two new pairs of arms grew out.

His body was completely dark-green. HIs feet ripped apart the leather boots and stepped on the grassland, creating a deep crater.

The protruding fangs turned dark brown and a third vertical eye opened from the center of his forehead!

Howl!

Ouyang Bi Sang roared, the berserk sound shaking the whole battlefield.

The three Hei tribe's Gu Masters felt their momentum slowed down.

Ouyang Bi Sang waved his fist like swatting a fly, sending one flying far away.

The other two attacked violently, golden blades striking rapidly like thunder, but Ouyang Bi Sang took it forcibly; his enormous body not even budging.

"Die!" He attacked with all six hands - punching, swatting, grabbing, holding - with extremely fierce power. And all his hands moved smoothly, not hindering each other in the slightest.

The two rank four could not take it head on, and started retreating.

Ouyang Bi Sang was not satisfied, his every punch produced a sonic boom with power that caused people to pale.

One rank four Gu Master lasted only a short while under this crazed offense and was smashed into blood paste; while another Gu Master was grabbed by Ouyang Bi Sang.

"Don't kill me, don't kil—!"

His pleadings came to an end abruptly, blood started flowing rapidly out of his seven facial orifices, his ribs were crushed and his body started deflating - Ouyang Bi Sang had crushed him to death with two hands.

"So violent!" Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han involuntarily cried out.

Hei Lou Lan's expressed turned extremely unsightly, and Tai Bai Yun Sheng also had a solemn expression.

Liu tribe's army started cheering loudly while Hei tribe's Gu Masters were in disorder, their morale falling down to the abyss.

Liu Wen Wu laughed at this sight before waving his hand: "Commence the battle! All troops, charge!"

Immediately, Liu tribe army rushed forward like a flood with the gates opened, bringing a momentum that wanted to drown the world! Mo Shi Kuang, Pei Yan Fei and others were leading.

Hei Lou Lan gnashed his teeth and also sent the command for the army to prepare to receive the attack.

The large battle unfolded with all kinds of shouts and cries resounding through the battlefield.

During the intense battle, Liu tribe's several great experts rampaged everywhere, causing Hei Lou Lan and the higher-ups to fall into disadvantage at the very start.

But at the low level, Hei tribe was actually winning. Under Fang Yuan's control, the wolf group started wildly slaughtering Liu tribe's Gu Masters, while Liu tribe army's Gu Masters had no choice but to waste their precious primeval essence against the encroaching wolves. Thus, even if the wolves died, they died after contributing greatly.

Liu tribe's Gu Masters experts sensed this unfavorably situation and started searching for Fang Yuan.

However, Fang Yuan used the same old trick, hiding in some corner of the battlefield. He now already had three rank four lurking soul coat Gu, and with the concealment from these Gu, as long as he did not use over eighty percent of his strength, his soul fluctuations would be concealed.

This large battle continued from the early morning to evening.

The setting sun shone like blood as it shone down on the grassland that was covered with corpses and blood.

There was no winner in this battle.

Liu tribe suffered disastrous losses in their military forces because of the wolf group. After the Liu tribe's Gu Master experts were not able to find Fang Yuan's location, they all concentrated in attacking Hei tribe's Gu Master experts.

Hei tribe's Gu Master experts thus suffered serious damage. Mo Shi Kuang and Ouyang Bi Sang were difficult to restrain, and almost all the Hei tribe Gu Masters were too terrified to confront them.

Hei tribe's battle intent was dissipating and was barely able to hold on. When the night fell, the night wolves became fierce and Liu Wen Wu, not wanting the lower ranked Gu Master casualties to increase, also had the thought of retreating.

The first battle ended up in a draw with their killing intent gradually calming down as the night progressed. Both sides retreated behind their defense lines to rest and prepare.

Chapter 527: Wolf King, Striving For Victory

Hei tribe's main tent. The atmosphere here was stifling, almost everyone including Hei Lou Lan was injured.

The lofty and grand Gu Master experts looked very miserable at this moment.

"Liu tribe's offense was too fierce. Liu Wen Wu, Luo Bo Jun and Nie Ya Qing are rank five experts, Mo Shi Kuang and Ouyang Bi Sang are rank four peak stage experts with battle strength of rank five. Furthermore, there are other strong experts like Pei Yan Fei and Chang Biao... Such quality of experts were rarely seen in the past ten struggles for Imperial Court." Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han sighed.

Rank four Gu Masters were already rare; each was the head of small or mid-sized forces or elders of large-sized forces.

And with the high demand of aptitude, rank five was even rarer. Even a super force would only have two-three rank five Gu Masters openly.

Actually, when comparing, Hei tribe was stronger in higher ranked forces.

Hei Lou Lan, Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Gu Guo Long were rank five experts. And there were over twenty rank four experts including Chang Shan Yin, Tang Miao Ming, Hao Ji Liu, Bian Si Xuan and Pan Ping.

However, even between same ranked Gu Masters, there was a difference in their battle strength. Gu Masters were a force that surpassed group battles, their individual strength could surpass the accumulation of a group. For example, just Fang Yuan alone could slaughter small or mid-sized tribes. In today's battle, Ouyang Bi Sang, alone, had slaughtered five rank four Gu Masters and twelve rank three elders.

It was not that Hei tribe was weak but that Liu tribe's higher ranked battle strength was too strong!

Especially in this battle, Liu tribe had slaughtered many of Hei tribe's higher ranked Gu Masters, cutting down rank four Gu Masters to almost half, causing the gap to further increase.

The way to deal with the enormous dominance of Liu tribe was a problem Hei tribe had to quickly come up with a solution for.

"If I had some time, I could annex several large armies, and with old sir's prestige, subdue some experts, maybe we could contend against Liu tribe's higher ranked strength then." Hei Lou Lan sighed, hating Liu Wen Wu for choosing this time to attack, not giving him any space to develop.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng immediately realized the deep intent behind Hei Lou Lan's words: "I once rescued Gao Yang and Zhu Zai, and they had said they would repay the favor. I can write them a letter, and maybe they will come over."

Everyone's spirits rose.

Gao Yang and Zhu Zai were called the twin demons of demonic path in northern plains, they always worked together, having great teamwork with each other. These two were both rank four peak stage experts and had once killed a rank five expert by combining their strength!

The pressure on Hei Lou Lan eased: "If I can get Gao Yang and Zhu Zai's help, it can slightly make up for the gap between the two armies. But the events of the battle concerns everyone's life, and we cannot hope for others' mood in repaying the favor. In today's battle, it was thanks to Wolf King that we were able to exterminate large numbers of low ranked enemy Gu Masters, causing an enormous loss to Liu tribe. If it were not for Liu Wen Wu feeling hesitation, how could he have retreated so easily?"

Everyone's gaze landed on Fang Yuan, wanting to hear his thoughts.

Fang Yuan had a tranquil expression, not having a trace of injury on his body. He had been hiding while commanding the wolf group in the battle, but he was the one who gained the most battle merits.

Most of the ones in the main tent were inwardly infuriated at this, having envious and jealous feelings. But due to the situation, they did not dare to flare up.

After the battle, Fang Yuan had been looking through his memories, trying to excavate the information on how Hei Lou Lan had prevailed over Liu Wen Wu, but even after a long time of racking up his brain, he did not get any results.

There was way too much information in the memories of his five hundred years of past life, and much was forgotten. And from the look of it, this enormous problem that was troubling everyone was no more than just a minor detail in the long river of history in his past life.

Feeling everyone's gaze, Fang Yuan raised his eyelids and lightly said: "Liu tribe has enslavement path Gu Masters but their strongest expert is only Bei Cao Chuan whose grass soldier troops is of no importance. Now, both the enemy and us have our strengths. We are like two giants stabbing each other with spears. Liu tribe is strong in terms of higher ranked Gu Masters, while I can slaughter many of their low ranked Gu Masters with my wolf group. Thus, it resulted in the draw today."

"The way to victory is restraining the enemy's advantage as well as strengthening our advantage. And restraining the enemy's Gu Master experts is not an impossible thing, as long as I can have a group of strong wolves as trump cards, I can restrain them. But with this, I will have to use all my strength and the rank four lurking soul coat Gu on me will no longer be able to conceal my soul fluctuations, and thus I will become the enemy's target."

Fang Yuan's words caused everyone's eyes to brighten.

"Trump card wolf group..." Hei Lou Lan lowered his head and mumbled.

The current five great enslavement masters of northern plains were called the five beast kings. Among them, Horse King Ma Zun has mutated pegasus group. Eagle King Yang Po Ying has mutated thunder eagle group. Rat King Jiang Bao Ya has mutated mountain drilling rat group. And the newly advanced enslavement master Leopard King Nu Er Tu controlled glimpse leopard group. Only Wolf King Chang Shan Yin did not have a mutated beast group.

Every mature mutated beast possessed the battle strength of rank four Gu Masters. Once a group of mutated beasts formed, they would be more terrifying than the same amount of Gu Masters. After all, beast group would charge dauntlessly under the enslavement path Gu Master's control. As Gu Masters had all kinds of self benefits to think about, even if they were under poison vow, they could not be made to fight to the death.

If they had a group of mutated beasts, there was a huge chance of killing rank five experts.

After all, even rank five Gu Masters were mortals in the end, with limited primeval essence and there were times when their strength was exhausted.

However, making a mutated beast group was too time-consuming of a process and would exhaust enormous energy and resources.

To look for a group of mutated wolf group for Fang Yuan in this short period of time, there was only one way - requesting help from Hei tribe's Gu Immortals.

The people in the main tent, even if they did not know the existence of treasure yellow heaven, they were aware of the huge power of Gu Immortals.

In the history of northern plains, there were several examples where Gu Immortals organized mutated beast group to provide assistance to their respective force.

"Mutated beast group is indeed a way out, I will give it a try first." Hei Lou Lan pondered for a while before saying vaguely.

But everyone clearly knew the meaning behind Hei Lou Lan's words was to request help from the Gu Immortal behind him.

This immediately caused a new change in the gaze everyone looked at Fang Yuan.

How could this Wolf King Chang Shan Yin have such good luck? Making a Gu Immortal help him to organize a mutated wolf group. If he had to do this himself, he might not even be able to accomplish it in twenty to thirty years! Why don't we get such benefits?

Everyone felt envious and jealous.

Ultimately, it was the identity of Chang Shan Yin that Fang Yuan carried; an enslavement master was an existence that could turn tides around. Hei tribe was fighting Liu tribe, it was indeed wise to put heavy importance on Fang Yuan and give more resources to him.

"If I remember right, even if there is a mutated beast group, Lord Wolf King's battle merits is ranked number one from the bottom, the last place in the battle merits list, right?" Cunning Gentleman was filled with jealousy, 'kindly' reminding as if he had suddenly recalled it.

"Of course, I can't receive a mutated wolf group for nothing!" Fang Yuan righteously nodded, "Our rules cannot be broken, I will use battle merits to exchange for it. Of course, my battle merits are insufficient right now, so I can only borrow a bit more. This is something that cannot be helped!"

Everyone was speechless.

Many people shouted inwardly at the same time:

'Do you feel no shame speaking such words?'

'Do you still want your face, you already borrowed one million and three hundred thousand battle merits before and you still want to borrow more?!'

'In the entire Hei tribe army, only you have borrowed battle merits! Don't you feel guilt holding that rank five amplify effect Gu?'

In fact, Fang Yuan not only did not feel any guilt, instead he said with a 'not satisfied' voice: "Just a mutated beast group won't do, I still require rank five lurking soul coat Gu. Unfortunately, refining a rank five Gu has a success rate that is too low. I have collected three rank four Gu, but I don't dare to fuse them to rank five."

Hei Lou Lan gnashed his teeth, the number of times he could request help from the tribe was limited, the more he asked for help, the less the tribe's evaluation of him would be. But there was no other way, he could only nod at Fang Yuan in order to defeat Liu Wen Wu: "I will do something about it."

Just as Hei Lou Lan and his group were strategizing, Liu Wen Wu and his group were also planning on how to battle Hei tribe.

"In Hei tribe army, Wolf King Chang Shan Yin is the biggest problem. It was because of him that my army suffered disastrous losses in today's battle, with at least thirty thousand Gu Masters dying in the wolves' mouths. Sigh, this number is truly making my heart bleed, everyone came forward to side with me because they believed in me. But it is because of my incompetence, we had to suffer such heavy casualties!"

In the main tent, Liu Wen Wu shed tears and sighed.

"Big brother, how is it your fault? We can only blame those Gu Masters for being useless!" Mo Shi Kuang almost jumped up as he hurriedly retorted.

"Wolf King Chang Shan Yin might have huge reputation, but he is not a true hero." Ouyang Bi Sang, however, loftily snorted, his tone contained disdain, "The grand Wolf King was actually sneakily hiding in some corner like a rat, it really makes people look down upon him."

"But, such a Wolf King is the most troublesome!" Liu Wen Wu sighed inwardly while opening his weeping eyes and asked the group, "Do any of you have a good method to deal with Wolf King?"

Mo Shi Kuang and Ouyang Bi Sang stopped speaking.

They were experts at fighting, things like strategizing were not their strong points.

"I have a plan." Bei Cao Chuan stood up and said confidently, "Wolf King Chang Shan Yin was originally Chang tribe's tribesman. Although he spoke of taking revenge, the blood-ties he has with Chang tribe is unmistakable and cannot be severed. The current Chang tribe leader Lord Chang Biao was once Chang Shan Yin's best friend. After Chang Shan Yin disappeared, Chang Biao married his wife and raised his three year old son who is currently Chang tribe's young tribe leader Chang Ji You. We might as well try to use this to deal with Wolf King, who knows if it might be effective?"

"Hmm...this idea is not bad!" Liu Wen Wu's eyes gleamed.

　　...

After the discussion ended, Fang Yuan returned to his large lizard house Gu.

The problem of refining rank five lurking soul coat Gu had been hurting his head recently. If he could borrow Hei tribe's Gu Immortal's power to organize a mutated beast group and also refine rank five lurking soul coat Gu, it would be the best.

Fang Yuan felt there was a huge chance for this to succeed. Although he could not remember all the minor details of this time's struggle for Imperial Court, but he knew clearly Hei Lou Lan was able to enter Imperial Court and the support of the Gu Immortal behind Hei Lou Lan was inseparable from this.

"The two sides will at least rest and reorganize for three days. In this time, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals will have received Hei Lou Lan's letter for assistance. Before this, I need to prepare..."

Thinking of his great plan, the corners of Fang Yuan's lips involuntarily curled up into a smile.

Chapter 528: True Martial Secret, Awaiting Assistance

Xiao Hun blessed land.

This place was always covered in dense dark clouds and female-shaped trees grew on the ground.

These trees were very peculiar; the tree trunk was curved and branches wrapped around each other like a girl's naked body. The trees were in all kinds of enchanting postures.

Female-shaped trees grew all over the place, becoming a forest.

In the deepest part of the forest was the tallest female-shaped tree with a height of one thousand feet and roots that extended for a range of ten thousand li.

This female-shaped tree king, however, did not look seductive, instead giving off pure and holy aura.

The tree king's trunk was ramrod straight, giving a highly spirited feeling. Its two enormous branches formed into hands that covered the chest. The side branches from them formed into two well-developed and large palms that lifted a green treehouse.

Red vermillion fruits grew all over the treehouse with reddish-brown rattan twining around them, making the fruits look like hearts.

Two Gu Immortals were sitting inside this treehouse, both in black clothes.

On the left was an ordinary looking man who was called 'Hei tribe stoneman' during his young age, he was awkward at conversing but was smart and careful inside; he was Hei Bai.

On the right side, however, was a handsome man who was radiating with vigor, having eyes that seemed to shine, and appeared confident and at ease; he was Hei tribe's supreme elder Hei Cheng, Hei Lou Lan's father and a famous handsome man as well as the male lead in Su Xian's night elopement.

"Say, you just returned from Ni Yu blessed land, did you see Dong Fang Chang Fan? How is he?" Hei Cheng asked leisurely while taking a sip of tea.

Hei Bai nodded: "Senior Dong Fang isn't looking for lifespan Gu, there is not much of his lifespan left, he can probably only live for two-three years more. But his vision is broad and has magnanimous conduct, already seeing through the trouble of life and death and only wants to wholeheartedly nurture his successor Dong Fang Yu Liang now."

"Magnanimous conduct, broad vision?" Hei Cheng scoffed, shaking his head in disdain, "Brother, you saw wrong. Dong Fang Chang Fan is a genuine petty person, he schemed against the northern plains and is extremely insidious and so is hated by all the Gu Immortals. If it was not so, he could have already bought lifespan Gu, why would he have fallen into this state? I have been secretly investigating over these years and have discovered he had a hand in my wife Su Xian Er's death!"

Hei Cheng revealed this secret information, causing Hei Bai to be extremely startled.

"What? There was such a thing?" Hei Bai exclaimed in shock.

Su Xian Er was Hei Cheng's wife. Over two hundred years back, Su Xian Er was no more than a daughter of a concubine in Su tribe; and while she poured wine for Lord Hei Cheng back then in the banquet, Hei Cheng immediately fell in love at first sight.

In that banquet, Hei Cheng was poisoned by Su tribe leader, his strength fell to the bottom and he was hunted down.

After Su Xian Er accidentally learned of it, she resolutely rushed out of the tribe in the dead of night to rescue Hei Cheng whom she had only met once.

At that time, Su Xian Er only had rank one cultivation, and ferocious beasts roamed the night grassland that were beyond her ability to contend.

But under the play of fate, she was able to find the unconscious Hei Cheng.

Hei Cheng was thus saved and managed to live. He had then asked Su Xian Er with suspicion: "I was plotted against by your tribe leader and you are a Su tribesman, why would you save an enemy of your tribe?"

Su Xian Er had answered: "Lord has a noble spirit, this humble girl fell in love at first sight. Su tribe leader is short-sighted and plotted against lord under the persuasion of some petty people, but he never considered the result of offending Hei tribe. If he was allowed to have his way, Su tribe is destined to become a sacrificial pawn between two super tribes. People say lord repays a favor received by a hundred times. This humble girl saved lord today and only hopes lord can give me a place to stay. It is just and proper for lord to take revenge against Su tribe, but I hope lord can be merciful and leave behind a trace of bloodline for Su tribe."

The moonlight shone on the jade-like beauty with slender and fair hands.

Hei Cheng was overwhelmed at this sight, he tightly held Su Xian Er's hand and swore: "Your love is as deep as the sea, I, Hei Cheng, am not a cruel person, how could I not repay you? From today onwards, you will be my only wife! I will not care for any other beauties, no matter how beautiful they are. In this life, I will never betray you!"

Su Xian Er saving Hei Cheng was akin to betraying the tribe. Hei Cheng was very grateful and interlinked with her as husband and wife.

From that day onwards, the two helped each other, loving and respecting each other their whole life. Hundred years later, both became Gu Immortals, becoming a story that spread far and wide in northern plains. And Su Xian's night elopement was also spread wide, encouraging countless women to bravely take the initiative to love.

Hei Bai's mood became solemn: "Could it be over twenty years ago sister-in-law did not die because of the blessed land's earthly calamity?"

Hei Cheng scoffed: "There was indeed an earthly calamity, but the earthly calamity was influenced by people. Don't forget brother, old ancestor Giant Sun Immortal Venerable has such methods. Dong Fang tribe has entered Imperial Court many times as a tribe with Huang Jin bloodline, they might have received an inheritance relevant to such methods from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Sigh, I only have a little evidence, it is not enough to prove Dong Fang Chang Fan as the main culprit."

Hei Bai remained dazed for quite a while before sighing: "You really can't judge people by appearance."

Hei Cheng patted his shoulder and comforted in a gentle voice: "Brother, you have become a Gu Immortal for less than ten years. Gu Immortals' circle might not be big, but the treacherous conspiracies inside it are much deeper than between mortals."

Hei Bai was just about to speak, when his expression blanked: "Hei Lou Lan has send a letter."

Hei Cheng nodded, and with a shift of his mind, loosened the defense over Xiao Hun blessed land by a little; the space opened up and in flew a butterfly.

Hei Bai stretched his right hand; this butterfly fluttered and gently landed on his palm.

This was rank five butterfly letter Gu.

Hei Bai closed his eyes and concentrated on the butterfly letter Gu from Hei Lou Lan, containing his request.

"What is it, did that disappointing child of mine ask you for help again?" When Hei Bai opened his eyes, Hei Cheng snorted and asked with a displeased tone.

Hei Bai forced a smile: "Brother, Hei Lou Lan is you and sister-in-law Su Xian Er's son. Although sister-in-law suffered and fell seriously ill when giving birth to Hei Lou Lan, leading to her strength being greatly diminished and thus passing away in the earthly calamity several years later, the child is still innocent, you should not disregard him because of it. You even gave him to the twenty-seventh concubine Fairy Jiang Yu to adopt and did not allow him to light an incense to pay respects to his own mother."

Hei Cheng snorted with dissatisfaction, but did not argue.

Hei Bai sighed: "This is your family affair and it is truly not my place to meddle. But I have given a lot of thoughts to big brother's actions; you sent Hei Lou Lan to be adopted by the childless Fairy Jiang Yu in order to preserve Hei Lou Lan's life though her Immortal Gu Dark Limit. Hei Lou Lan has the ten extreme physique — Great Strength True Martial. To stimulate his spirit, you gave him a condition that as long as he advanced to Gu Immortal, he could light the incense for his mother. Little brother deeply admire your actions, but big brother, your way of doing things will only deepen the misunderstandings between father and son, it is not a good method looking at the long term drawbacks."

Hei Cheng heaved a sigh, not replying Hei Bai, but instead asked: "What did that child mention in the request?"

Hei Bai clapped his palm and smiled: "Look big brother, you showed indifference but you still care about nephew's safety in your heart. Nephew hopes we can prepare a mutated wolf group and also a rank five lurking soul coat Gu."

"Hmph, this kid is truly insolent! Lurking soul coat Gu is okay, but our Hei tribe does not have mutated wolf group."

"Right now, our Hei tribe is battling Liu tribe, Liu tribe's current generation tribe leader Liu Wen Wu is not someone who can be underestimated. Back then, the inheritance of Harmony Immortal fell in his hand. He has two sworn brothers, both are fierce warriors and can match ten thousand soldiers. However, nephew Lou Lan also has a great general under him - Wolf King Chang Shan Yin. This time's request is because he has placed his hopes on Chang Shan Yin." Hei Bai explained.

Hei Cheng mumbled: "Rank five lurking soul coat Gu is no issue, I have one with me. But mutated wolf group would have to be purchased from treasure yellow heaven. I will have to request brother for this."

Hei Bai quickly shook his hand: "Brother, you don't have to be so polite. I still need to rely on nephew to enter Imperial Court and find Immortal Gu Wooden Chicken in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building."

Hei Cheng heaved a long sigh and said with an exhausted voice: "Great Strength True Martial physique needs a strength path Immortal Gu to advance to Gu Immortal realm. Unfortunately, Immortal Gu are very difficult to find, our Hei tribe also does not have any strength path Immortal Gu. Success and failure is decided by heaven, we can only try our best. We have already done all we can, now everything will depend on Hei Lou Lan's efforts and luck."

'Parents are truly constantly worrying about their children.' Hei Bai sighed inwardly and said his farewell to Hei Cheng.

After he returned to his Ku Mu blessed land, he immediately connected to treasure yellow heaven and started buying mutated wolves.

Wolf emperors could be considered as a strength of blessed land, it was very hard to find Gu Immortals selling them. But mutated wolves were only equivalent to rank four and were much easier to find.

Hei Bai was not worried, mutated beasts were not rare and precious goods and as long as one had sufficient immortal essence stones, they could buy a large group of them.

Of course, spending a lot to buy the mutated wolf group was a loss to Hei Bai. But he was planning for a Immortal Gu in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, and it was right for him to invest in the early stages.

Imperial Court blessed land was the work of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, and unless one reached rank nine, no Gu Immortals could enter inside!

After the news of buying mutated wolf group in high price was spread, Hei Bai soon received a divine sense from someone called 'Fox Immortal'.

'Fox Immortal' had over a hundred mutated wolves and quoted a rather high price for them, they were clearly taking advantage of Hei Bai's difficulty.

Hei Bai had already anticipated such a situation, it was only that he had not expected this 'Fox Immortal' to move so quickly at the chance. He gnashed his teeth and bought this group of mutated wolves.

The one selling this group of mutated wolves was none other than Little Hu Immortal who had received Fang Yuan's instructions.

Previously, they had resold Immortal Gu recipes and earned dozen or so immortal essence stones; Fang Yuan had then instructed Little Hu Immortal to purchase purple crystal relic Gu and also look for any wolf groups sold cheaply at treasure yellow heaven, and buy them.

Thus, Hu Immortal blessed land had accumulated over a hundred mutated wolves; among them were blood forest wolf, berserk wolf, shark fin wolf, white-eyes wolf and others.

Now, by reselling these mutated wolves at high price to Hei Bai, they had profited quite a bit.

As for Fang Yuan, he was calmly resting in the camp, waiting for Hei tribe's assistance.

Chapter 529: Diligence despite transmigration

It was difficult to move through the muddy swamp, but Ma tribe's army was in high spirits.

The happiness of annexing Dou tribe army as well as the excitement of a decisive victory could still be seen on everyone's faces.

Ma Ying Jie was riding a horse and as he looked at the generals and soldiers around him with satisfaction, as an investigative Gu Master brought him the latest battle reports.

He opened up the documents and read:

"Hei tribe and Liu tribe has begun to fight. The first battle resulted in a draw, and currently, both are garrisoned opposite each other. The situation is in a stalemate."

"Ye Lui army was ambushed at night by the seven army alliance. Ye Lui Sang was very powerful and defeated six rank five experts one after another, but he was only one person and was unable to save the situation. Currently, Ye Lui tribe's remnant army is fleeing towards Qing An region."

"Rat King Jiang Bao Ya has accepted Yang tribe's invitation and has officially entered Yang tribe's alliance."

"Nu Er Tu army has not resumed their expedition, instead resting and capturing huge numbers of leopard groups."

　　...

These battle reports caused Ma Ying Jie to smile with joy: 'Hei Lou Lan and Liu Wen Wu are popular candidates to win this time's Imperial Court contest. I did not think these two would confront each other this early, it will be good if they both suffer. Since Ye Lui Sang obtained Immortal Gu, he is a one-man army. But for Ye Lui tribe to be suddenly attacked by the seven armies, Snowy Mountain most likely has influence behind it.'

Ma tribe, to advance to a super tribe, had secretly joined hands with demonic path Gu Immortals who were coveting after Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. Ma Ying Jie was Ma tribe's young tribe leader and thus was aware of the undertable deals of the tribes.

Northern plains was like a huge chessboard while the Gu Immortals were the chess players.

Besides righteous path Gu Masters, demonic path Gu Immortals also had their own pawns whom they supported. And as the tribes with Huang Jin bloodline were willing to join hands with demonic path Gu Immortals in order to have a better survival chance. If they lost in the struggle for Imperial Court, these tribes would often enter the blessed lands of the demonic path Gu Immortals to escape from the blizzard disaster.

Immortal Gu were rare.

Ye Lui tribe's supreme elder had entrusted an Immortal Gu to Ye Lui Sang; it was equivalent to placing a bet in this game.

According to the rules set by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, as long as Immortal Gu were snatched by mortals in the struggle for Imperial Court, the Gu Immortals cannot take them back.

Such a huge bet had its corresponding risk.

It was because of the Immortal Gu on Ye Lui Sang that caused him to be the target of Gu Immortals. Thus they incited seven armies to ambush Ye Lui army.

"Rat King has joined Yang tribe which means an alliance of Rat King and Eagle King Yang Po Ying, causing this underdog Yang tribe to become a new contender to win the struggle for Imperial Court. But Yang tribe's foundations are far inferior to our Ma tribe and Rat King was also already crippled, they aren't of much threat to us."

"Although Nu Er Tu is called Leopard King, his leopard group has been inflicted heavy losses. However, he has been capturing wild leopard groups by himself without asking for help from the Gu Immortal behind him, this is a bit strange..."

"But overall, my Ma tribe's situation is still much better. Our next opponents are weaker than us. As long as we keep on winning, continue to devour other tribes and expand, our hopes of entering Imperial Court will become bigger and bigger!"

Ma Ying Jie could not help clenching his fists at this, his eyes letting out a fierce light. The ambitions and goals of a man were pushing him to establish great feats and accomplishments.

And at the same time, within the high spirited army was a little girl, who was weeping in a carriage.

"Lady Xiao Yun, don't keep on grieving, your father's death was a heart rending event, but you need to eat, if not you will faint from hunger." Beside the little girl, the anxious Fei Cai was comforting her in a clumsy way.

This weeping little girl was none other than Zhao Lian Yun.

Her father, Zhao tribe's leader, had sacrificed his life in the previous large battle.

Losing the protection of the father who loved her dearly, Zhao Lian Yun immediately felt her world toppling. On the very night of her father's death, her stepmother remarried the new Zhao tribe leader, and Zhao Lian Yun's position took a sharp dive.

"There will always be deaths in war, this is normal. My father was also killed by others." Fei Cai continued to persuade Zhao Lian Yun when he saw she was still crying.

Zhao Lian Yun suddenly raised her head while sobbing, looking at Fei Cai with an insoluble hatred in her tear-filled eyes, and kicked him: "You idiot, you don't even know how to comfort people!"

The sorrow in her heart was not fake. Although she inexplicably arrived in this world and it had not been long since her arrival, her father's love towards her was filled with sincerity. She was very grateful for this genuine love and her dependence on him had slowly grown into true affection.

But now, her father had died in the battlefield, making her alone and helpless.

"Missy, you were hiding here, you really caused much trouble for me! Quick, follow me, your mother is calling you." At this time, the curtain of the carriage was lifted open by the old caretaker who then grabbed Zhao Lian Yun's small arm.

Zhao Lian Yun struggled and shouted: "My mother is dead, she is not my mother! I won't go!"

"This is not up to you!" The old caretaker scoffed and tried to forcibly drag Zhao Lian Yun out of the carriage.

When she had been serving Zhao Lian Yun, she was teased and pranked by Zhao Lian Yun time and again. Now, as she looked at Zhao Lian Yun's miserable state, the old caretaker felt the pleasure of taking revenge.

"Let go of Lady Xiao Yun!" Fei Cai shouted and punched the old caretaker.

The old caretaker fell out of the carriage from this heavy punch. She stood up and touched her eye that had become purple from the bruise. She screamed in a shrill voice: "You hit me, a slave dared to hit a civilian? Who gave you such big guts!! I will report you, you are going to die. You will be skinned alive and your corpse will be hung up in the sunlight till it dries up!"

The old caretaker was extremely furious, and with her unkempt hair and sinister gaze, she looked like a hopping old hen.

However, her scream had indeed attracted the surrounding people.

Fei Cai clenched his fists and furiously stared at the old caretaker while firmly protecting Zhao Lian Yun behind him.

Zhao Lian Yun pushed aside Fei Cai's arm and stood on the carriage, her fair face still had tear stains, she looked at the old caretaker and scoffed: "What was it? You want to punish Fei Cai? Alright! Report him, but according to the rules, you need to first inform his master to demand compensation. Since it is so, go look for young tribe leader. Fei Cai is Lord Ma Ying Jie's slave leader!"

"What?!" The old caretaker cried out in shock, her screams abruptly stopped and the anger in her heart dissipated like a tide, only leaving behind an extreme terror.

This rash stupid kid was actually lord Ma Ying Jie personal slave? Moreover, he was lord Ma Ying Jie's slave leader who was in charge of his everyday life?

One needed to look at the owner before beating the dog.

The old caretaker might be a civilian with a status higher than that of a slave, but it was a different matter when Fei Cai was Ma Ying Jie's slave leader.

If she truly reported recklessly, she might instead be sacrificed by Zhao tribe!

After the shock, the old caretaker who had lost her face greatly looked gloomy. She rigidly stared at Zhao Lian Yun: "Little girl, even young tribe leader Ma Ying Jie's slave leader cannot protect you. You are a person of Zhao tribe, even after your death, you will be our Zhao tribe's ghost. Your mother is our Zhao tribe's current tribe lady. Listen to me properly, tribe lady has already arranged your marriage to Wei tribe's eldest young master! Now behave properly!"

"What?!" Zhao Lian Yun involuntarily cried out.

"Marrying to Wei tribe's eldest young master is your blessing." The old caretaker sinisterly smiled.

Zhao Lian Yun's whole body shook and fell down on the wooden board of the carriage.

"Lady Xiao Yun!" Fei Cai quickly supported her.

The old caretaker felt incomparable pleasure at this sight and left with immense satisfaction. She still needed report to Zhao tribe's tribe lady.

Zhao Lian Yun was expressionlessly, this immense shock left her in a dazed state filled with despair, allowing Fei Cai to hold her in the carriage. For three days, she curled up at a corner of the carriage, without moving or speaking.

Fei Cai's persuasion was of no use, and could only helplessly feed her.

Zhao Lian Yun was like a wooden puppet, letting Fei Cai control her.

Fei Cai also could not accompany her all the time, and every time Ma Ying Jie summoned him, he would immediately leave.

This sudden change of events and this ice-cold reality shattered the foolish pride Zhao Lian Yun had as a transmigrator.

She suddenly had a profound realization: 'A transmigrator is nothing special. Why did I think I could whip up a storm in this world after being so ordinary in my previous world?'

Moreover, women were discriminated in northern plains and were treated as goods to be used for political marriage. Northern plains' women could only adhere to men and could not refuse a man's forceful marriage. This was a rule set by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Previously, when she heard of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's deeds, she felt like she was listening to a story, listening to a legend of a hero. But now, she was personally experiencing the torment caused by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

"Women are like clothes while brothers are like our hands and feet." This was the favorite catchphrase of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, he pulled apart the status of man and woman to an extremely unfair level. Now he had become the most detestable person in Zhao Lian Yun's heart!

"No wonder Su Xian's night elopement story pierced so deep into people's hearts, causing northern plains' women to eagerly imitate it. Rather than passively suffering fate's arrangement, it is better to take the initiative to chase after one's happiness. But this carries unknown risks!"

As she thought of this, Zhao Lian Yun's awareness of the vile living environment deepened by another layer.

"Wei tribe's eldest young master is a famous trash. He is fat like a pig with pockmarks all over his face and only at rank one peak stage but is extremely lecherous and very fickle-hearted. It is because of his incompetence, Wei tribe's young tribe leader position went to his younger brother."

"I won't marry that pig even if I die! But what should I do? I am only a mortal, and since I haven't reached thirteen, I cannot awaken my aperture and cannot cultivate. It is also possible that I don't have any cultivation aptitude. And the person who killed my father is Dou E, a rank five Gu Master who has sided with Ma tribe now and is now a higher-up of the alliance!"

"Who can I rely on? What path should I take?"

Bewilderment, hesitation and fear filled Zhao Lian Yun's heart.

In the early morning of the fourth day, Fei Cai lifted up the carriage curtain and entered with food and clean water. The light of the dawn followed the curtain opening and shone on Zhao Lian Yun's face.

Zhao Lian Yun woke up, slowly opening her swollen eyes.

"You brought food?" She grabbed the food from Fei Cai's hand and began to devour it.

"Lady Xiao Yun, are you okay?" Fei Cai was happy at this change.

"Yes, I have thought it through, it is better to rely on myself. Although I have been bound by the wedding betrothment, it can only be implemented when I am sixteen. I still have time!" Zhao Lian Yun's gaze shone like fire.

"Ah, Lady Xiao Yun, you don't accept the betrothal?" Fei Cai was startled; in his impression, northern plains could only accept their fate when their marriage was decided.

Zhao Lian Yun rolled her eyes and spoke in a righteous tone: "Hmph, I am not an ordinary person, I absolutely won't compromise! But I cannot go to the tribe now and can only live here for some time, and rely on you Fei Cai."

"No problem." Fei Cai patted his chest, laughing foolishly.

Zhao Lian Yun's heart warmed and her tone turned softer: "Fei Cai, your father also died in battlefield?"

"Yes, he died. I was heartbroken during that time. But death is normal in northern plains. Father died in battle, he died a glorious death." Fei Cai said with a smile.

'As expected, winner takes it all! Under the dazzling and splendid throne lies a path of bones.' Zhao Lian Yun sighed, before cursing, 'What a scam, I crossed over to this world and have yet to mature but my fate has already been decided by others, I can't even begin to feel anger!'

　　...

A letter was placed in front of Fang Yuan.

This special letter was openly sent by the enemy and was now brought over by Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han.

Fang Yuan opened it and read; this letter was personally written by Chang Biao, reminiscing the past and how they were on opposite sides now. He was inviting Wolf King to have a discussion before the battle and reminisce about the old times. And at that time, he could let Chang Ji You meet his father.

"Great ploy." Fang Yuan scoffed and placed down the letter.

At this time, Sun Shi Han smiled: "The mutated wolf group and rank five lurking soul coat gu have both arrived. But the higher-ups of the alliance are hesitating because of this letter. They are hoping Lord Wolf King would battle against your kin in the name of righteousness, to prove your innocence. Otherwise, I'm afraid this mutated wolf group..."

Chapter 530: Adjusting his appearance for him

Liu tribe defense line, inside the camp tent.

"Mother, what kind of person was father?" Chang Ji You had a hesitant expression, after a long while, he asked the burning question in his heart.

He had never met Chang Shan Yin, back then when Chang Shan Yin's mother died from poison, and when Chang Shan Yin fought to the death with Ha Tu Gu, Chang Ji You was only an unborn child in his mother's womb.

His mother Ni Xue Tong had a frowned expression as she breathed out, using a nostalgic tone: "My child, has your heart wavered? Don't forget our current circumstances. Don't worry about your father, he is a legend in northern plains, back then he killed Ha Tu Gu and the bandits single-handedly, he is a hero who exterminated a great threat for the people."

Chang Ji You interrupted his mother: "Mother, I'm sick of hearing that. Since birth, I've been hearing these stories all my life, wherever I go, whatever I do, people will say 'oh look, as expected of Chang Shan Yin's son'. Father is like the eagle in the sky, flying high and casting his shadow on the ground. In a few days, I will be meeting him, my heart is in a mess, I just want to hear his..."

Chang Ji You was still speaking, when the tent flap was opened, as a domineering middle-aged man with a powerful aura walked in.

It was Chang tribe's current tribe leader, Chang Shan Yin's brother, rank four upper stage wind path expert, Chang Biao.

"Greetings to lord stepfather." Chang Ji You quickly paid respects.

"My child, go out first, I need to talk with your mother." Chang Biao said gently.

"Yes." Chang Ji You had to leave the tent.

Once the flap was closed, with the guards outside, there were only Chang Biao and Ni Xue Tong left in the tent.

"Husband!" Ni Xue Tong jumped into Chang Biao's embrace, tears flowing out of her weak and feeble eyes.

"Sigh, I know you have been feeling terrible these days!" Chang Biao embraced Ni Xue Tong as he caressed her hair softly. At the same time, he used his Gu worm to isolate the place from the outside.

Ni Xue Tong sobbed: "You Er has been asking me about Chang Shan Yin again, what should I say? Do you know, just now I had the urge and almost told him the truth, that he is not Chang Shan Yin's flesh and blood, that he is the crystallization of our love!"

Chang Biao's body shuddered, he was also feeling great conflict and pain in his heart.

He solemnly said: "This is all my fault for being useless! Back then we were childhood friends, it was Chang Shan Yin who came into the picture abruptly and lusted after your beauty. On the day of our marriage, he snatched you away. I was not his match, I could only find you at night secretly and that resulted in our son Chang Ji You. But once he was born, if his bloodline was examined, the truth would be out and we would be doomed. Thus, I and Ha Tu Gu cooperated and plotted against Chang Shan Yin."

"Next, I used my status as Chang Shan Yin's brother to marry you and make Chang Ji You my godson. These years, although the tribe isn't in good shape, this is the happiest years of our lives. Chang Ji You was successfully made young tribe leader by me, but precisely so, you cannot expose this secret."

Once the secret is exposed, Chang Biao and Ni Xue Tong would get publicly shamed, they would be called an 'adulterous couple', and they will never be able to raise their heads again. They even caused harm to an expert of the tribe, for their own selfish motives, they disregarded the tribe's situation, it was truly a heinous crime!

As for Chang Ji You, he would be the shameful 'illegitimate child'. Be it his young tribe leader position, or Chang Biao's tribe leader position, they would be at risk of being taken, as people with ambitions would target them.

Righteous path had its own rules.

All along, Chang Biao had been taking care of his deceased brother's wife, and treated his godson as his own. Such brotherhood was admirable, such gracefulness was praised widely.

And exactly because of this, Chang Biao held a small advantage and became Chang tribe's new tribe leader.

Once this truth was exposed, he would lose everything. The ambitionists in the tribe would not let him go. In order to recruit Chang Shan Yin, Liu Wen Wu would not give up this chance.

By then, his only option would be to escape with Ni Xue Tong and his own flesh and blood Chang Ji You, becoming a demonic Gu Master. He would be despised by his tribe, and chased by his tribe.

"Why? Why! Why is Longevity Heaven doing this to us! We love each other so dearly, yet we end up in such a spot! Chang Shan Yin was the real culprit, he is an evil person, why is he praised. As for us, we can only wear a mask to live, even lying to our own son?" Ni Xue Tong cried profusely, she was very emotional.

These days, she had been under a lot of pressure.

Ever since 'Chang Shan Yin' reappeared, she had not been sleeping well, her former nightmare reappeared, causing her to fall into deep worry.

"Do you think that Liu tribe alliance leader is trying to recruit Chang Shan Yin? If Chang Shan Yin agrees, would we have to go back to that life? Chang Shan Yin is taking revenge everywhere now, will he find out the fact that we plotted against him? If he returns to the tribe, what will we do?" Lying in her lover's embrace, Ni Xue Tong asked multiple questions as she raised her neck.

"It won't happen, it won't. Don't think of it as such a severe situation." Chang Biao gently consoled the woman of his life.

"Firstly, Chang Shan Yin has not found out we were the culprit. Otherwise, with his nature, he would've declared it long ago and caused our reputation to go down the drain. He is only suspicious of Chang tribe having a traitor, but he does not know who."

"Liu alliance leader does want to recruit Chang Shan Yin, he is Wolf King after all, an enslavement path master, any alliance would welcome him and get his assistance. But Lord Liu Wen Wu is not a normal person, he knows clearly in his heart that there is little hope of getting the Wolf King to come over, his greatest intention is to sow discord and waver the Wolf King's fighting spirit."

"Think about it, Chang Shan Yin does not know about Chang Ji You's true identity, he thinks this is his son. As a father, what would he be thinking? Blood is thicker than water, when Chang Shan Yin thinks about Chang Ji You being killed by his wolf group, would he go all out in the upcoming battle?"

"Is that so..." Ni Xue Tong heard this and calmed down.

"Alright, stop worrying, I am here." Chang Biao patted Ni Xue Tong's back with an affectionate gaze.

The tent was filled with the warmth of love.

But this kind of atmosphere, how long would it last?

Neither Chang Biao nor Ni Xue Tong had any confidence in this.

Whoosh!

A person broke the large lizard house Gu's window and crashed in.

Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han sprawled on the ground, his face was bruised as he shouted loudly with a fearful and vicious expression: "Wolf King attacked, Wolf King attacked me! He is revolting, he is murdering us, help, save me!"

Sun Shi Han was a popular person near Hei Lou Lan, his shouts quickly attracted many Gu Masters.

Fang Yuan snorted, jumping out of the window and giving Sun Shi Han another kick.

Sun Shi Han did not dare to activate his Gu worm, he could only evade.

But Fang Yuan changed his attack just in time, sweeping with his right fist and slamming into Sun Shi Han's nose.

Sun Shi Han groaned, just as he got up from the ground, he fell again. His entire face was full of blood, his nose bridge was broken and two of his front teeth fell out, he was in a pathetic state.

But the Gu Masters who came did not do anything, they breathed a sigh of relief secretly.

Be it Fang Yuan or Sun Shi Han, they did not use their Gu worms. This was not breaking the rules, it was merely a small scuffle.

When people interacted, there was bound to be conflict. As arguments occur, it was normal to get physical. As long as Gu worms were not used to fight, the poison vow would not be violated.

"Chang Shan Yin, you are too arrogant! Your wife and children are at the enemy's camp, I am only reminding you out of kindness, you actually got furious and beat me! You are definitely guilty!" Sun Shi Han crawled up, shouting with his shrill voice.

The words caused the surrounding Gu Masters to talk among themselves. Chang tribe and Chang Shan Yin's relationship was known to all. These days, Hei tribe army had been talking about it.

Seeing Sun Shi Han's smug and vicious gaze, Fang Yuan laughed in disdain, he did not say a thing, but instead, responded with his fist.

Bam bam bam!

Fang Yuan's attacks were full of strength, although Sun Shi Han had some strength path foundation, how could it compare to Fang Yuan's immense investment in the strength path?

After several moves, he was beaten on the floor again, lying there as he was punched and kicked.

"Wolf King is amazing, although he is an enslavement path master, his strength path foundation is very strong." Everyone was shocked.

"Great fight, I had wanted to thrash this scoundrel Cunning Gentleman long ago." Some of the army's higher-ups smirked.

"Chang Shan Yin, you think I am easy to bully!" Sun Shi Han was thrashed until his body felt pain all over, his head was in a daze as his heart was filled with rage and humiliation.

"You still have the strength to speak." Fang Yuan snorted as he unleashed another round of punches.

Sun Shi Han was beaten to a pulp, he vomited blood as his front teeth all fell off, even the teeth at the back of his mouth were shaking.

"Wolf King is so ruthless..."

"Sun Shi Han is a rank four expert after all, to think he was beaten defenseless, what a weakling."

"Stupid! He made a poison vow and could not use Gu worms, in terms of close combat, Wolf King is an enslavement path master, he would definitely be suppressed by Sun Shi Han."

The discussions became louder, be it Chang Shan Yin or Sun Shi Han, they were people with great authority. Right now they were brawling it out, such a scene was rare, everyone was watching with bright eyes.

Sun Shi Han heard the comments and felt humiliated, he almost gritted his teeth off.

Although he barely had any left.

He wanted to resist, but neither his strength nor moves were Fang Yuan's match, he could not take a thrashing.

"Endure, I must endure! If I use a Gu, I would truly lose. I need to wait for alliance leader to come and uphold justice for me, Chang Shan Yin will get it!!" Sun Shi Han screamed in his heart.

"Alliance leader is here!"

"Greetings to lord alliance leader!!"

The surrounding people went into chaos as they quickly gave way.

Hei Lou Lan, Hao Ji Liu and others came to the area. Seeing this, Hei Lou Lan frowned as he asked Fang Yuan coldly: "What is going on?"

Sun Shi Han's body shuddered, using a mystical source of strength, he struggled as he crawled up and shouted: "Alliance leader, please seek justice for me..."

Plop.

Before he finished, Fang Yuan stepped on his head as he used great force, causing Sun Shi Han's entire face to sink into the soil.

Hei Lou Lan shouted loudly: "Stop it! Wolf King, what are you doing?!"

"H... he iz revulting! He ish revorting..." Sun Shi Han shouted loudly, his mouth was filled with soil as he spoke unclearly.

Fang Yuan sneered, exerting strength and stepping three times, burying Sun Shi Han's voice in the soil. Sun Shi Han's nose and mouth were blocked, his head also suffered a great hit, he felt dizzy and suffocation, his limbs struggled wildly but he could do nothing against Fang Yuan's strength.

Hei Lou Lan's face turned pitch black like charcoal.

Fang Yuan's gaze was like a dagger, staring coldly at him and the Gu Masters behind him: "Can't you all see what I am doing? I am thrashing him."

Hei Lou Lan stared at Fang Yuan angrily, shouting: "Wolf King, give me a clear explanation, why did you beat him up?! Are you really trying to rebel?"

Fang Yuan laughed in disdain, saying slowly: "No need to be angry Hei tribe leader, if I wanted to rebel, why would I need to make such a din?"

Saying so, he let go of Sun Shi Han.

Sun Shi Han lost the pressure and bounced up, desperately gasping for air like he was suffocating.

But Fang Yuan stepped again, this time, on his right cheek.

Sun Shi Han used both his hands to pull Fang Yuan's feet, but he was already weak and out of energy. Just like this, he was stepped on the face by someone in public, his reputation was ruined.

Fang Yuan said slowly and casually: "Although I have not thought of rebelling, I do not want any schemes or plots to fall on my wife and children. During the battle, I will do my part and fight with my full strength. By then, if they die, that would be their honor to die on the battlefield. Since I, Wolf King, have joined the Hei army, I would not change my stance just because of relationships. However..."

Saying so, he raised his head as he laughed arrogantly: "It is your own business to be suspicious, that has nothing to do with me. All the mutated beast groups that I want are exchanged using my battle merit, this is a fair trade. I have never owed you anything. Hei tribe leader, if you are suspicious of me, you can take away the mutated beast wolf groups and not let me control them. In the future battle, I swear in the name of the Wolf King, I will still go all-out."

"You..." Hei Lou Lan was furious.

Fang Yuan ignored his threat, and in fact, threatened him instead.

Being suspicious is your problem, you can keep the mutated wolves to yourselves. If we lose the battle, that will be your responsibility.

Can Hei Lou Lan not give them to him?

He had the great strength true martial physique, even if he used dark limit Immortal Gu, he was starting to feel the inability to suppress it. He needed a strength path Immortal Gu to advance to Gu Immortal realm.

However, Wolf King created a din and made everyone know about this. If he did not give him the mutated beast group, what would the army think of him? They would think that Hei Lou Lan refused to utilize Wolf King despite him being here. Like the saying goes, a man being used cannot be suspected while a suspected man cannot be used, if he loses the battle, everyone would begrudge Hei Lou Lan.

"Good, you are amazing Wolf King." Hei Lou Lan's gaze was cold, he laughed out of anger: "Of course I know the Wolf King's loyalty, but why did you beat up Sun Shi Han? He is your alliance mate, the enemy is before us, yet you engage in internal scuffle, what are you trying to do?"

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan shrugged: "This is my fault, because this Sun Shi Han looks way too ugly, he made my heart feel bad. Thus, I thrashed him and adjusted his appearance for him, as expected, he looks much better now. This was my personal action, I will take responsibility for it. According to the rules, I have to compensate Sun Shi Han ten thousand battle merits, no worries, I will compensate him!"

Sun Shi Han heard this and his anger rushed to his brain, he vomited out a mouthful of blood and fainted.

The words made all the Gu Master experts present unable to hold in their laughter.

It was too satisfying!

There were many who were unhappy with this scoundrel Sun Shi Han.

Fang Yuan's assault was truly soothing their hearts.

Even Tai Bai Yun Sheng's gaze towards Fang Yuan turned to admiration. He felt that although this Chang Shan Yin was ruthless, he did not strike at his family, but still maintained his righteousness and standpoint, he had his limits and was a true man.

Hei Lou Lan's expression turned even darker.

Sun Shi Han was his man, Fang Yuan beating him up in public was also slapping Hei Lou Lan's face.

Fang Yuan said it easily, but his battle merits were still in the negative!

But what could Hei Lou Lan do?

To deal with Liu tribe army, he needed to rely on the Wolf King's strength!

Threatening the Wolf King was to make him carry the sin of killing his own tribesmen, so that his reputation would be affected, allowing Hei Lou Lan to control him more easily.

But since threats had no effect, Hei Lou Lan only had one option left, that was to comply.

Chapter 531: Huge Battle (1/4)

The mornings of northern plains were getting colder.

White frost covered the grassland, and people blew out vapor when they breathed.

The two armies, with hundreds of thousands of soldiers, were confronting each other.

Banners fluttered in the sky and the troops formation were as dense as forests.

Liu tribe and Hei tribe had rested and reorganized for over a dozen days after the first battle before sending the war letter, and today, they both came out to battle once again.

"Second brother, you went out the previous time, it is my turn now!" Mo Shi Kuang restlessly shouted and impatiently charged towards the front.

Mo Shi Kuang's white hair fluttered, his black skin and panther-like eyes shone, his momentum was thunderous as he shouted: "Who seeks death?"

"This black barbarian again!" Hei tribe's higher-ups felt anger and fear at the sight of Mo Shi Kuang. In the battle before, many rank four Gu Masters had lost their lives at Mo Shi Kuang's hands. Mo Shi Kuang's brutal fighting style caused people to be fearful.

Hei Lou Lan scoffed, his expression much relaxed than before. He looked at the two new faces in the main tent: "Who among you would like to go first?"

These two were Gao Yang and Zhu Zai, rank four peak stage Gu Masters, their name of demonic path's twin demons was spread far and wide.

In their early days, demonic path's twin demons had received Tai Bai Yun Sheng's grace and swore to repay him. Not long ago, Tai Bai Yun Sheng used a letter Gu to try calling them. And a few days ago, they took the initiative to side with Hei tribe army.

The addition of the two of them immediately filled the gap between Hei tribe and Liu tribe army and allowed Hei tribe's higher ranked strength to be free from the previous strained circumstances.

Demonic path's twin demons were inseparable, but the rule of the challenge was that every side could only send one person to battle.

The two glanced at each other, already having discussed according to the intel Hei tribe had given them. Zhu Zai stood up and slightly bowed: "I shall go."

Hei Lou Lan nodded.

Mo Shi Kuang stared at Zhu Zai's arrival, revealing a happy expression.

"A rank four peak stage, good, good! But you don't look that impressive, I hope you won't go down with just a few punches."

Zhu Zai snorted and activated a Gu, his body then rapidly charged forward like an artillery shell.

Mo Shi Kuang stood at the spot while licking his dried lips, prepared to receive the attack.

BOOM!

Zhu Zai ruthlessly smashed against Mo Shi Kuang, creating an explosive sound like that of crackling thunder. The berserk collision of strength resulted in Zhu Zai retreating several steps while Mo Shi Kuang was directly sent flying.

"Third brother, be careful. This person is Zhu Zai of the demonic path's twin demons, he cultivates strength path!" Liu Wen Wu reminded in a loud voice from the main tent.

"Hahaha, strength path Gu Master? Great! I like fighting with such exciting opponents!" Mo Shi Kuang spurted out blood from the injury. He jumped up from the ground, the injury making him more excited instead.

A crazed look appeared on his coal-like inky black skin, a loud sound echoed, his aura started surging and Mo Shi Kuang charged towards Zhu Zai.

"Courting death!" Zhu Zai smiled sinisterly as he pounced forward as well.

BOOM BOOM BOOM.

The two sides engaged in close combat, their attacks were so fierce and heavy that the collision produced a series of explosive sounds. Mo Shi Kuang was a qi path Gu Master and was using his weakness to fight the enemy's strong point, but he unexpectedly was not in a disadvantage while fighting such an intense battle with the strength path Gu Master Zhu Zai!

"Strange, could it be that this Mo Shi Kuang cultivates both qi and strength path?" Hei tribe camp was in a state of shock.

"It is not like that, Mo Shi Kuang looks like he is fighting close combat, but in truth, his punches are not really landing physically, instead he has a translucent qi armor over his body which he explodes by using qi explosion Gu at the same time, creating an explosive strength comparable to strength path." Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han said in a solemn voice.

He was specialized in investigating and with careful observation, he managed to see through the trick Mo Shi Kuang was playing.

By synergizing with qi explosion Gu, qi armor Gu became a weapon that could both attack and defend. Gu Masters relied on their wits to use Gu. Often, the coordination of different Gu worms could form a complementing effect.

"This Mo Shi Kuang is really fierce, this is the first time I saw someone actually suppressing brother Zhu Zai head on!" Gao Yang's expression was solemn, he had been observing the battle since the start.

He was extremely familiar with Zhu Zai and understood Zhu Zai was already using almost all his strength, but the enemy, however, was moving so easily and was clearly much relaxed.

Suddenly, the mad growl of a boar exploded in the air.

The beast phantom of a grand emperor boar that was as large as an elephant and had awe-inspiring might, appeared in the air.

Grand emperor boar was a mutated boar, its strength could not be looked down on.

After dozen or so moves, Zhu Zai finally unleashed a beast phantom. Instantly, his offensive power rose sharply and Mo Shi Kuang was caught unprepared as the huge strength struck him and sent him rolling on the ground.

Zhu Zai took the chance to chase him and activated his trump card.

The grand emperor boar phantom gradually disappeared from the air before condensing again. Moreover, another two grand emperor boar phantoms also appeared.

Three grand emperor boar strength!

BOOM!

The enormous strength burst out, causing Zhu Zai's every punch to create sonic booms.

Mo Shi Kuang felt a sense of crisis and laughed madly: "Interesting! Come, I will show you my true strength!"

He activated his movement Gu and swiftly flew up, easily dodging the attack of Zhu Zai's three boar strength.

Zhu Zai's punch landed on the ground, creating a huge crater with stones and mud flying everywhere.

Mo Shi Kuang's white hair fluttered in the air as he hovered in the air. He then sent punches after punches towards Zhu Zai.

ORAORAORA...

Fist qi smashed down like a meteor rain.

Zhu Zai kept on dodging while also striking back and destroying these fist qi. But soon after, he was falling into a disadvantage.

Facing a qi path opponent, Zhu Zai's strength path's most common weakness started becoming obvious. He was not like Fang Yuan who had strength qi Gu. Zhu Zai lacked long range attacking methods, and Mo Shi Kuang was able to quickly suppress him after changing his battle tactics.

"Not good, brother Zhu Zai won't be able to hold on if he keeps on defending!" Gao Yang knew Zhu Zai's strengths and weaknesses, and was very anxious at this scene as he immediately asked to be sent to battle.

Hei Lou Lan also saw the unfavorable situation and immediately agreed.

"A mere variant human, I will teach you a lesson!" Gao Yang softly shouted, mist started curling around him before condensing into a ribbon that pushed him forward.

"Don't even think of using numbers as an advantage!" Ouyang Bi Sang snorted and moved almost at the same time. His speed was very fast, intercepting Gao Yang midway.

Gao Yang was concerned about Zhu Zai and did not even have any thoughts of fighting Ouyang Bi Sang as he activated cloud rope Gu from a distance.

Milky white mist surged around Ouyang Bi Sang before condensing into a rope which firmly bound him.

Gao Yang was specialized in defense and pinning down enemies, while Zhu Zai was specialized in attacking and investigation; the cooperation between the two complemented each other very well.

Ouyang Bi Sang struggled, the cloud rope shook and broke before condensing again, and actually had the signs of multiplying.

Ouyang Bi Sang was furious as he started transferring his primeval essence into asura zombie Gu in his aperture and transforming into a zombie.

With the transformation into asura zombie, his defense and strength surged rapidly.

Ouyang Bi Sang growled and completely broke the cloud rope with three times the strength. He stamped his foot and flew to the air, blocking Gao Yang again.

Asura zombie was one of the five great flying zombie Gu, it naturally had the ability to fly.

Gao Yang simply did not want to tangle with Ouyang Bi Sang; his brows furrowed deeply as he looked at Ouyang Bi Sang blocking him again, and knew the other wanted to provide time for Mo Shi Kuang to kill Zhu Zai. At this thought, he directly activated his trump card Gu.

Rank five, treacherous cloud wave Gu!

His primeval sea rapidly fell down, almost lowering by half.

A grey cloud that was as big as a carriage surged with dark red light floating inside, and rapidly flew towards Ouyang Bi Sang.

Ouyang Bi Sang moved around and dodged few times, but this cloud followed him like a shadow and finally covered him.

The instant Ouyang Bi Sang was struck by treacherous cloud wave Gu, he felt his sense of direction was lost, his mind seemed to work extremely slowly and his thoughts were slowed down by many times!

He could not differentiate which way was east and which was west and even lost the sense of up and down, left and right. For a moment, as he was covered in the grey cloud, he was like a headless fly that was tossing around in the sky.

"Mo Shi Kuang, don't be too rampant!" Gao Yang left Ouyang Bi Sang and finally was able to reinforce Zhu Zai in time.

The two combined their strength, and with their deep tacit-understanding, even Mo Shi Kuang who was fierce and fearless was being gradually suppressed.

But the three had exchanged no more than over twenty moves when they heard Ouyang Bi Sang's shout: "Asura transformation!"

Instantly, six thick arms which looked like they were casted in bronze stretched out through the grey cloud.

From outside, one could vaguely see the figure, inside the grey cloud, inflating like a balloon.

Ouyang Bi Sang used his killer move, his battle strength exploding by several times. His body shook, shaking the dim and lightless grey cloud into dispersing!

"You despicable scoundrels, die!" Ouyang Bi Sang was thoroughly furious as he flew into the air and attacked Gao Yang and Zhu Zai with Mo Shi Kuang.

With such an expert joining the battle, Zhu Zai and Gao Yang were forced to passively defend; the situation had dramatically turned into that of a crisis.

"Alliance leader, Gao Yang and Zhu Zai are experts we must have, we cannot let them die like this!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng saw the situation had turned bad and immediately spoke up.

"Sir's words are reasonable!" Hei Lou Lan was solemn, and suddenly stood up from his seat.

Although Gao Yang and Zhu Zai had joined them, Hei tribe was still weaker than Liu tribe in terms of higher ranked strength. Hei Lou Lan waved his hand, and just like what he saw Fang Yuan doing, sent the order for an all-out war!

The command was sent and the army began to move.

Liu Wen Wu sneered: "You could not win in experts challenge and now come to gang up. Good, I will accompany you!"

Buggles rang and war drums shook the battlefield; Liu tribe army also moved out.

Two sides, both with hundreds of thousands of soldiers, surged towards the other like a torrent.

The distance between the two army was quickly cut down, and when they were few hundred steps afar, Gu Masters began to attack almost at the same time. For a moment, large numbers of pill fire, icicles, bone spears and wind blades shot towards the enemies. Light armors, bone shields, water barriers and all kinds of defensive abilities were also activated. The originally simple scene had turned into a gorgeous painting of all colors.

BOOM BOOM BOOM......

The attacks from both sides landed on each other almost at the same time.

Like a rainstorm falling down on the lake, ripples started spreading. Only a few Gu Masters with bad luck died or were heavily injured in the intense storm of attack. Most of the Gu Masters continued to attack till the army of the both sides collided. Like the collision of two torrents, blood splattered and chaos descended.

Chapter 532: Huge Battle (2/4)

At once, even Gao Yang, Zhu Zai, Mo Shi Kuang, and Ouyang Bi Sang's battles were interrupted by the huge influx of people.

The two armies intertwined completely, as fighting sounds erupted and filled the heavens.

Waterfall Gu!

In the chaotic battle, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu pushed with his palms as a great current burst forth, sweeping the Gu Masters in front of him irregardless of alliance.

Great tornado Gu!

A large dark-green tornado over tens of meters tall swept the battlefield. Everywhere it went, humans and beasts flew into the air as they lost their balance.

The tornado dispersed and revealed Chang Biao within.

He was floating in the air with his green robe, he had an overwhelming aura.

He and Hao Ji Liu were not far away, naturally, the two rank four experts made eye contact with each other.

The next moment, there were no trash talks, they fought immediately.

　　...

A flash of golden lightning pierced the battlefield, all the Hei tribe Gu Masters in its path lost their lives.

The golden light dispersed, and a stoic man with broad shoulders and thin waist appeared, it was Pei Yan Fei!

"Chang Shan Yin, today, I will behead you and take revenge for what happened back then! Eh?" Pei Yan Fei was overflowing with battle intent, fire was burning within him when suddenly, his gaze concentrated and he activated his defensive Gu in time.

Behind him, a lump of shadow exploded.

The shadow was deep and profound, turning into multiple sword shadows as it attacked his back, causing Pei Yan Fei to sway violently.

"It's you, Shadow Sword Expert!" Pei Yan Fei stabilized his footing as he looked at the Gu Master who attacked him, his gaze becoming serious.

Bian Si Xuan who had a black veil covering her face laughed: "Lord Pei Yan Fei is too courteous."

She spoke very respectfully, but her actions were not. The black shadow swords appeared again like a windmill, engulfing Pei Yan Fei.

"Then I shall kill you first!" Pei Yan Fei laughed loudly as he charged forward.

　　...

"Our battle has not ended, where are you two going?" Ouyang Bi Sang, Mo Shi Kuang came before the demonic path twin demons.

Gao Yang and Zhu Zai felt bitter, they could only continue and engage in battle with Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang.

As the Gu Master experts continued fighting, their battle rings formed into distinct areas, and the chaotic battlefield gradually became clear.

Tens of large battle rings were filled with rank four to five experts. Outside the large rings, there were small battle rings with rank three Gu Masters as the main strength.

Outside the small rings, low rank Gu Masters form into groups as they fought together in teams.

As the main commander, Hei Lou Lan and Liu Wen Wu were sitting in their main tents, observing the battle situation. At times, they gave orders and dispatched their elite troops to areas of the battlefield to stabilize the situation or to pursue their advantage.

The giant battlefield soon gave off the thick scent of blood. Gu Masters continued to fall, some were turned into icicles, while others were charred, some were torn to pieces while others were poisoned to death.

The clean grassland became a weird monster, devouring fresh blood and life every minute and second.

The battle was so intense, after a while, Hei Lou Lan and Liu Wen Wu were both breaking out in cold sweat.

Large numbers of casualties made their hearts turn cold. The intensity of battle made people's hearts go numb.

To maintain the situation, the two quickly dispatched their trump cards, the elite troops. Only the black banner elite troops and grand white elite were left to control the area.

As time flowed, deaths and injuries became less, after all, the explosive strength only appeared at the start, by now, Gu Masters experienced intense primeval essence expenditure and were starting to reduce their usage, this way, the battle intensity started to decrease.

The battle entered a stalemate.

The two armies were like two giants competing at equal strength. Either side could snowball from a tiny advantage, until they emerged victorious, and become the winner of the battlefield.

"Our higher level battle strength are doing well. Wolf King, now that the rank five lurking soul coat Gu is in your hands, together with the mutated beast wolf group, the rest will be up to you." Hei Lou Lan transmitted with his Gu worm.

At the start of the battle, Fang Yuan was already not in the main tent, but lurking somewhere on the battlefield. His exact location was not known by Hei Lou Lan either.

Fang Yuan received Hei Lou Lan's words, but he did not reply. He mobilized the wolf group and started to sprint in two directions.

Liu tribe Gu Masters subconsciously chased after them, but this way, the tight formation was loosened.

Howl!

A group of over eight hundred mutated beast wolf group, comprising white-eyes wolves, blood forest wolves, frenzy wolves, shark fin wolves. The wolf group was like a sharp arrow, shooting out and piercing towards Liu tribe's main camp.

Fang Yuan's attack was a fatal blow, it was vicious and cruel, striking at the enemy's vital points.

"A group of mutated beasts reinforcement as expected huh..." Liu Wen Wu looked at the charging wolves that disrupted his formation, large numbers of Gu Masters lost their lives to the wolves as he frowned deeply.

Hei tribe's Gu Immortal supplying mutated wolves was information easy to obtain, it was no secret.

Liu Wen Wu was unfazed, he had Liu tribe's Gu Immortals backing him as well, along with the entire Liu tribe. He had his ways of dealing with this mutated beast wolf group.

"Bei Cao Chuan, it is time to strike." Liu Wen Wu instructed the Gu Master beside him.

Bei Cao Chuan was expressionless, standing up from his seat as he frowned: "I can only last for seven minutes."

Liu Wen Wu nodded:" No worry, go ahead."

Bei Cao Chuan walked out of the main tent, his primeval essence rapidly expending as he activated the Gu worm that he had obtained not long ago.

The refreshing aura of grass and wood spread from his body, for a radius of a hundred li.

All the grass within the range of this aura grew wildly, in a few breath's time, they grew taller than a man's height. The large blades of grass intertwined, forming rank two grass soldier puppets.

Soon, there were a thousand grass soldier puppets.

Bei Cao Chuan activated his Gu worm, as a jade colored light rained down. The grass puppets were bathed in the green rain water, as a portion of them advanced to rank three rattan shell grass soldiers. At the same time, the rank two grass puppets were still growing.

Bei Cao Chuan activated his Gu worm again, as an orange wind blew on the grassland. As the wind blew, a portion of the rattan shell grass soldiers advanced into the rank four grass sword elite soldiers!

The empty central camp quickly was filled with an army of grass soldiers. At once, it became the most densely packed area in the battlefield.

The charging mutated wolf group was obstructed by these obstacles.

Fang Yuan frowned, he manipulated wholeheartedly. He hid on the back of the blood forest wolf, his body cloaked in the rank five lurking soul coat Gu, it was like a green-grey wolf skin cape.

The lurking soul coat Gu was indeed amazing, it concealed Fang Yuan's soul and allowed him to strike with his full strength.

But at this time, Fang Yuan felt that he was battling against an enslavement path master.

Bei Cao Chuan manipulated the grass soldier army as tears overflowed his face.

He now had two souls in one body, in order to defeat Wolf King Chang Shan Yin, Bei tribe's elder Bei Cao Sheng sacrificed himself and entrusted his soul to Bei Cao Chuan. Using Liu Wen Wu's Gu worm, Bei Cao Chuan absorbed the power of Bei Cao Sheng's soul, causing him to gain the attainment of an enslavement path master within this short period of time.

Bei Cao Chuan was originally a rank four enslavement path Gu Master, he was also Bei tribe leader, he had the resources of a clan, his soul foundation was not weak. With Bei Cao Sheng's help, he was like a tiger with wings, his enslavement path battle strength surged.

Except that this move had huge repercussions. Because he used another person's soul, Bei Cao Chuan's soul will be impure and he would have memory lapses, he would need to expend huge amounts of spirit and resources, using specialized soul path Gu worms to nourish his soul and heal this problem.

But now, in order to defeat Hei tribe army and take revenge, Bei Cao Chuan could not care less about the aftermath.

Hei tribe had invited Gao Yang and Zhu Zai to mend the gap of their higher level battle strength. And Liu tribe thought of this method to replenish their lower level battle strength, raising Bei Cao Chuan's strength to enslavement path master so that he could restrict Fang Yuan.

At once, Fang Yuan's mutated beast wolf group was barely resisted by the grass soldier army.

"We blocked it? Hahah! Hei Lou Lan, you are bound to lose!" Liu Wen Wu saw this and the worry in his heart vanished, he laughed heartily as his voice resounded the battlefield.

"Damn it..." Hei Lou Lan clenched his fist and gritted his teeth. The situation was terrible, Gao Yang and Zhu Zai were in great danger, and the mutated wolf group that he had placed his hope on was restricted at the enemy's camp, unable to progress!

Without a choice, he had to mobilize the black banner troops.

"Brothers, it is finally time for us black banner to strike!" Black banner commander received this order and shouted excitedly.

Black banner troop was nurtured by Hei tribe for a long time, the trump card made from expending huge amounts of resources. Once they were deployed, they were like a black blade that stabbed into the battlefield, easily slicing it like tofu.

The entire black banner troop was reinforced by battle will Gu, they were brave and peerless, not afraid of death. They could display 120% of their original strength!

"Can't control it anymore huh?" Liu Wen Wu's eyes shone brilliantly, staring at the black banner troop's movements.

When he saw the black banner troop making a curve around the battlefield, towards his central camp, he instantly understood Hei Lou Lan's intention.

"So you are trying to stake it all on this, gathering your advantage and piercing the grass soldier army. Hmph, Bei Cao Chuan had such difficulty resisting Chang Shan Yin, if the black banner troops appeared, he would definitely fall. By then, Hei tribe would have a mild advantage and this crucial beast group would be free to attack."

Thinking so, Liu Wen Wu laughed arrogantly: "Your Hei tribe has black banner troops, renowned in northern plains. My Liu tribe also has the grand white troops, of similar magnitude of fame. Black banner and grand white's competition had been ongoing for hundred of years, let's see who wins today."

Under his command, the grand white troops unleashed one of their three killer moves directly.

The grand white troops exploded with a piercing white light.

The white light formed into a giant light pillar that pierced into the heavens.

The light pillar rose up, but after an instant, it descended from the sky, shooting at the area that the black banner troops were advancing towards. The three black banner commanders saw this familiar killer move and ordered their troops to stay on guard.

The light pillar dispersed and the grand white troops appeared with a tight formation.

Grand white troops were foot soldiers, while black banner troops rode battle horses. But in terms of mobility, grand white troops were superior, it was none other than the ability of this killer move!

Chapter 533: Huge Battle (3/4)

Black banner troops and grand white troops started to fight, ever since they were created, they were opposing forces that had contested for hundreds of years, having victories and losses on both sides. At this moment, the two troops engaged in battle and unleashed their killer moves, having no clear advantage on each side.

Seeing his final trump card engaged in a deadlock, Hei Lou Lan's expression turned pitch black.

"Hehehe." Liu Wen Wu laughed heartily, feeling great pleasure, his opponent was at his wit's end, but he was in the same situation.

However, the grass soldier army could still blok the mutated beast wolf group for some time. As for Hei tribe's higher level battle force, they had already shown signs of collapsing, especially Gao Yang and Zhu Zai against Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang, their battle was very obviously showing signs of a victor emerging.

Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang, although they were not skilled at cooperating, they had greater individual strength than their opponents.

If Gao Yang and Zhu Zai were fighting two against one, using their great chemistry, they could have a mild advantage. But now, they could only be suppressed, defending desperately as they were in a passive situation.

Anyone could tell that Gao Yang and Zhu Zai were going to fail very soon. Once they lose, Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang would be like tigers out of a cage, they would start to reinforce other battles.

That way, their mild advantage will snowball and accumulate, allowing the entire battle to sway in his favor.

Once Liu tribe army gains the advantage, Hei tribe without any more backup would have no way of winning, they would only be able to watch their opponent grow stronger as they fall into a worse situation.

Eventually, the other side will turn advantage into victory, and Hei tribe army would crumble!

Hei Lou Lan could see the problem now, he was sweating profusely. He was all alone in the main tent, at this point, he could only rely on his own strength!

His body vanished in the main tent, appeared in the air above the grass soldier army.

He had the intention of killing Bei Cao Chuan, since Bei Cao Chuan did not have lurking soul coat Gu, he was easy to distinguish, once he is killed, the grass soldier army would crumble.

That way, this battle would go back into a double offense situation, at the end, it would be like the first battle, they would have to regroup and retreat.

Killer move — Dark Vortex!

Hei Lou Lan had just activated his killer move, when a white light appeared before him, showing Liu Wen Wu's body.

Hei Lou Lan was a dark path rank five, while Liu Wen Wu was a light path rank five, the two had engaged in combat for many times without a clear victor.

But this time, the gentleman-like Liu Wen Wu showed a mild smile of a victor: "Brother Lou Lan, today's battle depends on a single ray of light. My grass soldier army is going to fall soon, but your higher level battle strength will falter more quickly. What a pity, our armies have very close battle strength, we are nearly evenly matched."

"You are courting death!" Hei Lou Lan shouted furiously, growling and charging at Liu Wen Wu.

The two fought as they moved around, exploding with thunderous sounds or brilliant lights.

"Strange, in my previous life, Hei tribe defeated Liu tribe, but it seems that Liu tribe has the advantage now. Was it because of me that some weird changes occurred?" Fang Yuan hid at a corner as he secretly observed.

He was an enslavement-strength dual cultivator, he had not displayed his full strength yet.

In fact, he had not even displayed his full enslavement path abilities yet.

At this moment, the grass soldier army was barely holding on, he just had to show up and unleash the wolf howl Gu and rank five amplify effect Gu to instantly defeat Bei Cao Chuan.

But Fang Yuan did not move, he chose to observe.

His attention was on Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang.

Once he showed up, and activated wolf howl Gu and rank five amplify effect Gu, there was a huge possibility that the two of them would come after him.

Truthfully speaking, Fang Yuan was already accomplished in strength path, he was not afraid of fighting Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang together in close combat.

But...

"My vision cannot be limited to this battle. The fight for the Imperial Court is a competition among super tribes, a game manipulated by Gu Immortals. Once I expose my full strength, even if we win this battle, the other party will definitely target me when they get reinforced by their Gu Immortal. By then, I would have no more hidden trump cards left, my grasp over this situation would fall to rock bottom."

Fang Yuan's mind was on the Imperial Court, he kept calm at all times and was not disturbed by the dangerous situation ahead of him.

"In my previous life, how did Hei tribe defeat Liu tribe? Although the battle is extremely tense now, both sides had not used their trump cards yet. At least I know that Tai Bai Yun Sheng has a rank five Gu 'man as before'. The less battle strength I expose, the better it is for me. If I strike, it has to be a fatal blow! Now is not the time yet..."

Fang Yuan's heart was calm, despite this intense battlefield that was filled with corpses and rivers of blood.

In his eyes, these casualties were just numbers.

In this battle, many people screamed at the deaths of their friends and family, many people shouted in joy after killing a strong foe, some Gu Masters ran away under the fear of death. Some Gu Masters were filled with ambition, wanting to be a person of higher status.

Human emotions became riled up in such moments of life and death, they were frenzied, crazy, while arrogant and unrestrained.

Observing the ruthless expressions of the people around, hearing their screaming and shouting, Fang Yuan felt a great sense of serenity and peace.

His heart was firm like an ancient abyss, there were no ripples on the surface.

Fight, kill, a person is born to engage in battle.

Win, lose, continue walking on your path, by stepping on other people's corpses.

Let blood boil, let sweat flow, the best moment of life is now...

"Take this, this is my killer move — World Devouring Qi!" In the battlefield, an explosive and thunderous shout burst out.

His voice attracted numerous gazes as everyone subconsciously focused on it.

"Oh no, let's go!" An intense sense of danger assaulted him as Gao Yang shouted, activating his Gu worm and wanting to escape, but the surrounding air was as dense as walls, he could barely move.

Mo Shi Kuang floated in the air, opening his hands as his ten fingers converged before his chest.

Gao Yang and Zhu Zai felt a despairing sense of pressure, squashing them from all directions. Their shocked expressions froze on their faces, the feeling of imminent death filled their hearts.

"Go!" Before the moment of death, Zhu Zai burst out the strength of three grand emperor boar, piercing a hole on the wall-like air.

"Brother!" Gao Yang felt his world spinning, when he reacted, he had already been tossed far away by Zhu Zai, away from the battlefield.

As for Zhu Zai, he was squeezed into meat paste by Mo Shi Kuang's killer move, through an intense and concentrated air pressure.

"Brother!!" Gao Yang shouted, his heart felt like it was pierced by daggers as tears flowed out of his eyes like a flood.

Mo Shi Kuang also vomited a mouthful of blood.

"Second brother, your killer move is not completed yet, don't activate it casually." Ouyang Bi Sang quickly hurried over and held him in the air.

Mo Shi Kuang vomited blood as he laughed: "What a great battle, I used it without thinking, hahaha..."

Ouyang Bi Sang shook his head: "Alright, let's continue killing that Gao Yang, after we resolve the problem here, we will reinforce the other battles!"

Liu Wen Wu who saw this laughed, he declared with overwhelming confidence: "This is the start of our Liu tribe army's consecutive victories! Brother Lou Lan, you have no way of winning already!"

"Is that so?" It was not Hei Lou Lan who replied him, but Tai Bai Yun Sheng who was at another battle ring.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng who had always been evading attacks suddenly burst out with great speed as he pulled some distance from his opponent, opening his palms and shooting out a silver beam.

The silver beam shone on Zhu Zai's flesh and blood that became meat paste.

Rank five — Man As Before!

In an instant, silver light shone brilliantly, making people close their eyes in response.

After the light faded, Zhu Zai reappeared on the battlefield, without any injuries on him, as his primeval sea level was also at its peak.

Under the effect of man as before, Zhu Zai returned to the state right before the battle!

The shocked expression not only appeared on multiple Gu Masters' faces, even Liu Wen Wu, Mo Shi Kuang, and Ouyang Bi Sang had the same expression.

Man as before Gu had an incredible healing effect that made almost everyone feel shocked and speechless!

Man as before Gu, time path healing Gu, could return a target to his condition at a point in time.

"Good, what a great healing Gu!" Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily, he did not expect Tai Bai Yun Sheng to be concealing such a strong trump card. As long as they had this, Hei tribe's higher level battle could drag on for a long time.

"Good, now is the time!" Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance as he activated rank four eagle rise Gu, flying up into the sky.

Rank five amplify effect Gu and rank four wolf howl Gu!

Fang Yuan opened his mouth and howled, as his voice spread far and wide.

Under the effect of the wolf howl Gu, all his mutated beasts' bodies expanded, as their eyes turned bright red, their battle strength grew by five times!

"Go." Fang Yuan floated in the air, staring at the battlefield as he muttered.

The wolf tide burst out, like a tsunami out of nowhere!

"Damn it, I can't hold on!" Bei Cao Chuan was at his wit's end, he resisted desperately, but the grass soldier army was like a thin piece of paper under the wolf tide, it was torn to shreds without even lasting for a few breath's time.

Bei Cao Chuan did not even manage to escape before a frenzy wolf pounced on him and tore his armor with its sharp teeth, before biting his throat.

Bei Cao Chuan resisted with all his strength, sending this frenzy wolf flying, just as he was about to cover his neck and get up, three white-eyes wolves came and after a struggle, he was a corpse torn into several pieces.

The grass soldier army went down, Fang Yuan thus manipulated the wolf group and attacked grand white troops.

Grand white troops were fighting with black banner troops, they were stuck in a stalemate as they exchanged blows. Now that the mutated beast wolf group attacked them from behind, they suffered heavy injuries.

"Hahaha, Liu Wen Wu, it seems that I have the last laugh!" The battle turned in such a sudden direction, Hei Lou Lan was overjoyed and surprised.

"No, I have not lost yet!" Liu Wen Wu's face was distorted as he shouted frantically, like a gambler who had gone crazy from losing. He turned into a white light, flying towards Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang.

"Second brother, third brother!" He shouted.

Chapter 534: Huge Battle (4/4)

"We are here, big brother!" Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang shouted at the same time.

"Let them see the true strength of us three brothers!" Liu Wen Wu shouted, and without slowing down, directly smashed into Mo Shi Kuang and Ouyang Bi Sang.

The two laughed loudly, their body giving off green and grey light.

Green, grey and white, three lights collided. BOOM!. Light dispersed and on the spot appeared a human-shaped monster.

This monster had three heads and six arms. It was twenty feet tall with tight muscles and bronze skin.

The three heads had the appearance of Liu Wen Wu, Ouyang Bi Sang and Mo Shi Kuang.

"This....?!" Countless people looked on with wide eyes at this freakish scene.

"I will let you guys know, this is our three brothers' killer move — Three Heads Six Arms! Are you trembling in fear? Let out all your dread. This will be the last moment of your lives!"

The three heads spoke in unison.

"Hmph, shameless boasting!" Gao Yang snorted, activating his treacherous cloud wave Gu.

A grey cloud shot towards the three heads six arms giant, but before it even reached its target, Liu Wen Wu's eyes shot two light beams that pierced through the cloud.

BOOM!

With a sonic boom, the three heads six arms suddenly appeared above Gao Yang.

"So fast!" Gao Yang's pupils shrunk and from the battle experiences he had cultivated over a long period of time, he quickly activated his defense Gu.

The monster waved its two arms.

One arm pierced through the light barrier while another arm smashed Gao Yang's head like it smashed a watermelon.

Next moment, Gao Yang's headless corpse fell down from the sky.

"Brother!!!" Rage attacked Zhu Zai's heart and made him lose all reasoning, as he ferociously charged towards the monster.

"Muahahaha, the lamentation of ants." Mo Shi Kuang's head laughed loudly and lightly flicked his finger towards Zhu Zai.

BOOM!!!

Qi flow exploded and moved straight through the battlefield with formidable impact force, inflicting injuries for several thousands of steps.

Zhu Zai directly exploded from the attack, his blood and crushed bones flying in all directions. The Gu Masters who suffered the after-effects of the attack were all injured heavily.

"This power... it has increased by at least six times and the speed has increased by nine times at least! This three people combination, is it combining asura transformation, the attacking force of qi path and the effects of light path?" Fang Yuan had an intense urge to battle when he looked at this scene.

"I have all-out effort Gu, and by adding in rank five amplify effect Gu, I can burst out with five hundred jun of strength! I wonder who would win if I fight with this monster?"

But in the next moment, Fang Yuan suppressed his battle intent and flew down, again hiding among the mutated beast group.

Man as before Gu!

At this moment, two silver lights shone down; Zhu Zai and Gao Yang resurrected again, restored to their previous state!

"Old geezer!" The monster's six eyes were filled with icy glint, killing intent and battle intent, simultaneously charging towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng panickedly retreated; although he had man as before Gu, he could only use it on others and could not use it on himself.

"All those that are free, protect Tai Bai Yun Sheng!!" Hei Lou Lan hurried to reinforce while shouting to his army, realizing the crux of the battle.

"Who can stop me?" Ouyang Bi Sang's head loftily smiled.

Next instant, the monster turned into a ray of green light that shot towards Tai Bai Yun Sheng like lightning.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was hiding behind others, but no one was able to block the monster as it charged straight, sweeping everything on its path. Anyone that dared to block it, be it Gu Masters or beasts, would become pools of crushed flesh and bones.

"Benefactor, leave quickly!" Gao Yang and Zhu Zai rushed over, guarding Tai Bai Yun Sheng behind them.

"Cumbersome things." The monster waved its six arms so quick that one could only see their afterimage.

THUMP THUMP, Zhu Zai and Gao Yang were smashed again.

"Take my sole blade Gu!" Pan Ping hurried over and activated sole blade Gu.

Sole blade Gu successfully activated this time and the monster's huge body slightly shook, a shallow wound appearing on its chest.

"A little interesting." The monster laughed coldly; the wound had completely recovered by the time he finished laughing. Afterwards, the monster let out a breath of turbid air.

The turbid air detonated and exploded Pan Ping into pieces.

"Tai Bai Yun Sheng, where are you going?" The monster howled with laughter, the voices of the three heads gradually becoming one.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had not moved very far when the monster intercepted in front of him.

Swoosh!

Waterfall flowed in a torrent and Hao Ji Liu came riding it.

The monster pushed forward with all six hands and collapsed the water torrent; Hao Ji Liu screamed miserably and flew backwards in a faster speed than he came.

Seeing this scene, Bian Si Xuan who was charging forward immediately stopped, not daring to go forward.

Dark vortex!

Hei Lou Lan sped down from the sky, and the giant black sphere that was as large as a hill pressed down.

The monster roared, its six hands forming into a claw shape and slashing towards the distant black sphere.

Killer move — World Devouring Qi!

The air became as thick as a wall and solid as a mountain. Hei Lou Lan's face turned red and purple, but he was not able to continue forward.

Following after, air from all around surged and unexpectedly swallowed his killer move.

The killer move which Mo Shi Kuang could not carry out completely was suddenly perfected in the monster's hand.

Howl!

The mutated wolf group rushed over while Hei Lou Lan delayed the monster. In an instant, the mutated wolf group had surrounded the monster tightly.

A bloody battle broke out.

The mutated wolves which had a strength of rank four Gu Masters, fearlessly initiated a death charge at the monster.

"KILL KILL KILL!" The monster growled repeatedly as it turned into a berserk state and started fighting the mutated wolves.

His every movement carried his full power. Light path, qi path and transformation path Gu worms jointly attacked with deep tacit cooperation, as if the monster was a cultivator cultivating three paths!

The mutated wolves died one after another, but the monster's offensive was still as fierce as before.

"Lord alliance leader, let me lend you a hand!" At this moment, a Liu tribe Gu Master hurried over to assist.

But in the next moment, he was smashed apart alive by the monster which had lost its reason!

"Lord Liu Wen Wu has lost his mind!"

"He has become mad!!"

The battlefield was in an uproar and Liu tribe army's morale fell down sharply.

"My tribe has suffered tremendous losses, we have lost one-third of our Gu Masters, it is time to retreat."

"How can such an alliance leader be worth us giving up our lives?"

"Let's discuss after we retreat, the casualties have already reached a high level. Retreat now, don't care about violating the poison vow."

The battle had reached such a chaotic state that was beyond everyone's expectation. Deserters started to appear from both Hei and Liu tribe.

The black banner troops and grand white troops that had been managing the army were in an intense fight now, how could they have the energy to spare to suppress these deserters?

"What to do?" Hei Lou Lan asked; this monster gave him an extreme headache.

"Don't worry. Killer moves have astonishing might but their consumption of primeval essence is also enormous. Moreover, this killer move clearly has a defect, this monster has already lost its reasoning. A powerful being without intelligence is nothing to worry about." Fang Yuan calmly analyzed, his voice shaking everyone's mind.

"Yes, if nothing unexpected happens, then we have already won this battle!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng added.

But he had just finished speaking when the unexpected event happened.

The three heads six arms monster suddenly separated into three people who then charged into three directions.

Liu Wen Wu and Mo Shi Kuang's charge missed, but Ouyang Bi Sang's eyes shone as he shouted: "Chang Shan Yin, I have finally found you! Die!!"

Their three people combination into three heads six arms monster allowed their souls to mix and their battle strength would raise rapidly, but this state could not be maintained for long. The longer it was used, the more chaotic their memories would become, finally leading them to lose themself and become a delirious lunatic or become an idiot.

When they killed the Gu Master that had come for reinforcement, their minds shook and barely managed to regain a trace of sanity.

Relying on this sanity, they planned in making a comeback.

Compared to killing Tai Bai Yun Sheng, killing Chang Shan Yin would no doubt be much more important.

The investigative Gu of these three were not common Gu. By carefully observing the battlefield, they calculated the three places where Fang Yuan was most likely to be hiding.

In the end, Ouyang Bi Sang found Fang Yuan's hiding place.

'Damn it! If the Wolf King dies, the wolf group will crumble apart. Liu tribe's army will be able to turn around the situation and it will instead become my army's defeat.' Seeing Ouyang Bi Sang pouncing at Chang Shan Yin with a sinister smile, Hei Lou Lan shouted inwardly as he crazily rushed to assist, but he was still late.

"Die!" Ouyang Bi Sang unexpectedly still had enough primeval essence left to activate asura transformation again!

"Wolf King is finished!" Sun Shi Han was afraid but also happy.

"Bad! Chang Shan Yin is going to die!!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng and others had pale expressions.

"Father!" Chang Ji You shouted in desperation.

However, the person in question, Fang Yuan, had a strange smile on his face as he saw Ouyang Bi Sang's attack.

Rank four eagle raise Gu and rank five amplify effect Gu!

A pair of eagle wings suddenly grew out of Fang Yuan's back and took him towards the sky with five times the speed.

Ouyang Bi Sang was dazed for a second before he hurried chased, shouting: "Don't even think of escaping!"

But his speed was not enough and he could only look on as the gap between them spread apart.

"Let me!" Liu Wen Wu shouted and turned into a white light that rapidly charged over. But Fang Yuan nimbly turned around and dodged.

Mo Shi Kuang also rushed over at this moment, chasing and intercepting Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was extremely deft - at times, he was like a butterfly passing through the flowers; at times, he was like a lightning; at times, he was like a light wind; and at times, he was like a ghost, playfully circling the three.

"This... this is master level flying skill!" Everyone looked at this sight with dumbfounded gazes.

Gu Masters raised Gu, used Gu and refined Gu; no matter which aspect, they were all profound and vast. It was clearly the same Gu that they were using, but some Gu Masters could use them brilliantly, elevating it to a level of art.

People often called these individuals — masters!

"I had never thought that Wolf King was not only an enslavement path master but also flying master!" Everyone looked for a while and let go of their worries, exclaiming in surprise.

"Wolf King, don't run if you dare!" Ouyang Bi Sang shouted.

"Chang Shan Yin, if you have any guts, come exchange three hundred moves with me!" Mo Shi Kuang roared in fury.

"Damn it..." Liu Wen Wu gnashed his teeth, his heart already sinking to the bottom.

Fang Yuan's flying skills left them in the dust. What made them even more vexed was that Fang Yuan was unexpectedly separating his thoughts in controlling the wolf group to slaughter Liu tribe army, while dodging them!

"Oh for heaven's sake, if I knew you could fly this skillfully, why would we need to fight to this extent?" Looking at Fang Yuan's skillful maneuvers, Hei Lou Lan felt some resentment in his heart.

As for the Liu tribe three brothers, they were completely speechless.

Chapter 535: Meeting of ‘Father and Son’

Liu Wen Wu lost.

It was an indignant loss, but this was the truth, it would not change because of his feelings.　

Liu Wen Wu, Ouyang Bi Sang, Mo Shi Kuang all had flying abilities. But in terms of flying attainment, they could not compare to Fang Yuan.

The sky was different from the ground, people could fly freely in the air, up, down, left, right, they could dodge in all directions and fly everywhere. But on the ground, there was much less space for evasion.

No matter how Liu Wen Wu and gang tried to block him, they could do nothing to Fang Yuan.

Meanwhile, as Fang Yuan dodged, he mobilized the wolf army to slaughter Liu tribe's army.

Liu Wen Wu and gang had no choice but to give up on chasing Fang Yuan, turning to kill the wolf group and helping the low rank Gu Masters.

But this was what Hei Lou Lan, Fang Yuan and others wanted to see!

Using wolf kings or the mutated wolf group to expended the Liu tribe three brothers' precious primeval essence was very worth it, it was very advantageous to Fang Yuan as well.

As long as a Gu Master did not advance to immortal realm, their primeval essence would be limited. Once they expend their primeval essence, their battle strength would decrease drastically and hit rock bottom.　　

The wolf tide came again and again, the more wolves the Liu tribe three brothers killed, the more primeval essence they used up.

The wolf group's scale was huge, it was never-ending, eventually, Liu tribe three brothers killed until their primeval essence was depleted.

By the time they had to preserve their primeval essence they would no longer be able to battle freely. Hei tribe's higher level battle strength finally had something to do as they suppressed the three of them.

"Hei Lou Lan, today, I did not lose to you, but I lost to Tai Bai Yun Sheng and Chang Shan Yin!" Liu Wen Wu's hair was messy as his body was covered in injuries, he no longer had his gentleman-like attitude as he shouted indignantly.

He felt that: With their three brother's killer move 'three heads six arms', they had great battle strength and could suppress the battlefield. If back then, they got to Fang Yuan and used their supreme speed to kill Fang Yuan, the wolf group would've collapsed and Hei tribe would've lost.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng had the rank five healing Gu 'man as before', the effect was godly, it greatly weakened the effectiveness of their killer move.

When they were left with no choice and chased after Wolf King, they found that the enslavement master Chang Shan Yin was actually a mother****ing flying master!

The three brothers could not catch him, they could only watch the battle crumble. Eventually, Liu tribe lost and was chased down by Hei tribe, they suffered great losses and countless people surrendered.

As the alliance leader, Liu Wen Wu and others were captured after their primeval essence was depleted.

Hei tribe and Liu tribe had always been competing, the two super tribes had a tense relationship, it was well known in northern plains. Now, Hei tribe only captured Liu Wen Wu and others and did not kill them, they wisely sought for a great amount of battle reparation from Liu tribe.

Liu Wen Wu was one of Liu tribe's prospective Gu Immortals, if he was killed, the bottomline of this Imperial Court contest's rules would be infringed.

More importantly, although Hei tribe won, it was a tragic victory and they suffered huge losses as well. Without Liu Wen Wu to bargain for huge amounts of compensation, just ordinary battle gains would not allow Hei tribe to regain their strength. This was very disadvantageous for their future battles for the Imperial Court.

Three days later, Liu tribe's envoy came, and brought all of the Liu tribesmen and the tribes that submitted to them back into the blessed land.

As for the tired and heavily damaged Hei tribe army, they set up camp and managed the people who surrendered, reforming their alliance and collating the battle gains, giving out resources and digesting the spoils of war.

In the large lizard house Gu, Fang Yuan sat on the cushion as he cultivated intently.

A rank four wolf soul Gu appeared out of his body through his will.

The wolf soul Gu was only thumb-size, it was like a tiny grey wolf-shaped doll, it floated in the air as it was covered in an eerie blue light.

The primeval sea level in Fang Yuan's aperture dropped as primeval essence was injected into the wolf soul Gu, causing it to expand rapidly.

Howl!

Wolf soul Gu expanded and turned into a pure grey wolf soul, as large as an elephant.

Next, the wolf soul opened its mouth and howled soundlessly, crashing towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, how could a thousand man soul be so easily affected? The wolf soul crashed on his thousand man soul, and immediately froze, suppressed by his thousand man soul.

The two souls tangled as they turned into mist. A moment later, the wolf soul fused into the thousand man soul and reappeared.

At this moment, the thousand man soul had a long pair of wolf ears on its head, its body was thinner than Fang Yuan's body, and its nose also became sharper. The only part that had not changed were its long hair, eyes, and tail.

"Ever since the Imperial Court competition, I have been using wolf soul Gu daily to refine my soul. Now, I have achieved small success, my soul is around 30% wolfman soul."

Once he fully converts to wolfman soul, his control over the wolf group would experience another qualitative change. Not only would the numbers increase greatly, he would be able to command them like an extension of his limbs, controlling them would require a mere thought.

After a intense battle, his soul's tiredness and weariness would also be lower.

"But according to this speed, by the time I completely refine the wolfman soul, the Imperial Court contest would be over already. I only have rank four wolf soul Gu, the efficiency is way too slow." Fang Yuan sighed.

If he had rank five wolf soul Gu, that would be better compared to Fang Yuan's current situation. But rank four wolf soul Gu was like a grown man using a tiny knife to chop a tree.

In truth, Fang Yuan's soul cultivation was already very fast.

Ordinary Gu Masters needed to spend at least twenty to thirty years to reach his level. Even a genius Gu Master with a clan's support could only be like Dong Fang Yu Liang, reducing the time needed to ten years.

Fang Yuan had Dang Hun mountain, his soul foundation grew at rocket speed, his point of view was obviously different.

"If I can get that Thieving Heaven inheritance, and obtain Luo Po valley..." Fang Yuan's thoughts drifted to this.

But a moment later, he stopped this thought.

In Hu Immortal blessed land, Dang Hun mountain was corroded by the gruel mud continuously, there was only a small mountain left now.

His current objective was to save Dang Hun mountain. As for Luo Po valley, he could only search for it after the Imperial Court contest ends.

While Fang Yuan was cultivating, Chang Biao brought Ni Xue Tong, and Chang Ji You to the door of the large lizard house Gu.

I am Chang Biao, I was summoned by Lord Wolf King." Chang Biao's voice was low and polite, he respectfully informed the guarding Gu Master.

The two rank three Gu Masters had a plain expression as they stood by the door, one answered; "Lord Wolf King is cultivating now, we cannot enter the Gu house to inform him, you will have to wait!"

"Hehe, that is only natural." Chang Biao laughed, trying to conceal the bitterness and dreariness in his heart.

He and Chang Shan Yin had a huge grudge, he would not be willing to submit to Hei tribe. Originally, he wanted to go to Liu tribe, but Liu tribe wanted him to give up his family name and join Liu tribe, this request was impossible for Chang tribesmen and the elders to accept.

Chang tribe was a large size tribe, once they gave up their family name and became Liu tribesmen, Chang tribe would cease to exist.

Furthermore, Hei Lou Lan captured Liu Wen Wu alive and in order to appeal to the most important person Chang Shan Yin, he added in the condition of taking over Chang tribe among the battle reparation.

Thus, Chang tribe became the sacrificial lamb in Liu and Hei tribe's transaction. If Chang tribe did not submit to Hei tribe, they would be assaulted by Hei tribe's army. Forced by both tribes, Chang tribe had no choice but to lower their heads to Hei Lou Lan, becoming Hei tribe's captives.

Chang Shan Yin and Chang tribe's enmity was known to all. After Hei Lou Lan captured Chang tribe, he let Fang Yuan deal with them completely.

After Fang Yuan got the news, he expressed his gratitude to Hei Lou Lan, but in fact, he did not care about it.

He was only using Chang Shan Yin's identity, in order to enter the Imperial Court blessed land. Wolf King's grudges had nothing to do with him.

But if he settled this casually, it would not fit his current status, and people would get suspicious. Thus, Fang Yuan informed Chang tribe's current leader Chang Biao to meet him.

Chang Biao waited from evening to midnight.

At this period of time, northern plains' nights were extremely cold. Chang Biao and the others had their Gu worms confiscated, the primeval essence in their apertures could not resist the cold. Under the blowing night wind, they were shivering from the cold.

Chang Biao kept a calm expression, but Ni Xue Tong was very guilty, she could not conceal the worry in her heart. Chang Ji You was young and at the peak of his health, although his nose was red from the cold, and his body was shivering, his eyes were shining brightly with excitement.

All his life, he had been hearing about the 'Wolf King Chang Shan Yin' and his great deeds.

Everyone called him the 'hero's son', he was gifted this unique status from birth, this gave him great worries, pride, trouble, and even chance encounters.

When he had first heard about Wolf King Chang Shan Yin being alive and had returned, but wanted to exact revenge on Chang tribe, he had very complicated feelings. When he found out that he was going to battle his father, his intense battle intent wavered. During the earlier meeting, Chang Shan Yin did not appear, in fact he went to bash up Sun Shi Han, this made Chang Ji You feel disappointed but also great admiration. After Liu tribe lost, he became a captive but that made him sigh in relief — he no longer needed to fight with his father!

Right now after Liu tribe lost, he was going to meet his real father, Chang Ji You was very excited in his heart.

Even though he was outside shivering and suffering from the weather, it could not freeze the hot-bloodedness in him.

"The person who gave me everything, my father, what kind of person are you?" He was very curious, but he also felt a bit lost and anxious.

After using three wolf soul Gu, Fang Yuan opened his eyes.

The sound of the icy wind blowing outside the window could be heard in the warm room.

Fang Yuan purposely gave Chang Biao a display of authority, after counting the time that had passed, he knew it was time. Thus, he transmitted his message while controlling the large lizard house Gu and opened the doors.

"Lord Wolf King has finished his cultivation, he will meet you now." The Gu Master guards outside received the transmission and said expressionlessly.

Chang Biao's breathing paused, he felt great trepidation as he walked in first, with heavy footsteps.

If Wolf King found out the truth, then he would die without a proper corpse, his reputation would be ruined. Even if Wolf King did not find out the truth, as long as he wanted revenge, killing the whole of Chang tribe would only be a sentence worth of work.

Being meat on the chopping block, this was the helplessness of being in this world!

Fang Yuan looked at the three people kneeling before him.

Chang Biao lowered his head, gritting his teeth, while Ni Xue Tong had a pale expression and was shivering. As for Chang Ji You, he was breathing roughly, but he took peeks at Chang Shan Yin at times, showing an excited expression.

Fang Yuan laughed lightly.

The laughter was heard by all three of them, causing them to shudder.

Chang Biao shut his eyes, his heart had sank to rock bottom, he was waiting for judgement.

Ni Xue Tong almost collapsed on the ground weakly, but Chang Ji You was very agitated, this was father's laughter, he felt a strong sense of warmth from this laugh.

Chapter 536: Major Battles

Fang Yuan observed Chang Biao and the others' expressions fully.

Fang Yuan knew about Wolf King Chang Shan Yin's matters mostly from his biography, he did not know the true culprit behind Wolf King's situation.

But even if he found out, he would not bother taking revenge for the dead Wolf King.

He was Fang Yuan, the so-called Chang Shan Yin was merely a mask.

"From today onwards, I will be Chang tribe's one and only supreme elder." Fang Yuan spoke, breaking the silence.

Chang Biao's body shuddered, he opened his eyes and quickly bowed: "Chang Biao pays respect to lord supreme elder."

"Mm." Fang Yuan nodded: "We need to investigate the matters from back then thoroughly. But now is not the time, we have to wait till the Imperial Court contest ends. From today onwards, I will be Chang tribe's sole supreme elder. Chang Ji You, you will be the tribe leader. Chang Biao will be the number one elder. Ni Xue Tong, our relationship is over, continue to be Chang Biao's wife."

Because of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's tradition, in northern plains, women had lowly status, they were often sold as commodity in transactions. In fact, at times, when an esteemed guest comes to visit, the lord would send his own wife to the esteemed guest to sleep with him.

"Ah?" Chang Ji You was stunned on the spot, he froze completely.

Ni Xue Tong did not speak.

Chang Biao controlled the shock in his heart, he bowed once again: "This subordinate understands!"

"Leave." Fang Yuan waved his hand, sending them away. He had to make good use of his time to continue cultivating.

The three walked out of the large lizard house Gu in a daze, until the cold night wind blew on them and woke them up.

"I... survived just like this?" Chang Biao felt endless joy and happiness.

"But the matter back then was done flawlessly! Even though there are some traces here and there, after all these years, the evidences are long gone. Back then, I got close to Chang Shan Yin on purpose, and became good buddies with him. Now that Chang Shan Yin had gone through such a great change, plus it has already been so many years, it is normal for our relationship to turn bland." Chang Biao thought rapidly in his head.

The current situation was way better than what he had expected.

"Although I was demoted from tribe leader to elder, most of my authority is intact. Chang Shan Yin still trusts me seeing that he allowed me to be the number one elder! As for making Chang Ji You the new tribe leader, it shows that he is still caring about his own blood and flesh deeply! As long as he cares about his old relationships and friendships, everything will be easy to resolve..." Chang Biao thought and got more energetic.

He was dreaming within his own world, and did not notice his wife Ni Xue Tong's complicated expression.

The old Chang Shan Yin was extremely infatuated with her beauty, but earlier, Chang Shan Yin did not give her even an extra glance.

On the way here, she was extremely worried about Chang Shan Yin forcing her to his wife again. That way, she will be separated from her lover Chang Biao, that was too painful!

But now, the situation was way better than she had expected.

Not only did Chang Shan Yin not pursue the matters back then, he even allowed her to remain as Chang Biao's wife!

This was the result that Ni Xue Tong was dreaming of earlier. She should be happy, but for some reason, while she still felt some trepidation from earlier, there was also a sense of loss in her, that she did not want to admit.

As for Chang Ji You, he was in great joy, confusion, and suspicion.

"I've finally met father, he was just a few steps in front of me! He is much more authoritative than I imagined."

"Father did not call me his son, but instead called my name. Is he unaware that I am his flesh and blood?"

"But father, why did he let me become Chang tribe leader? I am so young and only have rank three cultivation, can I do it?"

"I get it! This must be a test from father. He is testing me, this son he had never met, if I can manage the tribe well and achieve outstanding results, will he feel happy and proud, will be recognise me as his son?"

Thinking so, Chang Ji You felt extremely excited, he made up his mind, he would exert all his efforts and perform well in the upcoming fight for the Imperial Court.

Fang Yuan would not expect that his simple arrangements would bring such great emotional changes in Chang Biao and gang.

But even if he knew, he would not care.

In the five hundred years of his past life, Chang Shan Yin helped Ma Hong Yun to ascend to the position of the Lord of the Imperial Court, he also had complete control over Chang tribe.

Different from Earth, when strength can be accumulated within a person, the stronger one is, the greater their authority would be.

At this point, Fang Yuan was no longer the low rank Gu Master on Qing Mao mountain, suppressed and weakened by the system. Right now, he had the authority to manipulate and change the power system of a tribe. One could say, he was at the peak of the mortal realm.

He knew in his heart, all this was because of the great strength that he had!

"Right now, my first aperture had already adapted, I can use rank five peak stage primeval essence. My second aperture has also reached rank five middle stage. My two apertures have ninety percent A grade aptitude, to use my two sets of Gu worms now, I have ample primeval essence.

"But enslavement and strength path Gu worms are not extremely strong. In terms of strength path, after getting the rank five amplify effect Gu, my explosive force is already high enough, except that my body is unable to endure the increment in strength.

Earlier, when fighting against Liu Wen Wu and his brother's combination killer move 'three heads six arms', Fang Yuan could definitely fight against them using his strength path cultivation.

But Fang Yuan knew clearly that the moment he unleashed five hundred jun of strength, regardless of how his opponent will ends up, his own body would definitely crumble first.

"My bones are impermanence bones. My skin is turtle jade wolf skin. To sustain five hundred jun of strength, this is not enough. But if I modify my muscles and tendons to accommodate strength path, they would not suit my enslavement path. If I modify them for enslavement path, they will not aid my strength path. The root of the problem is that enslavement and strength have some conflict between them, it is difficult to cultivate them together. It is unlike soul and enslavement path, or soul and wisdom path."

This problem had always been troubling Fang Yuan.

If he could not resolve this, Fang Yuan's enslavement and strength path would only go far, but would not reach the apex and attain ultimate strength.

Although Fang Yuan had information regarding Luo Po valley now, the future was uncertain, anything could happen. Fang Yuan was a vigilant guy, before getting Luo Po valley, he would not make up his mind to cultivate soul path, thus, he needed to perfect his enslavement-strength path route now.

Fang Yuan closed his eyes and thought about it, before opening them and taking out east window Gu from his aperture.

This Gu was a storage Gu, used to store information, it came from Lang Ya land spirit.

Inside east window Gu, there was information regarding the killer move 'three heads six arms'. This killer move was extremely powerful, it could allow Liu Wen Wu, Ouyang Bi Sang, and Mo Shi Kuang to become a giant monster, increasing their battle strength to a terrifying level.

After Hei tribe defeated Liu tribe, they make requests regarding this killer move, thus it became a part of the reparation. Thereafter, Fang Yuan exchanged for it using his battle merits.

These days, when Fang Yuan was free, he would research about this killer move.

When Gu Masters use multiple Gu worms at the same time, allowing their effects to merge and cooperate to form greater effects, that would be the so-called Gu Master killer move.

Killer move 'three heads six arms', needed eighteen Gu worms to be used at the same time. Gu worms used ranged from rank three to five, the primeval essence expenditure was huge as well. At the same time, three Gu Masters were needed, one could not activate it alone.

This killer move was unusable by Fang Yuan. But that did not mean it was worthless to him.

Killer move, or recipes, displayed exquisite usage of Gu worms.

Why was it that when these Gu worms were used in a specific way, they achieved such effects? Why can these Gu worms do it, but not others? If this Gu was changed to another Gu, can the same effect be achieved? If an enemy uses this killer move, what ways are there to counter it?

Man is the spirit of all being, Gu is the essence of heaven and earth.

Inside a Gu, there were tiny laws of heaven and earth, the fragments of the great Dao.

By understanding Gu, one would comprehend the great Dao, and understand the natural laws of this world. Just like on Earth, using experiments to learn scientific theories.

This Gu recipe gave great insight to Fang Yuan.

"If I had three heads and six arms, what would happen?"

A flash of inspiration appeared in his brain, like opening a new window.

His body was like the cornerstone. Enslavement and strength path were like the buildings on top of the cornerstone. Right now, this cornerstone was still small, thus the two buildings could only be low-rising. If he expanded this cornerstone in the future, would it be able to contain two tall buildings at the same time?

Fang Yuan had never cared about his own appearance.

Handsome, beauty, ugly, these were other people's opinions. What did that have to do with him?

If his battle strength was high, so what if he was called a monster?

Northern Plains, July.

The weather was turning cold, mist turned into frost, it was raining non-stop.

All the armies engaged in many intense battles, there were already less than fifty left.

Although Hei tribe won against Liu tribe, they suffered a great loss as well, they set up camp and made use of all their time to recuperate and recover, like an injured beast.

Middle of July.

At Du Jiao region, Ye Lui army defeated the alliance of seven armies, on the day of the counterattack, Ye Lui Sang killed three rank five Gu Masters.

But in this battle, the biggest achiever was a hidden elder in Qi Lian tribe, Qi Lian tribe leader's godson, Wu Ming.

Wu Ming was a rank five middle stage dark path Gu Master. During the battles, he snuck into the enemy camp and assassinated the enemies, successfully killing two rank five experts, thirteen rank four Gu Masters, causing the seven alliance armies to feel great fear and low morale.

Northern Plains, August.

After Yang tribe recruited enslavement master Jiang Bao Ya, their strength surged and they experienced many victories, after some battles, they were one of the new popular competitors for the Imperial Court.

The new enslavement master "Leopard King' Nu Er Tu led his army against Tao tribe. Tao tribe alliance army had suffered many setbacks during the battles, the alliance leader Tao You knew that he had no hopes of ascending to the Lord of Imperial Court position. Thus, he submitted to Nu Er Tu, and after their armies combined, their military power surged.

Middle of August, Hei Lou Lan gave orders to resume their conquest.

By September, the Imperial Court contest was starting to clear up. Only five armies had the highest hopes.

Hei tribe which had Chang Shan Yin, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Nu Er tribe with the new Leopard King, Yang tribe which had Rat King and Eagle King, Ma tribe with Horse King, as well as Ye Lui tribe which had Ye Lui Sang who possessed an Immortal Gu.

First half of September, Nu Er tribe army fought Yang tribe army. The leopard group could not contest the combination of eagles and rats, after half a month, Nu Er Tu lost.

Start of October, while Yang tribe was digesting the battle reparations, Ye Lui Sang targeted them.

Yang tribe army had people who wanted to fight, some wanted to defend, while some wanted to retreat. Because of differing opinions, the army could not execute proper orders, and thus, was taken down by Ye Lui Sang.

After Ye Lui Sang win, they could not gloat for long, because Ma tribe had their eyes on them.

Ma tribe rushed for three days and three nights, catching Ye Lui Sang off-guard.

A similar scene unfolded again, before Ye Lui army digested their battle gains, they were defeated by Ma tribe.

Ye Lui Sang escaped with his remaining troops, submitting to Hei tribe army.

Start of November, Hei tribe moved north rapidly, setting up eight defensive lines on the way, and during the middle of the month, engaged in the final battle with Ma tribe.

Only the victor could stay in the Imperial Court. Meanwhile, the loser would have to pay reparations and face the ten year blizzard amidst disappointment and pity.

At once, this battle attracted numerous gazes, both participants and the people behind the scenes.

During the first few battles, Hei tribe had the advantage, after Ma tribe lost two defensive lines, they retreated to the third.

Ye Lui Sang wanted to take revenge, thus he kept challenging them, killing till Ma tribe army could only hide and defend themselves, causing their morale to dampen.

Ma tribe had no choice, but to seek help from Snowy Mountain blessed land who was backing them.

Chapter 537: Xue Song Zi

The lofty Snowy Mountain stood tall and reached through the clouds.

Mountain ranges surrounded it like stars surrounding the moon.

The sky had a hue of light blue color. Thin snow fluttered lightly and landed on the ground.

This was a spotlessly white region with even the buildings on the mountain carved out of ice crystals.

Here was Snowy Mountain blessed land.

The nest of northern plains' demonic path Gu Immortals, with tens of Gu Immortals occupying different peaks.

On one of the peaks of Snowy Mountain, green pine trees grew everywhere and a seven storey pavilion made of ice crystal stood there. Three large words were carved on the board in the pavillion — Xue Song Pavilion.

The owner of this peak, Xue Song Zi, was a famous rank six demonic path Gu Immortal of northern plains.

He was tall and thin with snow white hair that reached the ground and was clothed in a light blue gown. Right now, he was on the top floor of Xue Song Pavilion, looking down at this Snowy Mountain branch peak that belonged exclusively to him.

He had deep blue eyes and his deep gaze swept through a thousand li of his territory.

"The snow pines are growing well, the snow willows planted two years ago have already grown to over ten thousand willows. This year, the number of Gu worms produced was close to three hundred rank five Gu; there are still a surplus of ice path and water path Gu worms after leaving some for research. I can sell them and gain at least two-three immortal essence stones."

"Of course, my most important income source is still the transaction of snowmen slaves."

Xue Song Zi raised six variant human tribes on his branch peak, they were all snowmen.

Snowman was one of the species of variant humans who lived in ice-cold snowy regions. They had white skin, icy blue eyes and aqua blue hair. When they die, their blood and flesh body would turn into an ice sculpture.

Snowmen normally did not cry or laugh, so their tears were very rare. The absolute majority of the snowmen would never experience crying from joy or pain in their life.

However, if a snowman sheds tears, their tear would instantly condense into ice. Icy tears were precious Gu refinement material that Gu Masters liked deeply.

Xue Song Zi looked around once and nodded, satisfied.

Snowmen looked expressionless, but Xue Song Zi, however, saw them as the variant humans with spirituality that was the closest to humans. Many Gu Immortals raised snowmen, torturing them brutally for their icy tears.

Icy tears could be used in many areas of Gu refinement, and so its transaction in treasure yellow heaven was flourishing.

Many Gu Immortals massacred and killed snowmen to profit from their icy tears.

Xue Song Zi also did such shady business before, but he soon discovered the market for trading snowmen was much more profitable than the icy tears themselves.

From then onwards, he began to raise snowmen and sell them in treasure yellow heaven for other Gu Immortals to torture.

Snowmen could shed tears at most three times in their life and the amount would not surpass sixty drops. Every time they shed tears, the snowman's lifespan and life essence would decrease by a huge amount.

The more the snowman sheds tears, the faster they will age, speeding up their death.

However, raising snowmen did not cost much.

Moreover, Xue Song Zi possessed this Snowy Mountain branch peak which was very beneficial for the growth of snow pines, snow trees and snowmen, thus his profit from selling snowmen was much higher than when he sold tears.

He was good at making money and had accumulated a large amount of immortal essence stones from his thriving business over the years, and was considered wealthy in the Gu Immortal circle.

But he had one great regret — decades had gone by since he became rank six Gu Immortal, but he still did not have even one Immortal Gu.

No matter how many immortal essence stones he had, he was not able to buy Immortal Gu. After all, there was only one of each Immortal Gu, others would not sell them even if they had it. At most, they would use Immortal Gu to exchange for Immortal Gu.

"Now, Ma tribe has already reached the final step, if it can prevail over Hei tribe and enter Imperial Court, maybe I can obtain my first Immortal Gu from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building... hmm?"

Xue Song Zi was thinking of all the matters, when suddenly he had a feeling and casually waved his hand.

Space tore open and a letter Gu flew in.

Xue Song Zi read the letter which was Ma tribe's request for help.

"So they have finally gotten to this stage." The corner of Xue Song Zi's lips curled up into a smile.

He had been paying close attention to the struggle for Imperial Court and already knew the difficulties Ma tribe was facing. Previously, he had gotten in contact with Ma tribe, but Ma tribe had not made a decision. Now due to the tense battle situation, Ma tribe sent a request for assistance, it was akin to agreeing to his previous conditions.

"With this, it is time to make my move." Xue Song Zi gradually restrained his smile and activated divine sense Gu.

Three divine senses separately flew towards three snowman tribes on the snowy peak.

After receiving the divine sense, three snowman Gu Masters immediately hurried towards the mountain peak.

After a while, they were kneeling in front of Xue Song Pavilion and greeted together: "Xue Wa, Xue Mi and Xue Ming greet Lord Immortal!"

Xue Song Zi did not reveal himself, instead sent some Gu worms towards these three snowmen's hands.

"Take these Gu worms and also battle troop D to the outside world and find Ma tribe, help them win the battle." Xue Song Zi sent another divine sense.

"As you command." The three snowman Gu Masters immediately accepted the order.

Xue Song Zi had four battle troops marked A, B, C and D. They were elite troops formed from experts of the six snowman tribes.

The three snowman Gu Masters led battle troop D out of the Snowy Mountain blessed land, but before they even reached Ma tribe, Hei tribe's Gu Immortals noticed them.

"Elder brother, this Ma tribe has relations to Snowy Mountain's demonic path Gu Immortals as we expected. The evidence is out in the open now, Liu tribe's external supreme elder Gu Immortal Tan Bi Ya was not wrong." Hei Bai said to Hei Cheng in Xiao Hun blessed land.

These two were Hei tribe's Gu Immortals.

Hei Bai had an ordinary appearance and looked to be middle-aged, he looked clumsy but was intelligent. While Hei Cheng was recognized as Hei tribe's genius since young, he looked elegant and confident, and was also Hei Lou Lan's father.

Hei Cheng glanced at Hei Bai and calmly said: "Brother, do not fret. Demonic path Gu Immortals have always been lone wolves. Snowy Mountain might be strong and have tens of Gu Immortals, but those that are supporting Ma tribe will only be two-three at most."

Hei Bai nodded: "Elder brother is right, but the current Ma tribe is truly strong. They were able to win great battles just by relying on themselves previously. Now if they obtain Gu Immortals' support, they are bound to get much stronger."

Hei Cheng was in agreement as he asked: "Have you investigated who the demonic path Gu Immortals supporting Ma tribe are?"

"I haven't but it should be easy."

"Do it. For the next few days, we will buy five hundred thousand wolves, three hundred mutated wolves, two wolf emperors and a few thousand Gu worms along with other resources to give to Hei Lou Lan."

"Yes, elder brother!"

"Also, instruct Hei Lou Lan to end the battle quickly so as to avoid new problems."

Hei Bai gave an understanding nod, and left Xiao Hun blessed land without speaking any more.

A war did not only pit human lives against each other, it was more about the competition between each other's foundations, a war of attrition.

The struggle for Imperial Court had advanced to the final stage; Hei Cheng and Hei Bai, two immortals who had been supporting Hei Lou Lan, gradually started to feel an extremely heavy burden.

Although Gu Immortals were rich, they could not support the whole army for such a long period of time.

The amount of resources and mortal Gu needed were extremely enormous. A part came from their blessed land, but most of them were purchased from treasure yellow heaven using immortal essence stones.

With such huge amounts of immortal essence stones being expended, both Hei Bai and Hei Cheng felt distressed inwardly.

The struggle for Imperial Court was essentially a game. But it was not a game all Gu Immortals could afford to play.

Many Gu Immortals would put huge stakes in this game to obtain an Immortal Gu. In the end, if the side they chose did not become the owner of Imperial Court, they would lose disastrously, there were even examples of going bankrupt.

But if they won and obtained Immortal Gu from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, all their investment would be worth it.

After all, no matter how many immortal essence stones they had, they would not be able to buy an Immortal Gu.

After ten days, Hei tribe and Ma tribe began another round of battle. Troops lined up in a seemingly endless battle formation.

In the main tent, Hei Lou Lan sat on the main seat with his eyes gazing at his front and his heroic spirit was overflowing: "We did not cause huge damage to Ma tribe the previous two times, we will teach them a good lesson this time. It is not that easy to become a super tribe, hmph! Who will go first?"

The moment he finished speaking, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu stood up and bowed: "Lord alliance leader, I would like to go first!"

Hei Lou Lan nodded in satisfaction.

Water Demon Hao Ji Liu was an expert who had chosen to submit to him since the heroes assembly.

And he had been assisting and fighting in the struggle for Imperial Court the whole journey, and killed countless enemies and had made huge battle contributions at this stage.

Although Pei Yan Fei also attached to Hei tribe after Liu Wen Wu lost, he could not shake rank four Hao Ji Liu's position as the first general.

Hao Ji Liu was an 'old general' of Hei tribe army and adding in the loyalty which he had revealed many times, if nothing unexpected happened, he would be taken in as an external elder by Hei tribe once they become the owner of Imperial Court.

Hei tribe was a super tribe with Huang Jin bloodline, one of the overlords of northern plains. If Hao Ji Liu joined Hei tribe, it would be like taking a shelter under a large tree, similar to Wind Demon Tan Wu Feng joining Dong Fang tribe.

Hao Ji Liu entered the battlefield and started taunting. Ma Shang Feng snorted and pointed at him: "This Water Demon again, who will go teach him a lesson?"

"Lord alliance leader, let me go take care of him this time." A boorish guy stood up; he was Ma tribe's general, rank four transformation path Gu Master — Cheng Hu.

Ma Shang Feng agreed, Cheng Hu impatiently went to the frontline and started fighting Hao Ji Liu.

Hao Ji Liu attacked cleverly with great offense, torrents surging around him. Because of many precious and rare Gu he had exchanged with his battle merits, Hao Ji Liu's current battle strength far surpassed the time when he had just started out in the struggle for Imperial Court.

The two sides exchanged moves after moves, and after over ten rounds, Hao Ji Liu slowly began to occupy the upper hand.

Cheng Hu felt stifled as kept on being pushed into disadvantage, he gave a furious roar and activated his killer move, transforming into slant-eye tiger.

The tiger was ferocious and powerful, immediately turning around the losing situation.

Hao Ji Liu was widely known for his fierce offense, but he was having trouble fending off the tiger's attacks, and could only keep on retreating, changing his battle tactics into defending and counter-attacking.

Chapter 538: Challenge

Swoosh swoosh.

A blue water current shot out. Slant-eye tiger roared in a thunderous volume.

This was the rank four tiger roar Gu!

The tiger roar sound waves caused ripples in the air, as it hit the currents, the water exploded into a huge rain.

After Cheng Hu became the slant-eye tiger, he had great offense, immediately giving off a dominating aura.

Tiger roar Gu, sends out sound waves. Tiger claw Gu, has overwhelming sharpness. Tiger skin Gu, has superb defense!

Tiger tooth Gu, is pointy like spears, has amazing penetration ability. Tiger tail Gu, strong like a whip, moving like one's arms!

Transformation path Gu Masters would collect relevant Gu worms for their killer move. Once the Gu worm set is complete, they would be able to transform and obtain a huge qualitative surge in their battle strength.

Of course, the stronger the transformation, the more valuable the Gu needed for their set, and the harder it is to collect them.

Even if a Gu Master could transform, they needed a lot of training. Humans were born to walk on two legs, having two arms and one head. If they transformed into another form, it would not be easy for them to adapt.

Same as flying, only huge amounts of training and talent would allow one to have great proficiency in using their new form.

Gu Masters nurture, use, and refine Gu, this was the deep profound aspect of using Gu.

The two armies placed their gaze on the battle ahead.

Hao Ji Liu and Cheng Hu's battle had already reached the crucial moment.

Cheng Hu used his killer move, turning into the slant-eye tiger, he had the advantage. Hao Ji Liu could only evade primilarily, compared to his earlier frenzied attacks, he was truly pathetic now.

However, as time continued to pass, the battle was still stuck at a deadlock. Although Cheng Hu had a huge advantage, he could not turn this advantage into victory.

Even though most of Ma tribe's troops were rejoicing, the people sitting inside Ma tribe's main tent were frowning.

"Not good, this Water Demon is very crafty! Cheng Hu is in danger." Ma Ying Jie said.

Many of the experts around nodded in agreement.

Although killer moves were strong, in truth, they were actually multiple Gu used at the same time. This meant that primeval essence expenditure was very high, for normal Gu Masters, this was a double-edged sword.

After Cheng Hu used his killer move, with Water Demon Hao Ji Liu's plentiful experience, he immediately changed his hard-hitting tactics. As Cheng Hu was unable to take down Water Demon in time, after his primeval essence was expended, he would return to human form. By then, Water Demon Hao Ji Liu would retaliate.

Ma Shang Feng looked calm, but his heart sank.

If this was the past, Cheng Hu's success or failure would not bother him. But now, Cheng Hu's victory or loss was not his problem alone, it concerned the morale of the entire army.

Ma tribe had lost twice already, Ma Shang Feng knew that the tribes that submitted to them had already wavered.

Ma tribe army was led by Ma tribe, the other tribes were needed to make the alliance. Once their hearts wavered, the situation would turn dangerous.

Ma Shang Feng did not wish to see Cheng Hu fail.

But with the current situations, Cheng Hu was very likely to fail, Ma Shang Feng could only sigh in his heart as he called: "Fei Sheng Cheng."

Fei Sheng Cheng immediately stepped up, placing his right palm at his heart, bowing: "I am here."

"You will go for the second battle." Ma Shang Feng said. In order to alleviate the negative influences caused by Cheng Hu's defeat, he placed his hopes on Fei Sheng Cheng.

Fei Sheng Cheng was a fierce general.

Earlier, he was ostracised by Fei tribe, and could not rise up. Ma tribe thus used him as an insider, and during Fei tribe's internal political strife, they launched a surprise attack while they were weak and managed to take down Fei tribe.

After Fei Sheng Cheng submitted to Ma tribe, which was a wise ruler, he made many accomplishments and was highly regarded and nurtured.

Right now, he came before the battle area and shouted.

"He is Fei Sheng Cheng, ever since the Imperial Court contest, he had killed eight rank four experts. In an earlier battle, he used numbness Gu and fought three experts of the same realm alone, showing great abilities." In Hei tribe main tent, Sun Shi Han said.

Ye Lui Sang's expression was cold.

The 'earlier battle' Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han mentioned was the battle between Ma tribe and Ye Lui tribe. In the end, Ye Lui Sang lost and was chased by Ma tribe, almost becoming a vagabond. The tribes that submitted to Ye Lui tribe, like Qi Lian tribe, all went to Ma tribe.

Numbness Gu, a rare rank four Gu, had value equivalent to a rank five. Once a Gu Master was struck, they would be paralyzed, unable to move. Although it lasted a short time, during an intense battle, this was a very deadly technique.

Hei Lou Lan responded in agreement, and looked around, asking: "Who can battle?"

Once he said so, one person laughed heartily and stood up: "Fei Sheng Cheng is nothing much, I am willing to battle and sweep the obstacles away in your path to conquest!"

Hei Lou Lan looked at this person, it was none other than Sole Blade Pan Ping.

Earlier, Pan Ping was defeated by Liu tribe's three brothers combination move, and was revived by Tai Bai Yun Sheng using man as before Gu after the battle. Not just him, Gao Yang and Zhu Zai were revived in the same way.

"Alright, then you shall go." Hei Lou Lan nodded.

If this was during the start of the battle, he would not think highly of Pan Ping. But after tens of battles, Pan Ping was no longer like before, he had grown quickly to become an expert like Pei Yan Fei.

"Fei tribe lad, you are just a traitor, a shameless scoundrel seeking glory. You being alive is the greatest humiliation, quickly receive your death!" Pan Ping jumped onto the battlefield and shouted, surging with battle intent.

Fei Sheng Cheng was furious, he hated people who called him this: "You are just a demonic path bastard, earlier I let you act arrogantly because you did not anger me yet!"

Immediately, the two fought.

At once, the scene was bursting with attacks as they were evenly matched. When two experts on par with each other battle, it would be an intense battle.

Actually, the two of them had similar circumstances. At the start of the Imperial Court contest, the two of them were people who were not doing well. Pan Ping was a demonic path Gu Master, he lived a tough life. As for Fei Sheng Cheng, he was suppressed by his clan and could not achieve his goals.

But because of this Imperial Court contest, the two gained fame and emerged from the battles while gaining great surge in strength.

Pan Ping only had one good Gu back then, sole blade Gu. But now, he used his battle merits to exchange for an exquisite set of Gu worms, his strength grew by leaps and bounds. It was unlike before when he relied on sole blade Gu alone.

Fei Sheng Cheng was the same.

Earlier, he was ostracised in his clan, even though he had a complete set of Gu worms, he lacked strong effective methods. He had also accumulated battle merits in battle, and exchanged the rank five equivalent numbness Gu, paired with his Gu worms, his battle strength rose sharply.

The two of them engaged with each other endlessly, but they both had their concerns.

Pan Ping was afraid of numbness Gu, while Fei Sheng Cheng was guarding against sole blade Gu.

Speaking of the sole blade Gu, it was Pan Ping's good luck, it resides in the scimitar instead of the Gu Master's body or aperture.

After Pan Ping was blown to bits, only the sole blade Gu survived.

After that, when Tai Bai Yun Sheng revived him, he lost all of his Gu worms except sole blade Gu. And thankfully, Pan Ping had a lot of battle merits which he had not used.

But Gao Yang and Zhu Zai were not so lucky.

After they died, they lost all their Gu worms. Most unfortunately, Gao Yang's rank five treacherous cloud wave Gu was destroyed as well.

Rank five man as before Gu, it could only target human bodies and not Gu worms.

But the two felt calm, after all, being able to revive was the biggest benefit!

Thereafter, they borrowed battle merits to replenish their Gu worms. After several battles, not only did they return all the battle merits they owed, they even had some gains left.

The battle of two rank four experts attracted countless gazes.

Ma tribe saw that Fei Sheng Cheng and Pan Ping were at a deadlock, and sent out another six fierce generals.

Hei Lou Lan accepted all the challenges, sending Pei Yan Fei, Gao Yang, Zhu Zai and others.

When the six pair of experts battled, Cheng Hu finally lost. Water Demon Hao Ji Liu had no strength to chase after him, he could only watch Cheng Hu escape safely.

Hei tribe's morale surged, but quickly, in the third battle, Ma tribe won, and tied the scores.

The two sides continued to send experts, as more than thirty battle rings appeared before the two troops.

That is so say, there were around seventy rank four Gu Masters fighting at once!

This was a grand scene, in the entire northern plains, there were billions of people, mostly being mortals, but only several hundred rank four Gu Masters, and less than fifty rank five Gu Masters.

Precisely because of the battle for the Imperial Court, all these people gathered and collided with each other, competing intensely. In the battle for life and death, even stronger Gu Masters emerge while the weak get exterminated.

It was near the end of the fight for the Imperial Court. Be it Hei tribe or Ma tribe, they were both huge forces.

Not counting Gu Immortals, either army had a scale that surpassed super tribes greatly.

All members of both armies were definitely excited and filled with ambitions.

Only Fang Yuan was calm, in his previous life he had seen even larger events, that was the chaotic battle of the five regions, it was truly a time of unrest.

"Lord alliance leader, I would like to battle!" A young rank four Gu Master walked up as he could not contain his battle intent.

This was none other than Ge Guang.

Ge Guang was Ge tribe leader, he was originally rank three, but after so many battles, he survived and gained a huge boost in strength, having advanced to rank four successfully not long ago.

Hei Lou Lan was stunned, turning his gaze towards Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan was Ge and Chang tribe's supreme elder, both tribes were under his control.

Fang Yuan sensed Hei Lou Lan's inquisitive gaze and lightly commanded: "Stand down Ge Guang, you are a tribe leader, how can you put yourself at risk?"

Ge Guang stepped down obediently.

Fang Yuan asked: "Where is Chang Biao?"

"Lord, I am here." Chang Biao had a sickly expression, he had yet to recover from his injuries from the previous battle.

But Fang Yuan did not care about this, saying: "You will go fight."

Chang Biao wanted to speak but he could not, filled with an intense rage in his heart. Ever since he joined the Hei alliance army, he would be ordered by Fang Yuan to participate in every huge battle.

Even if he was a famous expert, he could not undergo consecutive battles with such a high intensity.

"Damn it! This Chang Shan Yin, is he ordering me like a beast?! Curse my current weak position, I cannot oppose him. I will wait and endure, there is still a long way to go. If I can harm you more than ten years ago, I will still be able to send you to the underworld after so many years!"

Chang Biao screamed in his heart, but on the surface, he chose to obey Fang Yuan's orders, dragging his injured body into the battlefield.

Chapter 539: Rank Five Peak Stage!

With Chang Biao taking the stage, Ma tribe sent a female expert.

This person's name was Xi Xue, a rank four peak stage Gu Master, a famous expert of ice path. She possessed a rank five flying snow Gu which once activated could cause heavy snowfall and make a range of thousands of steps into an ice zone.

When Chang Biao saw this expert, he inwardly said: 'This will be difficult."

Even if he was at his peak condition, he would have to be careful when facing this woman, let alone now in his injured state.

The two started fighting, Xi Xue had a sharp offense while Chang Biao kept on dodging to prolong the battle; with this, he was unavoidably pressed in a disadvantageous situation.

The battles continued and as time passed, some rank four Gu Masters lost, some retreated due to injuries and some died at the enemy's hand.

There were casualties in both sides, but with regards to the overall situation, it was a draw.

Slowly, there were fewer and fewer rank four Gu Masters in the main tent of both sides; they did not have enough to mobilize.

"Gu tribe leader, please show your strength now." Hei Lou Lan's gaze landed on a man who was sitting upright.

Gu tribe leader Gu Guo Long was an earth path Gu Master who had once given huge trouble to Hei tribe army by piling stones into a mountain, and made Hei Lou Lan have the thought of retreating. But after Tai Bai Yun Sheng arrived, Hei tribe won and Gu tribe merged with Hei tribe army as the defeated side.

Gu Guo Long's appearance shocked Ma tribe army.

This was the first appearance of a rank five expert, Ma Shang Feng immediately responded by sending Cheng tribe leader Cheng Long.

This person was a rank five expert of transformation path and was big brother of Cheng Hu.

Gu Guo Long bowed slightly upon seeing Cheng Long and politely said: "So it is Cheng tribe leader, please give me pointers."

Cheng Long chuckled: "I won't dare to teach tribe leader Guo Long, let's just compare our moves."

The two started their battle with such a huge momentum that it suppressed everyone and became the focal point of countless gazes.

Gu Guo Long could attack and defend with stable and unflustered movements. While Cheng Long flew freely in the sky, fierce and calm.

When the two had exchanged twenty moves, Hei Lou Lan sent another rank five expert Luo Bo Jun.

Luo Bo Jun had previously sided with Liu Wen Wu, but after Liu tribe lost against Hei tribe, he became one of the higher-ups of Hei tribe army.

Ma tribe also sent out a rank five expert to take on Luo Bo Jun.

With regards to rank five experts, Ma tribe was not inferior in any respect. Previously, Nu Er Tu annexed Tao tribe but was then defeated by Yang tribe who was then attacked by Ye Lui tribe; in the end, Ma tribe defeated Ye Lui tribe, becoming the final winner. From this battle, Ma tribe gained many large tribes - Qi Lian tribe, Cheng tribe, Zhao tribe, Lui tribe, Tao tribe, Yang tribe and other formidable forces.

At the same time, they also gained Jiang Bao Ya and Yang Po Ying, and together with Ma Zun, they had three enslavement path masters!

Rank five Gu Masters mostly occupied positions of power and prestige; their tone of speaking in the fight was much calmer and cordial in comparison to the boiling killing intent between the rank four Gu Masters. When they attacked, they would also hold back some of their strength in consideration of each other's feelings.

Because if they died, their tribe would become a leaderless group and would be swallowed by Hei tribe or Ma tribe.

Although they were hostile to the enemy, their heart was still tied to their tribe's benefits. Even if they were under the constraints of poison vow, there were tacit unwritten rules.

Fang Yuan calmly observed the battle from his seat.

He had only showed rank four peak stage cultivation, but as an enslavement master and a key character that could influence the whole situation, his position was special and was higher than those rank five tribe leaders.

"What a great move by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, a truly wonderful plan!" As he was personally participating in the struggle for Imperial Court, Fang Yuan truly felt more and more overwhelmed.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable left built Eighty-Eight True Yang Building as an inheritance for his descendants and at the same time, also set up 'Imperial Court contest' tradition; one could tell he had pondered about it meticulously.

Leaving aside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, just this struggle for Imperial Court was a field of purging at every stage with Huang Jin tribes swallowed other tribes and strengthening themselves.

At the same time, the gathering of goods developed the abnormally blooming battle merits economy during the battles. And through war reparations, technology and skills were exchanged, which further deepened the foundation of the Huang Jin family.

What was even more important was the survival of the fittest rule which forced Gu Masters to exert their strength at the edge of life and death and become experts. For Huang Jin tribes, this was filtering out the Gu Immortal seeds.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was no longer alive, but his influence was still governing the whole northern plains.

"Compared to the Immortal Venerable, I am only an ant like existence at present. But it was also because I took advantage of this struggle for the Imperial Court that my strength could advance by leaps and bounds..."

Fang Yuan then divided a little of his concentration to look into his aperture.

There were many new Gu worms in his aperture. Most were rank four with one rank three along with one rank five asura zombie Gu and one rank five earth overlord Gu.

Ever since Fang Yuan had gained inspiration from 'three heads six arms' killer move, he had been combining his foundation and imagination to make some progress in his research.

He then condensed the research findings into a killer move which he called — Four Arm Earth King!

When he activates this killer move, a completely new pair of arms would grow out from his sides. His strength would increase sharply when he used all four of his arms, comparable to the killer move of Liu tribe's three brothers''three heads six arms'!

"But, compared to three arms six heads, my four arm earth king's form can only be maintained for a short time. I will only be able to exert full strength when my feet is touching the land. If I fly, my battle strength will fall by half."

This killer move had been newly created by Fang Yuan and was still not perfected. He would need to examine this killer move through battles, add in some new Gu, replace unnecessary Gu or directly cut down on them, and slowly this killer move would be perfected.

The sun gradually rose higher, but with blizzard disaster approaching closer, the normally intense hot sunlight appeared to have no heat.

The surging battle intent on the battlefield gradually accumulated to the climax.

All sorts of attacks burst out in dozens of battle rings like colorful fireworks, creating an extremely dazzling scene.

There were only a few Gu Masters left in the Hei tribe's main tent. The rest were either fighting, retreating, recovering or had died in the battlefield.

Considering the overall situation, Hei tribe was in a slightly weaker position.

Since the start till now, Hei Lou Lan had obtained Hei Bai and Hei Cheng, two immortals' active support. While Ma tribe had only requested assistance from Xue Song Zi only at this battle.

"Hmph, Ma tribe's bunch of trash can really take a beating!" Hei Lou Lan snorted with a fierce gaze as he started getting impatient.

His gaze landed on Fang Yuan and was just about to speak, when three beast groups rushed out of Ma tribe camp.

From the left side, many horses galloped on the earth, causing the ground to rumble like a muffled lightning!

From right side, countless rats rushed out while squeaking and hissing, so packed that it caused people to feel a chill down their spine.

From the center, eagle group soared up like dark clouds, actually looking like it could cover the sky!

Horse King Ma Zun, Rat King Jiang Bao Ya and Eagle King Yang Po Ying, these three enslavement path masters had moved at the same time.

Beast groups charged, immediately dispersing most of the battle rings.

Ma Shang Feng saw he was slightly winning in the experts challenging and wanted to rely on the dominance of their enslavement path masters to suppress Hei tribe army and change the unfavorable situation.

Facing the combined attack of three beast groups, Hei Lou Lan immediately tensed up and looked at Fang Yuan: "Wolf King, it is your turn now!"

Fang Yuan nodded and leisurely stood up from his seat.

He slowly strolled to the head of the twin-headed rhino and looked down at the three beast groups - all of them were fierce, powerful and were huge in size.

Either one of the three enslavement path masters were at the same level as him and were formidable opponents who would not lose to him in regards to enslavement path.

It was to the extent that the enslavement path Gu worms they had were much more comprehensive and superior to Fang Yuan's wolf enslavement Gu worms.

Under the condition that he did not reveal his strength path battle strength, Fang Yuan would find it hard to fight against this group by himself. In the previous two rounds of battle, his wolf group had all along been pushed into disadvantage by the three beast groups and had suffered huge losses. Meanwhile, Ma tribe had relied on this advantage to make the beast groups cover their backs and thus they could safely retreat behind defense lines the previous two times.

But at this moment, Fang Yuan coldly laughed, his heart filled with soaring battle intent.

His enslavement path Gu worms were slightly weaker in comparison to these three enslavement path masters, but he had received huge support from Hei tribe's Gu Immortals before the battle and his wolf group's size had increased by over ten times.

These wolf groups were hidden within the army and by using some Gu worms, the enemy was unable to sense them.

"Wolf King! I am Yang Po Ying, do you dare to fight me?" In the sky, Yang Po Ying was riding on a huge eagle, his heroic aura shone and his posture was upright as if it was a battle spear that would charge to the sky.

He took the initiative to challenge in order to pin down Fang Yuan's wolf group.

The eagle group could attack the wolf group from air, thus had a very advantageous position.

"Hahaha, Old Yang, go easy on brother Chang Shan Yin, after all he is an enslavement master like us. You need to give him some face." From the right, Rat King's ridiculing laughter could be heard.

And on the left, among the horse group, Ma Zun who was not good at talking just groaned and charged forward. Around him were large number of Gu Master experts on war horses, guarding him.

Enslavement path masters could display extreme strength when they themselves were present in the battle while commanding their beast group.

The three masters braved the risks and led their beast group in the charge. This was akin to three heavy punches, if the Hei tribe army did not block it off properly even by a little, they could very well be knocked out, the whole situation could crumble apart and they would have to retreat powerlessly.

After all, a battlefield was filled with unpredictable variables. There were many examples of the weak winning against the strong. Let alone when Hei tribe was only occupying a slight dominance.

"Brother Shan Yin..." Hei Lou Lan could not help revealing a worried expression. Although the scale of the wolf group had increased sharply, beyond that of the three beast groups, he was worried Fang Yuan would not be able to control all of them properly. After all, Fang Yuan had never controlled such a large number of wolves.

If he was not able to control them properly and instead became confused, or even if he could control them, with Wolf King's rank four peak stage primeval essence, how long could he hold on for?

Fang Yuan stood on the head of the twin-headed rhino, silent as his back faced Hei Lou Lan.

Looking at the three majestic beast groups charging and killing, pincer attacking from both sky and land, and were already approaching close, while Wolf King had yet to make any movement, Hei Lou Lan felt very anxious as he urged: "Brother Shan Yin, make your move quickly!"

Fang Yuan was still silent as if he did not hear it.

The three beast groups rushed over with great momentum and was less than two hundred steps away and looked like it would arrive in an instant; Hei tribe's army was in an uproar and Hei Lou Lan urged even more anxiously: "Brother Chang Shan Yin!!"

Fang Yuan raised his head and laughed: "It is time! The enemy poured all their strength to pressure me with the beast groups, but they do not know that they have brought about their own demise. Alliance leader Lou Lan, I need to congratulate you."

"Congratulate me for what?"

"This battle has already been won, the die is cast, alliance leader becoming the Lord of Imperial Court is a foregone conclusion." Fang Yuan lightly said.

Hei Lou Lan's eyes opened wide, he nearly shouted: 'The f*ck! Where are you getting this ridiculous sense of confidence from! Quick, mobilize your wolf group for me, the enemy is already near and you still have time to talk about such nonsense!?'

However, the very next moment, his eyes almost popped out like someone had struck the back of his eyes.

It was because he felt Fang Yuan's aura having astonishing changes.

From rank four peak stage to rank five initial stage...

From rank five initial stage to rank five middle stage...

From rank five middle stage to rank five upper stage...

And from rank five upper stage to rank five peak stage!

Right now, Fang Yuan was slowly lifting the concealment of breath concealment Gu and did not suppress his true cultivation anymore.

Rank five peak stage, a genuine rank five peak stage!

Wolf King Chang Shan Yin was actually a rank five peak stage enslavement path master!

Hei Lou Lan was dumbstruck and dazed as he stared at Fang Yuan's back view. The Gu Master guards nearby the main tent also looked with shocked and stunned gazes.

Under everyone's gaze, Fang Yuan activated eagle rise Gu; large eagle wings gently raised him to the sky.

In the sky, he gave a long howl.

Rank five amplify effect Gu and wolf howl Gu!

The wolf howl resounded throughout the skies, directly suppressing all the sounds from the three beast groups.

Howl... howl... howl!

The wolves started howling one after another in response to Fang Yuan.

Chapter 540: One vs Three!

Fang Yuan flew into the sky.

"Yang Po Ying, Jiang Bao Ya, Ma Zun, today is the day all of you die." He said plainly, his voice was loud and clear, reverbing in everyone's ears.

Ma Zun: "..."

Jiang Bao Ya snorted: "Hmph, shameless words!"

"You are actually rank five peak stage, Chang Shan Yin, you truly hid your abilities well." Yang Po Ying said with a solemn expression, her eyes burning with fire: "But this ignites my battle intent! This kind of battle is truly interesting!"

But at the next moment, when the wolf group emerged, his battle intent froze.

Many.

So many.

Too many!

A sea of wild wolves surged like the waves of the sea, first was the initial wave, then the second, third... as if connecting heaven and earth, it was unceasing and near infinite!

Ma Zun was finally moved!

The eagle group's movements halted as Yang Po Ying's expression was stiff.

"Such a huge wolf group, oh heaven, five hundred thousand? Eight hundred thousand? No, at least a million!" Jiang Bao Ya was shell-shocked, his battle intent vanished without a trace: "Retreat, my rat group was only six hundred thousand at its peak. After so many battles, I have not replenished them yet, thus I have less than two hundred thousand now! This is my foundation, I cannot lose them, retreat, retreat, retreat, we have to run!"

Jiang Bao Ya was a demonic cultivator, he was extremely selfish, he immediately turned around and ran away with his rat group.

Three things influenced an enslavement path Gu Master's strength. One was the size of their beast group, the second was the cooperation of the enslavement path Gu worms, and third was the foundation of the soul.

Fang Yuan's soul foundation was at the same level as the three enslavement masters due to Dang Hun mountain.

His enslavement Gu worms, although weaker than the three of them, was only inferior by a bit.

But his wolf group had reached an incredible number of one million five hundred and sixty thousand!

In contrast, the three of them had suffered huge losses to their beast groups after consecutive battles, especially the last two huge battles. There were two hundred thousand rats, a hundred and eighty thousand eagles, and the most number of horses, at three hundred and sixty. But together, there were no more than seven hundred and forty thousand!

Seven hundred and forty thousand, it was merely half of the one million five hundred and sixty thousand wolves!

Moreover, could beast groups really be counted in such a simple additive manner?

It has been mentioned before — No!

Different beast groups when mixed together, unless there were techniques like three hearts combination soul used, would impede each other and cause more trouble than good.

Large numbers of wolves gushed out. Before, they were hiding in the crevices underground, while some were hidden by Gu worms, and others were inside carriages. Now they all showed up!

Even Ma Zun who rarely spoke shouted in shock: "How can there be so many wolves!?"

They were originally going in a three way pincer attack, to take advantage of Fang Yuan being alone. In the end, there were countless wolves, and Hei tribe's weakness because their greatest strength instead!

The Gu Master guards beside him shouted loudly: "Lord Ma Zun, quickly retreat, the enemy forces are overwhelming, we cannot fight them head-on!"

Ma Zun was not a hot-blooded teenager, he quickly manipulated the horse group and changed direction to retreat.

But horse group was different from rat group, rats were mostly small and could change directions easily. When the horses run, it was hard to stop.

Especially when Fang Yuan had purposely waited until the horses and rats came close to Hei tribe army, before mobilizing his wolf group, his intentions were truly sinister.

But Ma Zun was an enslavement master, he had great attainments. He had a good grasp of his horse group's condition, he carefully controlled them and the horse group drew an arc across the ground as they brushed past Hei tribe army, turning to the outside, attempting to break out of this situation.

However, how could Fang Yuan let such a big piece of fat meat fly away?

Ma Zun was an enslavement master, but so was he.

Willing in his mind, the mutated wolf group howled as they chased.

"Mutated wolf group? So many!" Ma Zun's Gu Master guards turned around and looked, their expressions turning pale.

Ma Zun had a mutated beast group with him, called pegasus group, but their numbers could not compare with the mutated wolf group chasing them.

Most of his troops were ordinary horses like terror claw horse, how could these horses run faster than mutated wolves?

Ma Zun controlled the horse group's direction in an attempt to shrug off the wolf group.

But the mutated wolf group split into two, engaging in a pincer attack as they finally intercepted the horse group.

Soon after, a grand number of ordinary wolves pounced and surrounded the horses tightly.

"A spectacular intercept, as expected of a master level!" Seeing this, Hei Lou Lan was overjoyed, finally putting his worries about Chang Shan Yin away.

On the other end, Rat King escaped with a group of mutated wolves chasing him with a sea of wolves behind them. As the slower rats were constantly eaten by the wolves behind, they were like a huge beast rampaging, sucking up all the rats ahead of them.

Fang Yuan took a look and stopped caring about Rat King, he turned his gaze up towards the sky.

The wolf group ran on the ground, while the eagle group soared in the sky, it was beyond the wolf group's ability to deal with the eagle group.

Thus, among the three beast groups, even though the eagle group was weaker than the horse group, they were in a better position.

"Damn it, two beast groups have been targeted, the horse group is deep within encirclement, while Rat King ran away, only my group is left." Yang Po Ying felt a huge burden on his shoulders.

He knew that if he wanted to win this, the horse and rat groups were extremely precious battle strength, losses to either one would shrink Ma tribe's hopes of victory greatly.

"The only one who can salvage this situation is me. I have to use the eagle group to attack aggressively, to divert most of Chang Shan Yin's attention... eh?!"

Yang Po Ying was still thinking, when Fang Yuan controlled hundreds of thousand of wolves, charging and stomping towards Ma tribe's main tent in a grand manner.

Yang Po Ying was stuck between two hard decisions!

"If we fought one on one, my wolf group would definitely suffer against your eagle group. But we are at war now, if my wolf group slaughters large numbers of Gu Masters, no, even if they just expend most of their primeval essence, it would be a great victory in terms of attrition. Yang Po Ying, what will you do?"

Fang Yuan's eyes were calm as water, as the corners of his lips curled into a cold snicker.

Yang Po Ying thought rapidly in his head, but the more he thought about it, the colder his heart felt. Chang Shan Yin's decision was truly sinister and evil, it was a fatal blow.

But after hesitating for a while, Yang Po Ying gritted his teeth and decided to restrain Wolf King.

This way, the central wolf group did not have to engage the eagle group, and successfully charged into Ma tribe's army.

Ma Shang Feng's expression was cold as steel, he quickly mobilized his remaining enslavement path Gu Masters and formed a temporary defensive line.

But the wolf group was huge, and there were mutated wolves as vanguard, such a defensive line was thin as paper, easily broken through.

"This was a huge mistake due to my decision making! But we have not lost, everyone, the situation is dire, we have to stake it all here! Fight with me, we still have trump cards!!" Ma Shang Feng shouted, as Xue Wa and the other rank five snowmen showed their true form. At the same time, an elite troop comprising purely snowmen was formed.

Seeing such reinforcements, Ma tribe army's morale surged, they calmed down from the initial confusion, and rapidly shouted, fighting alongside Ma Shang Feng.

At once, wolves howled as blood splattered everywhere.

First was the central army, followed by Ma tribe's left and right troops, as the Gu Master starting their advancement.

Hei Lou Lan laughed heartily as he waved his hand, several elite troops of his started to move out. All the respective tribe leaders also led their tribesmen into the battlefield.

The two armies engaged in all-out combat.

Beast groups, humans, entangled together. Fire path, ice path, dark path, light path, all sorts of Gu Masters fought valiantly.

Experts laughed loudly as they slaughtered their enemies. While weaklings helped each other, forming groups as they resisted with their lives, fighting for a chance of survival.

The eagle group shrieked as they attacked Fang Yuan.

But beside Fang Yuan, there were Hei Lou Lan's personal guards, as well as Ye Lui Sang, Hao Ji Liu, Bian Si Xuan, Pan Ping and other experts, forming a tight defense.

The eagle group's attack was ineffective, while Fang Yuan used wolf care Gu to bypass his weakness of vision, allowing him to mobilize the wolf group to attack, slaughtering horses, rats, and people.

"We have urgent matters, Wu Ye, you guys go and restrain the experts near Chang Shan Yin!" On the eagle's back, Yang Po Ying was sweating profusely as he ordered.

Wu Ye was called Green Bat, one of the three flying masters in northern plains.

Among the three original flying masters, Flying Lightning Dong Po Kong was part of Dong Fang tribe, having returned to the blessed land. Water Fairy Song Qing Yin had died in battle already.

Only Green Bat Wu Ye was left, recruited by Ma tribe. He was especially left behind to deal with the new flying master Chang Shan Yin.

Wu Ye heard this and frowned: "If we strike, and the other party attacks, what will happen to your safety?"

Yang Po Ying laughed arrogantly: "I have the protection of the thunder eagles, I am extremely safe. Not even Hei Lou Lan can break my thunder eagles' defense instantly. Don't worry and go, don't forget our assassin Wu Ming!"

Wu Ye heard this and their hearts shook.

These people with flying abilities rushed out, causing Hei Lou Lan and the others' pressure to intensify when defending.

"Careful, they are trying to disturb us, don't step out easily. Don't forget that they have Wu Ming!" Hei Lou Lan snorted as he attacked, instructing his men.

Qi Lian tribe leader's godson Wu Ming, was a rank five dark path Gu Master. Ye Lui Sang could defeat the seven army alliance because he had assassinated many of their enemy's leaders, causing them to feel fear and a drop in morale.

After that, Wu Ming's performance was spectacular, a good number of rank five Gu Masters died in his hands, including even more rank four Gu masters.

He was hailed as the number one assassin in the current world, his reputation had greatly surpassed Shadow Sword Expert Bian Si Xuan.

Right now, he had not shown up yet, who knew which part of the battlefield he was lurking in.

Hei Lou Lan did not dare to be careless.

Once Wu Ming succeeds in assassinating Fang Yuan, the wolf group was collapse and the situation would reverse immediately.

"Charge, charge over and kill Wolf King Chang Shan Yin!" Not just Hei Lou Lan, Yang Po Ying and Ma tribe's experts also rapidly understood the crux of this battle.

At once, large numbers of Gu Master experts charged towards Hei tribe main camp.

"I will give five million battle merits to whoever kills Chang Shan Yin! He will be given the position of Ma tribe's supreme elder, and will enjoy Ma tribe's resources for life!" Ma Shang Feng fought and killed the wolves as he shouted loudly.

Such huge rewards naturally attracted many Gu Master experts, causing their eyes to turn red and their spears to point at Fang Yuan.

Chapter 541: Four Arm Earth King!

Very soon, Hei Lou Lan and the rest started to feel a pressure as heavy as a mountain!

"Not good, the enemy has gone crazy, we won't be able to hold on for long!"

"Black banner troops, come over to reinforce us quick!!"

"Pei Yan Fei, Zhong Fei You, Tang Miao Ming, you guys also come over to protect Wolf King!"

"We cannot continue to defend passively like this, we need to take the initiative to attack. Otherwise, the residual force of the battle will still endanger Wolf King!!"

Ma tribe was absolutely not resigned to losing.

If they lost, they would be completely finished!

They began to stake their lives, the heavy rewards alluring them to brave dangers. The situation quickly escaped out of Hei Lou Lan's control and the battlefield soon changed into attacking and defending Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan's safety and danger directly concerned the result of this battle.

The enemy rank four Gu Masters and rank five Gu Masters all rushed over, creating a huge chaotic scene.

This was a majestic spectacle that was rarely seen in the former Imperial Court contests.

In the battle rings, rank four Gu Masters were already reduced to a supporting role. Even rank five experts could not act freely and were in a risky situation.

Hei Lou Lan, Ye Lui Sang and others had still been paying some attention to Wolf King at first. But soon, they were finding it difficult to protect themselves, surrounding them were flames, ice and snow, sound waves and all sorts of attacks that flew chaotically among the battle rings. The enemy did not remain in a fixed place, fighting anyone they met. There were times they even attacked their own people.

The number one assassin Wu Ming stood at a distant, helplessly looking at the giant chaotic battle ring.

He was an assassin, an expert at getting close while hiding before striking the fatal attack.

But right now, the battleground had become so chaotic with all Gu Masters attacking madly, all kinds of investigative Gu worms scanning around, and Gu Masters killing anybody they came across. The situation was already out of control, the offense too overwhelming, and some rank four Gu Masters had already become hysterical to protect themselves.

Wu Ming was doubtful, if he entered stealthily, he might be discovered within a few breaths of time. It might even be his own people who might attack him in the heat of the moment!

"Even if I don't make a move, Wolf King will find it hard to keep his life in such a situation!" Wu Ming smiled coldly and kept on watching the show.

Soon, his eyes brightened and saw a rank four Gu Master of his side moving towards Wolf King from the side.

"Cheng Hu!" When he saw the person clearly, Wu Ming almost shouted in excitement.

Someone had struck Cheng Hu from behind and sent him flying towards Fang Yuan.

Previously, Fang Yuan had Bian Si Xuan guarding him from the side.

But just moments ago, Bian Si Xuan had taken the initiative to draw away the encroaching Fei Sheng Cheng. She was not a defensive Gu Master and also did not have any intention to sacrifice her life for Fang Yuan, thus she felt that was the most sensible choice.

"Which scoundrel sneak attacked me!" Cheng Hu fell on the ground and immediately stood up, furiously roaring before turning around and charging towards the direction he came from.

"This?!" Wu Ming did not know what to say at this scene.

However, Cheng Hu had only walked five-six steps when suddenly he seemed to have been struck by a body immobilization spell as he stopped on the spot. He furiously turned around and rigidly stared at Fang Yuan who was within his reach.

After few breaths of being dazed, he finally came back to his senses.

"The guys who sneak attacked me, I really love you!! Hahaha!" Cheng Hu's pores opened up in excitement and looked at Fang Yuan like he was looking at five million battle merits and endless fame and fortune!

Grrr!

He pounced forward, his limbs instantly transformed into a gorgeous tiger the moment he landed.

Transformation path killer move!

Slant-eye tiger roared, a reeking wind pounced towards Fang Yuan.

"Damn it! Hide quickly!" Bian Si Xuan glanced back and involuntarily screamed.

"Success!!" Wu Ming felt his blood pumping and his body shivering with excitement.

The tiger opened its bloody mouth, leaped to the air and pounced down! The huge shadow shrouded over Fang Yuan's face. The tiger's sharp teeth was almost closing at his head!

"I had not thought such a heaven-shaking contribution will fall to my hands... huh?!" The tiger's eyes suddenly flashed with a shocked look.

A pair of large hands grabbed the tiger's neck, immobilizing it!

"Hmph!" Cheng Hu snorted inwardly, his many years of battle experience and insight allowed him to quickly slash with his two sharp claws.

Thud.

A muffled sound echoed, the next moment, the two tiger claws were separately grabbed by two metallic hands.

'Where did these hands come from?' Cheng Hu gazed with bewilderment and saw Fang Yuan's cold gaze and tranquil-as-ice face, and two bronze arms that had grown from his sides since some unknown time ago!

The two bronze hands firmly grabbed Cheng Hu's tiger claws.

"Hmph!" Cheng Hu snorted and immediately used his tail as well. The tail lashed through the air, forming a fierce whip shadow that was agile and tricky as it smashed towards Fang Yuan's head.

SLAM!

A clear sound echoed. There was not the slightest of injuries on Fang Yuan's head, but instead it was the tiger tail that had turned numb from the pain and lost its control.

Cheng Hu had a killer move, Fang Yuan similarly possessed a killer move.

Killer move — Four Arm Earth King!

There were no less than fourteen Gu worms used for this killer move, including rank five amplify effect Gu!

In such a state, Fang Yuan's defense had increased by over four times. His strength reaching eight hundred jun! Moreover, when he was touching the ground, his strength would keep on increasing without end.

"Have you played enough?" Fang Yuan gave a cold smile, looking calmly at Cheng Hu, his gaze carrying a ridiculing and cold intent.

An intense coldness rose from Cheng Hu's heart before quickly spreading over his whole body.

Fear!

Even if Cheng Hu was usually carefree and took his bravery as an honor, right now as he looked at Fang Yuan's dark and cold eyes, he felt fear!

The intense fear caused him to erupt with strength!

The tiger moved its throat, preparing a sound wave attack.

However, at this moment, Fang Yuan gave a soft sigh.

"Such a boring trick... sigh, it is better for you to die."

His voice was tranquil and light, as if he was talking of an insignificant thing.

PSHHH!

The next moment, the bronze hands exerted strength and pulled.

The gorgeous tiger was ripped into two halves, fresh blood splattered and internal organs fell down to the ground.

Two irregular tiger part fell down to the ground and transformed back to two halves of a human.

And the tiger head turned back to Cheng Hu's head; his eyes were wide open in fear, completely revealing the fear of death!

Fang Yuan grabbed Cheng Hu's skull and slowly raised his head, his gaze traversing through everyone and landed on Yang Po Ying.

The hair all over Yang Po Ying's body stood on their end, an intense sense of danger was rising in his heart!

Fang Yuan flapped his eagle wings and flew to the sky!

Yang Po Ying's pupils shrunk, immediately mobilizing the thunder eagle group to protect him.

Fang Yuan smiled in disdain: Do you think you can block me with just these beasts with rank four battle strength?

Hehe.

Bam Bam Bam....

He directly charged straight ahead, the thunder eagles in his way were forcefully smashed into pieces.

By the time the Gu Masters in the chaotic battlefield reacted, Fang Yuan had already charged through the thunder eagle group like a hot knife cutting through butter and reached Yang Po Ying.

"You!" Yang Po Ying's face lost all blood as he looked at Fang Yuan with extreme fear.

Fang Yuan lifted him by his head, his whole body not even able to resist the slightest bit.

Fang Yuan lightly clenched his hand.

Crack!

Fang Yuan burst Eagle King Yang Po Ying's head as easily as bursting a watermelon.

Blood and brain matter splattered, and the eagle group instantly crumbled apart.

The eagle group flew away back to the sunny sky.

The enormous commotion attracted countless people.

"What? Wolf King personally killed Eagle King?!" A lot of people shouted incredulously at this sight.

"Now, it is your turn." Fang Yuan did not stop, his cold gaze landing on Ma Zun.

They were separated by ten thousand steps of distance and he was protected by the majestic horse group, but Ma Zun still felt a terror as if a calamity was descending upon him.

"Block him!"

"Kill Wolf King!!"

Wu Ye and Xi Xue flew together and pincer attacked Fang Yuan.

"A bunch of trash wants to block me?" Fang Yuan snorted in disdain, he flapped his two wings and easily shook away Xi Xue, directly charging towards Wu Ye.

"This..." Wu Ye had never expected Fang Yuan to be so violent! He overestimated his own defense while also underestimating Fang Yuan's fierce offensive.

The defensive light barrier only held for half a breath of time before collapsing apart. Wu Ye immediately sensed danger and with his master level flying skill, he was able to make a dodging movement which others simply could not do.

If it were others, they might only be able to let him escape, but Fang Yuan was similarly a flying master!

Bang!

A dull sound echoed, half of Wu Ye's body was smashed into paste with bones fracturing into pieces and internal organs of half his body bursting apart.

His eyes were wide open as he fell down from the sky.

A generation's flying master, a demonic path expert had perished!

Fang Yuan moved on towards Ma Zun without even glancing at Wu Ye.

ROAR!

A dragon roar echoed like a thunder, and an enormous dragon blocked Fang Yuan's way.

This giant dragon had golden horn, three claws and dragon eyes which were burning like lanterns, revealing the flames of revenge: "Chang Shan Yin! you dared to kill my younger brother, you shall pay the most bitter price for this!"

This person was a rank five expert of transformation path, Cheng Hu's big brother — Cheng Long!

"Noisy earthworm." Fang Yuan snorted and increased his speed, leaving behind an afterimage in the air as he fiercely smashed into the giant dragon.

BOOM!

The explosive sound of the collision was deafening.

The sound wave spread to all directions, resounding through the sky and earth.

Hearts trembled as countless gazes fixed at the distant, looking at Fang Yuan whose body had inflated by two times and was covered in a bronze luster, his four arms thicker than a grown man's thighs.

He stood proudly in the air, grabbing a broken dragon horn.

While the three clawed golden giant dragon fell down to the ground like a puppet with its strings cut. It fiercely smashed into the ground, creating a giant pit with dragon blood and dragon scales splattering all around.

"What?" Ma Shang Feng's pupils rapidly shrunk as he blurted out involuntarily, not daring to believe the reality, "Even Cheng Long could not take one move from him!"

"This killer move..." Hei Lou Lan absentmindedly looked at Fang Yuan, seeing the reflection of Liu tribe's three brothers''three heads six arms' killer move.

"Ma Zun, I, Wolf King, will take your life." Fang Yuan lightly said, his voice travelling across the battlefield, his calm tone was like he was once again speaking of insignificant matter.

But to everyone else, his words had a feeling of being unrivalled!

"Uncle Ma Zun, leave quickly. I will block him!" Ma tribe's young tribe leader Ma Ying Jie shouted from Ma Zun's side.

The other Gu Master guards also started persuading: "Wolf King is very fierce, we cannot face him head-on. Lord and young tribe leader, please leave, we will hold him back!"

Chapter 542: Dual Cultivating Two Paths!

People all around Ma Zun kept on persuading strongly; Ma Zun's expression was ashen as he resolutely refused: "No, my Ma tribe only has warriors who will fight to death, not cowards who will run away. I am a symbol of Ma tribe, it will be a heavy impact to our army's morale if I run away! I cannot leave, we have yet to lose, I still have my pegasus group!"

With a shift of his mind, the pegasus flew into the air like clouds.

These grand beasts had snow-white fur, their mane fluttered in the wind as they unfolded their pure white wings.

These pegasus were Ma tribe's pride.

A grand feeling emerged in Ma tribesmen's hearts as they looked at these pegasus, the feelings of fear quickly calmed down.

"Right, we still have pegasus.... ah!?" Ma Ying Jie was speaking, when suddenly he exclaimed in shock and terror!

Fang Yuan was shooting towards them like a meteor, fiercely crashing through the pegasus group without any intent to dodge.

The pegasus which had rank four battle strength were smashed through, their blood spurting high.

The horse group neighed in panic, their pure white feathers helplessly drifted in the air as their corpse fell down to the ground.

Fang Yuan moved straight through pegasus group and reached above Ma Zun and the group with none able to block him!

Ma Zun was stunned, the Gu Masters beside opened their mouth wide as they looked at Fang Yuan, their heart filled with extreme shock, helplessness and fear.

Fang Yuan's ghostly figure deeply imprinted itself in the depths of their heart, never to be forgotten!

"No, I have not lost yet!" Ma Zun freaked out and was about to use his killer move when he was blocked by Ma Ying Jie.

"Uncle, let me do it. Once you use this killer move, your cultivation will fall. Ma tribe can lose me, but it can never lose you!" Ma Ying Jie shouted, his gaze filled with determination.

"Ying Jie!" Ma Zun's body shook, he looked at this junior whom he appreciated and was most hopeful about, and felt his will to fight to the death.

Ma Zun did not want his nephew to sacrifice for him.

But just like Ma Ying Jie said, Ma tribe could lose Ma Ying Jie, but it needed him, Ma Zun, to command horse group. The eagle group had crumbled apart now and the rat group could not be counted on, if they lose the horse group as well, Ma tribe's defeat will be certain!

"Also, my death is not certain. Uncle, leave quickly!" Ma Ying Jie turned solemn, mobilizing his primeval essence into several Gu worms.

Killer move — Dragon Horse Spirit!

This was a killer move that was specially prepared for them by Snowy Mountain's demonic path Gu Immortal Xue Song Zi.

Neighhh Neighhh...

Many horses beside Ma Ying Jie raised their front legs and gave desperate and crazy neighs.

Large amount of blood seeped out of their body; they fell down one after another as they lost their life.

But at the same time, diverse and gorgeous horse souls resembling rainbows pierced out of the corpses.

"Mutated horse souls..." Fang Yuan's pupils slightly shrunk.

Normal souls were simply impossible to be detected by ordinary people.

But these horse souls had a pair of coral-like dragon horns on their head and were also of every size, as if they were alive, and they also shone with all kinds of colors; only the blind would not be able to see them.

Dragon horses floated up and charged towards Fang Yuan in a very fast speed.

Fang Yuan flew away, pulling apart some distance while also making probing attacks.

These horse souls were troublesome because they were souls. Ordinary physical attacks had no effect on them. At the same time, their self-destruction had the power equal to the soul explosion of the previous shark fin wolf!

Fang Yuan's killer move was strong, but it was not a soul path killer move; if three horse souls self-destructed at the same time, he would not be able to endure it.

After all, his soul cultivation was still at thousand man soul.

"But why would I face you head-on?" Fang Yuan scoffed and slowly landed on the ground.

He was not simply a pure strength path Gu Master, he still had enslavement path methods.

Next moment, wolf smoke surged and healed the wolves beside him. Wolf howl resounded raising the wolves' battle strength by several times.

The wolves then charged towards Ma Ying Jie and Ma Zun like hungry sharks.

"Damn it!" Ma Ying Jie immediately experienced Fang Yuan's insidiousness and unscrupulousness!

He had sacrificed large numbers of horses beside him to form into mutated horse souls for the killer move 'dragon horse spirit'.

But Fang Yuan did not face his horse souls, instead sending his wolf group to death.

The wolves used their lives to wear down the horse souls' strength, and the mutated horse souls started becoming dimmer as they defended against the wolf group's fierce attacks; some dispersed and some self-destructed.

Large numbers of wolves died in exchange for a sharp reduction of the horse souls.

Fang Yuan was displaying the essence of the enslavement path to the extreme.

Enslavement path Gu Masters used cannon fodder to exhaust the enemy's precious strength. For example, consuming their primeval essence, and right now, it was to perish along with the horse souls.

Ma Ying Jie could do nothing to Fang Yuan!

Mutated horse souls were strong, but after slaughtering so many wolves in such a short period of time, they were now powerless to be of any threat to Fang Yuan.

"Uncle, leave! You are our Ma tribe's hope, leave quickly!" Ma Ying Jie shouted, persuading Ma Zun to leave again.

Ma Zun's cheeks streamed with tears, his heart filled with pain, hatred, anger and hesitation.

He gritted his teeth to the point of almost breaking them, but in the end, under the urging of his rationality, he slowly moved his body and led a group of horses, leaving Ma Ying Jie and retreating towards Ma tribe camp.

"Hmm?" Fang Yuan immediately sensed Ma Zun's movement.

Ma Zun was an enslavement path master, hundred times more significant than Ma Ying Jie! Fang Yuan immediately flapped his wings and flew to the sky. He gave up on Ma Ying Jie and began to chase Ma Zun.

"Wolf King, don't leave!" Ma Ying Jie hurriedly mobilized horse souls to fly into the sky to intercept Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan coldly smiled in disdain and made an exquisite turn in the air, throwing all the horse souls behind him.

He was a flying master while these mutated horse souls were no more than Ma Ying Jie's puppets.

Looking at Fang Yuan rushing towards them with killing intent, the Gu Master guards beside Ma Zun immediately became fearful.

With no choice, Ma Zun also used the killer move 'dragon horse spirit'!

Under his control, mutated horse souls formed into a tight defense line; their might was much more than what Ma Ying Jie showed.

Even if Fang Yuan had flying master achievement, it would be difficult for him to break through.

ROAR!

A dragon roar resonated at this moment.

An enormous shadow shrouded over Fang Yuan.

The three clawed, golden horn giant dragon once again charged at Fang Yuan!

Cheng Long had been defeated in one move by Fang Yuan and had fallen down to the ground miserably. He had barely crawled out of the hole when he was attacked by several enemies, and after spending all his strength to thwart and beat away these obstacles, he chased after Fang Yuan in rage, to take revenge.

"You actually came to send yourself to death." Fang Yuan coldly smiled, not in the least moved as he looked at the dragon claws that were rapidly approaching him with an invincible might.

The eagle wings on his back flapped and he easily brushed past the dragon claws.

Relying on his exquisite flying skill, he made the giant dragon go circles around him.

"Not good, I am not Wolf King's match in the air!" Cheng Long soon realized his disadvantage, but it was already late.

Fang Yuan grabbed this gap to fly to the dragon head.

His two bronze arms ruthlessly pounded on the the two eyes of the giant dragon like a battle spear or a sharp sword.

The dragon eyes burst and blood splashed in all directions.

The giant dragon immediately went mad, roaring miserably due to the intense pain.

Fang Yuan was splashed all over with scarlet blood, but he did not stop, he gave a sinister smile and continued piercing deep into the eyes with his two hands, directly attacking the brain membrane. While his other two hands smashed at the dragon head like a heavy hammer.

BANG BANG BANG!

Huge sounds echoed out again and again as Fang Yuan continued to hammer at the dragon head like pounding on a war drum.

The giant dragon started falling down, it struggled with mad fervor and its long tail twisted into a braid.

Stones and mud flew, and the dragon tail lashed out, sending both humans and beasts flying.

Fang Yuan did not stop his attack, he continued to pound for twenty to thirty times and was finally satisfied when the dragon head was thoroughly smashed into pieces.

White brain matter and blood spurted upon his whole body.

He took a deep breath, the intense odor of blood instead making him feel satisfied! Especially when he looked silently at this giant dragon corpse that he had conquered.

"Man, no matter which world they live in, all lives to conquer; conquer the enemy, conquer themselves..." Fang Yuan sighed with emotion.

Although the dragon had already died, the dragon corpse had not transformed back, one could see how profound Cheng Long's achievement in transformation path was.

"His head was quite tough, but he was no more than an impulsive fool." Fang Yuan lightly commented before looking towards Ma Zun again.

"He... he even killed Cheng Long!"

"Is this still Wolf King? Wasn't he an enslavement path master?!"

The scene of Fang Yuan stepping on the corpse shocked many.

Most of them simply did not dare to believe their own eyes.

How could Wolf King change from an enslavement path master into such a fierce warrior that rampaged in the battlefield?

Meanwhile, the wolf group howled and charged waves after waves without any pause, showing Fang Yuan's exquisite beast controlling skill.

Ma Zun's face was pale, his primeval essence was gradually exhausted as he kept on maintaining the killer move 'dragon horse spirit'.

The mutated horse souls had formed a tight defensive battle formation; the wolf group throwing their lives as they charged forward waves after waves.

Fang Yuan remained unmoved at these sacrifices, only sneering inwardly: 'Now, let me show you the true power of dual cultivation in enslavement and strength path.'

With a shift of his mind, the wolf group immediately changed their offensive pattern, dividing into several groups and breaking forward like sharp cones. The mutated souls' battle formation was unavoidably pulled apart.

As the defensive line became thinly spread, Fang Yuan took the initiative to launch an assault.

Ma Zun felt a chill in his heart and promptly maneuvered the mutated horse souls to intercept Fang Yuan, but this caused the defensive line to turn chaotic.

Fang Yuan laughed and changed the direction of his assault while making the wolf group charge ahead by three hundred steps.

Ma Zun blocked left and right, soon being unable to hold off the attacks.

If he guarded against Fang Yuan's assault, the wolf group would be free to charge forward. If he defend against the wolf group, he would not be able to guard against Fang Yuan.

After several rounds, Fang Yuan saw a gap and fiercely charged towards Ma Zun. The first strike broke Ma Zun's defensive barrier, the second punch seriously injured Ma Zun and the third punch killed this famous enslavement path master!

Ma Zun died!

The horse group crumbled apart and Ma tribe's army's morale lowered to the abyss!

"If I had not seen it personally, I would never have believed this!"

"Horse King actually died by enslavement path master Wolf King's beheading the leader tactic!!"

"Wolf King concealed himself too deeply, he actually cultivated both enslavement and strength path. He simply does not need to fear beheading the leader tactics, how can we deal with such an enslavement path master?"

Chapter 543: Victory has been decided

The terrifying strength Fang Yuan displayed inflicted heavy pressure on everyone in Ma tribe army.

Despair was quickly spreading in their heart!

"Now, we can only rely on Rat King, only the rat group can contend against the wolf group!" Ma Shang Feng's face was ashen, Ma Zun's death made him feel like he had fallen into an ice cave. But he was Ma tribe leader, and under this desperation, he looked towards Jiang Bao Ya's direction.

However, the next moment, the only hope left in Ma Shang Feng's eyes was also obliterated.

Rat King had actually fled!

"Heavens, this Wolf King is a monster! Eagle King, Horse King, Cheng Long, Cheng Hu and Wu Ye were all killed by him, will I be able to survive if I don't run away now?"

Blood flowed out of all seven facial orifices of Jiang Bao Ya as he ran away.

He could not do anything about this, he had sworn the poison vow when he joined Ma tribe army. Now that he was deserting in the battle, he naturally suffered the backlash of the poison vow.

But Jiang Bao Ya wanted to retreat even if he had to risk the backlash!

Fang Yuan's terrifying performance had already completely obliterated all will to battle in his heart.

"Rat King, return right now!!" Ma Shang Feng shouted.

But Jiang Bao Ya ignored him and ran madly.

The blood from his seven facial orifices was dying the path, showing his determination to run!

His fleeing attracted the people around him and soon, a large number of Ma tribe Gu Masters began to retreat with large number of tribes gathering their forces as they retreated from the battlefield.

"One really shouldn't rely on outsiders!" Ma Shang Feng spurted out a large mouthful of blood before he blacked out and fainted.

Ma tribe army was utterly crushed, the situation was set!

Despite having the snowman elite troops, they could not turn around the situation.

Gu Master experts also started to retreat one after another.

'I almost had to break my seal and use my true martial physique to fight. Luckily! Luckily!' In a battle ring, Hei Lou Lan who had been attacked from all around, was gasping, his body full of injuries and his primeval essence heavily depleted, but the ominous glint in his eyes was becoming colder and sharper.

Under his order, Hei tribe army began a ruthless hunt.

The more they killed, the more battle merits they would obtain. Even a fool understood this.

Fame and fortune incited Hei tribe army to be like brutal famished wolves.

At first, the elite troops were covering Ma tribe's retreat, but soon Hei tribe's elite troops rushed to them and pinned them down. Ma tribe army had thoroughly collapsed and countless people were escaping to all directions.

Fang Yuan did not move, instead calling the wolf group to protect him.

"Heavy internal bleeding, soul has been weakened to five hundred man soul..." Fang Yuan inspected his body, swallowing the blood in his mouth as waves after waves of dizziness attacked him.

His two bronze arms quietly disappeared. The repercussions of four arm earth king killer move was much more serious than what he had expected.

"The several experiments before only scratched the surface. Now that I used it to its extreme, even going beyond the theorised time limit, a problem has occured. Sure enough, genuine knowledge comes from practice."

Killer move was an exquisite coordination between Gu worms.

But a killer move was not perfected by just planning it.

Only by putting it into practice and revising it continuously, could the killer move be perfected. And this process to perfect it could last a very long time, lasting generations and even over ten generations of continuous deductions and adjustments.

Four arm earth king was a result of Fang Yuan using his five hundred years of experience along with a moment of inspiration. It was made in a hurry and was still in experimental phase.

Fang Yuan was soon able to understand what caused such heavy repercussions.

"It is the rank five earth overlord Gu. This killer move was originally based on ground fight, the longer one is touching the ground, the lighter the repercussions. But I was flying almost all the time in this battle. Thus, this problem was exposed."

"It seems four arm earth king killer move has a lot of shortcomings. From this battle, I can see flying is much more convenient than charging crash Gu, and possesses much higher threat to enemies. Since I have master level attainment in flying, I should make full use of this superiority."

He was not willing to give up flying, so the four arm earth king killer move had to be greatly altered.

Fang Yuan sat on the aged night wolf emperor, quietly pondering while looking at the wanton slaughtering by Hei tribe army.

"Damn it... still vigilant, not giving me even a little chance!" Assassin Wu Ming was hiding in a distant while observing Fang Yuan.

He had been thinking of taking advantage of Wolf King's negligence after the battles, to sneak attack him.

If he succeeded and killed Wolf King, Ma tribe would still have a chance to regroup and make a comeback.

But Fang Yuan did not give him any opportunity, almost as if he saw through his plan.

Wu Ming waited for a while more, but because of Hei tribe experts moving about more frequently nearby, he could not endure anymore and quietly retreated.

Ma tribe was fleeing in defeat, and while they were fleeing, Ma tribe leader Ma Shang Feng woke up.

He was still not resigned and after they fled to the defense line, he tried to hold on by relying on the defense line.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng's mountain as before Gu wrecked his plan. Hei tribe army broke through the defense line, Pan Ping used his sole blade Gu and luckily managed to get Ma Shang Feng's head in the chaotic battle.

With Ma tribe leader's death, Ma tribesmen no longer had the will to battle.

Tao tribe, Yang tribe and Qi Lian tribe surrendered one after another. The surrendering process unavoidably attracted most of Hei tribe's attention.

"Move faster, faster, faster!" Zhao Lian Yun was urging from inside the carriage.

Fei Cai was taking the coachman position and used all his strength to lash at the horse, the carriage's two wheels moved at a rapid speed.

Fei Cai was Ma Ying Jie's head servant and being in charge of Ma tribe's young tribe leader's everyday life, he naturally had to accompany Ma Ying Jie to the battle. Zhao Lian Yun was homeless and so could only follow behind him.

Ma tribe was defeated, these two and other mortals also fled for their lives.

However, just relying on the horsepower, the carriage's speed simply could not surpass a Gu Master. While they escaped, they were thrown far behind by Gu Masters.

But because Fei Cai and Zhao Lian Yun were mortals, the army chasing after Ma tribe army let them go.

The battle merits in killing mortals were next to nothing.

Of course, if they encountered Gu Masters in a bad mood or those who liked to kill or wolves who did not care if they were mortals, just one or two casual moves from either of these could send them to their grave.

However, Fei Cai and Zhao Lian Yun's luck were really good, not only did they not encounter such situation, they were actually able to smoothly escape out of the battlefield under countless Gu Masters' eyes.

The two put in all their efforts in escaping.

The old horse pulling the carriage foamed in exhaustion and finally fell on the grassland.

The carriage overturned soon after and broke apart.

Fei Cai and Zhao Lian Yun broke out of the broken carriage in a miserable state. Although they were injured, it was not serious because of the soft grassland.

"Now where should we go?" Fei Cai was indecisive; they were in a vast land without any soldiers or Gu Masters chasing them.

Zhao Lian Yun panted heavily without replying, she was also feeling flustered and helpless.

'Wolf King Chang Shan Yin... there is actually such a terrifying monster in this world! Damn it, if I had known you were this fierce, why would I persuade father to travel so far to side with Ma tribe?'

As she thought of Fang Yuan's terrifying figure rampaging in the midst of innumerable troops, Zhao Lian Yun's body and mind trembled.

Remembering her father who had died in the battlefield, their current homeless situation and the ruthlessness of fate, Zhao Lian Yun began to weep in grief.

"Xiao Yun, don't cry, don't cry, don't worry, I am still here." Fei Cai immediately comforted her.

Zhao Lian Yun buried her head in her knees and cried even louder.

Fei Cai panicked as he comforted and apologizes repeatedly, cutting out a very clumsy figure.

Zhao Lian Yun cried for a while, then suddenly raised her head: "What's the use of your apology! I am really miserable, how could I come to such a world! Now our situation is desperate with nothing to eat or even drink. At night, the bloody odor on the battlefield will attract groups after groups of beasts to forage. Sooner or later, we will starve to death, die of thirst or even freeze to death."

"Eh? Then, then what should we do?" Fei Cai looked at Zhao Lian Yun with an expression that was seeking help.

Zhao Lian Yun rolled her eyes and furiously shouted: "You are really trash! You are older than me, can't you think of something! You want me to think of everything, do you think I am Dong Fang Yu Liang?!"

Fei Cai lowered his head after being scolded, only daring to look at his feet.

Suddenly, he raised his head with bright eyes: "I, I have thought of a good way."

"Ah? What way?" Zhao Lian Yun raised her brows in amazement, this fool had actually thought of a way?

"I feel that as long as we have a horse, we can escape far away from the battlefield. With no odor of blood, we will be able to avoid the beasts."

Zhao Lian Yun fiercely kicked Fei Cai: "Do you think I don't know?! You fool, you big idiot! What good method is this? I also want a horse, where will you get me one?"

Fei Cai jumped in pain from Zhao Lian Yun's kick.

Suddenly, he pointed ahead and shouted: "Look, there is a horse."

Zhao Lian Yun turned around to look and was stupefied, blurting out: "The fuc... there really is a horse!"

But she quickly reacted: "There are no lack of horses in northern plains, but what we lack is the method to capture and tame it. Fei Cai, do you have any method?"

Fei Cai exclaimed, his hand still pointing ahead as he shouted: "Look, there is a person on the horse!"

Zhao Lian Yun concentrated, there really was a person.

As the horse neared the two, Zhao Lian Yun's eyes suddenly opened wide because of the identity of the injured person on the horse's back: "Ma Ying Jie!"

　　...

"Congratulations brother, congratulations. Hei tribe has won this battle, even if Ma tribe gets support from Gu Immortals, they cannot reverse the situation." Hei Bai who had been observing the battle all along, saw Hei tribe was already beginning to clear up the battlefield through investigative Gu, and impatiently congratulated Hei Cheng who was beside him.

Hei Cheng lightly smiled: "Congratulations to you too. Hei Lou Lan, this kid did not betray our expectations. Ah, right, the demonic path Gu Immortal who supported Ma tribe has been discovered, it is Xue Song Zi of Snowy Mountain's sixth peak."

Hei Bai's expression immediately turned heavy: "Hmph, so it was him. If not for him meddling and fighting with me over wooden chicken Gu, the Immortal Gu would not have escaped the bindings, and I would have already been in possession of wooden chicken Gu."

Hei Cheng comforted him with a smile: "Brother, no need to worry, it will be the same thing if we can obtain wooden chicken Gu with the help of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. This is called: the road to happiness is strewn with setbacks. Once you obtain wooden chicken Gu, you will become an expert among Gu Immortals immediately."

"I don't deserve such praise!" Hei Bai immediately bowed at Hei Cheng and sincerely said: "If not for elder brother's generous help, how could I have such financial ability like Xue Song Zi? Elder brother is really wise and far-sighted, investing so much immortal essence stones, it was an amazing decision. As expected, stocking up the wolf groups before sending them out for support all at once truly caught Xue Song Zi unprepared. This time, even if Xue Song Zi wants to continue sending help, there is no one to receive it."

"Hahaha." Hei Cheng laughed brightly before sighing, "Without investment, how could there be profits?"

He paused a moment and continued: "Also, we were fortunate that other famous super tribes did not really make their move in this Imperial Court contest. There was also the information from Fairy Tan Bi Ya which allowed us to know of the secret relationship between Ma tribe and Snowy Mountain. Another point, this Wolf King Chang Shan Yin is truly a spectacular junior, his performance was outstanding, the one with the most radiance in this contest such that his brilliance surpasses this generation's Gu Masters in northern plains."

Hei Bai also nodded, having the same feeling: "I have already investigated Chang Shan Yin in detail, he is a person of Chang tribe and was very famous, even us Gu Immortals knew of him. Later, he mysteriously disappeared for over ten years, he clearly had a fortuitous encounter. Now, he cultivates both enslavement and strength path, I saw the killer move he used just before, its repercussions are not small but it is indeed somewhat interesting."

Fang Yuan could conceal his injuries from the surrounding people, but he could not conceal it from Gu Immortals.

Hei Cheng was silent for a while before speaking: "This is a Gu Immortal seed, I plan to take him into Hei tribe. After he enters Imperial Court blessed land, we will properly observe him. If he is willing to join us and offer his loyalty, he might be able to become our Hei tribe's external supreme elder in the future."

Hei Bai smiled: "The difficulty of ascending to Gu Immortal realm is unspeakable, elder brother truly thinks highly of him. In my opinion, Tai Bai Yun Sheng is also quite good, we can also ask him to join Hei tribe."

"Mm... but he is a little old." Hei Cheng nodded.

In these Gu Immortals' eyes, only Chang Shan Yin and Tai Bai Yun Sheng piqued their interest and gained their attention among the entire Hei tribe alliance army!

Chapter 544: Entrapping a Gu Immortal?

When Ma Ying Jie finally woke up, his first sight was Fei Cai's joyous smiling face.

Fei Cai shouted: "Young tribe leader, you are finally awake!"

The simple and honest voice warmed Ma Ying Jie's heart. He struggled to sit upright, but the intense pain caused him to grimace and froth started to bubble from his mouth, he was barely able to ask: "Where is this place?"

Fei Cai scratched his head, and said in shame: "I also don't know where this is, but we should have escaped the battlefield."

"Battlefield?" Ma Ying Jie suddenly started and immediately asked, "The battle, what happened?"

"We lost, lord young tribe leader. Many people escaped and even more people surrendered." Fei Cai answered.

Ma Ying Jie's face turned pale white and his body shook, almost fainting down, but luckily Fei Cai was supporting his back.

Zhao Lian Yun stood at the side, looking at this formerly radiant Ma tribe young tribe leader who had now fallen into such a miserable state; it left a bad taste in her mouth.

'Sigh, this Ma Ying Jie is young and promising, it is a pity he ran into Wolf King Chang Shan Yin. It was not that you didn't try hard enough, but that the enemy was too much of a monster...'

Ma Ying Jie closed his eyes, two streams of tears quietly falling down.

After a while, he opened his reddened eyes and looked at Fei Cai and Zhao Lian Yun, asking in a hoarse voice: "Did you guys save me?"

Fei Cai and Zhao Lian Yun nodded.

"Young tribe leader, what do we do now?" Fei Cai asked.

Ma Ying Jie said with a gloomy expression: "We will return! This battle is our Ma tribe's defeat, but we still have some tribesmen remaining behind in warm pond valley."

Back then, before heroes assembly, Ma tribe schemed and brought about internal disorder in Fei tribe, before swallowing Fei tribe and occupying warm pond valley.

Ma tribe's higher-ups, to be prepared for the unexpected, left behind the old, weak, sick and crippled behind at warm pond valley.

If Ma tribe won, they would take these people back. But if Ma tribe lost, these people would be the seeds to continue the tribe's bloodline!

"Return to warm pond valley? But we don't have water and also don't have any rations. To travel such a long distance..." Zhao Lian Yun's brows furrowed into a knot.

"Heh, little girl, as long as I am here, there will be sufficient water and food. You guys don't need to worry." Ma Ying Jie replied.

The three started their journey, coming across many Ma tribesmen who had fled; Ma Ying Jie took all of them in.

"Lord young tribe leader, I had not thought that I, Ma You Liang, would still live to see you!" When Ma You Liang saw Ma Ying Jie, he immediately said this in a sobbing voice.

He was Ma tribe's rank three elder and was lying on a stretcher now; he had lost an arm and his right leg was fractured, his injuries were severe.

When Ma Ying Jie saw Ma You Liang, tears involuntarily welled up in his eyes: "Elder Ma You Liang, it really is good to see you!"

Although he had taken in many tribesmen along the way, most of them were mortals, while Ma You Liang might be heavily injured and also crippled, but he was still a Gu Master.

Ma tribe had been utterly defeated in this battle.

Before the battle, they had been a large tribe whose foundations were deep enough to charge to super tribe level. But after the battle, Ma tribe was completely reduced to a small tribe, falling down from the pinnacle of their power.

To the current Ma tribe, every Gu Master was a very precious strength and hope of the tribe!

"Lord young tribe leader, old tribe leader died in the battlefield." Ma You Liang cried bitterly as he told this grievous news to Ma Ying Jie.

Ma Ying Jie's body shook intensely, and despite having already made mental preparations, his heart was still filled with endless sadness and sorrow after hearing this news.

He gritted his teeth, his whole body seemingly having turned into an iron statue.

After a while of silence, he slowly wiped away his tears and spoke: "From today onwards, I am Ma tribe leader! Elder Ma You Liang, you need to pull yourself together. Our Ma tribe might have lost, but we are not exterminated. Back then, Ancestor Giant Sun set the rule that Huang Jin family's bloodline could not be exterminated. Ma tribe has already paid a disastrous price for the battle, now even Hei tribe cannot eradicate us. We will return to warm pond valley and climb up from this loss. I believe our Ma tribe's radiance won't disperse like this!"

Ma You Liang dazedly looked at the young tribe leader in front of him, and in his blurred vision, he seemed to be looking at Ma Shang Feng and Ma Zun's silhouettes. He stopped sobbing as hope rose up in his heart again.

He then answered with a very deep voice: "Lord tribe leader, I also believe so!"

-------------

Winner takes all.

While Ma Ying Jie was miserably fleeing, it was a scene of celebratory feasts in the many tents of Hei tribe's alliance army with plentiful food and people crowding around the warm bonfire.

"We have won, we were victorious!"

"Ma tribe's ambition was too big, they actually wanted to become a super tribe. This ambition was the cause of their destruction."

"Congratulations to Lord Hei Lou Lan for becoming the Lord of Imperial Court!"

"Esteemed Lord Wolf King, please allow me to propose a toast to you."

The main tent was also a scene of festivity. Besides the fine wine and food, there were also beautiful and passionate northern plains' women dancing gracefully to their heart's content.

The ones present in the main tent were the higher-ups of Hei tribe's alliance army and were all experts. The cultivations of these people were at least rank four, one could say they were the most radiant heroes of this generation of northern plains.

Hei Lou Lan was sitting on the main seat, and to the first seat on his left was Fang Yuan.

Before, because of Tai Bai Yun Sheng's arrival as well as successive joining of several rank five tribe elders, Fang Yuan's position had been pushed to the back.

But after the third battle with Ma tribe, Fang Yuan revealed his rank five peak stage cultivation and with his strength alone, battled the enemy's three enslavement masters, and beheaded Cheng Long, Wu Ye and other famous experts.

One could say Fang Yuan was at least seventy percent of the reason Hei tribe could win against Ma tribe decisively.

Everyone in Hei tribe was shocked at Wolf King's terrifying battle strength and that very night, they readjusted the seat rankings in the main tent.

No one opposed this.

Experts proposed toasts to Fang Yuan one after another, Fang Yuan did not refuse anyone, but only took a sip every time. This was completely not a demeanour of a grand northern plains' warrior, but right now, this instead formed an arrogant and aloof aura on Fang Yuan.

The main tent was filled with a joyful atmosphere.

The Gu Master who proposed the toast just before was Sole Blade General Pan Ping. He used his sole blade Gu and luckily managed to take Ma tribe leader Ma Shang Feng's head in the battle. Thus, his position was only inferior to Fang Yuan in the battle merit board now, being ranked at second.

Seeing Fang Yuan taking a sip in response to his toast, Pan Ping gratefully stepped to the side.

Northern plains natives admire warriors, a terrifying performance like Fang Yuan's was extremely rare even when considering all the Imperial Court contests.

Flying master and enslavement path master, two master level halos shone on his body. His enslavement path and strength path dual cultivation would give an extreme headache to all his enemies.

Seeing Pan Ping becoming satisfied and overwhelmed, and retreating in deference, the surrounding gazes showed respect, worship or fear. Fang Yuan calmly placed down the wine cup and sighed inwardly: "Unknowingly, I have already reached this stage."

Riding on the great wave known as the Imperial Court contest, Fang Yuan's individual battle strength rapidly inflated. Now, he was already at the summit of the mortal world.

He had reached the peak of the mortals.

Advancing further would be the realm of immortals!

In the battle before, he slaughtered famed experts, rampaging all around with no one being able to obstruct him; very few rank five peak stage Gu Masters could display such performance. Hei Lou Lan's light was completely seized by Fang Yuan.

Despite there being great flaws in cultivating both enslavement and strength path, despite four arm earth king killer move being newly created and not yet perfected, they were already enough as a cornerstone to allow Fang Yuan to stand proud in the mortal world.

In three kings blessed land, Fang Yuan used the blessed land's power to kill rank four and rank five Gu Master experts.

And now, he was able to do it with his own strength. Even if Tie clan's previous clan leader Tie Mu Bai resurrected, Fang Yuan had the confidence of killing him.

In a short period of time, Fang Yuan's battle strength had truly increased at a sharply flying speed. This accomplishment that others would find it almost impossible to achieve their whole life, was established on five hundred years of his former life's experience, Hu Immortal blessed land, painstaking efforts and strategies as a base.

'But it is still not enough, far from enough! What can being the peak of the mortal world be considered as? As long as one is not a Gu Immortal, they will simply be chess pieces. Not mentioning the goal of eternal life, just looking at my current goal, I have yet to save Dang Hun mountain.'

Fang Yuan's gaze turned solemn as the flames of ambition burned in his heart.

He glanced at Tai Bai Yun Sheng who was at the side.

To save Dang Hun mountain, he required Tai Bai Yun Sheng's Immortal Gu — Landscape As Before.

This was his most important target for this trip to northern plains. Even Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was secondary.

In his plan, if Dang Hun mountain could not be saved, then Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's inheritance could only barely fill his losses.

However, it was a very troublesome thing to take away other's Gu worms.

A Gu worm's survival could be decided on simply a thought from its master.

For example, Fang Yuan only needed a thought and even his Immortal Gu, Spring Autumn Cicada, would easily self-destruct.

Precisely because of this, when Gu Masters battled to death, they would often get next to nothing in terms of Gu worms from the corpse.

And Tai Bai Yun Sheng's situation was even more troublesome!

Immortal Gu Landscape As Before had yet to be born; it was an Immortal Gu created by Tai Bai Yun Sheng after he became a Gu Immortal, and by using river as before and mountain as before as the main materials.

Hence, there were two courses of actions Fang Yuan could take.

First was to capture Tai Bai Yun Sheng and use soul path Gu worms to soul search and plunder the recipe of Landscape As Before from his mind, then refine it by himself.

This plan was too risky.

First of all, Fang Yuan might not be able to capture Tai Bai Yun Sheng alive. Capturing alive and killing were two completely different concepts. Especially when Tai Bai Yun Sheng was very powerful and was a time path Gu Master; the failure of the plan would have huge consequences.

Secondly, even if Fang Yuan was able to capture Tai Bai Yun Sheng alive, does it mean he could get the river as before and mountain as before Gu? In case Tai Bai Yun Sheng made these two Gu self-destruct, all of Fang Yuan's efforts would go to waste.

Finally, it was still unknown if the current Tai Bai Yun Sheng had the Gu recipe for Landscape As Before in his mind.

The possibility of a mortal being able to come up with an Immortal Gu recipe was extremely small. Especially when Tai Bai Yun Sheng was not a refinement path master.

According to the vague rumors in Fang Yuan's previous life, when Tai Bai Yun Sheng became a Gu Immortal, heaven and earth reacted, Dao marks attracted each other and his inspiration exploded, making the two rank five Gu spontaneously merge together to form rank six Immortal Gu Landscape As Before.

If it really was so, then the Gu recipe for Landscape As Before simply did not exist and its refinement process could not be duplicated.

The first course of action could not be adopted, then what about the second?

In truth, it was not any better than the first!

After Tai Bai Yun Sheng entered Imperial Court blessed land, he would advance to Gu Immortal realm. The second plan was to wait for him to become a Gu Immortal and possess the Immortal Gu, then deal with him!

The meaning of this was that Fang Yuan, as a mortal, would be entrapping a Gu Immortal!

Chapter 545: Ma Hong Yun

How big was the possibility of a mortal successfully plotting against a Gu Immortal?

Fang Yuan might be a rank five peak stage Gu Master, but it would be almost impossible for him as well to cross the boundaries of immortal and mortal.

Fang Yuan was a Gu Immortal in his past life, there might be no mortal that had as deep of an understanding of this as him.

Fortunately, Fang Yuan's plan was not just himself as a mortal going against a Gu Immortal. He would borrow the strength of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the bright guidance from his previous life's rich experience and also the precious information from Lang Ya land spirit; all these allowed his plan to have a higher chance of success. With this, he had a twenty percent chance of seizing Immortal Gu Landscape As Before.

Twenty percent probability was already the highest among the three ways to save Dang Hun mountain.

Only an Immortal Gu could contend against Immortal Gu Gruel Mud.

Based on his wide vision and experience from his five hundred years of experience, Fang Yuan knew of only three Immortal Gu that could save Dang Hun mountain.

First was the rank six earth path turn rock Gu, this Gu was with Western Desert's rank six Gu Immortal Sun Cu.

Second was similarly an earth path rank six Immortal Gu Rebuilding Mount Dongshan, which was in Eastern Sea's Hai Shi blessed land.

Third was time path rank six Immortal Gu Landscape As Before. This Gu had not yet been created and was not a naturally formed Gu. Its master Tai Bai Yun Sheng was only a rank five Gu Master currently.

To seize turn rock Gu, Fang Yuan would have to deal with Gu Immortal Sun Cu who had been a Gu Immortal for over a dozen years.

And the situation would be even more bad if he wanted to scheme against Rebuilding Mount Dongshan; Fang Yuan would be placing himself under the radar of Gu Immortals, and would he be able to exchange for the Immortal Gu as a mortal? This was nothing more than a kid carrying gold and strolling around the black market.

Thus, the third plan of Immortal Gu Landscape As Before had the lowest risk and the highest probability of success.

Even if Tai Bai Yun Sheng would advance into a Gu Immortal, he would only be a greenhorn and would not be familiar with the qualitative change of strength.

Compared to the veteran Sun Cu and that group of Gu Immortals in the Hai Shi blessed land, this opponent was much more easy to deal with.

　　...

Northern Plains, December.

The blizzard was gradually becoming bigger and appeared more frequently. Even if there was no blizzard, the pure white snow had covered the whole northern plains, and even the blistering hot sunlight became powerless.

The time of the ten year blizzard was already approaching closer.

Tian Chuan, warm pond valley.

"Tribe leader, this is the spirit spring C." Ma You Liang worriedly pointed at the dried spirit spring and introduced it to Ma Ying Jie.

Ma Ying Jie's brows furrowed deeply.

This spirit spring C was one of the only three remaining spirit springs of warm pond valley.

Now that it was dried up, only spirit springs A and B were left to support Ma tribe. This was disastrous news to Ma tribe.

The spirit springs in northern plains were different from the spirit springs in other regions.

Northern springs had little spring water and narrow spring opening, so they burst out fiercely and had poor foundation, so they lasted the shortest time.

Eastern springs were plentiful in numbers, southern springs gurgled, northern springs were intense and western springs were pure.

A mid-sized clan could last for over ten years in southern border, using one spirit spring. As long as they did not use up the spirit spring excessively, they could continue to use the thin and continuous flow of the spirit spring.

But it was different in northern plains.

Spirit springs formed quickly in northern plains and quickly finished as well. Add in the intense warfares in northern plains, a mid-sized tribe would require at least three or four spirit springs to sustain themselves.

Ma Ying Jie became Ma tribe's new tribe leader after he returned to the tribe. Ma tribe had lost at their attempt to charge into super tribe level and was now reduced to a small tribe, causing the large warm pond valley to appear spacious and empty.

Ma tribe had rations and water sources, moreover had made ample preparations.

But a spirit spring was a commodity that was an essential and important resource to a Gu Master's cultivation. Once the blizzard arrives, places like warm pond valley would become the final place of refuge.

Not only beast groups, other Gu Masters would also come to stay.

As the owner of the place, Ma tribe not only had to resist against the blizzard but had to negotiate with these people as well.

The primeval stones from the spirit spring were the backbone in supporting a Gu Master's battles. Now, out of the three backbones of Ma tribe, one was broken. The weak Ma tribe that was left with thirty percent of their foundations suddenly had ten percent less because of the drying spirit spring C.

However, Ma Ying Jie had no countermeasures to deal with such a problem.

If he had a 'river as before' Gu, he could immediately restore spirit spring C to its original condition, resolving this problem, but he did not have it.

"Lord tribe leader, are spirit springs really so important?" Fei Cai asked on the way back.

After he returned to the tribe, as a benefactor who saved Ma Ying Jie, he was immediately liberated from his slave status and was now a free person.

At the same time, he was still Ma Ying Jie's personal attendant.

Ma Ying Jie worriedly nodded: "A spirit spring's drying up has an extremely huge influence towards Gu Masters. And Gu Masters are the pillars of a tribe. Our Ma tribe not only needs Gu Masters as an important strength to resist all kinds of calamities during the blizzard disaster, but also to fight for new resources to develop the tribe after the disaster..."

Fei Cai exclaimed then asked while walking: "Then, can't we find new spirit springs? Our warm pond valley is so large, who is to say that there are only these three spirit springs."

Fei Cai's words were filled with his optimistic spirit.

Ma Ying Jie gave a bitter laugh: "Northern plains' spirit springs can indeed form in a short time, there might be a fourth spirit spring in warm pond valley, but the probability is close to zero. The thing is every ten years as the blizzard approaches, spirit springs in all regions of northern plains will continue to become dry and dead. After the blizzard disperses, new spirit springs will gush out in large numbers. At that time, all the regions of northern plains will have plentiful water vegetation and you might even find one spirit spring every hundred li. That is the best time for every tribe and every beast group to grow."

"It was like that..." Fei Cai only then realized he had lived for this long and was still ignorant, and was not familiar to such situations.

"Ahh!" Suddenly, he screamed as he fell down to the side.

They were walking a path beside the cliff, fortunately it was a gentle slope and not a precipice. Fei Cai had lost his footing and rolled down from the slope, screaming as he fell.

"This guy..." Ma Ying Jie was amused at the series of hilarious screams from Fei Cai, his tightly knitted brows slightly relaxed.

"You idiot, you can't even walk now? Climb up quickly... hmm?!" Ma Ying Jie suddenly stopped, his eyes opened wide as he looked incredulously at a brand new spirit spring gushing out from the slope.

This spirit spring's mouth had been covered by a rock.

But this stone was pushed by the rolling Fei Cai, letting the spirit spring that was covered reveal itself.

This was clearly a recently formed spirit spring, otherwise Ma tribe would not have missed it during their search before the battle.

The volume of the spirit spring was enormous and in a short few moments of time, over a hundred primeval stones gushed with the spring water and fell on the surrounding ground.

"This...This is actually a new spirit spring and one that directly surpasses the volume of spirit spring A!" Ma Ying Jie was so happy that even his eyes started reddening, "Is this the so-called joy after extreme sorrow? This is definitely the blessing of our ancestors in Longevity Heaven!"

"Tribe..tribe leader... I have returned!" At this time, Fei Cai came back while limping a little, and as he saw the new spring, his eyes similarly opened wide, "Strange, how could there suddenly be a spring here?"

Ma Ying Jie laughed heartily: "Fei Cai, you are the lucky star that heaven sent to me. From today onwards, you should change your name. Fei Cai sounds similar to trash, how could I Ma Ying Jie have trash beside me? From now, you shall be called Hong Yun, Fei Hong Yun! It indicates luck shining on our Ma tribe, joy after extreme sorrow!"

However, Ma Ying Jie was not happy for long, as seven days later, Hei tribe army arrived and surrounded warm pond valley.

The very night the Hei tribe army garrisoned nearby, the three spirit springs of warm pond valley simultaneous turned black, completely polluted.

A letter to surrender soon reached Ma Ying Jie's land.

Ma Ying Jie had not expected Hei Lou Lan to not let him go even after clearly achieving the final victory!

The spirit springs that were contaminated by the use of Gu worms could no longer produce primeval stones and were all useless. Although Ma tribe still had stocks of primeval stones, they had already lost the possibility of continuing to stay in warm pond valley.

"I had not thought Hei Lou Lan would be so hell-bent on attacking! He has requested our Ma tribe to surrender in the letter, which does not violate the rules set by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable back then! Damn it, he is truly hateful!" Ma Ying Jie clenched his fists, his heart filled with anger, hatred, helplessness and powerlessness.

"Hei Lou Lan who is nicknamed Black Tyrant, has always been brutal and violent. It seems the battle before created a fear in him towards Ma tribe. But because of Ancestor Giant Sun's rules, he wants to put Ma tribe under his sight and continue to oppress us." Ma You Liang was sitting stiffly on his chair and analyzed this with a heavy voice.

After pausing for a while, he continued: "Actually, this is also good, we can surrender to Hei Lou Lan which would mean we can enter Imperial Court blessed land as well."

Ma Ying Jie shook his head: "This is where Hei Lou Lan's sinister intent lies in. It is true Ma tribe will be able to stay in Imperial Court, but what about others? Let me ask you, how many tribesmen do we have left with surname Ma?"

Ma You Liang paled as he answered: "Only over one hundred and thirty."

"Precisely so." Ma Ying Jie nodded with a heavy expression, "To grow our tribe, we would need to take in outsiders and also wantonly connect with marriage and have large numbers of offspring. But as long as Hei Lou Lan sent a command to forbid our Ma tribe from taking in outsiders and even only allowing us to have inter-tribe marriage, then how long would it take for our Ma tribe to grow?"

Ma You Liang's face turned even paler.

He realized the seriousness of this problem.

Politics was dirty, and not allowing them to marry outsiders could be easily done. Hei Lou Lan would only need to use the reason of protecting the purity of Huang Jin family's bloodline and he would be able to justly suppress Ma tribe's development.

"Then what should we do?" Ma You Liang lost his composure.

Ma Ying Jie was silent for a while before resolutely saying: "We will bestow surname Ma to the outsiders and take them as our own tribesmen!"

"Lord tribe leader, if we do this, our Ma tribe's Huang Jin bloodline will really be..." Ma You Liang spoke hesitantly.

"We will have preventive measures. Huang Jin bloodline is our Ma tribe's pride, we can never let it be contaminated. If the situation takes a turn for the better, we can denounce these people and strip away their Ma surname."

Ma You Liang only then felt at ease and nodded, approving this plan.

Chapter 546: The way forward for the insignificant people

Moving carriages and neighing horses.

The huge group of nearly a million advanced towards the central Imperial Court region of northern plains.

The blizzard outside was blowing intensely, causing the big stomach horse to lower its head helplessly.

The white snow on the ground was knee-deep, as everyone moved with extremely difficult steps..

One by one, the blue farm slug Gu moved forward. Their stomachs were stuffed with all sorts of resources, turning their original size of three elephants into a mound-like hill.

Carriages after carriages followed behind the blue farm slug Gu. In order to shield these mortals from the approaching blizzard, they were covered in frost.

To prevent the slug Gu from freezing to death, three Gu Masters would be in charge of one slug Gu, removing the frost on them while using fire path Gu worms to give them warmth, maintaining their temperature.

The army pressed forward towards the Imperial Court. As the blizzard became larger, the army's speed became slower.

Large number of mortal slaves fell during the journey, and never got up again.

Hei Lou Lan could order Gu Masters to save them, but he did not do so.

Even though the Imperial Court blessed land was huge and could accommodate five million people, in Hei Lou Lan's opinion, the resources within the blessed land were his, why would he distribute them to these lowly slaves?

Every extra person meant he had to lose another bit of benefit.

Using the blizzard to sacrifice large numbers of useless mortals, this was a hidden rule among all past lords of the Imperial Court.

Mortal lives were cheap. They were like grass, once the blizzard was over, they would rapidly grow again, increasing in numbers and using up northern plains' scarce resources like leeches, awaiting the next ten year blizzard.

As the blizzard became stronger, the people move against the force of the wind.

Fang Yuan was inside the large lizard house Gu, he could hear the wind outside the windows.

Within the large lizard house Gu, it was warm as spring. Using it to move in such an environment had about five to six times the primeval essence expenditure as before.

But to Fang Yuan, just his rank five peak stage ninety percent aperture could easily sustain this expenditure with no problem.

Moreover, his second aperture had also advanced to rank five upper stage recently.

Fang Yuan came before the window, looking outside the tightly sealed glass window, towards the left.

Ma tribe's members were there.

After Ma Ying Jie took the role of tribe leader, Ma Hong Yun appeared, even Zhao Lian Yun was beside him.

Fang Yuan had already confirmed this secretly, and even instructed Ge tribe to pay special attention to Ma Hong Yun and Zhao Lian Yun.

In his memory, Ma Hong Yun obtained an inheritance of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. In Fang Yuan's following plans, he was a very useful pawn piece. As for Zhao Lian Yun, she was still just a child, she posed no threat. At the same time, she was very close to Ma Hong Yun, Fang Yuan wanted to observe them further.

"In my previous life, Ma Hong Yun appeared. Now, despite my influence, Ma Hong Yun still appeared. Then in the future, will he and Zhao Lian Yun still reach that level of achievement just like in the previous life?"

After rebirth, Fang Yuan had been deeply interested towards the topic of changing history, a desire to know growing deep inside his heart.

The flow of history had inertia, as well as changes.

With his personal experience, the butterfly effect theorized on Earth was slightly off.

Five hundred years in his past life, Ma Hong Yun was given a surname and allowed to cultivate as a Gu Master. That was because he obtained a relic Gu and gave it to Ma Ying Jie.

Right now, it was because of Hei Lou Lan's pressure, that caused Ma Ying Jie to have no choice but make this decision. This decision, gave birth to a new Ma Hong Yun.

The process was different, but the result was the same.

The event that unfolded before him made Fang Yuan ponder, as he uncontrollably thought of one word — fate!

Fate, this was a word much more mysterious and ethereal than space or time.

Legend says that there was a luck path among Gu Master paths, but until today, no one could confirm it.

However, there were many important characters that were connected to fate.

In \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, it clearly indicated the existence of fate Gu.

The second generation Immortal Venerable of the Heavenly Court, the creator of wisdom path, controlled this Gu, thus being able to plot against three future Demon Venerables.

In three kings blessed land, Fang Yuan was informed by the land spirit — Red Lotus Demon Venerable was a great hero, breaking the restriction of fate, allowing all life in this world to regain control of their own fate.

In fact, Fang Yuan had vaguely heard such a rumor: Giant Sun Immortal Venerable controlled a luck path Gu worm, thus he had extremely good fortune and ease in his cultivation journey, avoiding disasters and gaining great blessings.

"In this world, is there really a thread of fate that connects all living beings together?" Fang Yuan went into deep thought.

In the five hundred years of his previous life, although he became a Gu Immortal, he only managed to unravel a tiny portion of this world's mystery and secrets.

Be it his previous life, or this life, the more he progressed, the stronger he got, the more he felt his own ignorance and insignificance.

The more insignificant and ignorant he felt, the more interest he had in moving forward, he wanted to progress further!

"Compared to this world, I am merely an ant..." Fang Yuan's blood was filled with pride and humility, obstinance and understanding.

Collecting all his scattered thoughts, Fang Yuan concentrated his attention on the matter ahead.

"Imperial Court blessed land rejects Gu Immortals, I am already rank five peak stage, this is likely the first and the last time I am entering the Imperial Court, to physically come into contact with Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"But this time, Hei Lou Lan purposely went over to warm pond valley to force Ma tribe to surrender, this was a strange move." Fang Yuan's gaze became solemn.

Ma tribe had already lost terribly, and they had the Huang Jin bloodline, why would Hei Lou Lan do this?

This was understandable in his previous life.

Back then, Ma tribe was not completely helpless, they had strong defense and was a turtle shell that was hard to take down. Hei Lou Lan had no choice but to force them to surrender.

Now that Ma tribe was declining, Hei Lou Lan still moved his army and laboriously forced Ma tribe to surrender, he spent so much effort to suppress Ma tribe, did he have deep enmity with Ma tribe personally?

Fang Yuan shook his head.

There were no evidence that could support this thought.

"Nevermind, maybe Hei Lou Lan was just spurred on and wanted to raise his merits. This is only a small detail, my own strength is always the most important thing."

Thinking so, his mind entered his aperture.

The injuries from using the killer move four arm earth king had already recovered.

As for the killer move, he had several adjustments.

He changed earth overlord Gu to wind overlord Gu. As for the other supplementary Gu worms, they were adjusted accordingly.

This way, he would not need to step on the ground, and would fight best in the wind. The stronger the wind, the more battle strength he can display, and the smaller the drawbacks he would face after using the killer move.

But Fang Yuan was not satisfied.

This was only a temporary compromise, the weakness of this killer move had not been reduced.

If he fought in an environment without wind, the consequences of using the killer move would not be any better as before.

For Gu Masters, there were way too many methods to restrict the wind.

Once his weakness was exposed publicly, his killer move would no longer have any threat to his enemies, they would have no fear towards it.

"Actually, no matter how good my modifications were, I would not be satisfied. My true aim is to eliminate the weakness of my strength-enslavement dual cultivation. The killer move four arm earth king is merely a starting point."

But this result could not escape from the limits of transformation path.

What Fang Yuan wanted was to completely and utterly modify his body, he did not want to achieve such temporary transformation.

Nevertheless, reaching this point had already expended Fang Yuan's five hundred years of knowledge accumulation.

After all, Fang Yuan was a blood path Gu Immortal back then, his attainment in strength and enslavement paths were merely subsidiaries, he merely touched the tip of the iceberg.

If possible, Fang Yuan wanted to quickly become a blood path Gu Immortal. But it was different now after rebirth. His vital Gu was not a blood path Gu.

A crucial condition for becoming a Gu Immortal was the vital Gu.

Originally, after Fang Yuan got the second aperture Gu, he would have a second chance. But that crucial blood path vital Gu was still buried in the inheritance, it had not appeared yet.

Fang Yuan could not wait in vain, the situation was forcing him, he could only choose to strengthen himself now, to deal with the challenges ahead, and all the enemies lurking around him.

Staying alive, that was the most important thing!

Fang Yuan had also realized that his foundation in strength and enslavement paths were lacking. His involvement in a wide range of paths in his previous life allowed him to easily control Gu worms of many paths, while being skilled in the combination of different Gu worms. Among them, his attainment in enslavement path was the highest.

But to resolve the issue of strength-enslavement dual cultivation, an age old question, he would need to move ahead of history and undergo creative and daring experiments, his foundation was lacking in this aspect.

Even though Fang Yuan had clues to Luo Po valley now, maybe after he obtains Luo Po valley, he would be able to convert to the glorious soul path.

But Fang Yuan never liked placing his hopes on certain possibilities in the future.

Even if he changes to soul path in the future, his hard work in enslavement and strength would be a precious resource and would greatly benefit his future cultivation.

Knowing his own inaptitude, Fang Yuan had been reading intensely these few days.

He used his huge pool of battle merits to exchange for dragon horse spirit, three hearts combination soul, all sorts of killer moves, as well as dozens of small strength path inheritances. He also got the recorded journal of four enslavement masters, among them, rat epidemic, thunder explosion. leopard rush, and horse barrage, these four killer moves were invaluable.

Fang Yuan's foundation had always been thick, these days he had been reading laboriously, his understanding and knowledge in strength and enslavement path surged greatly by several times compared to before.

Different from his previous life where he studied these paths as a side path, he had personally experienced these paths this time, and together with his theories, he gained countless inspirations.

But these inspirations could not resolve his problem now.

"Actually, looking at information about the transformation of the body, the first records were in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>. When Ren Zu fell into a certain-death situation, in order to save her own father, Desolate Ancient Moon came to Cheng Bai mountain and killed the rockman..."

Fang Yuan had a burst of inspiration as he flipped \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> beside him.

This was the first classic of the Gu Master world, countless mysteries were hidden within it. Even existences like Gu Immortal kept a copy of it with them at all times, occasionally flipping and learning from it.

Chapter 547: Search for Success

Fang Yuan flipped \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, and this was recorded within —

When Ren Zu was in a certain-death situation, after he fell into Luo Po valley and had no way to get out.

Desolate Ancient Moon, in order to save her father, climbed up Cheng Bai mountain and tried to get to the top, in order to get that one and only success Gu.

As long as she made a wish to success Gu, Desolate Ancient Moon would be able to save Ren Zu.

But when Desolate Ancient Moon got to the foot of the mountain, she was obstructed by the rockman.

It turns out that when Ren Zu's second daughter arrived at Cheng Bai mountain, she ruined love Gu's wonderful dream.

Out of anger, love Gu awakened the rockman in order to obstruct Desolate Ancient Moon.

After Desolate Ancient Moon killed the rockman, and got to the mountain waist.

Love Gu had yet to leave, it appeared before Desolate Ancient Moon and said: "Oh human, you interrupted my sweet dream, yet you still desire to take away success Gu. Now I will topple the entire Cheng Bai mountain, you can have fun finding that one and only success Gu out of billions of rocks. Hahaha."

Saying so, love Gu crashed towards Cheng Bai mountain.

Cheng Bai mountain was not an ordinary mountain, it was a mound entirely made up of stacked rocks.

After love Gu crashed into it, the entire mountain crumbled.

Love Gu left smugly, leaving behind Desolate Ancient Moon who looked at this huge pile of rocks in a daze.

How was she going to find that one and only success Gu among this chaotic pile of rocks?

Desolate Ancient Moon was troubled, without a choice, she had to return to cognition Gu to seek advice.

After cognition Gu heard Desolate Ancient Moon's description, it sighed: "Love Gu had always been demanding and unreasonable, even if it was me, or my child wisdom Gu, we would not want to confront it."

"Right now, Cheng Bai mountain had collapsed, you can only look at these rocks one by one, to find the real success Gu from among them. There are no other ways."

Cognition Gu said again: "But you have to be careful, there are two Gu on Cheng Bai mountain. One is success Gu, at the peak of the mountain. The other is failure Gu, at the bottom of the mountain. Failure is the mother of success, but it also has many other children. Those rocks are success Gu's siblings. When you pick those rocks, many unthinkably bad situations will occur. I will tell you a secret here, as long as you continue to affirm the belief of 'me' in your heart, these disastrous situations will gradually disappear."

Desolate Ancient Moon heard this and her heart sank, she asked again: "Then how do I differentiate the rocks in my hand? What do success Gu and failure Gu look like?"

Cognition Gu sighed: "They look almost the same, but it is easy to differentiate them. Just hold them in your hands, you will learn about their identities."

"In your search for success Gu, that failure Gu will be your biggest threat. You cannot hold on to the failure Gu, otherwise, you will be completely lost and your life would be in danger."

Desolate Ancient Moon heard this and nodded, expressing her gratitude.

Cognition instructed her again before leaving: "Do not say that I taught you that. If love Gu comes to find me, I'd be in trouble. In the face of fanatic and toyful love, wisdom and cognition can only run away."

"Don't worry, I won't expose you." Desolate Ancient Moon agreed, returning to Cheng Bai mountain.

Seeing the huge pile of rocks, her heart was gloomy.

Success was not easily obtainable, to obtain success, she would need to bend down and search while taking great risks.

Desolate Ancient Moon breathed in deeply, picking up the first rock.

This rock was ordinary, but when Desolate Ancient Moon held it in her hand, it shook slightly.

A light wound appeared on Desolate Ancient Moon's hand.

This was not success Gu, but one of success' siblings, one of the children of failure Gu.

Desolate Ancient Moon's heart was shocked, she touched the wound on her hand as she recalled what cognition Gu said —"When you pick those rocks, many unthinkably bad situations will occur. You have to affirm the belief of 'me' in your heart."

"So this is the terrible situation." Desolate Ancient Moon understood.

She chanted in her heart: "Me, me, me, me..."

As she chanted, the wound on her hand miraculously healed! Only a light scar was left.

She tossed the first rock away, and picked up the second rock.

When she held this rock in her hand, Desolate Ancient Moon's heart jumped, as an intense feeling of fear assaulted her.

Desolate Ancient Moon was shivering in fear, she almost ran away to escape, away from this place.

But she held on, and chanted 'me'.

After a long time, she slowly recovered as the fear in her heart was gone by half, finally picking up the third rock.

This rock made her dejected. She could not help but think: "I want to find that one and only success Gu among these billions of rocks, how difficult is that, how long would it take me?"

She could barely move anymore, she felt that the future was shrouded in darkness, it was too difficult to find success Gu.

She almost wanted to give up, but she thought about her father who was trapped in life and death door.

"If I give up, who will save father?" Desolate Ancient Moon shuddered: "Oh no, I forgot to chant 'me'."

Desolate Ancient Moon chanted again, getting rid of the despair in her heart, bending down to pick up another rock.

Once she held the fourth rock in her hand, Desolate Ancient Moon was shocked to find out that her nose had changed, it turned into a pig's nose.

She chanted 'me' once again, allowing her nose to recover.

Spending a lot of time, she exerted all her effort to get rid of the pig nose. But her nose was still slightly deformed compared to before.

Like this, Desolate Ancient Moon continued to pick up rocks, hoping to find that success Gu.

But days passed, and all she found was failure Gu's children.

Among these rocks, some made her injured, some made her dejected, despair, or fear, while some made her grow a pig head, rat's tail, etc.

Despite Desolate Ancient Moon chanting 'me' continuously, some of the scars still remained on her. As they accumulated, these scars turned her into a monster.

She grew six heads, three arms, five tails, and looked like a centaur. She had sixteen legs, and some of her legs had soft fur, some had snake-like scales, some had sharp claws, some had tough hooves.

In the search for success, people often transform and become completely different.

But Desolate Ancient Moon also became much stronger because of this.

After going through so much, she had become several hundred times as strong as before. These rocks could not longer trouble her.

"Success, oh success, where in the world are you?" Her seven mouths opened together. Some were screaming, some were shouting, some were whispering while others were growling.

The more she failed, the more she desired success in her heart.

After her great effort, the number of unpicked rocks became fewer and fewer.

Eventually, when there were only two rocks left, Desolate Ancient Moon was stuck between two difficult choices.

Undeniably, among these two rocks, one was success Gu, while the other was failure Gu.

If she obtains success Gu, that would be the best. But if she picked failure Gu, then Desolate Ancient Moon would become completely lost, she would be in danger of dying.

Even if Desolate Ancient Moon became a monster, becoming so much stronger.

One step to heaven, one step to hell, what should she choose? Desolate Ancient Moon could not help but become hesitant.

"If I do not dare to take the next step for fear of failure, then I will never succeed! I am already so strong, success is a step away from me, even if I take failure Gu, as long as I chant 'me', I should be able to endure it right?" Eventually, she mustered her courage and stretched out her palm, picking one of the rocks.

Unfortunately, she picked failure Gu.

An unforseen feeling of lost, self-doubt assaulted her.

"Me, me, me..."

Desolate Ancient Moon continued to chant 'me, but her voice became softer, as her seven mouths stopped moving eventually, her expression turning into a daze.

She had fallen into endless perplexity, she had completely lost herself.

The biggest tragedy for a human, is to lose your sense of self.

　　...

"Sigh..." After reading this, Fang Yuan sighed as he closed the book.

At once, his thoughts were drifting as he showed a very complicated expression.

It was still snowing outside the window, snowflakes were floating in the air.

As the ten year disaster approaches, the blizzard did not show signs of weakening, instead it was growing.

Northern Plains, end of December.

When Hei Lou Lan led the army and and arrived at the last minute, at Imperial Court blessed land's entrance, the alliance had about half its members left.

A large number of mortals died on the way there.

In fact, many Gu Masters died from the attacks of beast groups.

The item to open the Imperial Court blessed land was on Hei Lou Lan.

When he stood up, a mild golden light shone in the air.

Immediately after, the golden light intensified, forming a light ring.

The light ring expanded, turning into a grand city gate.

On the gate, there were exquisite silvery flower patterns. Many fist-sized copper buttons were plastered on the gate.

Boom...

There was like an invisible hand behind the door, pulling the heavy door open.

Immediately, the thick smell of sandalwood spread.

The snow in the air stopped moving. Under the influence of a mysterious power, the snow in the air gathered like bees, in an instant, a solid and magnificent ice ladder was created.

At the top of the ladder, it was connected to the floating Imperial Court gate. It extended all the way to the ground.

"Imperial Court blessed land!" Hei Lou Lan could not conceal his excitement, he took three steps as one step as he ascended the ice ladder, becoming the first person to enter the Imperial Court.

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building..." Fang Yuan was the second person, his gaze became solemn as he took calm strides in.

After that, Tai Bai Yun Sheng, Hao Ji Liu and other high level experts went in.

About an hour later, the entire Hei tribe army had entered Imperial Court blessed land. The ice ladder broke apart, as the red city gate closed itself.

The light ring shrunk into one dot, and vanished.

"They have all entered." The Gu Immortals observed in secret retracted their helpless and nostalgic gazes.

Chapter 548: Inheritance hidden in Eerie Fire Python’s den

When Fang Yuan opened his eyes, the scene before him had completely transformed.

The sky was light gold in color, the land was like spring, with green agricultural terraces, there were gentle streams flowing, and low-lying mounds, one could see far and wide in this boundless plains.

This was a serene and peaceful world, forming a great contrast to the blizzard outside.

This was northern plains' greatest utopia — Imperial Court blessed land, it opens every ten years, as a reward to the lord of northern plains.

Fang Yuan looked around and found that he was alone.

Although everyone entered from the same gate, after they stepped through the gate, they were separated and randomly transported to any area of the blessed land.

This was as per usual, Fang Yuan was not shocked. According to the earlier agreement, next he had to travel towards the center of the blessed land, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's former place of residence was there — Northern Plains Sacred Palace!

"I am finally in here." Fang Yuan regulated his breathing, the Imperial Court contest was only a prelude, what was truly important was the following events.

He tried activating eagle rise Gu, his crystal purple primeval essence moved according to his will, entering the eagle rise Gu.

Swoosh!

With a light sound, followed by intense pain, two broad and huge pitch-black eagle wings grew on his back.

Within Imperial Court blessed land, the use of mortal Gu was not restricted. As for Immortal Gu, they could not be restrained in any blessed land.

The strong eagle wings flapped lightly and brought Fang Yuan into the air.

Flying in the air, feeling the light wind brushing past his face, he could smell the unique scent of nature that permeated the entire blessed land.

Compared to the outside world, this place was extremely peaceful, it was like heaven.

Fang Yuan was in no hurry, he flew slowly as he enjoyed the scenery around him.

Imperial Court blessed land's landscape was quite similar to northern plains. At one glance, it was a huge plain, there were mounds and slopes with beautiful and elegant lines, it was like a stream of jade green flowing smoothly without obstacles.

But different from northern plains, every eight li, there would be a tower on the ground.

These towers made Fang Yuan think of totem pillars. Each one was about twenty-five meters tall, they were tall and straight, with a gold and silver surface, with lots of precious gems adorning it, beautiful and exquisite.

In the tower, there were countless barriers, like a beehive. Inside, were many Gu worms.

When the worm groups in the blessed land give birth to Gu, these Gu worms would detach themselves from the group and live in these towers.

The towers were built by Giant Sun, no matter what type of Gu worm it was, they would be able to find their food inside the towers.

Every tower had tens of thousands of Gu worms. These Gu consists of many species, there were large numbers of common Gu and few rare Gu.

Undeniably, each of these towers were a huge fortune, even Fang Yuan can feel his attraction to them. He could even see a group of about a thousand starlight firefly Gu in one of the towers.

"Unfortunately, I cannot take these Gu as I wish. When the Imperial Court contest first started, some daring Gu Masters tried to steal or even attack the towers, to take the wild Gu inside. In the end, they were like candles, their entire body melted until their white bone skeleton was left, smashed into a pile." Fang Yuan's gaze concentrated.

This was the heavenly power of the blessed land, the power of heaven and earth.

No mortals could resist it.

Even Gu Immortals would be left in a pathetic state when competing against it.

After enough lessons taught, by now, no Gu Master had the intention to attack the towers.

"If we chase the origin, the Gu Immortal who created Imperial Court blessed land was a space path Gu Immortal whose name can no longer be found. Because of this, this blessed land is huge, far larger than other blessed lands. Before Giant Sun Immortal Venerable became an immortal, he inherited this place luckily and became the blessed land's new owner. After Giant Sun became an Immortal Venerable, and obtained unparalleled power, he displayed great methods and set up the tradition of the Imperial Court contest, allowing this ancient blessed land to continue existing until now.

Fang Yuan flew as he recalled.

The methods of an Immortal Venerable were beyond his understanding. Who knows how Giant Sun Immortal Venerable managed to do it, but the result was, under his manipulation, Imperial Court blessed land no longer suffered from heavenly tribulations or earthly calamities.

Hiss hiss hiss...

After flying for an hour, past numerous towers, Fang Yuan was provoked by a giant python on a small valley.

This bright red giant python was at least a hundred meters long, its body was as thick as a tower.

There was a sharp horn on its head, a pair of blood eyes stared at Fang Yuan fixatedly, hissing with its tongue continuously.

Its tongue was a creepy purple color, and there were eerie blue flames on it.

"Eh? It's a rarely seen eerie fire dragon python." Fang Yuan was slightly shocked.

At this moment, the giant python opened its mouth, and shot out a carriage-sized blue purple flame.

The flame approached quickly, as the temperature in the air rose sharply, from a few hundred steps away, Fang Yuan's hair and eyebrows were showing signs of drying up. It showed the terrifying temperature of the blue purple flame!

Fang Yuan's eyebrows rose as he flapped his eagle wings, going to a higher altitude and avoiding the flame easily.

Killer move — Four Arm Wind King!

He activated more than ten Gu worms at once, his crystal purple was expending rapidly, meanwhile two bronze arms grew out of his body.

Thereafter, he flew down like a comet, straight towards the python.

Bam!

He crashed fiercely into the eerie fire dragon python, engaging in fierce combat with it.

At once, smoke rose as shockwaves were sent out, flames shot out as the valley shook.

Eerie fire dragon python was a mutated beast king, mutated beasts has rank four battle strength, while their king had strength equivalent to a rank five Gu Master. But Fang Yuan was rank five peak stage long ago, and after using his killer move, his battle strength was even higher.

If the eerie fire dragon python laid low and hid itself, Fang Yuan might not have noticed it while being on the move. But since it provoked him on purpose, Fang Yuan felt the urge to hunt and improve his killer move by using it as a training dummy.

After half an hour, the battle was over.

Fang Yuan's body was charred black, he stood in the completely destroyed and ruined valley.

The eerie fire dragon python's huge body was half covered in broken mountain rocks.

Fang Yuan coughed a few times, throwing up some blood.

The improved killer move had much less severe aftermath than before. A part of the reason was that the eerie fire dragon python did not have wisdom like humans, it could not find out Fang Yuan's weakness amidst battle.

If the wind was restricted, Fang Yuan would be in a much worse state.

This battle was not easy.

Imperial Court blessed land was a great environment, there were many Gu worms, thus there was a larger number of fire path wild Gu worms on the eerie fire dragon python. Among them, there were several valuable ones.

Fang Yuan's killer move was strong, but it did not have much defense against fire path.

If he did not need to dodge the flames, the thirty minute battle would be faster by at least a third.

Fang Yuan started collecting his loot.

This mutated beast king's body was full of value. For example, the python blood was a top ingredient in feeding blood path Gu worms. The python skin, tendons etc, would cause a huge commotion if sold in the mortal market.

Especially the eerie fire snake gall, it was extremely valuable, it could even be sold in treasure yellow heaven.

Fang Yuan organised his gains, in order to save time, he only kept the valuable items in his Gu.

"Eerie fire dragon python, they live in caves as a family. If there are any young dragon pythons, I can capture them and place them inside Hu Immortal blessed land to breed. It would be a good investment for the future." Fang Yuan thought about this and searched around.

Very soon, he made a discovery.

"Eh? There's a Gu Master inheritance here." Fang Yuan did not find a baby dragon python, but found a bright red rock, like that of a fire lotus.

With his expertise, he quickly understood that this was a Gu Master's work.

When he got close to the huge rock, this fire lotus-like rock opened up in layers, like a blossoming lotus.

The fire lotus rock opened completely, showing the Gu worms inside as well as a stele.

The stele was one with the huge rock, there were northern plains words on it.

Fang Yuan read it thoroughly and understood its existence.

The fire path Gu Master who left behind his inheritance was called Huo Zheng Jun, he was a righteous rank four fire path Gu Master. He entered this valley by accident, and was attacked by the eerie fire dragon python. Before dying from his injuries, he left behind his Gu worms helplessly and made the inheritance.

In the future, if a fated individual comes here, them this set of Gu worms would be his.

Huo Zheng Jun left behind seven Gu worms. But after these years, four died, and only three remained.

Among the three Gu worms, only one attracted Fang Yuan, it was the rank four fire pupil Gu.

When a Gu Master uses fire pupil Gu, fire would burn at anywhere they looked at, burning their opponents. Such a convenient attacking method often caught people off guard.

But it had its weaknesses.

If it was used for a long time, the Gu Master's eyes would be damaged. They would need to use good healing Gu as well as complementing Gu worms to weaken this side effect.

This fire pupil Gu was Huo Zheng Jun's core Gu worm.

Aside from the Gu worms he left behind, there were Gu recipes that he recorded on the stele.

Fang Yuan looked at it three times, storing the information inside east window Gu.

Although he did not cultivate fire path, these recipes were useful for him when researching about Gu refinement or even in his cultivation, as a form of inspiration. Especially the refinement recipe of the fire pupil Gu, it had high value.

According to this Gu Master, rank four fire pupil Gu was advanced using rank three fire eye Gu, together with sight blow Gu and some associated Gu refinement materials.

Fang Yuan knew about rank three fire eye Gu, it was a one time expenditure Gu used for investigative purposes. It could transform the eyes into fire eyes, having the ability to see through fog, but it did not work every time, once it failed, one would turn blind.

Fang Yuan knew about sight blow Gu too, Hao Ji Liu from the Hei tribe army had one. He had once used it together with rank four location swap Gu.

Fang Yuan kept the fire pupil Gu, he did not intend to go onto the fire path.

Fire pupil Gu did not suit his current style. While the attacking method was convenient, it was very restrictive, it was too reliant on visual contact.

There were too many strange Gu in this world, there were countless methods to prevent eye contact.

There was no strongest Gu worm, only strongest Gu Master.

Gu worms were the hosts of the great Dao, they were fundamentally tools. When Gu master use them together, they could form great effects. Some combinations were even far superior and harder to counter, they were known as killer moves.

"This means, this should be the first Gu Master inheritance I've obtained in Imperial Court blessed land." Fang Yuan thought about it, feeling interested.

In Imperial Court blessed land, there were countless Gu Master inheritances.

It was because of the superb environment, in contrast, many inheritances in the main world were often destroyed by calamities and beasts before the fated person arrives.

Furthermore, all the Gu Masters that entered Imperial Court blessed land were experts that had undergone tough battles, they had to have at least some superior qualities, if they were not heroes or grand conquerors already.

Thus, there were abundant inheritances inside Imperial Court blessed land. Anyone who was fated would have gains.

Fang Yuan kept the three Gu worms inside his aperture, before smashing the stele to bits.

Next, he searched around, finding a cave indeed. He entered the cave and walked to the lowest part of it, at about a hundred meters underground, he found six eerie fire dragon python eggs.

He was troubled now.

If it was a baby eerie fire dragon python, he could bring them away to Hu Immortal blessed land and allow them to hunt freely.

But it was not easy to hatch an eerie fire dragon python's egg. He needed to use eerie fire and python blood to bathe them daily. After the little dragon python hatches, they need to taught by the eerie fire dragon python personally, on how to use their strength to hunt.

Fang Yuan did not have the time or effort to waste just to hatch these eggs.

There was no choice, he quickly kept these eggs before getting out of the hot cave, flying towards the sky and continuing on his journey without any lingering feelings.

Chapter 549: Subduing azure wolves with the help of snow bats

Just like this, Fang Yuan flew for another three days, but could not see even a glimpse of the sacred palace on the plains.

Fang Yuan thought to himself: "It seems that I was transported very far away after entering Imperial Court blessed land. Otherwise with my speed, I would've reached the sacred palace within three days."

On the way, Fang Yuan met many Gu Masters and mortals.

They were Hei tribe alliance members, after entering the blessed land, those with ability would gather at the sacred palace. Those who did not would choose a place and settle down.

Imperial Court blessed land was not safe, there were large numbers of wild Gu worms and vicious beasts.

Hei tribe army came here and destroyed their order, disturbing the beasts and worms which had already sorted out their territory.

Thus, conflict and killing was natural.

But all in all, the environment was infinitely better than the outside world, which was face a fierce blizzard.

Fang Yuan had seen several slaughtering scenes along the way. Some were beast group corpses, some were humans with broken limbs.

Imperial Court blessed land had much greater foundation than Hu Immortal blessed land. There was no weather changes in Hu Immortal blessed land, but Imperial Court blessed land had it.

In fact, Imperial Court blessed land had morning and night!

This might not be spectacular in mortal eyes, because in northern plains, there was also day and night, they were used to it.

Only someone like Fang Yuan would understand the true value of this.

It was very rare for blessed land to have weather changes. If there was day and night, it meant that this particular heaven and earth had sufficiently deep foundations, at least, the time path law here was quite complete.

Normally, blessed land with astronomical phenomenon were first rate blessed lands. Fang Yuan's Hu Immortal blessed land had not reached this level yet.

Day and night was the characteristic of grotto-heavens.

Blessed lands were small worlds. Above blessed lands, there were even more complete and refined small worlds, they were grotto-heavens.

Imperial Court blessed land already had the characteristics of a grotto-heaven, it could be said to be a quasi grotto-heaven. Lang Ya blessed land was originally a grotto-heaven that fell, by now, it had lost its day and night trait.

Night descended.

Fang Yuan looked at the sky, it turned from a glorious gold color to a light and elegant silver.

The daytime in Imperial Court blessed land was a dazzling golden day. At night, it was not completely dark, as silver light shine in the sky.

Flying in the air, Fang Yuan witnessed the changing of the sky.

Silver light rained down, compared to the hot and dazzling golden rays during daytime, it had traces of sharpness to it.

Fang Yuan's flying speed was slowing down, he looked down and after searching for a while, he found a gentle slope.

With his years of experience, he knew that the gentle slope was a great place to set up camp.

But he was in no hurry to descend, he circled around the slope several times, like a bird flying freely.

Eventually, when he confirmed that this area was safe, he landed and kept his wings.

The strong eagle wings were pitch-black like steel. After Fang Yuan stopped using eagle rise Gu, the wings vanished into thin air, as one or two black feathers were left floating in the air, landing on the grass.

Fang Yuan willed and activated big lizard house Gu.

Immediately, a mystical light shot out from his aperture, landing in front of him.

The light expanded and grew, as a big lizard house Gu eventually appeared.

The lizard opened its mouth and shot out its tongue, showing the door in its mouth.

The tongue was like a red carpet ladder, as Fang Yuan stepped on it, the door opened automatically. After he entered the lizard house Gu, the door closed on its own, as the lizard closed its huge mouth without a gap.

Although Fang Yuan was energetic, he was still of mortal body, when fatigue accumulates to a degree, he will need to rest to ensure that he stays at peak condition in terms of mind and body.

Chichichichi...

After Fang Yuan got into the lizard house, he heard some noises outside.

His gaze concentrated as he muttered: "As expected, it is the blissful snow bats..."

Fang Yuan had already understood the rules, when day turns to night, large groups of blissful snow bats would fly out.

The blissful snow bats were pure white like snow, they were furry and did not look ugly like ordinary bats, in fact they were rather cute.

Such a beast group was huge in scale, each group had about several hundreds of thousands of bats. Among them were beast kings, and myriad beast kings were very common, there were even snow bat beast emperors.

Even with Fang Yuan's dual aperture and killer move like four arm wind king, he could not fight against them, he could only avoid them.

The snow bats only hunted in the air, eating the particles in the air or flying worms. The big lizard house Gu was not part of their food chain. But because of Fang Yuan's vigilance, he moved the big lizard house Gu to the back of the slope.

The big lizard curled up into a ball, from the sky, it resembled a huge rock.

Fang Yuan was on the bed as he slept, but before long, the cries of the blissful snow bats became very erratic, as wolf howls could be heard as well.

"What's going on?" Fang Yuan was woken up by this noise, he opened his eyes and got up from bed, going to the window.

Only to see that in the silvery backdrop, two beast groups were fighting.

The snow-white lump had a grand scale, it was the blissful snow bats. As for the dark-green lump, it was a pack of azure wolves, although they were fewer in numbers, they fought fiercely and had great cooperation.

Although they were many snow bats, under the wolves' attacks, they suffered huge losses.

Fang Yuan's brows lifted, feeling slightly shocked.

Azure wolf had a trace of the desolate beast heavenly wolf's bloodline, thus it could float in mid air even as a cub. A mature azure wolf can use this talent to its limits, able to run freely in the air.

Azure wolves were elites, they were different from ordinary wolf groups. Among the azure wolf group, each azure wolf was at least a hundred beast king!

Azure wolf groups were often small, but they had great battle strength. But regardless of how strong a wolf group is, they cannot withstand the trial of time, and the trials of mortality.

Right now, in northern plains' sky, barely any azure wolves could be seen. They were getting rarer, going to be extinct soon.

However, as the largest blessed land in northern plains, Imperial Court blessed land had such a huge scaled azure wolf group, it was not a surprise.

The wolves got more energetic as they fought, as the bat group gradually got into a disadvantage, after leaving behind several tens of thousands of corpses, they escaped.

The azure wolves did not have many deaths, most of the azure wolves landed on the ground and started consuming the bat corpses. Some of them remained in the air, looking around and staying vigilant.

Fang Yuan's heart was moved: "After entering the blessed land, my wolf group had scattered. Imperial Court blessed land is too wide, I cannot gather them here in such a short time. This azure wolf group is really timely, not only can they fly to keep up with my pace, they can even protect me, in the future when we encounter bat groups, we can just charge through."

At the same time, several wolves found Fang Yuan's big lizard house Gu and surrounded it.

Fang Yuan left the Gu house immediately and kept the big lizard house Gu, charging towards the myriad beast king in the sky.

The wolf group went into a commotion as they attacked Fang Yuan from all directions.

But the azure wolves which had just eaten were moving sluggishly, their battle intent had also decreased severely. This was the best time for Fang Yuan to subdue the myriad wolf king.

Fang Yuan snickered, he turned left and right, making circles in the air. With his flying master attainment, these azure wolves could only chase after him fruitlessly.

The myriad wolf king that Fang Yuan was going after was different from the other two myriad wolf kings, in the earlier battle, it had charged ahead and sustained some injuries, as well as losing some wild Gu on it. Fang Yuan had paid close attention to it earlier, and knew all the wild Gu worms currently on it.

Going up to the myriad wolf king, Fang Yuan activated the killer move four arm wind king and thrashed the wolf king.

This unlucky myriad wolf king was beaten into a daze by Fang Yuan.

Fang Yuan used this chance to activate rank five wolf enslavement Gu, subduing it.

Once it joined Fang Yuan, it howled and a third of the azure wolf group changed sides along with it.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly, it was dangerous to subdue a myriad wolf king under the attack of the wolf group, but now that he had succeeded, the situation was different.

With the wolf group, the situation was overturned.

Under Fang Yuan's manipulation, the wolf group attacked from left and right, cooperating with him and surrounding the second azure myriad wolf king.

The wild wolf group attacked furiously, as Fang Yuan used his wolf group to form a line of defense, protecting himself. He himself, engaged with the myriad wolf king.

After fifteen minutes, Fang Yuan subdued the second myriad wolf king.

Victory was assured!

The final myriad wolf king saw this and immediately ran, bringing its subordinates to escape with it.

Fang Yuan first stopped his bleeding and checked his own injuries. After checking the battlefield, he kept the big lizard house Gu and shifted the campsite.

This area was filled with the intense smell of blood, quickly, waves and waves of beast groups were attracted. If Fang Yuan continued staying there, he would be disturbed endlessly.

About ten li away, he rested for four hours before flapping his wings and continuing his journey.

But different from before, Fang Yuan was now surrounded by two azure myriad wolf kings, thirty-eight thousand beast kings, and two hundred fifty-six hundred beast kings. It was a huge force.

In the blink of an eye, six days of travelling went by.

In this process, Fang Yuan found three inheritances. They were small inheritances however, in Fang Yuan's eyes, they were as good as nothing.

What was worth mentioning was, the wolf group expanded.

With the foundation of two azure myriad wolf kings, another was subdued. This way, Fang Yuan had three azure myriad wolf kings under his control.

Imperial Court blessed land was a true land of treasures. There were huge beast groups within, and even the rare azure wolf was a common species here.

Other than the azure wolves, Fang Yuan subdued batches of night wolves, wind wolves, turtleback wolves, and vermillion flame wolves along the way.

These wolves were originally his to begin with, except that they were scattered after entering the blessed land. Fang Yuan had only found a small portion of them by now.

Chapter 550: Poet Immortal’s demise on Xing Jiu peak

Two days later. A high mountain peak protruded Fang Yuan's vision.

The deep blue mountain was like a lone vulture with a bizarre shape.

Fang Yuan was somewhat startled as his gaze became suffused with joy: "This should be Xing Jiu peak. It seems my direction is correct, according to Gu Immortal Lord Tian Ku's description in the past life, the place where the vulture's gaze falls in is the sacred palace!"

Imperial Court blessed land had a lofty and holy position in the hearts of northern plains' people, and was a spiritual symbol. It was also a cradle which had nurtured many northern plains' Gu Immortals in the Imperial Court contests before.

When central continent invaded northern plains, they had first attacked this significant strategic location.

Due to the lack of preparations, Imperial Court blessed land was breached by the alliance of central continent's Gu Immortals and the sacred palace was ruthlessly destroyed, turning into a ruin. Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was also destroyed, vanishing in the surging river of history, and causing people to sigh while wringing their hands.

Lord Tian Ku was one of the Gu Immortals who participated in the surprise attack against Imperial Court blessed land. Fang Yuan made his plan by referencing the surprise attack methods of the central continent's Gu Immortals.

"Hmm? There are people on Xing Jiu peak." When Fang Yuan was about to cross the Xing Jiu peak with his wolf group, he suddenly paused as he saw many Gu Masters at the summit of the peak, among were familiar people as well.

His thoughts moved and decided to not hurry on his way, but instead descended to the Xing Jiu peak with his wolf group.

"Pan Ping greets Lord Wolf King."

"Brother Shan Yin, we meet again."

Looking at the Wolf King descending, the Gu Masters all felt their hearts shiver. From among them, two Gu Masters walked out; one was Pan Ping who had become rich and famous with this time's Imperial Court contest, while the other was one of the twin demons Tai Bai Yun Sheng invited, Zhu Zai.

Pan Ping was now already at rank four peak stage, and with sole blade Gu, his battle strength could match against some rank five Gu Masters.

Zhu Zai was a strength path rank five Gu Master and was an expert in close combat, thus he was much more fearful of sole blade Gu than other people. He had been separated from Gao Yang when he entered Imperial Court, and on the way to the sacred palace, he got into an argument with Pan Ping.

"We greet Wolf King!" After Pan Ping and Zhu Zai, the rest of the Gu Masters greeted one after another while kneeling on the ground.

In Ma tribe army, Fang Yuan's prestige was raised to the highest status, and was recognized as the number one person of this generation. His prestige suppressing Hei Lou Lan and even Ye Lui Sang who had a fire path Immortal Gu.

If not for Chang Shan Yin not being of Huang Jin bloodline and Hei Lou Lan being the alliance leader, there might have been people who would have shouted to change the alliance leader.

"Stand up, there is no need to be so restrained." Fang Yuan was sitting on an azure myriad wolf king as he lightly nodded and then directly asked, "For you guys to gather here, what inheritance did you discover?"

Everyone inwardly grumbled.

The truth was indeed so. At first, someone had discovered an inheritance in Xing Jiu peak, but did not have enough strength to get it. Helplessly, the Gu Master called for other Gu Masters to explore together. But the result was, they lost several people instead.

The Gu Masters were not resigned to failure and searched all around for help, inviting Pan Ping and Zhu Zai one after another.

The two, for their respective benefits, competed with each other, creating the situation to turn into a stalemate before finally Fang Yuan crashed in.

Now, since Fang Yuan directly asked it, Pan Ping and Zhu Zai did not dare to hide it and could only explain this matter.

"Lord Wolf King, it is fortunate you are here. This inheritance opens every seven days, and during the opening, it lets out a soaring high starlight and reveals a starlight door. This duration is not only extremely short, there are also insect groups that rush out of the starlight door, preventing us from entering." Pan Ping introduced with a slight smile.

"There is only a short time before the inheritance opens now. Lord Chang Shan Yin, since you graced us with your presence, I represent all the Gu Masters here to request you to uphold justice." Zhu Zai said with sincerity on his face.

The corners of Pan Ping's lips twitched as he glanced at Zhu Zai with extreme disdain.

'Zhu Zai's reputation of being a famous expert in the demonic path is laughable, he actually is going so far in his flattery!' Pan Ping was filled with disdain towards Zhu Zai.

'Wolf King might be strong, but I, Pan Ping, will have a day when I can reach his level!' Pan Ping was young, his heart still had arrogance, but he did not show it, instead lowering his head to show his respect towards Wolf King.

He was a demonic path Gu Master and naturally was extremely clear of his current situation and understood the logic of being able to bow and submit.

Fang Yuan straightforwardly agreed, immediately becoming the main person in charge here.

As time gradually passed, everyone was indeed able to see starlight gradually filling the summit.

When the time arrived, the starlight majestically soared up, piercing through the sky. A small door then slowly opened in the dazzling starlight.

Bzzz Bzzz Bzzz....

Large numbers of insect groups rushed out like a tide.

These insect groups were of all kinds of colors with many wild Gu mixed among them; their stance was fierce but they only hovered near the starlight door and did not pounce upon the people.

Clearly, this was a test.

Fang Yuan carefully observed before snickering - this insect group test was not difficult. Even without him, with the combined strength of the rest of the Gu Masters, they would be able to overcome this.

However, Pan Ping and Zhu Zai's internal dispute caused the overall strength to be divided with other Gu Masters supporting different sides; no one conceded which allowed Fang Yuan to take this opportunity.

Fang Yuan glanced at Pan Ping and Zhu Zai; these two both had somewhat unsightly expressions right now.

Fang Yuan did not care, instead he sent an order: "These insect groups are often more difficult to deal with than beast groups. All of you, listen to my arrangement, and we will be able to reduce the losses and deal with this easily."

Everyone promptly agreed. Under Fang Yuan's command, they attacked in segments, drawing away the insect group and exterminating them.

After a dozen or so breaths of time, most of the insect groups had been drawn away and the originally tight defense line now had a huge gap.

Pan Ping said in joy: "Lord Wolf King is truly amazing! All of our eyes were obscured, exterminating the insect groups is not important, the main thing was to open a passageway. With this, we will have plenty of time."

Zhu Zai also sighed: "Having Lord Wolf King to lead us is our fortune."

But Fang Yuan's next words shocked them: "You guys stay here to hold back the insect groups, don't make a mistake. I will make a trip inside."

With that, he suddenly rushed to the starlight door with the wolf group.

"Thi... This... Lord Wolf King..." Zhu Zai's expression paled, he had not expected Fang Yuan to act so selfishly in the open.

Pan Ping's eyes also opened wide as his heart filled with anger at the injustice.

Under everyone's gazes, Fang Yuan first sent an azure wolf to investigate the inside and seeing there were no dangers, he rode an azure wolf king and entered the door.

Of course, he left behind a large number of azure wolves to form a defensive line around the entrance to protect his escape route.

"Didn't they say Wolf King was proud and aloof, how could he be so shameless?"

"He is truly too overbearing, this inheritance was clearly discovered by us first, but now it was snatched by Chang Shan Yin!"

"Chang Shan Yin has let down the name of the grand Wolf King, he actually left us out here..."

The people present were all furious but they did not dare to express their anger.

"Lord Pan Ping, should we also charge in?" A rank three Gu Master rolled his eyes, then turned towards Pan Ping and urged him.

Pan Ping snorted and sent this Gu Master flying with a kick, shouting fiercely: "If you want to go in, feel free. What, you want me to test the water?"

"Lord, you misunderstood, how could I dare!" The rank three Gu Master immediately retorted.

"Get lost!"

Pan Ping angrily rebuked while clenching his fists tightly.

He rigidly looked at the starlight door with sharp light flashing past his eyes.

The gap that had been cleared was now jammed with azure wolves. There were two myriad wolf kings, dozens of thousand wolf kings, over 300 hundred wolf kings, and even over two hundred guarding the air.

Pan Ping could not charge through this scale of wolves.

His thoughts turned around and he then looked at Zhu Zai, speaking in a faint ridiculing tone: "This is the result of you wanting Wolf King to uphold justice?"

Zhu Zai coldly glanced at Pan Ping, immediately seeing through Pan Ping's thoughts.

He snorted inwardly with disdain: 'This Pan Ping is still young and has been infected by hastiness gained from the recent fame. He actually wants to entice me to ally with him to break the wolf group's defense line, too naive! Is Wolf King so easy to deal with? Even if Wolf King only left behind one ordinary night wolf, I would not dare to make a move. This brat simply overestimates his own abilities!'

Pan Ping furiously snorted as he saw Zhu Zai not answering him, and could only swallow the words that he had been about to speak.

----------

Fang Yuan arrived before a courtyard after entering the starlight door.

The style of the courtyard was peculiar, it was completely constructed out of blue metal and its shape was strange and abstract, not belonging to any style of the five regions.

Fang Yuan pushed upon the gate and entered. The courtyard was covered in a layer of thin light cotton, and appeared mysterious, quiet and magnificent.

At first, Fang Yuan moved cautiously, but after searching around once, he did not find any mechanisms for tests or traps.

The courtyard had six rooms, and Fang Yuan explored all of them.

"So over a hundred years ago, this was the residence of northern plains' great poet Du Min Jun." Fang Yuan received the entire inheritance left behind by the courtyard master and learned this person's identity.

Du Min Jun was a rank five Gu Master, he travelled alone and had never married in his whole life. He was called Vagrant Lone Star by people. He was the famous Poet Immortal in northern plains and his verses mostly portrayed the starry sky, his longing towards his hometown and his powerless struggle against fate.

He was proud and noble, and separated himself from mortal affairs. He had been pursued by many northern plains' women throughout his life and there were even men who pursued him, but they were all heartlessly rejected by him.

Future generations evaluated and praised him: He was immersed in his own world, although he was in northern plains, his mind was in the starry sky. He was not a northern plains' man, he was a poet, he was a Poet Immortal who was denounced to the mortal world from the starry sky!

"So Du Min Jun eventually chose to suicide at this place." Fang Yuan sighed.

Du Min Jun was not able to endure the melancholy in his heart in the end; he built his final residence in Xing Jiu peak and ended his life of his own accord. What he had left behind were countless poems to be read and admired by the later generations.

Du Min Jun had outstanding talents and his inheritance was also extremely valuable.

First of all was an emotion poetry Gu. Emotion poetry Gu was specially used to store emotions and along with painting idea Gu, was a wisdom path Gu. It was extremely rare and very expensive.

Then, there were large numbers of star path Gu worms of all types. It basically had all the star path Gu of northern plains.

Fang Yuan was amazed at this.

"It seems Du Min Jun had a fortuitous encounter, otherwise how could he have so many and such complete star path Gu worms? Hmm? He actually innovated an entire set of star Gu recipes?"

Fang Yuan flipped through the recipes and realized how shockingly talented Du Min Jun was.

He founded a set of new Gu, from rank one 'a bit of star Gu' to rank two 'brilliance of two stars Gu', rank three 'three stars in the sky Gu', rank four 'four stars cube Gu' to rank five 'five stars aligned Gu'.

This set of Gu worms was especially targeted star path Gu and could raise star path Gu's effects by a huge degree; it was equivalent to a non-mainstream amplify effect Gu. But this set of Gu worms had much higher success rate than amplify effect Gu, moreover their refinement materials were extremely common. This meant, if this set of Gu recipes was spread, it would definitely lead to a huge rise in popularity of star path Gu and would have some amount of influence towards all Gu Master paths!

Chapter 551: Educate well

"Although I am not a star path Gu Master, if I refine this set of star Gu, it would be a huge help in opening the stargate and linking to Hu Immortal blessed land."

Fang Yuan could not help but feel a bit of joy in his heart.

He had invested heavily earlier to nurture a batch of starlight firefly Gu in his Hu Immortal blessed land. He also got many air bubble fish to increase the starlight firefly Gu's growth.

But even so, the starlight firefly Gu's expenditure was greater than its production.

Every time the stargate was opened, large numbers of starlight firefly Gu would be used. But to nurture starlight firefly Gu, a lot of time was needed.

It was easier for Fang Yuan back in northern plains, when he could use the starlight in the sky for one of the two sides of the gate. But in Imperial Court blessed land, there was no starlight in the sky. Thus, to open the stargate, he would needed to expend even more starlight firefly Gu.

But if he could refine this set of Gu that could amplify the power of star path, one starlight firefly would be able to achieve the effects of a few, that way, he would have several times less expenditure than currently.

"Furthermore, this Gu recipe is interesting, the thought process and viewpoint is different from the norm, it is like a deduction done using Earth's science and math. To think that Poet Immortal was so knowledgeable, having such incredible ideas."

Fang Yuan could see a portion of Poet Immortal's wisdom from this Gu recipe.

Taking all that was valuable in these few rooms, Fang Yuan returned back to where he came from.

Du Min Jun was a righteous path Gu Master, his inheritance was naturally a righteous path inheritance, there was only one trial and was not difficult.

When Fang Yuan returned to the mountain peak, the worm group that was troubling everyone had dispersed.

"Lord Chang Shan Yin, you are finally back! I wonder what gains lord had made inside?" Pan Ping's expression was ominous as he walked up to Fang Yuan. His intention was obvious: You Wolf King took the meat, you have to at least leave us the soup right!

"Hahaha, congrats Lord Wolf King, with this inheritance, you are like a tiger who gained wings." Zhu Zai cupped his fists and spoke, not mentioning anything related to splitting the gains.

Fang Yuan nodded lightly: "This inheritance was set by Poet Immortal Du Min Jun, there are still a lot of beautiful treasures left inside. You can go take it."

Saying so, he sat on the azure myriad wolf king and flew into the sky.

Pan Ping saw him leaving and immediately shouted: Sir Chang Shan Yin! We restrained the worm group for you painstakingly, yet you took all the best things inside the inheritance, according to the rules, you have to give us some compensation."

"Compensation?" Fang Yuan stopped his wolf, floating in the air as he looked at this Sole Blade General with a half-smiling expression.

"What compensation do you want?" Fang Yuan asked.

Pan Ping expressionlessly requested: "We can't determine what compensation to get yet. Why don't lord show us the inheritance you obtained, so that we can evaluate it?"

"Hehehe." Fang Yuan laughed, looking at Pan Ping amicably: "Look at this compensation, are you happy with it?"

Saying so, he willed and the azure wolf group surrounded Pan Ping from the ground and the sky tightly.

Pan Ping's expression changed, he held onto his scimitar as he shouted: "Lord Wolf King, what are you doing?"

Fang Yuan sat on the wolf back, looking down at Sole Blade General, snickering.

Howl!

The azure wolf group moved and charged at Pan Ping.

Pan Ping's expression turned into shock as he blocked left and right, unleashing all his moves.

He was a rank four peak stage cultivation, after getting much gains in the battles, he had high quality Gu worms that were a complete set, his battle strength far surpassed his previous state.

But the azure wolves were not ordinary wolves. Each one was at least a hundred beast king, this meant that they each had large numbers of wild Gu in them.

After Pan Ping killed several azure wolves, he could not hold on anymore, bleeding profusely as he got into a desperate situation.

"Lord Wolf King, you are too overbearing. We are of the same army, are you trying to kill me?!" He shouted loudly, trying to suppress Fang Yuan using righteousness.

The other Gu Masters had no idea what to do.

Fang Yuan's overbearing attitude made them uncomfortable. But because of his strength, they did not dare to say anything.

"Lord Wolf King, please calm down. Pan Ping did not know what was good for him, he verbally insulted lord, but lord is such a grand hero, why is there a need to put yourself at his level?" Zhu Zai urged quickly.

Pan Ping was Hei Lou Lan's beloved general, it is said that he was already part of Hei tribe. If he died here, when Hei Lou Lan pursues the matter, he might not do anything to Chang Shan Yin, but he Zhu Zai would be doomed.

Since Zhu Zai joined Hei tribe alliance army, he naturally wanted to join Hei tribe!

"Zhu Zai, you're overthinking this, I am not angry." Fang Yuan smiled at Zhu Zai lightly, but the azure wolves were attacking even more fiercely under his manipulation.

Zhu Zai's heart was anxious, but he was secretly shocked by Fang Yuan's ruthlessness.

Over there, Pan Ping was in a critical state, he activated sole blade Gu but could only defend himself, he could not break out of the wolves' encirclement.

"Lord Wolf King, please have mercy. Pan Ping is going to die!" Zhu Zai showed an expression of fear as he urged once again.

Fang Yuan finally stopped his attack, sighing at Zhu Zai: "Sigh, I am not violent, but this junior does not know how to respect his seniors. If I do not teach him a lesson today, is he going to dance on my head in the future?"

"Yes, yes, yes, lord is absolutely right!" Zhu Zai quickly answered.

Fang Yuan waved his hand and the azure wolves stopped attacking, they moved back but the encirclement was still present.

Without the pressure of the wolves, Pan Ping collapsed on the ground.

He was bathed in blood and covered in injuries, he breathed roughly as he stared at Fang Yuan with eyes filled with hatred.

Fang Yuan saw his expression and laughed: "It seems you have not had enough? Maybe my lesson wasn't severe enough, Zhu Zai, what do you think?"

Zhu Zai shuddered, he could see the overwhelming killing intent hidden in Fang Yuan's calm gaze. He quickly waved his hand: "Enough, it is enough. Pan Ping had received a sufficient lesson. Pan Ping! Quickly apologise to Lord Wolf King!"

Pan Ping clenched his fist, he gritted his teeth as he took a few deep breaths, closing his eyes and saying with much pain: "Lord Wolf King, I... I am sorry!"

He howled in his heart however: 'Today's humiliation, I will return it to you a hundred fold! Wolf King, remember this! I am not someone you can humiliate as you please!'

Pan Ping was a vigilant and low-profile person, but after the Imperial Court contest, the pride in the deep parts of his heart burst out. Especially in the battle against Liu tribe, he was first killed by three heads six arms, but was revived by Tai Bai Yun Sheng later using man as before Gu.

Such a revival process made his nature change slightly, making him feel like he was a 'person blessed by the heavens'.

'According to the rules, I should be allowed to check the gains from the inheritance. Wolf King, you are too overbearing, you will definitely regret all that you did today! Although you are strong now, it is only because you started cultivating several years earlier than me. One day, I will catch up to you, surpass you, and return all this humiliation right back at you!' Pan Ping screamed internally.

Fang Yuan naturally had no idea what he was thinking, but he was not interested either.

"If I kill him here, Hei Lou Lan would not pursue the matter with me. But this is a demonic act, it clashes with my identity. Furthermore, it does not benefit my future plans at all. I might as well leave this Pan Ping for the future..."

Pan Ping only had one sole blade Gu which Fang Yuan had some interest in.

If he was killed now, Fang Yuan would probably not receive the Gu.

Thus, Fang Yuan said: "Since you admitted your mistake, that is very good, it means you have noticed my hard work. A junior should behave like a junior, do you understand now?"

"Un... understood..." Pan Ping shut his eyes, he was furious but he squeezed out the words.

Fang Yuan snickered, he understood his feelings but he did not expose him, only continuing to say: "Very good. Since that is the case, compensate me. In order to educate you, I made quite a loss, look at my wolves, fifteen corpses are lying here."

"What?!" Pan Ping opened his eyes out of pure rage.

"What, are you unwilling?" Fang Yuan smiled lightly, looking at Pan Ping with an obvious expression of mockery, like a cat toying with a mouse.

"I, I am willing to!" Pan Ping breathed in deeply, nodding his head as he accepted his fate.

"Mm, this is the attitude of a junior indeed." Fang Yuan chuckled, smiling gently and kindly. But in everyone's view, he looked extremely scary.

"It was all thanks to lord." Zhu Zai was smiling at the side.

"Mm, of course." Fang Yuan nodded in agreement, smiling as he accepted this hypocritical flattery. He then looked around: "What about you guys? Do you need some lessons too?"

Everyone quickly rejected him with pale expression, they were shuddering, obviously scared out of their wits.

Fang Yuan laughed loudly, extorting all of Pan Ping's Gu recipes and several of his Gu worms.

Pan Ping was extremely furious, the few Gu that Fang Yuan chose were critical to his Gu set, without them, his strength would fall by at least two levels.

After toying around with Pan Ping, Fang Yuan felt the fun turning into boredom as he patted the wolf head, rising into the sky: "That will be all, there are still rather good things inside, they are unique. Go ahead and take them."

Everyone heard this and were revitalized. Many people thought: Lord Wolf King is truly righteous, it was natural for him to take the bulk of the meat, Lord Pan Ping was simply too small-hearted.

Only until Fang Yuan and the azure wolf group vanished into the sky did everyone start moving towards the starlight door.

According to seniority, Zhu Zai and Pan Ping were the first two to charge in.

The two first entered a small courtyard, but only found Du Min Jun's original poems. As for Gu worms, Gu recipes, they were all swept away by Fang Yuan, not a trace of them were left.

"Lord Wolf King was right, these are really unique treasures." Zhu Zai held the poems in his hand as he laughed bitterly.

Pan Ping who was hopeful and wanted to get some benefits to recoup his losses had a dark expression.

Puu!

Suddenly, he threw up a mouthful of blood as he fainted from anger.

Several days later.

"With my current speed, the sacred palace should be close by." Fang Yuan rode on the azure myriad wolf king's back, pondering to himself.

Soon after, his gaze became fixed at an area on the ground below him.

"Eh? This terrain is so familiar, don't tell me..."

Chapter 552: Giant Sun Immortal Venerable

Fang Yuan looked at the ground.

He saw that there was a mound protruding high up above the ground.

There were no forceful contours on the mound, there was an opening on it that showed a huge hole, like a tunnel underground.

As for the surroundings of this mound, it was a huge swampy area.

There were sparse trees in the swamp.

On the southwest side, there was a river. The river water was not clear, but it was a very long river, both the start and end of the river were beyond Fang Yuan's field of vision.

"Light in the soil, shine up to a hundred thousand feet high, swimming in the sky for a hundred li, praising plum fragrant snow." Looking at this scene, Fang Yuan could not help but think of this phrase in his mind.

"Is this Di Qiu inheritance ground?" Fang Yuan had a flash of inspiration as he felt dazed.

Back then, he had obtained information about Di Qiu inheritance from a fake grey-white stone slab. The painting idea Gu on the grey-white stone slab etched this map into his brain.

Thus, Fang Yuan had a clear memory of it, he could not forget it even if he tried.

He flapped his wings and flew around it in the sky, confirming that this terrain was exactly as he remembered.

"So this is it. I was wondering before, an inheritance using terrain as a clue was not reliable. If this was outside in northern plains, the terrain could be easily changed or destroyed. But in Imperial Court blessed land, that would be a different case." Fang Yuan thought.

This Imperial Court blessed land opened once every ten years. The victors of the Imperial Court contest would enter and might change the terrain due to battles.

However, when Imperial Court blessed land closes, the terrain slowly recovers.

Until ten years later, it would reopen after being restored to its original state.

"Di Qiu inheritance... since it was set up inside Imperial Court blessed land, and even had an innovative idea of using a fake grey-white stone slab to do it, the owner definitely put in huge effort and time for this. The inheritance should not be bad."

With such thoughts, Fang Yuan slowly flew to the mound, after observing the mound's entrance for a while, he summoned several azure wolves, and entered the dark hole.

Fifteen minutes later, the azure wolf returned to Fang Yuan unscathed.

This deep hole looked pitch black from the outside, but once someone entered, they would realize that it was full of glowing moss, it was not dark at all.

There was nothing inside the hole, the air was moist and there were only rocks and moss.

Fang Yuan personally entered to check it out, but still found nothing.

He frowned slightly, leaving the place. He was prepared for this result long ago: "This inheritance is not simple, if it can easily obtained, others would have gotten it long ago. Of course, I cannot rule out the possibility that someone else got it before me."

But Fang Yuan analyzed and realized that the possibility of that was very low.

"To come here, there are two conditions, one is to obtain the clue to the inheritance, and decipher the grey-white stone slab, a Gu Master skilled at appraisal is needed to do it. Secondly, they need to enter Imperial Court blessed land, that means they need to survive the Imperial Court contest, thus they need to have a keen eye, in order to be part of the victors."

"This inheritance is not simple at all. It seems that to get it, I will need to interpret the cipher." Fang Yuan concluded.

Light in the soil, shine up to a hundred thousand feet high, swimming in the sky for a hundred li, praising plum fragrant snow.

What was this cipher trying to say?

Fang Yuan thought about it but he got no answers. Even though he had many thoughts, none of them lead to any conclusive ideas.

"Nevermind, I'll leave it at that. There is still some time left inside Imperial Court blessed land."

Fang Yuan flapped his wings and flew, bringing the wolf group with him towards the blessed land's central sacred palace. That was the most important part of his plan, he spent so much time disguising himself, it was all in order to enter Imperial Court blessed land.

Obtaining landscape as before Gu was his top priority, but other than that, it was the inheritance of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Not just him, most of the strong Gu Masters would choose to go to the sacred palace.

The sacred palace was the central area of Imperial Court blessed land, it was the essence of the blessed land.

The sacred palace was one of the four resting chambers of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, it was also his most important resting chamber. His other chambers were in eastern sea, western desert and southern border.

In central continent, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had an even larger and grander resting chamber in the sky, it was situated within Longevity Heaven.

In history, there were ten rank nine Gu Masters, known as 'Immortal Venerable' and 'Demon Venerable'.

These ten existed across the long river of time, from the immemorial antiquity era to the remote antiquity era, to the olden antiquity era, to the medieval antiquity era, and finally, the late antiquity era. Each one of them was the absolute expert of their time, they were unparalleled and invincible in the world. At the same time, they each had their specialities and unique abilities, they were all very different.

The bloodthirsty Spectral Soul Demon Venerable, the mysterious Red Lotus Demon Venerable, the knowledgeable Star Constellation Immortal Venerable, the peaceful Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable...

Similarly, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was also a person full of legends and incredible stories.

He was a demonic path Gu Master born of northern plains. He was always lucky and fortunate in his life, having lots of good events. Not only could he avoid dangers, he could even turn them into blessings.

After he became a demonic path Gu Immortal, he was a casonova and toyed with women everywhere, no one could restrain him. Even the number one fairy of Spirit Affinity House in central continent back then, one of the top ten sects, became his wife.

Because of that, he became an external supreme elder of Spirit Affinity House, and converted over to the righteous path.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a dissolute nature, after becoming an Immortal Venerable, and ascending to the Immortal Court, he became the fourth generation Immortal King. He next built five great resting chambers, and had over several tens of millions of concubines.

He was extremely energetic, when he was a thousand years old, he was still taking in young girls from all over the world to expand his harem.

Thus, among all of the venerables, he had the most offsprings.

He had too many children, he could not even remember most of their names.

These children were spread all over the five regions. Right now, they were mostly concentrated in northern plains, and those Gu Masters who had Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's bloodline, were collectively known as the Huang Jin family.

"Women are like clothes while brothers are like our hands and feet.""Hereditary monarchy!""Beauty is the natural dowry of a woman.""I wish I could marry every single woman in the world!" All these were his catchphrases.

Even though time flowed mercilessly, and eras changed, he still left behind a dazzling proof of his glorious existence in history.

Especially in northern plains, Huang Jin family controlled nearly the entire region, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable was still influencing every generation thus far.

Sacred palace, the central control hall.

Night.

The silvery brilliant light shone on Hei Lou Lan's face.

He raised his head as he looked at a plaque on the central control hall. His giant bear-like body stood upright under the silver light.

As the alliance leader, with the Huang Jin bloodline flowing in him, once he entered Imperial Court blessed land, he would automatically arrive in the sacred palace.

This plaque in the central control hall was huge. It was sixty meters long, twenty-five meters wide, and there were two huge words on it — Hereditary Monarchy!

The golden light shining off it was clear and dazzling.

The central control hall was huge and grand, like the house of a giant. Under this plaque, even Hei Lou Lan's fat body seemed tiny.

"Hereditary monarchy huh..." He looked with a complicated expression, there was pain and hatred, admiration, anger, and aloofness.

"Lord." Cunning Gentleman Sun Shi Han came over, calling out softly.

"What is the matter?" Hei Lou Lan turned around, his expression had been completely sealed away, he returned to his usual arrogant, boorish, and irritable attitude.

Cunning Gentleman did not feel anything amiss as he took out a letter from his pocket, reporting: "This is Sole Blade General Pan Ping's letter. He said in the letter that Wolf King Chang Shan Yin devoured an inheritance alone, extorting him in public and made very vile actions. He hopes lord can seek justice for him."

"Oh?" Hei Lou Lan stretched out his fat right arm.

Cunning Gentleman quickly passed the letter to him with both hands.

"Lord, I am not trying to be nosy, but this Chang Shan Yin is getting more overbearing. He actually bullied and humiliated his own alliance mate. Sigh, Lord Pan Ping was too kind hearted, he thought about old relationships and wanted to share an inheritance with Chang Shan Yin. But the result was that he was treated like this. Wolf King Chang Shan Yin has great merits indeed, but this does not mean he can act as he wish. Otherwise, if everyone was like him, wouldn't we be in complete chaos?"

Cunning Gentleman carefully chose his words while Hei Lou Lan was reading the letter.

Hei Lou Lan snorted, stretching out his hand: "Hand it over."

"Ah, lord you mean..." Cunning Gentleman was shocked.

"This is only Pan Ping's side of the story, Zhu Zai should've sent a letter too." Hei Lou Lan had a sharp gaze.

Cunning Gentleman quickly laughed: "Lord is truly wise and mighty, I am in complete awe."

Hei Lou Lan took the second letter and swept through the content, he was expressionless and Sun Shi Han could not read his intentions at all.

This letter was merely Zhu Zai seeking credit for his actions, combined with the first letter, Hei Lou Lan understood what had happened.

He squeezed with his hand and the two letters were corroded into nothingness by a dark light.

"After Pan Ping and the others arrive, go to the supply camp and give them some compensation." Hei Lou Lan instructed.

"Yes, lord." Cunning Gentleman bowed, but after a while, he raised his head in confusion as Hei Lou Lan did not speak further: "Are we not punishing that Wolf King Chang Shan Yin?"

"Punish? What a joke!" Hei Lou Lan laughed: "Why do I need to punish him? If it was me, I would've done the same. Except I would not do it in such an ugly way."

Sun Shi Han was indignant, urging: "Lord, I am of different opinions. This Wolf King Chang Shan Yin regards himself highly and is untamable, we cannot tolerate his actions. Although he has great achievements, without lord's tribe funding him, would he have such a huge wolf group? He is a northern plains hero, he has great reputation. If lord does not punish him, he is just going to become more overbearing. In fact, he might even overthrow you and in the end, everyone would know the name of Chang Shan Yin, but not lord's name."

"Hahaha."

"Lord, why are you laughing?"

"Shi Han, you're overthinking it. After this happened, what reputation would Chang Shan Yin still have? Bullying the weak because he is strong, greedily taking an inheritance for himself, it would ruin his reputation. Furthermore, he does not have the Huang Jin bloodline, without a guest token, he cannot enter the True Yang Building."

After pausing for a while, Hei Lou Lan continued: "From this matter, we can see that Chang Shan Yin is only a mortal. He has desires, and greed, that makes things easy. Moreover, I have Chang tribe and Ge tribe in my hands now. He is already rank five peak stage, such a genius like him would definitely want to progress further. But I will only reveal to him the method to reach Gu Immortal realm after he joins Hei tribe."

"I know you hate Chang Shan Yin, but later, I still need him when challenging True Yang Building. Do not bother me in the future with such tiny matters. Do you understand?"

"Yes lord." Cunning Gentleman lowered his head, his voice slightly trembling.

"Mm, you may leave."

"This subordinate takes his leave." Sun Shi Han brought his disappointment with him as he left the central control hall.

Chapter 553: Imperial Court Sacred Palace

The wind was blowing past the ears.

In the golden sky, brilliant rays were shining down.

The azure wolf group moved in the sky, as Fang Yuan rode the azure wolf king, allowing the wind to blow his hair backwards.

His gaze was solemn, he was pondering internally. These days, he had been trying to decipher the quote from Di Qiu inheritance, but he was making no progress.

A glorious palace gradually appeared in his vision, emerging from the plain horizon.

Sensing this, Fang Yuan looked over as he swept the scattered thoughts in his mind away.

A trace of relief flashed past his face.

Sacred palace, he was finally there!

As Fang Yuan got closer, the large palace slowly showed its full features.

It had eight levels, each was about two kilometers tall. The first level, which was the bottom level, had the greatest surface area. The second level was above the first level, and so on.

Each level had walls around it, forming a hollow tube.

The snow-white walls were nine meters thick, the walls were joined together with no gaps. On the walls, there were rainbow colors towers at set intervals. Each tower had different colors, red, orange, yellow, green, azure, blue, purple, respectively.

After many levels were stacked together, the entire sacred palace looked like a tall mountain.

As Fang Yuan got closer, it was as if the sacred palace was rising from the ground, shooting up and piercing the heavens!

Grand and spectacular, the sacred palace!

Even with Fang Yuan's depth of knowledge, he was gasping in admiration when he saw this.

"What's that thing flying in the sky[1]?"

"Wolf King has arrived!"

"Just like what the information said, that should be the azure wolf group."

Fang Yuan's arrival attracted the attention of the Gu Masters inside the sacred palace.

At this point, there were almost ten thousand people in the sacred palace. These people were lucky, after entering the blessed land, they landed close to the sacred palace. Thus, they were earlier than Fang Yuan.

Hei Lou Lan had given instructions already, thus the Gu Master tasked to welcome him quickly reacted.

When Fang Yuan landed, there were already people standing at the huge gate of the first level.

The moment Fang Yuan's myriad wolf king touched the ground, the escort Gu Master came to greet him: "Lord Wolf King, you have arrived. It is my honor to bring you into the city. Your place of residence is on the eighth level, we have already prepared the room for you."

"Mm, no rush, bring me around the place first." Fang Yuan said lightly, getting off the azure wolf. As a form of respect to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, Gu Masters were not allowed to ride their steed inside the sacred palace, they could only walk.

"As you wish lord, this is my honor."

Fang Yuan followed the escort Gu Master into the sacred palace.

Inside the sacred palace, there were large numbers of pavilions and terraces, palaces and courtyards. Looking from outside, the edges of the roof were curved outside, they were silver and golden in color, looking magnificent and grand.

All sorts of buildings were interconnected. At some places, there was lots of free space and buildings were huge. At some places, the pathways were intercrossed and halls were everywhere, making it easy to get lost.

As for the interior of the pavilion hall, be it the pillars or the main support, they were carved with lots of beautiful images and decorations, it radiated an aura of prosperity.

"Lord, this is entertainment palace, the noble ancestor Giant Sun would hold a grand music festival here in this palace daily when he lived here. According to history, during each festival, there would be large numbers of concubines fighting to present their dance, in order to get ancestor Giant Sun's attention."

"Lord, this is spring soup hall, it has the largest hot spring in northern plains. Ancestor Giant Sun would come here weekly with a thousand concubines, to soak in the water and have fun."

"This is floating scent yard, ancestor Giant Sun had once moved the legendary 'wine pool' and 'meat forest' here. Every morning, the meat forest would produce all sorts of delicious meat fruits. At night, the wine pool would produce lots of fragrant wine."

The escort Gu Master introduced each area they went to, he was very eloquent.

Fang Yuan walked casually, looking around, he found it very interesting.

At the sacred palace's fourth level, the escort Gu Master brought Fang Yuan into the main palace.

"Lord, this is one of the eight main palaces of sacred palace, drawing palace. Ancestor Giant Sun was very talented, he was very skilled at drawing beauties. All of the drawings inside this palace were done by him alone. Please come this way."

The escort Gu Master opened the side door of the palace, inviting Fang Yuan in.

The eight main palaces of sacred palace had main doors, but only Giant Sun Immortal Venerable could use them. Although he was dead already, this rule was passed down, and his descendants followed this rule as a form of respect and reverence towards Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Once they entered the palace, a large wall of drawings filled Fang Yuan's vision.

There were nothing in this drawing palace, but huge walls. On these walls, there were all sorts of beauties, alluring ones, innocent ones, smiling ones, or those deep in thought. They were in all sorts of postures and positions, there were eighty thousand drawings!

"Those that were drawn here were well-liked by ancestor Giant Sun for a period of time. Of course, it is a woman's greatest honor to be hand-drawn by a venerable. Ancestor Giant Sun had lots of concubines, but those recorded here were the cream of the crop, they could be preserved eternally here."

The escort Gu master said with a look of admiration.

Fang Yuan did not speak, he only looked and thought to himself: "I wouldn't call this eternally. At least in my previous five hundred years, Imperial Court blessed land was destroyed by central continent Gu Immortals, and the sacred palace became history. Sigh, true immortality is something that not even someone as strong as an Immortal Venerable could achieve..."

When people came here, they would be stunned by the sacred palace's grand and imposing aura, even if they were not overwhelmed, they would feel great admiration.

But Fang Yuan could sense a trace of decay and rot in this brilliance.

Without eternal life, so what if you were as strong as a venerable?

Even the casanova Giant Sun had turned into ashes now. His traces were still here, proving his existence, but in Fang Yuan's opinion, such a proof was filled with the mockery of failure, it was truly pitiful.

His interest had waned.

"Let's go, bring me to the eighth level's accommodation." Fang Yuan sighed, instruction.

The escort Gu Master got out of his daze and said hesitantly: "But lord, sacred palace has a lot of famous sites, we just started! Other than these, there are also beauty palace, young girl palace, alluring palace, innocent palace, and unique scent palace. Back then, female variant humans lived there, there were even hairy men. There is also jade statue palace, meant to sculpt beauties, and offer them to the ancestor."

The escort Gu Master was anxious, all these places that he mentioned were not accessible with his status.

He wanted to use this chance to satisfy his curiosity.

But Fang Yuan did not fulfill his wish.

During Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's final years, he rarely went to the mortal realm to stay in sacred palace. He lived in Longevity Heaven, in a reclusive manner.

As for northern plains, large numbers of girls would be chosen for him to fill the sacred palace.

The last time Giant Sun Immortal Venerable came to the sacred palace, he did not meet these girls, instead he built the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and established the rules for the Imperial Court contest, before vanishing from this world completely.

The sacred palace thus faded out of history and those beautiful yet pitiful women became sparrows trapped in cages.

Although Imperial Court blessed land was huge, it had no freedom, it was a prison even though the place was large.

Eventually, they stayed there obediently and exhausted their lifespan. They could not escape, and no one had the guts to save them either.

Under Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's glorious and noble light, countless women were buried in pain, grudge, and sadness.

In Fang Yuan's eyes, the sacred palace did not have high value.

It was merely Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's inheritance, no Gu Masters dared to set up their inheritance here. As for the precious resources he left behind, they had been taken by previous generations of Gu Masters already. Even the central continent Gu Immortals who came later could not find anything valuable.

The only thing valuable in the sacred palace, was also the entire Imperial Court blessed land, no, more accurately, the most valuable thing in northern plains.

That was at the peak of the eighth level — Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!

As Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had suggested, the Gu house made by Long Hair Ancestor personally.

Rank eight Immortal Gu!

But now was not the time.

At the peak of the eighth level, it was complete emptiness. Only when the ten year blizzard strike would the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building show up.

In the following days, Fang Yuan lived in seclusion, cultivating as he waited for True Yang Building to open.

The azure wolf group was taken care of by others, he did not need to bother with it.

During this period, Hei Lou Lan sent people to invite him, and revealed the intention to recruit him.

To join Hei tribe, and become an external elder?

Towards this suggestion, Fang Yuan said he needed to consider it. Although he showed a moved expression, he would definitely refuse this in this heart.

Human skin Gu could disguise him as Wolf King, but it was a mortal Gu, the investigation of an Immortal Gu could expose him.

The recruitment of external elders was a common trick used by northern plains' super forces. This way, demonic path Gu Immortals could become become righteous, and it would help the Huang Jin tribes greatly in managing northern plains.

As for the incident on Xing Jiu peak, Hei Lou Lan did not mention a word about it. There was a rumor growing however, that Wolf King was extremely overbearing, describing his actions on Xing Jiu peak as vile and evil, using his strength to suppress the weak, the description was extremely biased but it sounded very convincing.

Fang Yuan laughed in his heart, someone was obviously trying to ruin his reputation behind the scenes.

"It is likely to be Pan Ping or Sun Shi Han who has motives to do this, or even Hei Lou Lan. But so what if my reputation turns sour?"

Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had a terrible reputation, he was a demonic Gu Master who toyed with women all over the region. But now? He was a revered Immortal Venerable!

When he expanded his harem, how many women's lives and happiness were ruined by him?

But now, no one publicly accused him of anything.

In this world, strength was everything.

On Earth, one had to be mindful of rumors, it was easy to ruin a person's life with some malicious lies. But that was because they were all mortals, the laws of the world was different, individuals could not surpass the power of society.

But here, it was different.

That was one of the reasons why Fang Yuan loved this world.

Half a month later, there was a water-like ripple in the golden sky.

The entire land started shaking.

Out of nowhere, there was wind as a piercing light shone at the peak of the sacred palace.

The light lasted for forty-five minutes, as it gradually dispersed. A tower appeared at a previously barren area.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!

[1] It's a Bird... It's a Plane... It's... Back

Chapter 554: Plotting is difficult, Living is tough

It was a tower.

Like a spring bamboo shoot, it was tall and slender and was upright.

The tower's shape was vague with all kinds of gorgeous colors, like a body of colorful ink in the shape of a tower as it continually shook.

"This is the initial appearance of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, and only when the storm and snow covers the northern plains, and all the small towers of Imperial Court blessed land sink to the ground, will each layer of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building stabilize. Only then can one enter inside and explore." Fang Yuan stood at the entrance of his residence and looked to the direction of the dome.

At this moment, there were shouts of jubilation and surprise in sacred palace. Gu Masters were cheering in high spirits while many mortals kneeled on the ground, praising the might of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

"But even when Eighty-Eight True Yang Building takes form completely, I won't be able to enter because I am not a descendant of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable and don't have his bloodline. If I want to enter inside, I would need Hei Lou Lan to get me a guest token. Well, there is no hurry, is True Yang Building so easy to rush into? Hei Lou Lan will need external help like me sooner or later."

After a while, Fang Yuan retracted his gaze and walked back to his room.

As the door of the room closed, the sound of cheers from the outside immediately softened.

Fang Yuan entered a secret room specially meant for cultivation and sat upright on a cushion.

"Both of my apertures have now already reached rank five peak stage. In regards to enslavement path, I have azure wolf group, while with regards to strength path, I have killer move four arm wind king. Combined with my battle experience, I am already at the peak among the mortals. But to deal with a Gu Immortal..."

Fang Yuan's brows slowly started to furrow.

He was well aware of the enormous gap between immortal and mortal; a mortal going against an immortal was as hard as ascending to heaven.

To him, the best situation right now would be Tai Bai Yun Sheng already having the recipe for Immortal Gu Landscape As Before in his mind.

It would not have been good for Fang Yuan to make a move outside in northern plains, but it would be very convenient for him to do so in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Using Gu to plunder river as before and mountain as before Gu from Tai Bai Yun Sheng, and then plunder the Immortal Gu recipe from his mind.

With such ample conditions, Fang Yuan could jump out of the chessboard and directly kill Tai Bai Yun Sheng who had yet to become an immortal, and then use the third refinement opportunity to request Lang Ya land spirit to refine landscape as before Gu.

However, the possibility of Tai Bai Yun Sheng, a mortal, possessing the Immortal Gu recipe of Landscape As Before was next to nothing.

Moreover, according to the vague rumors in his previous life, when Tai Bai Yun Sheng became a Gu Immortal, heaven and earth reacted and Dao marks attracted each other, making the two rank five Gu spontaneously merge together to form rank six Immortal Gu Landscape As Before.

Fang Yuan had a prudent nature, and would never place all his hopes on an indistinct future.

"If the situation is messed up, then I will have to deal with the Gu Immortal Tai Bai Yun Sheng. At that time, I can only rely on myself. Azure wolf group and four arm wind king clearly won't be enough."

Fang Yuan's strength was already at the peak among mortals. Despite cultivation of both enslavement and strength path having the greatest unresolved issue, he was still among the first class of rank five experts.

If compared to southern border, he was in the same level as Shang clan's genius clan leader Shang Yan Fei and Wu clan leader Empress Wu Ji.

Using the experiences of his past lives, the advantage of rebirth and taking a series of risks, struggling at death's door several times, Fang Yuan achieved such rapid growth that it would shock the world.

But even so, in front of a Gu Immortal, even if it was a newly advanced Gu Immortal, this strength was not enough.

"To resolve this huge issue, there are only about three ways."

"First is to search Eighty-Eight True Yang Building for the strongest Gu worms or unique methods."

"Second is to secretly make arrangements against Tai Bai Yun Sheng as much as possible so that there will be ample preparation when I have to truly make a move."

"Third is to resolve the problem of enslavement and strength dual cultivation and raise my battle strength further."

Fang Yuan silently pondered.

He was fully aware that he had exhausted almost all his previous life's foundation in creating four arm wind king. After all, he had specialized in blood path in his previous life and had only dabbled in enslavement and strength paths.

The so-called plots and traps against Gu Immortals were too inferior to be even mentioned and were not reliable. Fang Yuan had advanced to Gu Immortal in his previous life, thus he knew when a mortal transformed to a Gu Immortal, from their head to toe, inside to outside, they would go through baptism, and even their appearance would change.

The only thing that he could truly place high hopes on was Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!

Days passed by, the golden light and silver light in the sky continued to switch between one another.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was still gradually forming, its sunset hues gradually rose and covered most of the sacred palace in its light.

Cool wind breezed through Imperial Court blessed land with birds singing and the fragrance of flowers filling the air. But at the outside world in northern plains, snow had continued to fall for over a month already.

Blizzard was spreading over the northern plains in full force with its bone-chilling cold wind and snow.

Both the sky and ground were a scene of white, and mist covered one's vision.

Trees had already started dying and were frozen into pillars of ice. Mounds and hills were covered with thick layers of snow and large piles had formed in valleys as well.

Beast groups died in large numbers and even weeds with vigorous life force were also frozen into ice.

Even when one spat, the saliva would instantly turn into ice.

But heaven never blocked all paths, somehow, there would always be a trace of hope left.

In each region of northern plains, there were remnants of tribes. Some were small and some big, and relying on geographically advantageous places like warm pond valley, they were able to resist the wind and snow and survive in the blizzard.

Man tribe who occupied Hong Yan valley was one of them.

Hall of affairs.

The elders divided into two rows with Man tribe leader sitting high at the main seat.

Rank three external elder Shi Wu kneeled on the ground: "Lord tribe leader, I come forward to beg for forgiveness."

"Oh, what is your fault?" Man Tu asked with a slight smile.

"Reporting to lord tribe leader, I was in charge of looking after spirit spring D, but it suddenly froze and dried up yesterday, it is now ruined." Shi Wu respectfully replied.

"Hehehe, not a problem." Man Tu lightly waved his hand; as a matter of fact, he had already known this news.

"Elder Shi Wu, stand up, it is the ten year disaster now, there is a chance of every spirit spring suddenly freezing and drying up. This is not your fault."

'Lord tribe leader's kindness knows no bounds, I am ashamed!' Shi Wu was moved to tears and sighed inwardly.

His surname was Shi and was half an outsider to Man tribe. Although he had married into Man tribe, but he had still been pushed aside.

A problem occurred in the spirit spring he had been put in charge of, this matter could have been big or small. Fortunately, this generation's Man tribe leader was open-minded and did not look into it.

"However, anything concerning spirit springs are major affairs of the tribe. Man Duo, how many spirit springs do we have left now?" Man Tu's brows slightly furrowed as he asked.

Man Duo was Man Tu's third son; thin and small in physique but was shrewd and crafty, and had been assisting Man Tu in handling internal affairs of the tribe till now.

He immediately replied: "Lord father, Hong Yan valley now still has seven spirit springs marked A, B, C, E, F, G and H. Among them, G and H spirit springs are already close to drying up and will only last less than a month."

"Alright." Man Tu nodded, "That is to say, a month later, we will only have five spirit springs. Elders, what do you think?"

"Lord tribe leader, this thing is very difficult to deal with. This is a natural disaster, it is almost impossible for humans to reverse the situation, we might as well cut down on the primeval stones given to Gu Masters."

"Hong Yan valley's eight spirit springs were accumulated bitterly over these ten years by our tribe. The situation of our tribe this year is much better than the previous times. It is all thanks to Lord tribe leader's wise guidance that we don't need to worry, other tribes are in a much more worse situation."

"Even if all the spirit springs dry up, it won't be much problem. Wait till this ten year snow disaster passes, and at that time, new spirit springs will emerge one after another; when fortune arises after extreme suffering."

Elders expressed their thoughts one after another.

Man Tu calmly listened to them and nodded: "Spirit springs are very important for a Gu Master's cultivation and cannot be neglected. It is difficult for a Gu Master's cultivation to progress without primeval stones. The blizzard has just started, snow monsters will start roaming about soon. The main defense of the Hong Yan valley will still rely on Gu Masters."

He paused before mumbling: "Let's do it like this, take out one spring egg Gu from the tribe warehouse and plant it. This new spirit spring shall be titled D."

"Lord tribe leader, spring egg Gu is a rank five Gu." An elder objected in heartache.

Man Tu raised his brows: "So what if it is a rank five Gu? You all know that only with a spirit spring's supply of primeval stones can our tribe's Gu Masters advance forward continually. They can then preserve their strength and prepare themselves when resisting snow monsters. As long as there is not a huge loss of our Gu Masters, our tribe can preserve its strength. And when the blizzard passes and spring blossoms, it will be time for our tribe to realize our ambitions!"

Realize our ambitions...

The elders' eyes brightened at these words.

Man Tu had been putting all his efforts in developing the tribe and under his leadership, Man tribe had continually expanded and swallowed many small tribes over these years. Now, Man tribe was occupying Hong Yan valley, it could already be said to be a ruler of a region.

But from his words, everyone could hear this Man tribe leader still wanted to progress further. The current Man tribe was still not able to satisfy his ambitions!

The elder who had objected quickly apologized: "Lord tribe leader is wise and resolute, I am willing to lay down my life at tribe leader's command."

"We are willing to give our lives for tribe leader!" Soon after, the other elders spoke together.

"Having everyone with me, we can seek supremacy." Man Tu laughed loudly, then his expression concentrated and he ordered, "Elder Shi Wu will be in charge of the new spirit spring D."

Everyone present gazed at Shi Wu with envy.

Looking after a spirit spring was a lucrative job.

Shi Wu was truly moved this time, his eyes reddened as he said: "I am fortunate to have tribe leader's trust, I will definitely do my best to repay the tribe!"

The discussions continued for a while longer before everyone dispersed.

Shi Wu did not leave, instead following Man Duo to the tribe warehouse and took a spring egg Gu.

"This is spring egg Gu?" Shi Wu held the Gu in his hand and gazed at it strangely, his tone trembling.

His expression quickly concentrated and he then bowed towards Man Duo: "Third young master, please enlighten me on how to activate this Gu."

Man Duo smiled as he saw Shi Wu adapting to circumstances: "I do not dare to give you advice. This spring egg Gu is a rank five Gu and has extremely high demand on primeval essence, even a rank five middle stage Gu Master cannot activate it at one try. Elder Shi Wu, you have a rank three cultivation, and as such you would need to use lasting Gu and continuing Gu to activate it. But this way, the quickest it will take for you to plant the spirit spring is close to a month. Elder, you don't need to worry, I will help you by the side during this time."

"I am very grateful to third young master." Shi Wu promptly expressed his thanks.

Chapter 555: Dancing snow claws, Appearance of the building

The location to create the spirit spring had already been decided.

Shi Wu brought the spring egg Gu and went with Man Duo, after making the preparations, he starting using his primeval essence and sent it into the lasting Gu and continuing Gu, before injecting it into the spring egg Gu.

The spring egg Gu floated in the air, absorbing primeval essence as it moved up and down slowly.

For the next eighteen days, Shi Wu slept three hours a day, rushing to eat his meals and settle his excretion. Although it was tough, the effects were showing.

As he continued to inject primeval essence, the spring egg Gu was shining with a brilliant light.

These days, Man Duo had come to inspect again, and upon seeing this, he was overjoyed: "We are almost there. There are mild cracks on the spring egg Gu already, once it breaks, we will succeed. It has been tough on elder Shi Wu."

"Not at all, not at all." Shi Wu refined the Gu while humbly replying.

He was mentally fatigued, his body had gotten thinner. With his cultivation, forcefully activating a rank five Gu was very tiring. But if he succeeded, it would be a huge service to the tribe.

Man Duo continued: "During this elder meeting, lord father had specially mentioned it. Lord Shi Wu's hard work is evident in everyone's eyes, if you have any requests, we will try to satisfy it."

Shi Wu was extremely grateful: "I am ashamed, with lord tribe leader's care, how can I go overboard and request for more. But I have a question."

"Oh? Please speak."

"Young master Man Duo, I feel that Hong Yan valley had been getting colder these days. The surrounding vegetation and beasts have been freezing to death."

Man Duo's expression turned ugly. Hong Yan valley was indeed facing a problem. It had been mentioned during the last few tribe meetings. The result was, the underground magma supporting Hong Yan valley had been reduced due to unknown reasons.

This was different from historical records.

In the earlier meeting, tribe leader Man Tu flew into a rage, wanting everyone to think of a solution. At the same time, they had to conceal this matter to prevent their morale from sinking.

"Elder Shi Wu is at a crucial moment of refining the spirit spring, I should not tell him this bad news, or his mind will waver and ruin this important matter."

Thinking so, Man Duo lied and reassured Shi Wu.

Shi Wu did not sense anything wrong, he was about to speak but suddenly, his expression changed, shouting: "Oh no, it's the flying hand snow!"

Man Duo turned around and was shocked: "How can there be flying hand snow in Hong Yan valley?!"

Only to see that in the sky, fierce winds were blowing as palm-sized snowflakes carrying the aura of rank five Gu descended slowly.

"Oh no, come quickly and protect the spring egg Gu!" Man Duo shouted, calling the nearby Gu Masters over.

But the blizzard was powerful, the wind cut like razors and the might of heaven and earth descended, after resisting it for a while, everyone starting to fall into a disadvantage.

"Snow monster!"

"Snow monsters have appeared!"

Trouble comes in pairs, the blizzard gathered and formed into a six meter tall snow monster.

The defense of the Gu Masters was easily broken. In the sky, large numbers of flying hand snow gathered into a huge palm. Under everyone's furious and indignant, while completely helpless stares, the giant snow hand grabbed the spring egg Gu in the air and squeezed.

Crack!

With a light sound, the snow hand disintegrated.

The snowflakes landed on the ground, the rank five spring egg Gu inside had vanished already.

　　...

The silver light shone like a miasma gently raining down on Imperial Court blessed land.

Howl howl...

Azure wolf group sprinted on the ground, some ran in the air, while others were dashing with their claws.

Even though there were Gu masters feeding them in the sacred palace, these wolves still desired freedom. They wanted to be ferocious beasts roaming the sky, and not canaries trapped in cages.

As their master, Fang Yuan let them do as they wished. He himself was spreading his eagle wings as he flew in the sky, looking at the ground below him.

It was Di Qiu inheritance.

"Light in the soil, shine up to a hundred thousand feet high, swimming in the sky for a hundred li, praising plum fragrant snow... what does this sentence mean?" Fang Yuan pondered.

He had been coming over to explore the inheritance grounds every few days.

Instinct told him that this Di Qiu inheritance was not simple.

Thus, every time he went out, he used the excuse of walking his wolves, to train them and practise his manipulation skills.

But even so, he could not stay for long.

Fang Yuan was now a person with high status, second to only Hei Lou Lan. His every movement was scrutinized by everyone. He was no longer as invisible as before.

This time, he had no findings, and to prevent suspicion, he could only leave for now.

Even though he could completely occupy this entire area using his status now, Fang Yuan did not do that.

If this inheritance had high value, even if he had great strength, others would compete with him.

He did not have Huang Jin bloodline, to enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, he needed Hei Lou Lan's guest token.

However, he had been sending people to scout the area.

The reason was naturally the azure wolf group.

Everytime he went out to hunt with the azure wolf group, there would be a route. Before moving out, he would send Gu Masters to scout out the path for him, and go to the path that had the most prey.

There were five to six routes to choose from each time, but each one of them would be close to Di Qiu inheritance.

One must act flawlessly, Fang Yuan followed the route that he planned and continued hunting with the azure wolf group.

There were a lot of beasts and resources inside Imperial Court blessed land. Especially near the small towers, there were swarms of worms and countless wild Gu.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was something only a small number of Gu Masters had the chance to enter. Most Gu Masters would roam in the huge blessed land, subdue wild Gu, or find inheritances.

Fang Yuan followed the trail and found many Gu Masters.

As for the area near Di Qiu inheritance, there were naturally many Gu Masters passing by.

Fang Yuan was not afraid that Di Qiu mountain would get taken by someone. In fact, he was hoping that someone would find it and trigger it. He would get news of it by then and would be able to strike easily.

After all, he had already used his strength to snatch an inheritance back on Xing Jiu peak.

Rumble rumble...

There were some loud sounds coming from the ground.

Fang Yuan rode the azure myriad wolf king, and looked down, seeing a small tower shining with a bright light, sinking into the ground slowly.

Fang Yuan was not surprised.

In the progress of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's gradually appearance, the small towers in Imperial Court blessed land would slowly sink into the ground.

These small towers were like nests that were filled with all the wild Gu that had grown in the last ten years.

Many people guessed: The wild Gu in these small towers were the energy source to form Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. In a way, these small towers were a portion of the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

This guessed had never gotten confirmation.

Gu Immortals who could confirm this were unable to enter Imperial Court blessed land. And those mortals who could enter were way too weak compared to Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, they could not decipher it.

But Fang Yuan was an exception.

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building has an intriguing design, it is truly a work of heaven. These small towers are indeed a portion of True Yang Building." Fang Yuan was far more knowledgeable than other Gu Immortals in this aspect, because he controlled the most complete information regarding Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

This source of information was Lang Ya land spirit. The land spirit in his life was the rank eight Gu Immortal Long Hair Ancestor who created the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"Eh? Wait!" Fang Yuan's body shook, a flash of inspiration appeared in his heart, sweeping away the confusion in his heart.

This moment, he finally found the strange thing about Di Qiu — there was no small tower near Di Qiu!

"Indeed, that is the case." Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance, in the last few times he brought the azure wolves to hunt, he would either be in the sky near Di Qiu, or the ground near it.

Now that he recalled it, he realized the peculiarity of Di Qiu.

"By logic, every eight li should have a small tower. And every small tower corresponds to the regions in northern plains. But near Di Qiu, there is nothing!"

Thinking so, Fang Yuan got excited.

This was a huge breakthrough!

Following this lead, he could potentially unravel the mystery of Di Qiu inheritance.

But Fang Yuan did not turn back.

Rushing over in an excited manner like this was asking to be suspected.

He controlled his excited emotions, and continued on the route he had prepared. The azure wolves moved out from the sacred palace, and after one round, returned.

The sacred palace was like a mountain peak, the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building at its peak was still nurturing. The aurora it emitted was covering the entire sacred palace. The grand and beautiful sacred palace was shrouded in a mysterious and powerful aura.

Fang Yuan went out to hunt every six or seven days with the azure wolf group.

But plans cannot keep up with circumstances, three days later, the aurora gathered into one point and starting taking form.

The first layer of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had formed!

This was a joyful news, causing the sacred palace to go into a commotion. At once, everyone's hot topic was about this building.

Of course, most of the Gu Masters could only watch.

Hei Lou Lan went in excitedly, several hours later, he returned in a pathetic state, wounds covering his body.

His injuries were not light, but they could not conceal the shock in his eyes.

During the second expedition, he brought many Hei tribe Gu Masters.

Hei tribesmen had the bloodline of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, they could freely enter and exit True Yang Building without restriction.

During such times, tribesmen were the most reliable. Why was there a need to share with outsiders what one could devour alone?

When Hei Lou Lan returned, he looked extremely tired. As for the Gu Masters who went in, only sixty percent returned.

Thereafter, all sorts of rumors and information spread, they were all regarding True Yang Building.

Some said that the True Yang Building was a work of heaven, it was spectacular; some said that it was difficult to explore, every step was precarious; some said that the rewards for passing it was very enticing...

By now, everyone was moved.

Chapter 556: It's actually a Gu Immortal Inheritance!

Bam!

Hei Lou Lan raised his leg, kicking his tribesman Hei Qi Sheng to the ground.

"Useless thing!" The black fatty cursed, the muscles on his face twitched as he revealed a ruthless and savage gaze.

The hall was silent, all of the Hei tribe Gu Masters did not dare to speak a word.

Hei Lou Lan was called 'Black Tyrant', it was due to his famous ruthless and cruel personality. Especially when he was obstructed six times by the 54th round, his anger was ignited like a barrel of gunpowder.

"Lord tribe leader, it was my inability, I deserve death!" Hei Qi Sheng sprawled on the ground, begging for forgiveness while prostrating.

"Idiot! Why is there such a useless idiot in our Hei tribe?!" Hei Lou Lan gritted his teeth, kicking Hei Qi Sheng several times. Seeing that he was coughing blood due to the kicks, Hei Lou Lan's anger subsided slightly.

The surrounding elders were silent, not daring to say a word.

Last time, the elders who pleaded for Hei Qi Sheng were beaten until they received heavy injuries by Hei Lou Lan, they were still bedridden now.

Hei Lou Lan's temper had been curbed slightly during the Imperial Court contest. But now that they were in the blessed land, his poor temper and cruel nature were back at full force.

"You are also all idiots, useless trash! Why are you all standing here? Speak, tell me a good method to break through the 54th round. Otherwise, I will dock your salary. The tribe does not feed useless people! I gave you primeval stones, I gave you a luxurious life, raising your status, what was it all for? Now is the time to perform your duties!!" Hei Lou Lan screamed, the windows were shaking from the force of his voice.

The elders were sighing bitterly internally. They were like drooping eggplants, lowering their heads and communicating with their expressions, but no one dared to speak first.

Hei Lou Lan stared and looked around, fixing his gaze on elder Hei Pei.

As the most senior and experienced first elder Hei Pei, he gritted his teeth and walked out, bowing in respect: "Lord, the way I see it, this 54th round is a test of enslavement path, it is very difficult and it cannot be passed without master level enslavement attainment. Although elder Hei Qi Sheng is an enslavement path Gu Master that we nurtured, he is not a master. To pass this round, we need Lord Wolf King's strength."

"Hmph, you are asking me to seek outside help? You want to let the whole world see us, Hei tribe, as a joke, as a weakling that needs outside reinforcements?" Hei Lou Lan's gaze was filled with ruthlessness as he screamed fiercely.

Hei Pei's heart was shivering, but he bowed deeply and responded: "Lord tribe leader is strong and intelligent, you are an amazing leader, the Lord of the Imperial Court. With your presence, whoever dares to think that Hei tribe is useless would be the number one fool in this world. This is not outside reinforcement to be exact. This Wolf King Chang Shan Yin is part of the alliance army, he is your subordinate. Using him for this is but natural. I am sure Chang Shan Yin would be very grateful to lord, after all, he is an outsider but he is given the chance to enter True Yang Building, it is his greatest honor."

Hei Lou Lan heard this and his angered expression softened.

The elders watched this as they praised Hei Pei's eloquence internally, he was indeed skilled to be the first elder.

Hei Lou Lan walked slowly, he was very indignant.

Currently, he had two guest tokens, they were obtained from the 12th and 46th rounds respectively as a reward from True Yang Building.

It was not that he did not want to waste the tokens, but once he invited Wolf King, the reward for clearing the 54th round would go to Chang Shan Yin.

If it were his tribesmen, Hei Lou Lan could use the authority of the tribe leader to make all of the rewards his. But according to the rules, these rewards should be given to the reinforcement.

The rewards in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building were extraordinary, even Hei Lou Lan was deeply moved.

Be it Gu recipes, Gu worms, or others, each item could allow a Gu Master to rise up despite an ordinary background.

Hei Lou Lan walked for several steps, sighing lightly.

He knew that there was no point in forcing Hei Qi Sheng. Hei tribe had nurtured three enslavement path Gu Masters, one died in the Imperial Court contest, while Hei Qi Sheng was the stronger one out of the two left.

But he was not an enslavement master, any master needed sufficient talent, it was not something that could be nurtured through abundant resources.

Hei Lou Lan stopped walking: "Where is Hei Shu?"

"Subordinate is here." Hei Shu was standing outside the hall, he was Hei Lou Lan's personal Gu Master attendant, hearing Hei Lou Lan's summon, he came in to greet him.

"Go invite Wolf King here." Hei Lou Lan instructed.

Hearing this, the elders in the hall sighed in relief. Hei Qi Sheng who was lying on the ground relaxed his body — this nightmare was over!

"Yes, lord tribe leader." Hei Shu left after receiving his orders.

Bam!

Hei Lou Lan kicked Hei Qi Sheng again: "You trash, why are you still lying here? You want Chang Shan Yin to see how pathetic our Hei tribe is after he comes here?"

"Lord, lord I was wrong!" Hei Qi Sheng quickly apologised profusely.

"Get lost and nurse your injuries!!" Hei Lou Lan screamed.

"Yes, yes, yes lord!" Hei Qi Sheng struggled to get up, leaving in a wobbling state.

Not long after, Hei Shu reported back with an apologetic look: "Lord tribe leader, Lord Wolf King is not in the sacred palace, he is out feeding his wolves."

"What?" Hei Lou Lan's volume became louder, his brows were raised as his calm expression showed anger again.

The elders were terrified, the first elder Hei Pei accused Hei Shu: "You junior, you do not know how to do your job. Even if Wolf King was not around, how could you return empty-handed? Could you not send a letter over, and state your intention, that Wolf King would come crawling back immediately!"

"Lord, it was not my fault!" Hei Shu cried out innocently: "I already sent a letter over, but Wolf King replied already. He said that he was leading his wolves to hunt, it was a habit and he did not want to cut it in the middle. He wants us to wait, if we cannot wait, we can call Tang Miao Ming and the others instead."

At once, everyone was shocked.

First elder Hei Pei stared with his eyes wide open, he did not believe it: "How can anyone be so indifferent? Did he really say that?!"

"I have concrete evidence! Lord tribe leader, this is the letter Gu that Wolf King Chang Shan Yin sent back!" Hei Shu said, handing a star letter Gu to Hei Lou Lan.

This was a star path Gu, it was rank four and gave the fastest replies. But it shone in the air as it flew, it created huge commotion and was easy to intercept.

Of course, in Imperial Court blessed land, there were no such worries.

Hei Lou Lan's mind entered the star letter Gu, as he snickered continuously: "This Wolf King has good temperament, he is able to control his desires so well."

"Lord, Wolf King is an arrogant loner, everyone knows that. The way I see it, he is already laughing secretly, but is trying to put up a front." First elder Hei Pei analyzed, as the others elders nodded in agreement.

"Hmph, of course he is being haughty. He is an enslavement master, and also a flying master. If you guys were masters, would we need to ask an outsider for help?" Hei Lou Lan screamed, causing the elders to shut up as some of the elders lowered their head even more.

Honestly speaking, Fang Yuan was really not placing his attention on True Yang Building.

He looked at Di Qiu below him, his heart palpitating: "There really isn't a small tower here. According to the terrain, this area should have a small tower, directly above Di Qiu, but now, this is just a pitch black hole... impressive, the Gu Master who made this inheritance is very impressive!"

The Imperial Court blessed land had a small tower at every eight li interval. Actually, all of them were a part of the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was an Immortal Gu house that Long Hair Ancestor had refined back in the day, it was as high as rank eight.

Next, after Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's preparations, it was a mirror of northern plains. The small towers were all over Imperial Court blessed land, they could be seen everywhere. Each of the towers had thousands of wild Gu, no one dared to target them or they would die.

But now it seems that, the Gu Master who set up Di Qiu inheritance not only moved the small tower, he even set up this inheritance on that spot. Such methods and courage, such abilities, it made Fang Yuan confirm that this mysterious Gu Master was not a simple person.

"No, rather than Gu Master, I might as well call him a Gu Immortal! Even with the long time that had passed, and Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's setup might have weakened, but it is not something mortals can alter. Only Gu Immortals can make minor changes to these arrangements, and create such a place." Fang Yuan's eyes were shining with uncertainty.

He had accidentally gotten Di Qiu inheritance, but it was a Gu Immortal inheritance!

Light in the soil, shine up to a hundred thousand feet high, swimming in the sky for a hundred li, praising plum fragrant snow. What did this really mean?

What sorts of treasures would be inside a Gu Immortal's inheritance.

"Will there be an Immortal Gu?" Fang Yuan guessed daringly.

If there was an Immortal Gu, it could match against the first floor of True Yang Building. Because even in the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the final round of every floor might not have an Immortal Gu reward.

"Even without an Immortal Gu, Di Qiu inheritance was created with so much effort, there had to be an Immortal Gu recipe at least."

Without Immortal Gu, an Immortal Gu recipe was also a huge reward. A complete Immortal Gu recipe was something not sold inside treasure yellow heaven.

Gu Immortals would sell remnant recipes mostly. Even if they had complete Immortal Gu recipes, they would break it up and add in some mistakes before selling it.

Complete Immortal Gu recipes could only be exchanged. And there were few instances of this happening throughout history.

Fang Yuan curbed his imagination, and began to think calmly.

With a crucial clue, his current train of thought had improved rapidly.

He pieced together all sorts of clues, deciphering the time of Di Qiu inheritance's creation. It should be very long ago, at least, it should've existed since Paradise Earth Immortal Venerable's time.

But the more he thought, the more questions he had.

Let's call this person Gu Immortal Di Qiu for now, who were they? Why did they set up an inheritance here? As a Gu Immortal, how did they get in? Most importantly, how did they know about the setup here, and the true principle behind the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building?

If they were like Tai Bai Yun Sheng, and advanced to Gu Immortal realm inside Imperial Court blessed land, then there would be new explanations for what happened...

Fang Yuan felt a headache as he stopped thinking.

One star letter Gu tore through the sky and flew towards him.

Fang Yuan received it, and saw that it was Hei Lou Lan urging him to return.

"Never mind, I shall go to True Yang Building first, and come back later. Gu Immortal Di Qiu most likely made use of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's setup flaws, once I enter True Yang Building, I might be able to find some clues and understand the mystery behind this!"

Thinking so, Fang Yuan replied with the letter.

Since Hei Lou Lan wrote a letter personally to rush him, Fang Yuan stopped acting arrogantly anymore, he immediately returned.

"I will need to rely on Wolf King's strength this time." Hei Lou Lan saw Fang Yuan and laughed.

He was very anxious in his heart.

There was not much time inside Imperial Court blessed land. Once the ten year blizzard outside subsides, Imperial Court blessed land would close, and they would need to leave.

Before that happened, Hei Lou Lan not only needed to complete the mission given by his tribe's Gu Immortals, he also needed to find a strength path Immortal Gu for himself.

After Wolf King returned, Hei Lou Lan quickly organised the group again.

The gang got to the building, as Hei Lou Lan handed Fang Yuan an ancient token: "This is the guest token. Wolf King does not have Huang Jin bloodline, you are an outsider in the building's perspective. To enter it, you will need a guest token each time."

Fang Yuan received the token and laughed lightly without any concern, saying: "I can't wait to witness the splendor of True Yang Building!"

At this point, Hei Lou Lan did not push the door open, instead, he 'crashed' into the door.

Fang Yuan followed suit, as the guest token shone in his hand, he imitated Hei Lou Lan and entered True Yang Building as well.

Chapter 557: Three grades of evaluation, clearing with high grade?

Fang Yuan felt his body stiffen as a strong sense of pressure assaulted him as he entered the building.

But soon after, the pressure lifted.

He had entered True Yang Building completely, there was a lake in front of him.

The sky was blue, there was ripples on the surface of the lake, and the surroundings were shrouded in vague foggy mountain shadows.

The guest token in his hand turned into a puddle of cold molten iron, flowing down the gaps between his fingers.

Each guest token could only be used once.

Fang Yuan shook off the liquid from his hand, until they were all gone.

He looked around, finding himself on an island at the center of the lake. There was someone beside him, it was Hei Lou Lan.

"This is the 54th round." Hei Lou Lan did not look at Fang Yuan, instead facing forward: "Look, that is the problem brother Shan Yin has to deal with."

Fang Yuan looked at the same direction, and saw that not far away, there was another island.

On the island, there was a group of water snake lions.

These water snake lions had a body of bright blue fur, they were extremely smooth. Its limbs were not claws, but were webbed feet like that of frogs. Their tails were poisonous snakes, coiling around the water lion's back or standing straight up, hissing with their tongues.

Without Hei Lou Lan's introduction, a barrage of information from a mystical source entered Fang Yuan's brain at the same time —

"Use the hedgehog fish on the island and break past the water snake lions' defense, occupy the island over there."

Fang Yuan retracted his gaze, turning to look at the island around him.

In the jade-blue water around the island, he saw the shadows of hedgehog fish swimming.

At this time, Hei tribe elders came in one by one, standing beside Hei Lou Lan.

"Be it water snake lions or hedgehog fish, they are wild beasts from the medieval era. Right now, they can only be found in the deep areas of eastern sea." An elder sighed.

"In my opinion, this round is extremely unfair. The water snake lions are very strong, one of them can compete against five or six hedgehog fish. But the number of hedgehog fish we have here is only about twice of the water snake lions." A Hei tribe elder looked at the island ahead as he explained the situation to Fang Yuan.

"No need to worry brother Shan Yin, we are here today for practice." Hei Lou Lan patted Fang Yuan's shoulders.

After all, Fang Yuan enslaved wolf groups. But now, it was a fish group, and it was even an extremely rare, nearly extinct hedgehog fish in northern plains.

Hei Lou Lan had failed about eight to nine times already, his best result was only killing thirty percent of the water snake lions. This made Hei tribe Gu Masters understand the difficulty of this round.

Although Chang Shan Yin was an enslavement master, this was the True Yang Building set up by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

Fang Yuan looked for a while and frowned.

He estimated, with his abilities, controlling these hedgehog fish to kill the water snake lions was not hard. In fact, it was almost a guaranteed success.

But although this round seemed simple, it was very elaborate.

Back when Giant Sun Immortal Venerable set up the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the purpose was to leave an inheritance for descendants, and reward the outstanding ones. Thus, every round in True Yang Building would be split into low, middle, and high grade.

Getting through with low grade would reward the least rewards, they would directly go to the next round.

Getting through with middle grade would have twice the reward of low grade, during the next round, they would receive information about it.

As for getting through with high grade, not only would they get twice the reward of middle grade, they would even be transported into a deep part of True Yang Building, a place called treasure room.

This treasure room was filled with countless treasures, there were even several true immortal inheritances by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable.

But the things inside the treasure room cannot be taken away easily, the person who cleared the round would need to exchange for them.

Be it Gu worms, Gu recipes, or even their own cultivation experience, all these could be used for exchanging the items within.

When the person finishes the exchange, they would go to the next round.

Hei Lou Lan only needed a low grade pass to get to the 55th round, that would satisfy him. But Fang Yuan's goal was different.

He needed high grade pass to enter the treasure room. Only within the treasure room can he be alone, to use the methods he had prepared to obtain the greatest benefits!

"Low grade pass is easy as breathing. But middle and high grade, I do not know what are the conditions for those. I can only try now!"

Thinking so, Fang Yuan breathed in deeply, and nodded at Hei Lou Lan, indicating for him to start.

Hei Lou Lan took out a token and waved it at the sky.

This token was different from the guest token, it was the the owner token. When Hei Lou Lan first entered Imperial Court blessed land, this token appeared before him, signifying his prestigious status.

The owner token vibrated, as ripples formed in the air, dozens of fish enslavement Gu appeared, of rank one, two, and three.

When Fang Yuan received these Gu worms, he easily refined them, the other people were immobilized by an invisible gentle force, no one could assist him.

Only Hei Lou Lan could still speak, he advised: "Brother Shan Yin, mind the time. You have only fifteen minutes."

Fang Yuan nodded, and waved his hand, as the fish enslavement Gu in his hand flew out with dozens of mystical lights.

Everyone saw Fang Yuan's casual action and was shocked in their hearts.

If it was Hei Qi Sheng, he would need to enslave them one by one, being extremely careful. When using enslavement Gu, the Gu Master would definitely face the resistance of the fish group. If they were careless, the enslavement would fail. If it was severe, the Gu Master would suffer some backlash on his soul.

"Was Wolf King too overconfident?"

"I've never seen such an enslavement method before!"

"He's in troub..."

Everyone's heart was pounding.

But immediately after, they stared with huge eyes as the fish group swam away towards the island immediately after the enslavement. It was as if they belonged to Fang Yuan from the start, not a single enslavement failed.

The water snake lions were alerted by this, they stopped their lazy actions and sat up, the lion head roared as the snake head hissed.

Many of the water snake lions jumped into the water, setting up their defense lines.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan was standing upright, his arms behind his back as he did not waver at all. The enslavement attainment as well as foundation of the soul he displayed made almost everyone praise him in secret.

"Oh heaven, he did it!"

"Just this alone was an eye opener."

"Wolf King is an enslavement master indeed, he is different from ordinary people."

"A master is a master, maybe he can succeed this time, who knows."

Everyone's eyes began to show a look of anticipation. Even Hei Lou Lan was looking with a hopeful expression.

But the fish group did not attack the water snake lion group like they wished, instead they were swimming around the area, surveilling the place.

"This... what is Wolf King thinking?"

"Wolf King is being careful, it seems he is trying to get familiar with the fish's habits!"

But as time passed, the fish continued to swim. Everyone did not get to see the fight between fish and lion as they wished.

By now, even Hei Lou Lan was a bit anxious, he urged: "Brother Shan Yin, there isn't much time left."

"No rush." Fang Yuan was calm as he replied casually.

The water snake lions saw that the fish group did not attack, some of the water snake fish crawled out of the water, onto the island. The strong defense around the island weakened.

After a moment, Hei Lou Lan urged again:" Brother Shan Yin, half the time has already passed!"

"No rush." Fang Yuan waved his hand, his eyelids drooping, as if he was very sleepy.

Even more water snake lions went onshore. The old lion king even sprawled on the ground, shutting its eyes in slumber.

Everyone was greatly disappointed, they were cursing in their minds.

"This Wolf King is merely strong on the outside, to think I thought so highly of him earlier!"

"So what if he is a master level, this is True Yang Building..."

"It seems that this time, Chang Shan Yin's goal is to get familiar with the fish group, to accumulate experience for the next assault!"

Seeing that the time was going to be used up, everyone's remaining bit of hope was expended.

"What a waste of a token, expended like this."

"What shall I eat for dinner tonight?"[1]

"After failing this time, I wonder how lord tribe leader will deal with Chang Shan Yin?"

Just as everyone were thinking about random things, Fang Yuan suddenly laughed, manipulating the fish group to charge, attacking the water snake lion group from all directions.

"As expected!" Hei Lou Lan's eyes shone with brilliance.

He had guessed in his heart already: "Chang Shan Yin wants to save his efforts for the next attempt, then this time, he would definitely familiarise himself with the fish group and their attacking pattern. He would also need to probe the strength of the lion group!"

The fish group's sudden attack caught the water snake lion group off guard.

The hedgehog fish group was like a hungry shark, devouring the small number of water snake lions in the water in an instant.

"So that's it! Chang Shan Yin was training the fish group earlier while making the lion group let their guard down."

"This attack has already taken down thirty percent of the lion group, as expected of master level!"

"What breathtaking beast enslavement attainment, Hei Qi Sheng is like a baby compared to Chang Shan Yin."

Everyone stared intently, shocked by Fang Yuan's amazing talent.

Howl!

Seeing that its subjects were being slaughtered, the old lion king roared, leading the lion group into the water to take revenge on the hedgehog fish.

But what was peculiar was that Fang Yuan stopped his powerful assault, and under his manipulation, the fish group retreated.

The lion group chased after him, but at when they got to one area, the group fell into chaos.

"What happened?" Everyone was perplexed.

"So there was a hidden whirlpool here!" Hei Lou Lan mumbled.

Immediately after, the elders' eyes shone: "I get it! Wolf King was making the fish scout the area, it was not just to train them, he also wanted to investigate the terrain!"

"That's right! When beast groups fight, it is like war between two armies. Not only would they need to consider both of the armies, they also need to care about the terrain." Many Gu Masters saw this and almost wanted to pat their legs and scream.

The water snake lion group was trapped by the whirlpool, as the fish group turned around and attacked.

The lions had huge bodies, they were more affected by the water currents. As for the fish group, they were barely affected by it due to their small size.

An exceptional battle strategy unfolded before the crowd.

The strong water snake lion group was as fragile as a piece of water. Under Fang Yuan's manipulation, the fish group was like an elite troop, they cooperated well and attacked and retreated at will, taking down their opponents one by one.

The fish group gathered and spread at will, attacking fiercely. At times they scattered, causing the lions' attacks to miss.

"He has them dancing in the palm of his hands!"

"Amazing, incredible!! In just a dozen breaths' time, Wolf King became victorious!"

"We got through, we got through!"

Hei tribesmen were shocked and exhilarated, their gaze towards Fang Yuan revealed admiration, amazement, and fear etc.

"Good, what a great Wolf King!" Hei Lou Lan laughed as he clapped.

Fang Yuan also laughed heartily, because when he finished killing the lion group, an information went into his head — high grade evaluation!

The next moment, Fang Yuan vanished on the spot.

"What happened?" Hei tribesmen were shocked at this, their eyeballs also fell out.

"He got a high grade evaluation!!" Only Hei Lou Lan was shouting in his heart.

[1] Chicken Back

Chapter 558: Giant Sun’s great scheme, treasure within the crystal

Fang Yuan was in a long crystal hallway.

Light was flashing in all directions, the four walls were made of shiny crystals, one could see their own reflection in them.

Fang Yuan gazed around, behind him, and to his left and right were walls, he could only move forward.

"I am finally inside the treasure room." Fang Yuan's lips curled into a smile, as he walked forward with huge strides.

The crystal hallway was long and clear, in about five steps, Fang Yuan saw that Gu worms or Gu recipes started appearing on the crystal walls to his left and right. They were like insects sealed in amber, motionlessly fixed in the crystal walls.

These were all the precious treasures in the treasure room, to obtain them, he needed to exchange them with an equivalent item.

"Oh? There's a Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus here." Fang Yuan halted his steps, he found a familiar looking Gu sealed in the crystal wall before him.

This Gu was like a blue and white lotus, as large as a face. It had an amazing origin, it was created by Genesis Lotus Immortal Venerable.

They were a series, the rank three Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, the rank four Heavenly Essence Treasure Monarch Lotus, rank five Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus, and rank six Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus.

Among them, Heavenly Essence Treasure Imperial Lotus was ranked sixth among the top ten Immortal Gu, its value was equivalent to Spring Autumn Cicada, and was held in the hands of Lang Ya land spirit now.

Fang Yuan had once used a Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus, it made up for his lack of aptitude during that period, and was a huge help to him. But to advance the Gu, Fang Yuan lacked the relevant recipes, and the refinement cost was too huge, a natural spirit spring had to be used, and it had to be full of primeval energy as well. Old spirit springs that were running dry could not be used. Once he succeeds, the spirit spring would be destroyed.

Rank four Heavenly Lotus needed seven spirit springs. Rank five needed nine. To reach rank six, it needed eleven.

This sum was counted using southern border's level of spirit springs. If northern plains' spirit springs were used, he would need 60% more of them.

Back then, it was too difficult for Fang Yuan to advance the Heavenly Lotus, and after his aptitude improved greatly, he gave up on the heavenly essence treasure lotus Gu.

But now, he was moved by this rank five Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus.

"The series of Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus are known as mobile spirit springs. Once refined, they can produce primeval essence naturally. There's no point in using the rank three Heavenly Essence Treasure Lotus anymore, but the rank five Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus is suitable for my current condition."

But to get his Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus, Fang Yuan would need to exchange for it using an equivalent treasure according to the rules.

"Let's exchange then." Fang Yuan was rather rich now, having a blessed land was like having the foundation of a Gu Immortal.

To exchange for the Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus, others might have to use all of their assets to get it, but for Fang Yuan, it was a question of what to give up.

"What should I use for the exchange?"

Fang Yuan's mind entered his two apertures.

The strength and enslavement path Gu worms inside his apertures were not exchangeable. His first aperture's vital Gu Spring Autumn Cicada was the same.

Other than them, there were still quite a lot of Gu worms in his possession.

The individual value of these Gu worms were obviously lower than Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus, but if one was insufficient, he could put two, or even three in.

"Oh? Why are there eighteen spring egg Gu?"

Fang Yuan was shocked to find a batch of precious rank five Gu inside his first aperture.

But he quickly understood the reason: "I almost forgot, this is the reward for getting past the round with a high grade evaluation. It was directly sent into my aperture by True Yang Building."

Normally, a Gu Master's aperture was the basis of their cultivation, it was their biggest secret. But True Yang Building was truly made by Old Hair Ancestor, with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's setup, it had great power and could directly send Gu worms into a Gu Master's aperture.

Spring egg Gu was obviously inferior to Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus, but it was still a rank five Gu.

The spring egg Gu looked like a white goose egg, it could be obtained by killing a strong eggman emperor. Placing the spring egg Gu deep underground would give birth to a new spirit spring.

Spirit springs were the foundation for Gu Masters' cultivation. Many large tribes or clans would collect spring egg Gu to strengthen their foundation, in case of need. Even Gu Immortals would often buy them and plant them inside the blessed land, forming a spirit spring and nourishing their inhabitants.

Fang Yuan took out one spring egg Gu and looked at it.

This Gu was not in good shape, the surface was full of cracks, and there were primeval essence traces inside the Gu, someone had used it before.

Fang Yuan's eyes shone with brilliance, he sneered: "It seems that this Gu was snatched by the flying hand snow while it was activated. The rewards in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building are all of such sources."

In order to fulfill his dream of 'hereditary monarchy', Giant Sun Immortal Venerable set up a huge scheme painstakingly while making sure his descendants had the upper hand.

First was the Imperial Court contest, to weaken other tribes. Next, he used the ten year blizzard to send all sorts of treasures and materials from northern plains into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

After all, a Gu Master's cultivation was heavily reliant on resources.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable set up the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it was a fatal blow. After the resources were taken, he would give them to his bloodline descendants, destroying the hopes of success for other tribes.

In Fang Yuan's previous five hundred years, central continent Gu Immortals attacked and destroyed Imperial Court Blessed Land using this specialty of the True Yang Building.

They sent pawn pieces into Imperial Court Blessed Land. They then purposely scattered Gu worms and allowed the flying hand snow to take them. Eventually, True Yang Building faced destruction from the inside, causing a fatal loophole to appear.

After central continent Gu Immortals destroyed Imperial Court Blessed Land, they exposed all of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's evil deeds, telling the whole world about his schemes, causing a huge commotion in northern plains as all the mortals went into a frenzy.

But commotion aside, northern plains was still the second strongest region in terms of battle strength, only inferior to central continent. All sorts of super forces, Huang Jin family tribes worked together and caused northern plains to remain stable.

After all, Huang Jin family had controlled northern plains for so many years, they had deep foundations and roots, it could not be easily shaken by public opinion.

However much they reacted, without strength backing them, there was no point.

Fang Yuan placed the spring egg Gu in his hand closer to the crystal wall, towards the wall that sealed the Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus.

As it got closer to the crystal wall, there was a light red light, turning into orange, before finally glowing in yellow.

After the three lights shone, there were no more changes.

Fang Yuan took out another two spring egg Gu, placing them near the wall.

This time, there was a green light shining. But the green light was not strong, it was suppressed by the other three lights.

Fang Yuan sneered as he took out a fourth spring egg Gu, placing it at the crystal wall.

This time, the green light burst out, being balanced with the other three colors.

The crystal wall turned hollow as it vibrated. The Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus inside flew out slowly, while the four spring egg Gu in Fang Yuan's hands left his control and flew into the crystal wall, replacing the Heavenly Essence Treasure King lotus' position.

The Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus landed in Fang Yuan's hands, and Fang Yuan instantly refined it using his primeval essence.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was truly amazing, it allowed Gu Masters to instantly refine Gu inside the building.

"Red, orange, yellow, green, azure, blue, purple, black... it seems that inside this treasure room, there are eight categories. The more lights there are, the more valuable the treasure. Rank five Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus was only a green light item. This was only mid-tier among the range of treasures in this place."

Fang Yuan evaluated in his heart as his assessment of the treasure room's value rose and his knowledge of it deepened.

He stretched out his hand, touching the crystal wall.

He could feel an icy feeling on his palm, inside, there were four spring egg Gu, the ones he had used for exchange.

Fang Yuan tried to control them, but there was no effect.

He sighed in amazement in his heart.

To speak the truth, in this current world, Fang Yuan was easily among the top three people in terms of his understanding of the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

That was because he had the detailed information given to him by Lang Ya land spirit.

The more Fang Yuan's understanding of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building increased, the more he felt the genius mechanics of this building, it was really amazing.

Forget the others, just look at this crystal wall ahead of him, it had a huge origin.

This crystal wall was made back then by Long Hair Ancestor using tens of thousands of Gu Masters. Using a secret technique, he extracted their apertures. Using their aperture walls as the material, he used profound ice Gu, ice wall Gu, grand jade Gu, slow down Gu, vitality Gu, and others to refine it.

This crystal wall was the best spot to seal Gu worms, the Gu inside would go into deep slumber, they could be stored for hundreds or thousands of years without the slightest harm.

According to his information, a newly refined crystal wall would shine with ripples like that of a water surface, one would walk into it feeling like it was an illusory dream.

But now, the crystal wall no longer had that glamor, but it was still crystal clear.

With enough time, water could pierce through rock.

The power of time was one of the most noble heavenly powers.

Even a rank nine venerable could not defeat the power of time. Although True Yang Building was an Immortal Gu house, it opened every ten years, there was still some expenditure incurred.

If not, during Fang Yuan's previous life, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would not have been taken down and destroyed.

Right now, the luster of the crystal wall was no more, in fact, there was a thick layer of powder at the corner of the walls.

Fang Yuan continued moving forward.

In the crystal wall, there were all sorts of Gu worms, Gu recipes and special refinement materials sealed, but even more were the cultivation experiences of past generations of Gu Masters.

These experiences were extremely precious. Those who could enter the treasure room were geniuses who passed with high grade evaluation, the things they left behind were definitely top quality.

After walking for a little longer, Fang Yuan stopped his footsteps.

The hallway ahead of him looked endless. But a stele was blocking Fang Yuan's path.

The stele was squarish and smooth, it was about the height of Fang Yuan's knee. There were two words written in northern plains' script— guest halt!

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was set up by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, in consideration of his descendants. But those who entered the treasure room might not necessarily be Gu Masters who had the bloodline of Giant Sun.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable considered this point, and thus he placed the most precious resources behind the stele, outsiders like Chang Shan Yin could only watch helplessly.

But Fang Yuan was not Chang Shan Yin.

"Guest halt? Hmph." Fang Yuan laughed coldly in disdain.

He tried walking past the stele, but was blocked by an invisible wall.

"After so many years, although Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had some expenditure, the guest halt stele is still working properly, I cannot force my way through." After testing it for a while, Fang Yuan sat down facing the stele.

He had planned this for so long, he was naturally well prepared.

Immediately, he took out a Gu worm, and it shot into the stele.

The first step to refining Eighty-Eight True Yang Building has started!

Chapter 559: Immortal Venerable’s Will

Refining Eighty-Eight True Yang Building might sound like an absurd idea, but it was not wishful thinking.

In truth, Fang Yuan was not the 'first person' to refine Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

In his former five hundred years, when central continent Gu Immortals attacked Imperial Court Blessed Land, they first sent some Gu Masters to infiltrate Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's treasure room.

After they succeeded, they released the entire procedure after recording it with Gu worms, announcing it to the world.

Imperial Court Blessed Land was the spiritual symbol for northern plains Gu Masters, it had great importance. The recording of Imperial Court Blessed Land being taken down was spread over the five regions, it not only displayed central continent's strength, it was also a poisonous needle intended to destroy northern plains Gu Masters' mental support!

Most importantly, this recording also proved that Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had snatched Gu worms all over northern plains, in order to benefit his descendants.

Once the recording was released, northern plains was in huge turmoil, as the masses went into an uproar.

Although the Huang Jin tribes suppressed the situation, and the internal chaos did not reach the level that central continent Gu Immortals hoped, it did create a northern plains where the people's hearts wavered and undercurrents were flowing.

Central continent Gu Immortal Song Qie Xing, after seeing this video, gave an accurate prediction: "Once this video is spread all over the region, the spirit of freedom in northern plains would be released from Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's prison!"

Fang Yuan naturally had a vivid memory of this video.

After his rebirth, he immediately realized the huge value of this video.

For this trip to northern plains, saving Dang Hun mountain was merely one of his objectives.

Fang Yuan was a careful person, he often considered failure before success.

"How can there be something as good as 'success as one wishes' in this world? If I fail to save Dang Hun mountain, I can at least seek other forms of compensation inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building."

The video of central continent Gu Immortals taking down Imperial Court Blessed Land had great reference value for Fang Yuan.

But just this clip was not enough.

Fang Yuan could only see what happened on the surface from this clip. But luckily, Fang Yuan had obtained first hand information from Lang Ya land spirit.

Because of this, by fusing theory with practice, Fang Yuan had much greater confidence in refining Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

"With my current cultivation level, it is impossible to fully refine Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. But I can refine a portion of it."

Fang Yuan was very clear of the reality.

He was only a mortal Gu Master, one had to be at least a rank eight Gu Immortal to refine the Immortal Gu house.

In Fang Yuan's plans, he only wanted to refine a portion of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had existed for a very long time, it was worn down and had loopholes secretly. It was too grand, too majestic, like a giant wooden cage.

Fang Yuan was like a termite compared to it.

The strength of a termite could not destroy the entire wooden cage. But it could devour the edges, the difficulty of the two was as great as heaven and earth.

The guest halt stele in front of him, after a specialized Gu worm entered it, gave off a faint yellow light.

Fang Yuan stretched out his palms in the meantime, injecting his aperture's primeval essence into it.

At the same time, his will entered the guest halt stele, following the primeval essence.

Gu Masters refine Gu, it was to occupy the Gu worm's body with their will. And during this process, primeval essence was the perfect carrier.

Fang Yuan's brows were tightly knotted as his mind entered the stele.

The guest halt stele was only a portion of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was a rank eight Immortal Gu house, it was way too big.

Once Fang Yuan's will entered, he felt that he was in a sea of darkness.

In this endless darkness, there was a sun-like existence. It gave off a weak light, which moved in waves like that of breathing.

"This is Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's will?" Fang Yuan's mind went into high alert.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's property, since he refined it, his will was naturally inside the Immortal Gu.

Although Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's body had perished long ago, this will that he injected had survived while slumbering within this shell.

"Such a will is really grand, I feel like I am facing a real sun! Immortal Venerables have unthinkable strength, this is merely a small portion of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's will, left behind and weakened after such a long time."

"Thankfully, this will is currently unconscious, if I move carefully, it should not be alerted. I must not wake it up, otherwise, what happened to those two central continent Gu Immortals whose souls were dispersed in the video will happen to me."

The vast dark space represents the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's remnant will was like the sun, in the center emitting a weak light as it slept.

Meanwhile, Fang Yuan's will was like a sesame compared to it. He also gave off a weak light, but he was lurking at the furthest corner of the entire area.

Fang Yuan continued to inject primeval essence, slowly and carefully.

As the primeval essence entered the guest halt stele, the amount of his will that was inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building increased.

In the dark corner, the light that represented Fang Yuan was expanding, gradually repelling a portion of the darkness, gaining some territory for itself.

Time passed second by second.

Fang Yuan was very careful, his forehead was soon full of sweat.

"To think that refining this stele would be so difficult. With my two rank five peak stage apertures at ninety percent capacity, it was still not enough. If not for the Heavenly Essence Treasure King Lotus, I might have faced even more trouble."

Four hours passed, Fang Yuan finally breathed out a sigh as he pulled back his palms from the stele.

He was extremely tired, mostly from the mental stress, it was more precarious than walking on a tightrope.

"I finally succeeded."

Fang Yuan looked at the guest halt stele before him, a sense of closeness emitted from the stele into the deep parts of his heart.

But the joy of success quickly faded, as Fang Yuan frowned even more deeply.

"There were indeed many deleted scenes in the video that was shown in my previous life. I spent so much primeval essence, but the Gu Master in the clip was only rank five middle stage, yet he did not take any breaks in the middle, only spending an hour to refine it."

Maybe the Gu Master had some assistance Gu worms in his aperture, but Fang Yuan was more inclined to believe that there was more than meets the eye.

The reason why central continent Gu Immortals released this video was to deal a crushing blow to the Huang Jin tribes, to release the spirit of freedom in other northern plains tribes.

Deep into the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there were definitely gains or methods that could not be publicly shown.

At the same time, to make the video more concise and interesting, so that people would watch it, the boring and mundane parts were definitely deleted, that had certainly happened.

But this was bad news to Fang Yuan.

Refining the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was a very dangerous act, if he was misled by the video, one mistake would end his life!

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is truly phenomenal, I spent so much time, but I have not even refined half a percent of it."

Fang Yuan sighed as he patted the guest halt stele, standing up.

If he looked at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building as a hundred percent, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's remnant will would occupy thirty percent of it.

Out of a hundred percent, after refining the guest halt stele, Fang Yuan's refinement of the building was still less than half a percent.

"But even so..." Fang Yuan's lips curled into a smile.

He turned around, talking a few steps back and casually came to a crystal wall that had sealed some treasures.

His gaze concentrated as he stretched out his arm towards the wall.

If it was before, the crystal wall would be like an ice wall, blocking his hand. But now, the guest halt stele shone slightly, and the crystal wall turned hollow.

Fang Yuan's arm successfully entered the wall like it had gone into a water wall, taking the treasure out from inside.

Once he refined the guest halt stele, any treasure inside this section of the crystal wall could be taken out at will, Fang Yuan did not have to pay any price!

"Oh? This must be the rush thunder stone..."

Looking at the treasure in his hand, Fang Yuan had to appraise it carefully before confirming his guess.

Rush thunder stone was quite a rare Gu refinement material. It was nearly extinct now, it was very rare even inside treasure yellow heaven, only sold once in a while.

This stone was created from the essence of lightning and thunder when the thunder in the nine heavens exploded together.

But ever since the immemorial era, seven of the nine heavens fell, only white and black heaven were left. The chances of these two heavens' thunder and lightning clashing were very low. Thus, after the immemorial era, the production of rush thunder stones fell drastically.

When thunder path was flourishing, large numbers of rush thunder stones were used to refine Gu.

Thus, the remaining stock of rush thunder stones now was low.

"Heaven and earth is ever-changing, as time passed, thunder path also changed and no longer needed rush thunder stones. Only those Gu Masters or Gu Immortals who wanted to research immemorial thunder path Gu worms would be interested in rush thunder stones."

The value of the treasure room was extremely high, just a casual treasure that Fang Yuan took was a rush thunder stone.

But soon after, Fang Yuan returned the rush thunder stone back to the crystal wall.

Small greed ruins big plans.

Because exchange was needed to obtain treasures, the total treasure amount in the crystal walls was always the same.

Every item here was recorded by all the super forces, or even large-sized Huang Jin tribes.

If someone obtained high grade evaluation and came here later, they would find that treasures were missing, that would lead to great suspicion and shock!

Fang Yuan felt no pity, after testing for a while, he walked towards the deeper parts of the crystal path.

Arriving at the guest halt stele once again, his footsteps became slower.

A few hours ago, the invisible wall that blocked him had vanished. But this did not mean that he could enter safely.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was created by Long Hair Ancestor, it obviously had other defensive measures.

But Fang Yuan was prepared for them.

He willed and at once, five to six mystical Gu worms flew out of his aperture, turning into lumps of colorful smoke as they surrounded him.

Fang Yuan checked again, and after ensuring that he was fully covered, he walked past the guest halt stele.

Smoke of all colors rumbled as they formed into a flash of blood light, spreading out.

Fang Yuan looked around, finding that the treasures in the crystal walls were better than the previous segment by a tier.

"Oh? This is..."

Fang Yuan's gaze froze for a second as he saw a rank five strength path Gu worm inside the crystal wall.

He was overjoyed.

Chapter 560: Crucial problem

Fang Yuan had just taken a step past the guest halt stele and a pleasant surprise welcomed him.

A borrow strength Gu appeared in front of him.

This was a rank five strength path Gu, it was almost completely extinct and was even more rare than all-out effort Gu. It could not be used by itself, but instead had to be used together with other Gu worms.

When matched with sky strength Gu, it could allow the Gu Master to borrow the strength of the sky. When matched with earth strength Gu, the Gu Master could borrow the strength of the earth. With fire strength Gu, it allowed the Gu Master to borrow strength from fire. With water strength Gu, the Gu Master could take gain strength from water flow.

"My killer move four arm wind king uses wind overlord Gu and tyrant strength Gu. The combination of these two Gu was a substitute for borrow strength Gu, but their effects are not even fifty percent of borrow strength Gu. With this borrow strength Gu, I can raise my killer move to a whole new level!" Fang Yuan was truly happy.

Of course, borrow strength Gu still needed to be matched with other Gu worms.

By now, sky strength Gu was already extinct. But earth strength Gu, fire strength Gu, water strength Gu, wind strength Gu and so on were still widely circulated.

However, the usage of these Gu worms had already side-tracked from their original use.

Earth strength Gu was now frequently used to raise the fertility of the soil to help the Gu Masters in agriculture, or was used together with wood path Gu.

Fire strength Gu was used by some fire path Gu Masters as a support Gu that could slightly increase the strength of fire path Gu worms. Water strength, wind strength, lightning strength and so on were also used similar.

Fang Yuan approached the crystal wall and took out close to ten spring egg Gu to exchange for the borrow strength Gu.

Past the guest halt stele, he could only exchange for the treasures he wanted.

Fang Yuan continued to walk forward.

The treasures in the crystal wall here were clearly a level or two higher than before.

Meteor rain Gu, star lightning speed Gu, wind fog hair Gu, stellar fire prairie Gu, water curtain skyflower Gu...

Rank five Gu which were extremely rare in the outside world could be seen everywhere here. Instead, it was rank four Gu that were very rare in here. But any rank four Gu that appeared here were bound to be very rare and precious among the rank four Gu, their value and strength comparable to common rank five Gu.

Fang Yuan's gaze swept through the treasures, the blood flame light covering him was wearing down non-stop.

This blood flame light was a barrier protecting him. Once it completely disappeared, he would be detected by Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and be eradicated instantly.

"Before this protection disappears, I need to find that owner token!"

As time passed, Fang Yuan gradually started to feel anxious.

These Gu he used to disguise his identity and deceive Eighty-Eight True Yang Building were not easy to refine, moreover the costs in refining them were considerable. One of the main material was a thousand jin of Huang Jin family blood which required ninety-eight long steps of purification.

Now, Imperial Court contest had already ended; it was even more difficult for Fang Yuan to get these blood in large amounts.

What was even worse was a fork actually appeared in this long crystal corridor!

Fang Yuan could not help stopping to think about it carefully.

Which path was the one he needed to take?

At this moment, the image of the central continent Gu Immortals attacking Imperial Court blessed land in the previous life became a great help to Fang Yuan.

He chose the left path and moved rapidly through it.

Here, the treasures that appeared in the crystal wall were of a level higher in their worth. There were only rank five Gu with no more rank four Gu to be found, and at the same time, there were rare rank five Gu as well.

Fang Yuan quickly walked forward while sweeping his gaze over the treasures, suddenly his gaze stopped: "Found it!"

An owner token was sealed in the crystal wall, just at the knee height of Fang Yuan.

This owner token was the doing of central continent Gu Immortals.

A tall tree attracts the wind; Imperial Court blessed land had existed tall till now which had already attracted the attention of Gu Immortals of all regions. Central continent Gu Immortals had begun their plan hundreds of years ago.

The owner token was generally held by the alliance leader and would self-destruct once it left Imperial Court blessed land.

Close to a millennium ago, central continent Gu Immortals spent a lot of effort to scheme from the dark, not only did they bribe that time's alliance leader, it is rumored that they also used an Immortal Gu.

Using the power of the Immortal Gu, they tampered with the owner token which then hid inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, becoming a key for the future, waiting for the opportunity to use it.

In Fang Yuan's past life, central continent Gu Immortals first started the five regions battle and were able to create the opportunity not long after, finally breaching Imperial Court blessed land.

Imperial Court blessed land was an arrangement set by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable, breaching this place was much more difficult than breaching other blessed lands.

But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already passed away while central continent Gu Immortals had painstakingly brewed their scheme for close to a millennium, achieving some success in the end.

However, in this life, this owner token landed in Fang Yuan's hand.

The process of exchanging for this owner token was extremely smooth. But it would not be easy to make the token usable for him.

This was the final, crucial step.

Fang Yuan's expression turned solemn as he sat cross-legged on the ground and concentrated.

Gu worms after Gu worms moved at his will and struck the owner token non-stop.

Ding ding ding...

A pleasant music sounded from the collision, and the owner token gradually floated into the air. Every strike would create a layer of halo over the owner token.

When it was covered with thirty-eight halo, the dull color on its surface suddenly dispersed and revealed the words - 'owner token'.

The halo then started to burst like air bubbles.

The owner token lost its buoyancy and fell down, and was immediately caught by Fang Yuan.

He quickly bit his finger and let the blood drip onto the owner token.

The moment his blood seeped into the owner token, the metallic token suddenly became a translucent glass. Fang Yuan had seen Hei Lou Lan's owner token and was able to immediately be aware that there was a great difference between his token and the original owner token.

"The methods I used just now was in reference to my past life's video, awakening the true appearance of this owner token. It seems this is very possibly the strength of an Immortal Gu and also, only Immortal Gu can tamper with owner token while avoiding the detection of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building." Fang Yuan looked at the glass owner token and sank into contemplation.

After a dozen or so breaths, the blood flame light covering him thoroughly dispersed.

The world seemed to have gone mute at this moment as Fang Yuan could clearly hear his heartbeats.

"Safe and sound." The sound of his heartbeats gradually disappeared, Fang Yuan slowly stood up and let out a breath of turbid air.

"Success." He mumbled while clenching his left fist in excitement, but he found his voice was somewhat hoarse. At the same time, his whole body was soaked with sweat and he felt some dizziness.

Truly activating this owner token and making it recognize him was not easy at all. It was even more difficult than refining a rank five Gu.

If there was even a slight mistake, it might have very well been impossible to reprieve.

Fang Yuan endured the enormous mental pressure and finally succeeded.

"Now, as long as I hold the glass owner token, I can freely enter the treasure room. There is no need for any high grade evaluation!"

Holding the owner token was equivalent to being in control of a small part of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Fang Yuan tested the owner token and almost instantly, Hei Lou Lan's group's figures appeared in his mind.

After crossing the fifty-fourth round, they had already charged to sixty-first round. Right now, they were having a fierce fight with a golden-white tiger phantom.

A true golden-white tiger was a desolate beast level existence.

The golden-white tiger phantom possessed the aura of a desolate beast and was pressing down Hei Lou Lan's group.

Hei Lou Lan had numbers on his side, but their defeat was imminent.

Fang Yuan looked closely for a while and inwardly commented: 'If there is no accident, Hei Lou Lan and his group will only be able to last for less than forty-five minutes, before they have to retreat. I don't have a lot of time!"

Although Fang Yuan entered the treasure room, as long as the possessor of the owner token walked out of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, he would also have to leave.

Fang Yuan might have the glass owner token now, and could stay or leave according to his will. But it was not good to expose it at present.

"Just the glass owner token is still far from enough. I still need to find that loophole and completely blow it up; this will create a great hole in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and I will then be able to freely take away the treasures in the crystal wall."

The glass owner token shook slightly, and the next moment, Fang Yuan disappeared on the spot.

"This should be the central control room!"

When Fang Yuan opened his eyes, he had arrived at a secret room.

The secret room was round with its walls flickering with starlight, and a white jade round table on the center. There was an exquisite model of the whole Imperial Court blessed land on the round table, just like a military sand table.

Not only did it depict mountains and rivers and the sacred palace at the center, even the small towers in the blessed land were clearly visible.

Fang Yuan sent out a Gu worm which flew to air and turned into black smoke that fell down to the sand table.

The sand table was contaminated by the black smoke and rapidly turned into black color.

The black color gradually condensed, forming into a large patch of sticky liquid that slowly flowed on the sand table.

Fang Yuan looked at a spot where the black liquid had formed a funnel shape and as if there was a hole below, the surrounding black liquid was slowly entering it.

"Found it, this is that hole! Now, I just need to enlarge this hole and refine the glass owner token into a one-edge owner token. With a one-edge owner token, I can even control a floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building at will! Eh?"

Right at this time, Fang Yuan's movements paused as his eyes rigidly stared at the hole on the sand table.

The whole sand table was covered by the thick black oil like sticky liquid, thus Fang Yuan had not been able to see immediately. But now that he had looked for a while, he suddenly discovered this hole was none other than Di Qiu inheritance site!

"What is going on here? Could it be Di Qiu inheritance is also a concealed move set up by central continent Gu Immortals before like the glass owner token?!"

Fang Yuan was shocked.

But he quickly calmed down and became aware of the shortcomings to this assumption.

"No, wrong. If this was a concealed move prepared to breach the blessed land, then how do I explain that cipher and the clues from the grey-white stone slab? These clues are clearly the clues to the inheritance."

Fang Yuan's eyes flashed with bright light.

Right now, the scene in his previous life could not give him any help.

"Could it be that central continent Gu Immortals also discovered this inheritance, but they could not decipher the secret phrase and so are using the inheritance this way? No, this is wrong too. Thinking from their side, if they discovered this inheritance which very likely contained an Immortal Gu, they would definitely be moved. If that is so, then that means that they did not obtain any clues to the inheritance but only discovered this hole?"

"Of course, there is also another possibility that they were not able to decipher the secret of the inheritance, but as breaching the blessed land was an important matter, they chose to break this hole in the end. But if so, Di Qiu inheritance would also be destroyed!"

Fang Yuan thought of this and that, feeling the existence of these two probabilities. But he did not have conclusive evidence now so he could not confirm them.

He hesitated.

In case he used the methods in his previous life's scene and burst open this hole, then Di Qiu inheritance would definitely be destroyed.

But if he did not do so and chose to preserve Di Qiu inheritance, his plans for Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would stop here.

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's worth is much higher than Di Qiu inheritance. This is hopeless, I can only abandon Di Qiu inheritance. But the person who made this arrangement is really amazing, to actually be able to tamper with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangement... hmm? Wait a second!"

Fang Yuan's mind suddenly shook as he thought of an extremely crucial problem!

Chapter 561: Deciphering the code

This was a very obvious problem, but normal people would easily overlook it.

Why did this mysterious Gu Immortal go through such great trouble, brave enormous risk, tamper with and use Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangement to set up their inheritance?

"Thinking from their perspective, if I was this Gu Immortal, why would I insist on digging out Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's loophole to set up my inheritance? I could set up one by myself perfectly by just spending a little effort!"

"Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is a rank eight Immortal Gu house and was personally arranged by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable. There was truly an enormous risk in using its loophole. If I wanted to wholeheartedly leave behind an inheritance, there would be absolutely no need to go so far and intentionally take risks. Unless..."

Fang Yuan's eyelids drooped as a cold light flashed quickly past his dark pupils.

"Unless — the inheritance required such an arrangement!"

The moment he thought of this, the fog in Fang Yuan's mind seemed to be pushed aside by two large hands.

Humans always have objectives in doing things.

Only an enormous objective could make a Gu Immortal take such huge risks!

Maybe this Gu Immortal did not like Giant Sun Immortal Venerable or had hatred against him. But Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had already passed away for countless years, so this possibility was close to zero.

Removing the factor of emotions, then there was only the factor of benefits.

"For this benefit, the mysterious Gu Immortal was willing to brave the fatal danger of messing with Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's arrangement. What in the world did they intend to use Eighty-Eight True Yang Building for?"

Fang Yuan involuntarily thought of the information Lang Ya land spirit gave him.

He had already studied this information hundreds and thousands of times. Even on the day before the large battle of the Imperial Court contest, he had been studying non-stop.

Even after reading so many times, every time he read it again or recalled it, he could not help having a feeling of admiration.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was indeed of exquisite workmanship, its design was spectacular.

This was a fantasy turned into reality, it was a miracle!

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was essentially an Immortal Gu house.

Back then, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable made plans for his descendants and took the initiative to find Long Hair Ancestor, requesting him to refine an everlasting inheritance treasure.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's demand was too great, and as such Long Hair Ancestor had to rack his brains and think painstakingly for a hundred or so days to meet the standard.

One day, he suddenly had an inspiration and took an alternate way, coming up with a unique method.

The Immortal Gu house was truly overly enormous. Long Hair Ancestor could only settle for the second best option, and divide it into countless sub-bodies which were the small towers.

The quantity of these small towers reached untold numbers and attracted wild Gu worms for ten years.

As the ten year period neared its end, they would sink one after another, sacrificing the wild Gu inside and simultaneously resonate with the blizzard outside to form a heavenly power.

The heavenly power condensed bit by bit to generate a qualitative change, condensing into a floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

As layers and layers formed, they would finally become the complete Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!

From a different perspective: every time Eighty-Eight True Yang Building formed, it was the process of a new refinement.

Long Hair Ancestor was indeed worthy of being known as the number one refinement path immortal of all times, his Gu refinement attainment had already crossed the realm of mortal into a realm of divinity. It was already not easy for ordinary Gu Masters to refine a Gu successfully. It was the same for Gu Immortals as well when they refine Immortal Gu.

But Long Hair Ancestor had already surpassed the limits of the normal Gu refinement to a level of perfection.

So did Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's refinement succeed?

In truth, the refinement was not a complete success.

If a general standard was applied, the truly complete Eighty-Eight True Yang Building would be a tower that would exist for eternity in the blessed land, towering over the sacred palace.

However, this standard was too difficult to fulfill.

Back when Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had mentioned it, Long Hair Ancestor's brows had furrowed deeply and had immediately said: If the refinement truly succeeds, then this Immortal Gu house would be at rank nine realm!

What was the meaning of a rank nine Immortal Gu?

The Gu in legends like strength Gu, wisdom Gu, fate Gu and so on were all rank nine Immortal Gu. These Immortal Gu were priceless even among the priceless and had already vanished, their radiance only being revered in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

Just like rank nine Gu Immortals who were given the title of 'venerable'; throughout the boundless history, only ten of them appeared.

There had never been a rank nine realm Immortal Gu house, but Giant Sun Immortal Venerable did not give up on his request.

Long Hair Ancestor could only agree to the request, fearing the might of an Immortal Venerable.

Finally, he thought of a solution that was not a solution, to create a 'rank nine Immortal Gu house that could only exist for a short period of time' — thus, Eighty-Eight True Yang Building ended up being at rank eight realm.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable had not been pleased with it, but his attitude changed after inspecting it, and was full of praise as he said: Eighty-Eight True Yang Building itself holds the secret of a mortal becoming a Gu Immortal!

Why did he say that?

The reason was that a mortal had to cross over the hurdle of the three elements to become a Gu Immortal.

Element of heaven. Heaven above, with immeasurable might, mysterious and mighty.

Element of earth. Earth below, virtuous, stable and profound.

Element of man. Man in the center, the spirit of all beings, exerting oneself to soar above.

Mortal were like tiny insects, and only by connecting with heaven and earth, could they be free of their mortal state and make themselves go through a fundamental evolution.

And Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's formation made use of these three elements.

The Imperial Court contest was to spread the element of man. The ten year blizzard was a cruel and vicious element of heaven. The small towers sinking into the ground were borrowing the blessed land's element of earth.

The three elements combine into one, and a mortal becomes an immortal.

The three elements combined to form Eighty-Eight True Yang Building that plundered northern plains' resources to give rise to Huang Jin family's super tribes, and allowed Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's influence to be inextinguishable for countless years.

"Wait a moment, don't tell me?!"

Fang Yuan's body shook slightly as a bright light blossomed in his eyes.

"The small towers are a part of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the mysterious Gu Immortal who set up Di Qiu inheritance broke this small tower and created a hole."

"When the hole formed, according to the principle of the refinement of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, there should be a backflow of heavenly power to condense into a new small tower."

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was a rank eight Immortal Gu house and was very difficult to destroy. But the small towers could be easily destroyed, this was like the difference between a Gu Immortal and mortals. Thus, when Giant Sun Immortal Venerable arranged these small towers in the blessed land, he used the strength of Imperial Court blessed land to protect them tightly and isolate them from most sources of damage.

Long Hair Ancestor was the number one immortal in refinement path, so he naturally had considered the situation of the small towers being destroyed. Thus, every ten years, during the time of the formation of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's main body, the condensed heavenly power would first flow back to repair the gaps in the small towers before condensing into the main body.

However!

"Di Qiu inheritance had already been set up for many years, but the small tower over it has still not been repaired. Moreover, this mysterious Gu Immortal used some method to seal up this gap and deceive Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. I understand now, the reason they did this should be none other than to make use of the heavenly power that condenses into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building!"

"Light in the soil, shine up to a hundred thousand feet high, swimming in the sky for a hundred li, praising plum fragrant snow... it seems this secret phrase is the method of Gu refinement!"

In fact, Fang Yuan had guessed this before.

However, he did not have conclusive evidence back then.

Now, although it was still a guess, but after testing and probing it, Fang Yuan was much more confident.

Time always seemed to move faster when one was pondering deeply.

Hei Lou Lan and his group were defeated by the golden-white tiger phantom, and were sent out of the tower. To not attract any suspicion, Fang Yuan could only use the glass owner token to get out of the tower.

A group of people suddenly appeared at the entrance of the first floor of the tower.

"They have appeared, the lords have returned!"

"Subordinate greets lord tribe leader and all the lords."

The guards sitting there, who were of Hei tribe's direct line of descent, immediately came forward to greet.

Hei Lou Lan and the group all looked battered and exhausted or were covered in blood.

Although they had failed, they had made much progress and gains as they were even able to push forward for over ten rounds.

However, the situation this time was special, Hei Lou Lan and others' gazes landed on Fang Yuan, revealing the intent of probing, curiosity, doubts and investigating.

"Hahaha, everyone worked hard and contributed highly for this expedition, especially Wolf King who can be said to be the number one in contribution this time. After returning, organize a banquet immediately, we will celebrate for three days!" Hei Lou Lan laughed loudly and lightly patted Fang Yuan's shoulder, showing off their close relationship.

High grade evaluation made Fang Yuan's worth rise by another level in his heart.

"I gained some insight from this trip, I need to undergo closed cultivation to consolidate them. I hope Lord Hei Lou Lan would not blame me." Fang Yuan lightly smiled and directly turned down Hei Lou Lan.

Hei Lou Lan's smile froze before immediately recovering the next moment and said it was not a problem, showing the disposition of a magnanimous leader.

As for how furious he was inwardly, or how much the others were envious, Fang Yuan did not care. He wanted to return now to study the secrets of Di Qiu inheritance meticulously.

Six days later.

Fang Yuan pushed open the window and looked down at the sacred palace, his eyes flashing with a light of joy.

He had fully solved the secret of Di Qiu inheritance.

One only required a correct direction for such riddles and it would only be a matter of time.

Just as Fang Yuan guessed before, the cipher was a recipe for refining Immortal Gu.

The mysterious Gu Immortal who arranged the inheritance used the loophole of the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, borrowing the power which would condense into Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to refine an Immortal Gu.

As long as one followed the words of the secret phrase and refined the Gu step by step, even a mortal Gu Master could refine it successfully.

It was because the Immortal Gu refinement was not relying on the mortal Gu Master's power, but was borrowing from the strength of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

But as for what this Immortal Gu was, Fang Yuan did not know and could only make conjectures from the secret phrase.

"This Gu Immortal should very likely be from central continent. The Gu refinement method is filled with central continent's style. And adding on my previous life's video, this inheritance should be in the form of a chain and what I obtained was likely only a part of it." Fang Yuan estimated in his heart.

In Fang Yuan's past life, central continent Gu Immortals planned to use this loophole to breach Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. They should have discovered some preceding clue to this inheritance.

This was not strange.

Many Gu Masters, when setting inheritances, would arrange them step by step, and leave behind clues after clues. If the fated ones had enough ability, they could inherit the whole inheritance. If their ability was not up to par, they could only receive a part of the benefits.

Central continent Gu Immortals should have obtained the preceding clues to this inheritance and should not have known the latter part of the secret phrase.

Otherwise, they definitely would not waste the chance of obtaining an Immortal Gu.

And what Fang Yuan accidentally obtained was only the latter part. Without the preceding clues, it became extremely incomprehensible. If not for Fang Yuan having the intel of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and his previous life's memories, he would not have been able to comprehend it even if he was given ample time.

Chapter 562: Reason for being cowardly and afraid of death?

"Speaking of it, this central continent Gu Immortal is truly amazing, seeing through Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's hole and also using such an idea. Clearly, they were also a refinement path master... no, to reach this step, they have to be at least a grandmaster in refinement path!"

"They actually left behind an Immortal Gu as an inheritance. This is truly an immortal treasure! They put the clue in fake grey-white stone slabs, such creativity and innovation was really amazing. I wonder what kind of successor they want to choose..."

The most crucial problem of the secret phrase was resolved, but even more questions popped out.

Fang Yuan shook his head and cleared up his disorganized thoughts.

"No matter what, this inheritance is related to an Immortal Gu, I need to give it a try with all my effort. Now, it should take over half a month at least to prepare the relevant Gu worms..."

Light in the soil, shine up to a hundred thousand feet high, swimming in the sky for a hundred li, praising plum fragrant snow — these four phrases might be simple, but Fang Yuan would not have been able to decipher them without his refinement path master attainment.

Based on Fang Yuan's current comprehension, he needed over two hundred Gu worms to borrow the force of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and refine the mysterious Immortal Gu; among them were twenty-eight rank four and rank five Gu worms.

And this number was only enough for one use.

Fang Yuan, in preparing the Gu refinement, would have to make at least three times the preparatory materials to prevent any errors during the Gu refinement process which could lead to failure. And in case he failed, he would require spare Gu worms.

Sixteen days later.

In the hall, Hei Lou Lan showed the demeanor of the 'Black Tyrant' to the fullest, shouting fiercely and wantonly venting out the anger in his heart.

The elders who were scolded and even beaten by Hei Lou Lan could not raise their heads and were quiet out of fear.

Ever since Hei Lou Lan entered Imperial Court blessed land, his temper had been getting increasingly violent. After Eighty-Eight True Yang Building opened, this change intensified and his temper became like a barrel of gunpowder, berating and beating his subordinates at the slightest pretext. As of today, there were already three Hei tribe elders who were heavily beaten by him and were still bedridden.

"Lord tribe leader, it is not us slacking in our duty, but this seventy-eighth round is truly too difficult. The golden-white tiger phantom guardian is too strong and has thirty percent of the desolate beast's powers. With our mortal bodies, no matter how much we try, we can only harass it and have no way to harm it heavily. Moreover, if the golden-white tiger goes on the offense, our Gu Masters would not be able to resist it."

Hei Pei, the head of the elders, waited for Hei Lou Lan to finish venting his anger, before cautiously speaking.

Hei Lou Lan glanced at him and cursed: "Your words are bullshit! Golden-white tiger phantom might have strong attacking prowess, but as long as we all unite and disregard the sacrifices, we can definitely defeat it before the time limit! You guys are all afraid of difficulties, tarnishing my Hei tribe's reputation of bravery!"

The elders shrunk their heads after being scolded, not daring to say anything.

Hei Lou Lan's words were actually not without reason.

It was already not the first time in dealing with the golden-white tiger phantom.

If they truly disregarded sacrifices, and people were willing to be cannon fodder and fought to give others an opportunity, even at the cost of their own lives under the claws of the golden-white tiger phantom, then Hei tribe's offense, although powerless, would accumulate with time, and could be like groups of ants biting an elephant, eventually defeating the golden-white tiger phantom.

But the truth of the matter was when the golden-white tiger phantom attacked, everyone feared for their life and was afraid of going forward, causing Hei Lou Lan's advancement in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to stop at this round, unable to progress any further.

Hei Lou Lan's shouts kept on resounding in the hall.

Right now, no one dared to antagonize this furious Black Tyrant who did not spare even his tribesmen.

After Hei Lou Lan vented his anger once more, he sat down on the main seat with a gloomy expression.

His heart was filled with pent-up fury, especially when he looked at these silent elders, he felt sick to his stomach.

Besides anger, he felt helplessness.

During the Imperial Court contest, these Hei tribe elders had fought bravely and had no fear. But in this place, they were worried for their safety, where did their courage go?

Actually, Hei Lou Lan understood.

During the Imperial Court contest, rewards and punishments were openly issued; people fought to be the first, competing for fame and fortune, to be stronger and to survive.

However, in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the rewards for passing the stages would go to the tribe leader which caused everyone to have very little incentive to charge through the rounds.

The most important reason was that they had already won the Imperial Court contest and there were no more threats to their survival, and there were also many inheritances outside the sacred palace. As long as they survived this period of time, they were bound to have an even more radiant future when they exited Imperial Court blessed land.

Only fools would do things like abandoning their lives and acting as cannon fodder to help someone else!

Hei tribe's elders were all extremely crafty.

Preserving their lives was most important, and besides that, so what if they were scolded and beaten by Hei Lou Lan? Even if Hei Lou Lan heavily injured them and they had to lie on the bed, it was nothing compared to dying.

Hei Lou Lan was aware of the elders' thoughts.

'Even if I am a rank five expert, I cannot control their will. Once there is no unity, it will not be easy to lead even if the tribe is stronger. Never mind...'

Hei Lou Lan sighed inwardly and spoke: "Since it is so, then I can only open up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building and gather everyone's strength to charge through the rounds."

Requesting outside help required guest tokens.

But right now, besides Hei tribe, there were also other Huang Jin tribes like Ye Lui tribe, Ma tribe and so on in Imperial Court blessed land.

One could imagine that once Hei Lou Lan opens up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to them, these people would definitely charge forward madly. With this, they could be the cannon fodder.

After hearing Hei Lou Lan's words, the elders exchanged veiled communication with each other through their gazes. This method allowed them to stay away from the vanguard position, but they were somewhat unwilling.

The first elder Hei Pei stepped forward: "Lord tribe leader, this is a clever method but we need to keep up our guard. These people might have the old ancestor's bloodline running through them, but they are not of our Hei tribe. When they pass the rounds and get the benefits, I am afraid they won't hand over anything."

"That's right, lord." Elder Hei Qi Sheng also added, "Our Hei tribe racked our brains and suffered great difficulties before we were able to emerge as the winner in this time's Imperial Court contest. This Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is ours, why should we share it with outsiders?"

"There are precedents of such actions, but when looking at history, those were all weak tribes who won by fluke and did not have the ability to get through the stages, so they had no choice but to mobilize other Huang Jin tribes. Our Hei tribe is strong and has many competent experts, how can we seek other's help?"

"Hmph!" Hei Lou Lan raised his brows, "Since our troops are strong, why are we not able to challenge even one golden-white tiger phantom? You group of dogshit trash, only cherishing your lives dearly, but when I want to bring in outsiders to stake their lives for us, you are afraid of them taking the benefits? Do you think there is such a good thing in this world?"

Different from these elders, Hei Lou Lan was already feeling very anxious.

He was the possessor of Great Strength True Martial physique and must obtain a strength path Immortal Gu to advance to Gu Immortal.

Only by becoming an immortal, could he alleviate this threat to his life.

However, whether Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had any strength path Immortal Gu or which floor the strength path Immortal Gu was on, both were unknown.

As such, he wholeheartedly wanted to break the conventions and bring in the situation where the Huang Jin tribes cooperate to get through the rounds. Each round he passed would allow the owner token with him to advance and make it more convenient to proceed onwards.

Although they were defeated repeatedly at this round, Hei Lou Lan thought of it as a good opportunity.

He took the chance to create difficulty and shouted once again.

His furious shouts resounded in the hall, causing everyone's ears to hear buzzing.

Due to Hei Lou Lan's might and terrifying reputation, the elders could only choose to compromise.

The first elder Hei Pei said with worry: "Opening Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to others is like letting in a torrent, once its momentum increases, it will definitely cause disastrous losses. I suggest we place some limits. Wolf King Chang Shan Yin was a lesson that is right before us."

These words immediately caused an intense commotion among the elders.

Someone said with a bitter tone: "Right, Wolf King is really a hoodlum, he is hogging the benefits all to himself. Right now, he is in closed-door cultivation, maybe inwardly laughing to himself!"

Someone scoffed with disdain: "Eighty-Eight True Yang Building belongs to Hei tribe, we let him participate to tackle the round because we thought highly of him. But he repays us like this, hmph, what dogshit northern plains hero, he is just an ungrateful thief!"

Someone said with a cold and gloomy gaze: "In my opinion, when we open up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building this time, we should not bring Chang Shan Yin in. This will teach him a lesson!"

Hei Lou Lan coldly snorted, he was naturally greatly dissatisfied with Fang Yuan's behavior. If it was someone else, he would have already taken action.

But Chang Shan Yin was not a measly character, his bearing in the decisive battle of the Imperial Court contest was still deeply engraved in Hei Lou Lan's mind.

If he said he was not afraid, he would be lying.

However, openly excluding Chang Shan Yin was not appropriate as well. Not only would that be a display of narrow-mindedness, in case Wolf King was offended, even if Chang Shan Yin did not make a move, he still had the azure wolf group.

"First elder Hei Pei, since you mentioned this, then let's hear it." Hei Lou Lan spoke.

Hei Pei slightly smiled and said with confidence: "There is no problem in opening Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to the outside from tomorrow. But before entering the building, no matter who it is, they would need to pay a fee. There will only be a quota of eight hundred entrants every day and the fee for entrance will increase according to the order of the entrants. At the same time, they must use poison vow Gu and agree to give fifty percent of all their gains to Hei tribe."

He paused before continuing: "As for outsiders that want to enter the tower, they need to pay a high price to purchase our guest tokens!"

Every elder present at the scene immediately had bright gazes as they praised this suggestion.

Hei Lou Lan swept over the scene once before leaning back on his chair, slowly closing his eyes: "Alright, this matter shall be done as Hei Pei says."

Hei Pei was exulted: "Lord tribe leader is wise and powerful, thank you lord tribe leader for your appreciation."

The news of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building opening to the outside spread and immediately caused a huge sensation in the sacred palace.

Countless people rushed to the place of registration; one side cursed Hei tribesmen for their ruthlessness in asking such a greatly high fee, while another side paid generously and even fought others for a quota to enter.

Fang Yuan observed indifferently, but he was inwardly happy.

Right now, inheriting Di Qiu inheritance was of the utmost priority to him.

Even if Hei Lou Lan took the initiative to invite him, he would not have been very willing. While the others had their attentions on Eighty-Eight True Yang Building now, it was the perfect time for him to make his move on the inheritance!

Chapter 563: Nature of the Three Inheritances

The night sky of Imperial Court blessed land was covered in silvery light, like silk or fog, it shone down on the land like a vast veil.

A group of azure wolves were running freely in the sky, chasing birds in the air or hunting animals on the ground. They were not hunting for food, it was merely leisure.

Fang Yuan stood above Di Qiu, slowly opening his eyes.

These days, not only did he prepare for the Gu refinement, he even expanded his wolf groups.

Not just the azure wolf group, the land based ordinary wolves, including turtleback wolf, water wolf, night wolf etc, had reached two hundred thousand in numbers.

"The wolf group has previously been spread around a radius of a hundred li, it can be a good method of deterrence. Moreover, the azure wolf group in the sky has already become the symbol of Wolf King, most Gu Masters would understand that Chang Shan Yin is hunting here when they see the wolves, thus they will choose to take a detour."

If they did not detour, it meant that they had ill intentions.

Once these Gu Masters were discovered by the wolves, they would be attacked by them.

Of course, there were innocent people who entered by accident, but Fang Yuan could not care less about them, it is their bad luck if they get killed by wolves.

Fang Yuan turned his gaze towards the sacred palace, although he was far away, he could see the dazzling aurora in the sky.

The sacred palace was shining in bright light once again, it was a beautiful sight — and also the sign that Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was going to materialize the second floor.

This had another meaning in Fang Yuan's case.

The towers sink and countless wild Gu are sacrificed in order to become the mystical power that forms the Immortal Gu house.

This aurora was the accumulation of such power, and it had already reached the point of reaching a qualitative change.

In order to open Di Qiu inheritance, Fang Yuan needed to borrow the strength of this mystical power, and cause it to flow backwards.

"In order to get through the stages, Hei Lou Lan intentionally opened the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to the public, causing everyone to get excited and all Gu Masters to feel moved. Once the news spread, all the Gu Masters outside the sacred palace came and gathered here. Everyone's attention is on the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building now, this is the perfect time for me to open the inheritance!"

Fang Yuan's gaze shone as he smiled, without hesitation, he struck.

"Go." He patted his belly, and thirty-six Gu worms flew out of his aperture.

These Gu were of peculiar shapes. Their bodies were tiny and were half the size of a fingernail, they were like five-pointed stars, giving off a milky white light.

These were rank one little light Gu, a very famous light path assistance type Gu.

As Fang Yuan willed, these little light Gu flew into Di Qiu's cave. At once, the darkness in the cave was lifted.

Fang Yuan summoned another thirteen light fences Gu.

This Gu was rank three, also from the light path. Once activated, they can turn into fences and restrain the target.

The light fences Gu flew into the cave and mixed with the little light Gu, but there were no changes.

Fang Yuan smiled lightly, he waved his hand and three rank five light path Gu came out.

These three Gu were lightning flash Gu that increased speed, unlimited spring light Gu that healed, as well as the attack type heaven blazing spark Gu.

Lightning flash Gu gave off a blue light, it shone like lightning as it flew into the cave.

The motionless Di Qiu finally had some changes.

As if a mechanism was unlocked, the ground and soil around Di Qiu started to expand and connect.

The blue lightning destroyed the little light Gu from before, and became a light-blue glow, having an extremely powerful aura.

But at the same time, the light fences Gu connected with each other and formed light fences that kept the blue lightning in.

The blue light was about to break out, but at this time unlimited spring light flew in and gave off an unlimited jade-green aurora, it was gentle as water, suppressing the blue light and forming a stalemate.

Eventually, the blazing heaven spark Gu flew in and turned into a bright red light, it pierced the green aura and the blue light, going deeper into the cave.

With some loud sounds, the cave entrance slowly closed. In the deep parts of the land, three lights were mixing together, engaging in a mysterious transformation that Fang Yuan could not describe.

Fang Yuan saw this and his heart settled, he knew that he was right. This was the "light in the soil" part of the quote.

Although he was eighty percent sure, he was worried about mistakes. After all, he only had the latter half of the inheritance's clue, the first half was held in the hands of central continent Gu Immortals' hands.

But this latter half described the method to open this inheritance.

Fang Yuan used his foundation as a refinement master, and together with Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's information, he forcefully interpreted this code and gained the chance to snatch the inheritance midway.

About an hour later, the sounds from under the ground became softer.

But the ground became hotter, even though Fang Yuan was wearing northern plains' deer leather shoes, it could not isolate this heat.

The hole in the ground slowly opened, as the light was gone, leaving pure darkness inside.

Fang Yuan saw this and he became elated.

After 'light in the soil', it was 'shine up to a hundred thousand feet high'. If interpreted literally, it would be a huge mistake.

This quote was a test, to test the refinement ability of the Gu Master.

The quote was regarding refinement path, 'shine up to a hundred thousand feet high' was not just a description of the scenery, it also described the steps for the refinement process!

Fang Yuan was not flustered or worried, he threw two defensive rank five shine back spike Gu, three investigative type high observation Gu, one attack type ten thousand heart piercing arrow Gu, and nine assistance type nine feet flame Gu.

Only to see that inside the cave, grey-yellow smoke was rumbling but did not ooze out. The sounds of chirping birds or flying arrows, shrieking sounds that pierced the air came from within the smoke.

This scene lasted for seven minutes, until darkness returned again.

The ground closed again, as the cave vanished.

This time, Di Qiu no longer gave off heat, but instead cold air was seeping, causing Fang Yuan's legs to turn stiff from the cold.

Fang Yuan breathed out a sigh, turning his gaze towards the sacred palace.

"If my guess is correct, the sacred palace is going to become chaotic now..."

At this moment, in the sacred palace.

At a side hall, the secret door concealed by trees opened.

An elderly man with snow-white hair walked out with a middle aged Gu Master.

"Old sir, please take care." First elder Hei Pei brought Tai Bai Yun Sheng out from the secret door and patted his chest: "Don't worry, with me here, you are sure to have a guest token!"

Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed: "Since elder Hei Pei is making a promise, I am sure it will succeed. Of course I am assured, you do not have to send me off, goodbye."

"Goodbye." First elder Hei Pei placed his fist by his chest as he bowed, seeing Tai Bai Yun Sheng turn around the corner and vanishing from his vision under the concealment of the trees.

"The allure of an Immortal Venerable inheritance is really huge, to think that even Tai Bai Yun Sheng came to bribe me." Hei Pei sighed.

Ever since Hei Lou Lan opened up the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, elder Hei Pei who was in charge of this matter became extremely popular. Every day, all sorts of people came to visit him in secret, some used their relationships while others talked about and tried to obtain friendship, there were people who bribed him and people who tried to attract him sexually.

But Tai Bai Yun Sheng's visit was a shock to Hei Pei.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng had a huge reputation, he was the number one healer in northern plains, he saved countless people and was an extremely righteous man with great character, his influence was great.

Hei Pei had not expected Tai Bai Yun Sheng to bribe him of all people.

"In the end, Old Sir Tai Bai is still a mortal. There are only so many guest tokens, if it was me, I would not be able to resist it either." Hei Pei laughed, raising his head subconsciously towards the top of the sacred palace.

There, an aurora of dazzling lights had condensed into a thick fog.

Within the thick fog, the second layer of the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was already visible.

"In no time, the second layer will materialize." Not far away, Tai Bai Yun Sheng raised his head and looked.

The colorful aurora shone on his white hair and his wrinkled face.

Tai Bai Yun Sheng was in a daze, an event deep within his memories resurfaced.

That day, the sunset was bright like a fire, burning in the sky.

This was the fourteen year old Tai Bai Yun Sheng, who had just met the old beggar who changed his life forever.

"Young lad, you gave me a bowl of water, you saved this old beggar's life. What do you want, say it, I will try my best to fulfill your wishes!" The old beggar had messy purple-red hair, he was slightly insane at times, while unconscious sometimes. But when he was awake, his gaze was deep as the ocean, he gave off a disposition that could be etched into a person's memories.

"I want to be a Gu Master!" The young Tai Bai Yun Sheng said.

"What kind of Gu Master do you want to be? Hehehe, I have three complete inheritances! The first can allow you to bathe in flames and step on fire, surpassing mortals. The second can allow you to control wind and the air, roaming the world freely. The third can surpass life and death, allowing you to help the people in the world." The old beggar laughed and his rotten yellow teeth were exposed.

The young Tai Bai Yun Sheng frowned and thought about it, before choosing the third inheritance...

As he snapped out of his daze, returning from the trip to his memory lane, Tai Bai Yun Sheng laughed bitterly, muttering: "In the end, I am a person that is afraid of dying."

When he was young, he did not have such feelings, in fact, he became indifferent after witnessing many situations of death.

When Tai Bai Yun Sheng got old, his healthy body slowly became weak and feeble, he started reminiscing about the times in his youth.

Often, people's thoughts changed with their circumstances.

On Earth, one could not surpass the limits of life and death, they had no choice but to accept it. But here, as long as there was a trace of hope, they would struggle and fight!

Only when he was faced with such a situation, when Tai Bai Yun Sheng became closer and closer to death did he become aware of this great terror!

Because of this, he secretly observed and waited for several rounds, before clearly understanding the situation, deciding to participate in this Imperial Court contest and enter Imperial Court blessed land.

"If I can obtain lifespan Gu from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, I would be able to increase my lifespan. Although lifespan Gu is hard to find, and even harder to buy or sell, I'm sure there are some inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. If in the end, I cannot obtain a lifespan Gu, I can only attempt to ascend to Gu Immortal realm." Tai Bai Yun Sheng evaluated in his heart.

The inheritance the old beggar gave him was outstanding, it was an entire inheritance that allowed one to cultivate all the way to rank six Gu Immortal realm!

The inheritance stated very clearly the method for a mortal to ascend to Gu Immortal realm.

Thus, Tai Bai Yun Sheng was very clear of the risks he had to take to reach Gu Immortal realm.

To advance to Gu Immortal realm, one needed to gather and fuse the elements of heaven, earth, and man. If either of the three aspects were insufficient, they would die and their soul would dissipate.

If he was not desperate, Tai Bai Yun Sheng did not want to ascend to Gu Immortal realm. That was because even if he ascended to Gu Immortal realm, it could not raise his lifespan.

But in Tai Bai Yun Sheng's inheritance, there was hope left for him.

But this hope was very difficult to obtain, he needed to succeed in advancing to Gu Immortal realm for there to be a possibility.

These years, Tai Bai Yun Sheng had been searching for lifespan Gu, but lifespan Gu were created from heaven and earth, they could not be located easily and were hard to catch, Tai Bai Yun Sheng made no progress.

"There should be lifespan Gu inside Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, I can definitely find lifespan Gu there!" Tai Bai Yun Sheng looked at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's figure as he cheered for himself secretly.

But the next moment, his pupils expanded as he saw an unbelievable scene!

Chapter 564: Heavenly Power backflow shocks the Sacred Palace

The whole sacred palace fell into shock and fear.

After a while, a large commotion suddenly rose up.

"This... what the hell is going on?!"

"What happened, why is the aurora shrinking?"

A scene that had never occurred before was happening in everyone's sights.

The second floor that had been gradually condensing into form was slowly becoming fainter. Great amounts of the thick aurora were reducing and becoming lighter at a visible speed.

"What happened?!" Hei Lou Lan's brows furrowed into a knot as he grabbed elder Hei Pei's collar with his thick arm and pulled towards him.

His expression was twisted and his eyes opened with fury as he shouted: "Investigate it! I must know what the hell happened!"

Hei Lou Lan possessed one of the ten extreme physiques - great strength true martial physique. Only by becoming an immortal, could he avoid the pressure of death.

However, for ten extreme physiques to become immortal, they required the help of relevant Immortal Gu.

Hei Lou Lan placed his hopes on Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to find the key to become immortal — a strength path Immortal Gu, so how could he let an accident happen to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building?

Elder Hei Pei's body shivered in fright, Hei Lou Lan asked him to investigate the details, but he was only a mortal, how could he investigate it? What could he investigate? In a sobbing tone, he answered: "This... this subordinate does not know, there were no instances of this happening in historical records..."

"It is getting lighter, it is becoming even more light!" Someone shouted while pointing at Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The aurora became smaller, and the thick light, dimmer.

Many Gu Masters looked up in a daze, panic quickly spreading everywhere.

"Is Eighty-Eight True Yang Building damaged?"

"This is something our Immortal Venerable old ancestor personally arranged."

"Could it be that Eighty-Eight True Yang Building also cannot compete against the flow of the river of time?"

Some had pale expressions while even more covered their heads, their gaze filled with fear.

"They are in chaos." From far away, Fang Yuan looked with an eerie gaze and a cold smile on his face.

Even if he was far away, the panicked shouts in the sacred palace still reached his ears.

The culprit behind this terror glanced at the sacred palace before looking down at Di Qiu cave below.

His gaze shone with a strange light as he praised: "Amazing, truly amazing!"

Fang Yuan had originally estimated that only ten percent at most would be absorbed, but he had never thought when he activated the mechanism, the backflow of the heavenly power would surpass his estimation!

Based on just this, Fang Yuan could tell this Gu Immortal's understanding of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was absolutely not beneath his.

"Who is this mysterious Gu Immortal? What identity do they have? I had a fortuitous encounter, the advantage of rebirth and also the first hand information from Lang Ya land spirit. But how was he or she able to have such a deep understanding of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building?"

Right now, the cave was filled to the brim with light, almost to the point of overflowing, but it was firmly restrained by the layer of black light at the entrance.

The aurora surged freely; the intense light that was brewing inside was becoming more and more vigorous.

Crack...

Cracks started appearing on the first floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Hei Pei and the other elders went pale as they looked at this scene in a daze.

As for the other Gu Masters at the lower floors of the sacred palace, many were already kneeling on the ground, kowtowing non-stop.

Some shouted, some wept and some begged —

"Don't collapse, don't collapse!"

"Old ancestor, what mistake did we commit, why are you punishing us like this?"

"We beg old ancestor to show mercy, please give another chance to us unfilial descendants!"

All these voices entered Hei Lou Lan's ears as he stared at the first floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building rigidly.

The cracks were continuously spreading on the first floor.

Even if Hei Lou Lan was a rank five Gu Master with an extreme physique, an existence at the peak of mortals, right now he was feeling bewilderment, helplessness, hesitation and weakness!

"No, this can't go on! I cannot allow this to happen!!" Hei Lou Lan shouted in fury, his expression malevolent and his gaze filled with hot fury.

'I have yet to avenge mother! My vengeance! My strength path Immortal Gu!' He screamed in his heart.

Rumble.

A soft sound was heard, but the earth shook!

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's first floor, which was completely condensed, collapsed completely and turned back into the free aurora light.

The light was like a flood that had broken the dam as it gushed out and spread rapidly; in just a few breaths of time, it enshrouded the whole sacred palace and dyed the horizons.

Puff!

Hei Lou Lan's gaze lost its focus as suffocation filled his stomach, he involuntarily spurted out stagnated blood that had flowed in reverse towards his throat.

"No! I won't allow this! Form back right now! Come back!" He opened up his palms and tried to grab the aurora.

And as if it was responding to his effort, the aurora that were gushing out gradually reduced and the surrounding lights also started falling back.

Hei Lou Lan's gaze flashed, a spark of hope had just ignited in him, but was completely gone the next moment.

The aurora light might have gathered back together, but it did not condense back to the image of the first floor. The light continue to reduce as if a giant incorporeal beast was swallowing it.

"No, don't..." Far away, Tai Bai Yun Sheng mumbled, his expression becoming spiritless.

"Do the heavens want my Hei tribe dead?" First elder Hei Pei clutched his hair.

A problem occurred in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building in Hei tribe's hands, this meant Hei tribe was completely finished. Other super forces and Huang Jin tribes would not let them go.

"Heavens, what happened? Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is actually..." Ye Lui Sang grabbed his chest in fear. Near his heart resided the fire path Immortal Gu which was lent by Ye Lui tribe's Supreme Elder Ye Lui Lai before the Imperial Court contest. Right now, this fire path Immortal Gu was trembling non-stop.

Almost at the same time, Fang Yuan's expression also had a slight change.

In his aperture, Spring Autumn Cicada revealed its true body, trembling continuously and was emitting its Immortal Gu aura, causing his rank five aperture to creak from the pressure.

"This is the resonance of the Great Dao in heaven and earth." Fang Yuan was well aware of this.

Man was the spirit of all living beings, Gu was the essence of heaven and earth, a vessel of the Great Dao. If a mortal Gu was said to hold only a tiny fragment of the law of heaven and earth, then an Immortal Gu would hold a corner of the Great Dao, an intact piece of the rules of heaven and earth.

Because of this, there could only be one Immortal Gu of its kind.

Every time an Immortal Gu was born, other Immortal Gu in the surroundings would tremble and respond.

The more closely related or conflicting the law inside Gu worms' bodies are, the stronger the resonance between them, and the greater the extent they would tremble.

"From the extent of Spring Autumn Cicada's trembling, this Immortal Gu that is about to be born is not of the time path." Fang Yuan estimated, but his gaze was tightly looking at the cave without the least bit of negligence.

Inside the cave, the aurora from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was continuously being absorbed before fading away as it nurtured the intense light within.

This intense light was becoming more and more flourishing; the black membrane at the entrance was starting to show signs of not being able to restrain it.

"That'll do. If I don't make a move now, the black membrane will burst and the aurora will shoot to the sky and expose me. It is still a small matter if Hei Lou Lan and the rest are the ones that discover me, but in case it awakens Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's hibernating will, then it will just take one thought from the Immortal Venerable's will to turn me into ashes."

Fang Yuan had endured the impulse to make a move several times before, and now the timing was fully ripe, he made his move, throwing in large numbers of Gu worms.

Gu worms from rank one to rank five from all paths sprinkled down like rain.

This situation looked disorderly and complex, but it actually had a special profoundness to it. The Gu worms were not only divided into separate groups, they even had particularly specific distances from each other, to the extent that some Gu worms fell slightly slower while some fell faster.

This was a high grade technique of Gu refinement called the sprinkler. Gu Masters with natural talent and aptitude could master enslavement path and flying skills. But even the Gu Masters with higher natural talent required thousands of tries before they could display a decent use of the sprinkler technique.

Fang Yuan's attainment in this technique was beyond the level of just a decent performance, and was enough to make other refinement path masters exclaim in surprise.

After the Gu worms sprinkled down, the aurora slowly changed color into that of blue water or the sky, before becoming still.

In the blue light, countless white lights flew like birds and swam like fish. Specks of white light would occasionally gather into a heap and from time to time scatter like stars. Just glancing at this for a moment caused Fang Yuan to feel dizzy.

He quickly moved his gaze towards the sacred palace.

The clamors in the sacred palace had already decreased. After the aurora light enshrouding the sacred palace decreased by around half, the speed of its reduction slowed.

Seeing that no one was paying attention here and the scattered wolf groups were also not sending any battle signals, Fang Yuan inwardly breathed a sigh of relief.

"Everything is going smoothly, it should be the final step now." He was extremely cautious and did not even have the slightest intent of being conceited, instead he was even more vigilant.

Whether it was the history of this world or on Earth, how many cases were there of people failing at the last hurdle?

Moreover, this final step would create a huge commotion and was the step where a problem was most likely to appear.

Fang Yuan slightly flicked his wrist and and a smelly fart Gu that he had been holding lightly flew into the cave.

Immediately a peculiar fragrance spread out of the cave.

The peculiar fragrance flew even without wind, soon spreading out.

"Stopped, it has stopped!" After a while of shock and fear, the Gu Masters in the sacred palace became wild with joy.

"Lord, the aurora has stopped reducing and has begun to slowly increase again!" A Hei tribe elder shouted excitedly, and was kicked by Hei Lou Lan.

"I can see that!" Hei Lou Lan kicked the elder to the ground, his gaze was ruthless but the deep voice could not conceal his joy.

However, his heart was extremely nervous.

The reduction of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's aurora and even the collapse of the floor had never happened before.

What had happened?

Hei Lou Lan's mind was filled with doubts.

He did not know why there was a problem, it caused him to worry greatly. What made Hei Lou Lan even more helpless and indignant was that Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was the work of an Immortal Venerable —"even if I knew where the problem was, I probably would not be able to solve it with just my ability..."

If he was to know that it was all caused by Fang Yuan single-handedly, then he would probably risk his life and tear off the seal placed on him by Immortal Gu Dark Limit, to pit his life against Fang Yuan.

Chapter 565: Everyone with their own intentions

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's shocking change was a traumatic experience for everyone in the sacred palace, countless people were worried, scared and helpless.

Fortunately, the situation stabilized not long after Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's first floor collapsed.

The aurora no longer reduced and was instead beginning to increase again.

Maybe because it was provoked, the speed of this aurora's increase was somewhat faster than before.

Several days later, the thick as water aurora condensed back to the first floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

After it had completely formed, Hei Lou Lan and the others immediately entered it anxiously. Their entry to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building proceeded smoothly.

This made Hei Lou Lan greatly relieved and he gradually calmed down.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was extremely significant to him, he needed to become a Gu Immortal to avenge his mother. As the possessor of one of the ten extreme physiques, Great Strength True Martial physique, his only hope of becoming an immortal was to obtain a strength path Immortal Gu from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

This was depicted in \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>.

For humans to live, it was okay if they did not have strength or even wisdom, but they could not lose hope.

Hei Lou Lan regained the hope of saving his life, his mood gradually turned better as he started to plan his next breakthrough of the hundred rounds.

The first floor of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building had formed anew, so the checkpoints had reset, making Hei Lou Lan's previous efforts turn into smoke; he needed to overcome everything again.

To Hei Pei and the other elders, this was a very good thing.

"This is joy after extreme sorrow, going through the rounds again will allow us to get even more rewards!"

"Maybe that was a small joke by old ancestor Immortal Venerable..."

"Every floor in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building has a hundred rounds with the difficulty increasing sharply at the later rounds. Looking at history, there were very few Imperial Court winners who were able to cross through every round, we should not be optimistic in being able to overcome the final round. As long as we can put all our efforts in passing the earlier rounds, our tribe's strength will rise greatly!"

The elders were filled with joy, but this was bad news to Hei Lou Lan.

There were only two ways for him to obtain a strength path Immortal Gu from Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

First was to get a high grade evaluation and enter the treasure room, then use his bloodline identity to exchange for the Immortal Gu inside.

Second was to pass the final round of every floor which could give him the chance to obtain an Immortal Gu.

To Hei Lou Lan, the first method required him to bring out an equivalently valuable treasure to exchange, and thus was not practical. The only probability of success was in the second method.

Passing through the last few rounds would be extremely difficult. The rounds were reset now; they would have to overcome these rounds again, which no doubt would waste his precious time.

Time waits for no man, once their time was up, they would be sent out of Imperial Court blessed land. If he could not get a strength path Immortal Gu before this happens, Hei Lou Lan would not only be unable to take revenge, but would also have to welcome his death.

For this reason, Hei Lou Lan stubbornly maintained his stance in spite of others' wishes and started recruiting other tribes' Gu Masters, completely opening up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Everyone could casually enter or exit Eighty-Eight True Yang Building free of charge. Other than Hei tribe elders, everyone in the sacred palace was celebrating in joy.

"Hei Lou Lan has a grand demeanour, doing something that no other Lords of Imperial Court have done before. I, Ye Lui Sang, am in deep admiration!" Ye Lui Sang was the first to enter Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, his face covered in a joyful glow.

He was the current tribe leader of Ye Lui tribe and had been a popular candidate to win the prior Imperial Court contest; the tribe's Gu Immortals supported him greatly, not even stinting on lending a fire path Immortal Gu to him.

But he lost in the end and to preserve the fire path Immortal Gu, he had no choice but to side with Hei Lou Lan.

They finally won and succeeded in entering Imperial Court blessed land, but as one of the super forces, he felt that it was a disgrace to be a subordinate of Hei tribe. He was sure to be treated coldly, abandoned and even punished when he returned to the tribe.

"If I can have good gains in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, then I can make up for the earlier mistakes and return grandly to the tribe!" Ye Lui Sang's emotions surged.

"Chang Shan Yin, don't be proud of yourself. As long as you don't become an immortal, I will have a chance. Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is my cornerstone to rise up!" Chang Biao had a cold look in his eyes. He was also among the first batch of experts to enter the tower.

He was not moving alone and had a companion beside him.

It was Sole Blade General Pan Ping.

Previously at Xing Jiu mountain peak, Pan Ping's opportunity had been openly seized by Fang Yuan, which created a lot of indignance in his heart.

Chang Biao learned of this situation and intentionally approached Pan Ping; the two hit it off, becoming partners.

"Go, go, become the vanguards to open my path, use your lives to broaden my way." Hei Lou Lan sneered inwardly, using his owner token while calmly looking at the grand flow of people entering the tower.

After the flow of people had gradually become sparse, Tai Bai Yun Sheng ,with his simple and aged appearance, tall and sturdy physique, clothed in a white robe, he appeared at the top floor of the sacred palace.

"Old Sir Tai Bai." Hei Lou Lan greeted him.

"Lord tribe leader has astonishing mettle, this old man is overwhelmed." Tai Bai Yun Sheng exclaimed in admiration.

He had an elegant demeanour and leisurely attitude. Since everyone could casually enter and exit now, they were not restricted by the quota. He also did not anxiously enter the tower immediately since the rounds which might give lifespan Gu as the reward would definitely be the later rounds.

The two exchanged a few words before Tai Bai Yun Sheng entered the tower.

"There is strength in numbers." Hei Lou Lan was feeling overwhelmed in his mind.

From the information sent by the owner token; in just a short period of time, because of the enormous quantity of Gu Masters, they had successively gotten through the first thirty rounds.

However, at the fortieth round and above, just numbers would not work, they required specific Gu Master experts to cross those rounds.

Pan Ping, Chang Biao, Ye Lui Sang and Tai Bai Yun Sheng made their moves one after another, and were able to push to the fifty-third round. But here, their momentum came to a stop, they encountered a problem; they needed an enslavement path master to pass this round.

"Looks like we must have Wolf King to pass this round." Tai Bai Yun Sheng muttered while stroking his snow-white beard.

In this Imperial Court contest, Fang Yuan's performance left behind an extremely deep impression on everyone. The glorious title of the number one enslavement path Gu Master of this generation in northern plains was already given to him.

Thus, as they encountered this problem, everyone's first thought was Fang Yuan.

"Strange, why don't I see Chang Shan Yin?" Ye Lui Sang looked around him, but could not find Chang Shan Yin.

"Wolf King has been taking his wolves out for hunting these few days." Soon, someone replied.

"Chang Shan Yin is indeed an extraordinary person, we can casually enter and exit Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, but his heart is actually not moved!" Sighs and admiration could be heard among the group.

Pan Ping snorted, speaking in a gloomy tone: "Everyone, please don't forget that our Lord Wolf King has already entered the tower before. According to a reliable source, he passed with high grade evaluation. After he exited the tower, he immediately went to closed-door cultivation and even refused many invitations from tribe leader Hei Lou Lan."

The crowd here knew of the conflict between him and Fang Yuan, and as no one wished to offend this uprising Sole Blade General, the praises and admiration towards Fang Yuan immediately stopped.

Everyone sank into a momentary silence.

Many Gu Master experts also had a slight change in expressions as they showed a somewhat unexpected look on their face.

Pan Ping had a sinister motive in mentioning Fang Yuan had obtained a huge benefit before, leaving it to everyone's ample imagination as to what reward it was, and with this, succeeded in inciting jealousy in their hearts.

If it was before when these people did not have any experience of the enormous benefits provided by Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it would have been slightly better. But now that they had experienced it as they passed the rounds, the fire of envy was lit up in the depths of their hearts!

At this moment, a young Gu Master's voice broke the silence: "Since Eighty-Eight True Yang Building is opened for everyone, everyone can obtain benefits. Lord father being able to obtain the benefits was due to his own ability!"

The crowd's gazes quickly moved towards the source and discovered it was none other than Chang Shan Yin's own son — Chang Ji You.

Immediately, Pan Ping's expression turned sharp as he viciously gazed at Chang Ji You.

Although Chang Ji You was somewhat weaker than Pan Ping, his heart was filled with reverence towards his father, so he did not back down and instead returned Pan Ping's gaze with his own furious gaze.

Killing intent surged in Pan Ping's mind, but he did not dare to make a move. He was unexpected put on the spot by Chang Ji You, a junior!

The person with the most complicated feelings right now was Chang Biao.

He was Chang Ji You's own blood father, but right now, he had to look on at his own son defending his greatest enemy.

Grievance and hatred were surging up non-stop in his heart!

"Cough cough." Tai Bai Yun Sheng stood up to alleviate the tension, "Everyone, let's concentrate on this round."

"At this point, we can only request Lord Wolf King's assistance."

"Among us, Old Sir Tai Bai has the highest reputation; as long as you personally send a letter, Wolf King will definitely accept the request."

The Gu Masters spoke one after another, but Chang Biao and Pan Ping glanced at each other, their hearts filled with worry.

If Wolf King comes, he was sure to pass this round.

But with this, not speaking of the rewards he would get from passing the round, his prestige would increase even more. This was a situation these two were not willing to see.

Pan Ping wanted to speak up but hesitated.

He had the mind to prevent this, but it was not easy getting a chance to interrupt Tai Bai Yun Sheng and make him back down. If Chang Ji You again interrupted here, his face might be lost completely!

Chang Biao was secretly observing Pan Ping's expression and saw Pan Ping opening his mouth several times but did not manage to speak in the end. He inwardly cursed Pan Ping for being a coward, then looked around and signalled a planted agent among the crowd.

This planted agent immediately comprehended the signal and shouted out: "In my opinion, Lord Wolf King is occupied with important matters, it probably won't be easy to invite him. Why don't we request Lord Tang Miao Ming instead? Her enslavement path attainment is already very close to master realm."

Tai Bai Yun Sheng's thoughts could not help being shaken.

He did not have much interaction with Fang Yuan, but he knew deeply of the latter's 'arrogance'. Instead of taking the risk of facing embarrassment from being refused, it might truly be better to let Tang Miao Ming try first.

Flap flap flap....

Groups after groups of blissful snow bats flew from all around like rivers converging into the sea, as they flew towards Di Qiu cave.

The peculiar fragrance had spread for a hundred li.

It was this rich fragrance that had attracted the blissful snow bat groups.

At this stage, the Gu refinement was already approaching the end.

"This is using the lives of beasts as sacrifices, it is a wonderful method that is similar to the workings of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building. It is just that in case of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, the small towers sacrifice the wild Gu to combine their strength."

As he personally put it into practice, Fang Yuan gained an even more profound understanding of this Gu refinement.

The peculiar fragrance gradually dissipated, and without its temptation, the small number of remaining blissful snow bats flew away in disorder.

"It is about to finish!" Fang Yuan's breathing turned rough and his gaze staring at the cave fixatedly, unable to conceal his excited expression.

Chapter 566: Water Pavilion, Resolving the Mystery

By this point, Fang Yuan was overwhelmed with awe.

This mysterious Gu Immortal who created Di Qiu inheritance was definitely a grandmaster in terms of refinement attainment. The entire process was using Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's heavenly power, it was innovative and daring.

Although Fang Yuan was the executor, his role was really that of an assistant.

Refining Gu was hard, refining an Immortal Gu was even harder, it was harder than ascending to heaven!

For a comparable example, a rock has been pushed onto the peak of a cliff by a mysterious Gu Immortal. Fang Yuan is only giving it a final push, easily sending this rock flying towards the ground and crashing, that would be success.

Swish swish swish...

The cave had already formed into a black water spiral. The spiral continued to spin, letting out a weird noise.

Soon after, the tower's tip appeared, followed by its body and base. From within the spiral, a brand new small tower appeared with seemingly countless Gu worms inside.

"Incredible! With the appearance of this tower, the final loophole is gone. Even if someone comes here due to the commotion, they would not find anything." Fang Yuan praised as he sighed.

But...

Although the tower was formed, why has the Immortal Gu not appeared yet?

Fang Yuan's gaze focused, he found that in the small tower, there was a strong light that flickered. There was a weak feeling of connection with it in his heart.

He instantly understood that this was the early stage of the Immortal Gu.

He was about to use this connection to lure the Immortal Gu out.

When suddenly, this strong light escaped like an intangible shadow, towards the southeast direction.

"What happened?" Fang Yuan was shocked in his heart. By now, the four steps of "light in the soil, shine up to a hundred thousand feet high, swimming in the sky for a hundred li, praising plum fragrant snow" had been completed, Fang Yuan did not know what was going on with this sudden change.

"Hei Lou Lan opened up the Eighty-Eight True Yang Building after it formed once more, it was truly a huge move. According to logic, I should be heading to the building to challenge it, that is what a normal person would do..."

The early stage Immortal Gu had flown to a far away place, as Fang Yuan looked at the sacred palace hesitantly.

Although he was outside, he had already made preparations. Be it Chang tribe or Ge tribe, they were sending him real-time information.

The longer Fang Yuan was away from the sacred palace, the more suspicion he would attract. If they were stuck at a stage and needed the Wolf King's power, some people might come to find him and...

It took time for information to be transmitted.

Fang Yuan had no idea that his enemy Chang Biao helped him indirectly.

At this moment, Tang Miao Ming took great risks and was able to successfully pass the round, causing a huge wave of cheering inside the building.

The Immortal Gu was still the most important matter, Fang Yuan only hesitated for a moment before making up his mind, spreading his wings and chasing after the strong light.

This strong light was like a cocoon, it travelled along the ground at an absurd speed. Because of the trees and bushes shielding it from sight, no one took notice of it.

Fang Yuan chased it in the air, trying to hide his traces as he abandoned the wolves behind, travelling stealthily.

As time passed, this strong light became dimmer, but its speed rose.

Although he was rank five peak stage, his speed was not at the peak of the mortal realm, it was very tough chasing the Gu, but he did not lose sight of it.

In the end, it was because this early stage Immortal Gu was not created solely by Fang Yuan.

Different from when he refined divine travel Gu, Fang Yuan was only an assistant this time, it was all due to the backflow of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's heavenly power. He was a mortal, it was already a huge achievement from much effort to be able to gain a connection to the Immortal Gu.

The strong light entered a valley and flew into a waterfall, vanishing.

But using the connection, Fang Yuan could sense that the early stage Immortal Gu was still.

Fang Yuan penetrated the waterfall but collided on the smooth and wet mountain rock. At once, rocks crumbled as water splashed all over the place.

"Weird!"

Fang Yuan was confused, the connection in his heart told him that the strong light was inside this water, but he diverted the water flow and even destroyed this waterfall, and yet he could not find a trace of this Immortal Gu.

"Was my effort in vain? No, there is a huge trick here!"

He flew up and observed the terrain.

This small waterfall had already become a pool, it was extremely ordinary. The valley was nameless, it was not a unique location.

Fang Yuan placed his sights on this pool.

The connection in his heart told him that the early stage Immortal Gu was inside, but even if he went through the waterfall, or controlled the water flow, he could not find it.

At this time, the Gu master's investigative Gu worms would be tested.

Fang Yuan was obviously unresigned, he tried many investigative methods. Although he did not excel in investigation, he controlled Hu Immortal blessed land and had access to treasure yellow heaven, he did not lack rank five mortal Gu.

Only when he tried the fifty-seventh method, after a considerable expense in immortal essence stones did he have a discovery.

Only to see that in the pool, there was the silhouette of a pavilion, it looked like the reflection of the moon in the water.

He entered the water, but did not enter the pavilion.

After trying for several times without success, Fang Yuan gasped, he finally recognised this pavilion after a flash of inspiration struck him.

"Is this the long lost Immortal Gu house — Water Pavilion?"

Immortal Gu were unique, so were Immortal Gu houses.

This Water Pavilion was inferior to Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, it was only rank seven. But it had a great reputation, it was the signature method of the Gu Immortal Shui Ni.

Shui Ni was a rank eight Gu Immortal, the legend that created the water path. She was also the creator of one of the top ten sects in central continent, Spirit Affinity House.

In contrast to the grandness of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building, Water Pavilion could hide itself in the water, becoming like an illusion, it was very mystical. It could move with currents or hide inside mist and fog, flying in the sky. It could even hide in a corner of an iceberg, becoming undetectable.

Without the token to enter the pavilion, Water Pavilion could even repel rank eight Gu Immortals.

But right now, this pavilion was ownerless, its doors were open. Fang Yuan was kept in the dark earlier, but now that he found out the truth, he had the method to enter.

"To enter Water Pavilion, I have to become water. There is a killer move called water spirit transformation, together with a few Gu, I can turn into a water spirit, my battle strength would surge and I would have terrain advantage."

Fang Yuan searched through his memories and found a method.

But in the end, Hu Immortal land spirit bought a rank five current charge Gu for him in treasure yellow heaven.

This Gu could allow a Gu Master to turn into a water current temporarily and charge for a distance. But it was already outdated in the Gu world, that was because when the Gu Master transforms into a current, he might suffer heavy injuries or even die when hit by a fire path Gu worm.

But Fang Yuan was not using this Gu to battle, it was to enter Water Pavilion, it was more convenient than using the killer move to transform into a water spirit.

With a 'swoosh', Fang Yuan turned into a current and rushed towards Water Pavilion.

The pavilion was neither big nor small, it had three layers. It had a rustic flare to it, as the materials used were very ancient, having furniture and drawings.

Once Fang Yuan entered, he kept the current charge Gu and went to the third floor, pushing open a door to find the early stage Immortal Gu.

Only to see that this early stage Immortal Gu was like a thumb-sized cocoon. It was inside a large red bowl at the moment.

This bowl was larger than a water tank, the edges were uneven, looking like a shark's teeth.

Inside, there was some blue liquid that was oozing with coldness.

"So that's it."

Fang Yuan realized at once.

Although the four steps allowed the refinement of the early stage of the Immortal Gu, the Gu was still not complete.

It needed to further nurture and grow.

The mysterious Gu Immortal placed the Water Pavilion here in order to give the early stage Immortal Gu a good place to nurture itself.

There were some words on the large red bowl.

Fang Yuan looked at them and even with his knowledge, he could only decipher a portion of them.

"These are inkman characters, legend says that the splashes of literature water on Book Mountain in Qian Kun Crystal Wall created the first written characters in this world!"

These characters had been lost long ago. Even inkmen barely knew them after being chased out of Book Mountain.

"The Gu Immortals in treasure yellow heaven must have some research materials regarding the inkman language. After all, many Gu Immortals are interested in Book Mountain, they have been searching for the grey-white stone slab in order to recreate Qian Kun Crystal Wall."

Fang Yuan had a thought and immediately contacted little Hu Immortal.

The value of Hu Immortal blessed land was displayed again, it allowed a mortal like Fang Yuan to use the precious resource of mobilizing Gu Immortals.

The price was hefty, but after exchanging for some information regarding inkman language, Fang Yuan deciphered the words on this bowl on the spot.

The result made Fang Yuan become shocked and excited: "So this inheritance was created by Mo Yao!"

This Mo Yao was a brilliant person, the thirty-sixth generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House. She had a special identity, she was an inkman.

But eventually, she broke the limits of her race, and became a rank seven Gu Immortal.

She made tremendous contributions to the righteous path, and used her love to reform a huge demonic character ten thousand years ago, Sword Demon Bo Qing.

Bo Qing was a lone cultivator, he had a lowly start but his talent was superb, he created sword path Gu worms singlehandedly, and roamed the five regions without any obstruction or anyone that could match him.

He was among the most brilliant rank eight peak stage experts in history. He had great battle strength that shook the heavens, his sword path Gu worms were innovative and special, they had great strength. He was known as 'the pseudo-Immortal Venerable who split the five regions with his sword, it was fortunate for the people in the world that love changed him'.

It meant that: This person had great battle strength, only inferior to the Immortal and Demon Venerables of each era. Thankfully, because of love, he changed from demonic to righteous, it was truly a fortunate thing for all life in this world!

Back then, Bo Qing was even a hot favorite for the person to advance to rank nine.

But eventually, he failed when trying to get to rank nine and turned into ashes. As his wife, Mo Yao resisted with her life, and eventually died with him.

"In history, Mo Yao was a true refinement grandmaster. No wonder... back then when Giant Sun Immortal Venerable recruited concubines, the ten central continent sects provided beautiful female Gu Masters. Among them, Spirit Affinity House sent numerous female Gu Immortals into the palaces, as an offering to the Immortal Venerable. Between the concubines that gained Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's favor, a few were from Spirit Affinity House.

As an insider, it was no wonder that her understanding of the sacred palace and Eighty-Eight True Yang Building greatly surpassed ordinary people.

Mo Yao was the thirty-sixth generation fairy of Spirit Affinity House, she was naturally nurtured fully by Spirit Affinity House, it was easy for her to investigate the hidden secrets about Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

The origin of the Water Pavilion here could be explained as such.

In the inkman words, this Immortal Gu's information was written —

Calamity beckoning Gu!

Chapter 567: The comprehension of life since long ago (Double Chapter)

The corners of Fang Yuan's lips curled up into a smile as he read the ink text on the sides of the bowl.

This calamity beckoning Gu was a rank seven Immortal Gu, a rank higher than Fang Yuan's Spring Autumn Cicada. Its ability was extremely strange, actually involving the matter of earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations.

The middle section of the ink text explained its ability in detail. When a Gu Immortal goes through calamity and invokes disaster, calamity beckoning Gu could detach the earthly calamity and heavenly tribulation from the original target, and draw them to oneself.

Fang Yuan's expression could not help but become strange.

Such an Immortal Gu, who would dare to use it?

What terrifying and destructive strength did earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations have, how terrifying was its heavenly power? Instead of spending one's days to their heart's content, using calamity beckoning Gu to attract these earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations, wasn't this seeking one's own doom?

Gu Immortal Mo Yao was the thirty-sixth generation fairy of the grand Spirit Affinity House, why would she refine an Immortal Gu like this?

The last section of the ink text provided the reason.

It turned out she was really courting death!

Back then when she and Bo Qing were deeply in love, they were a famous couple of the righteous path and a romantic tale of their story spread throughout the five regions.

Sword Immortal Bo Qing had outstanding talent with no opponents that matched him in the whole world; he was well known as 'the pseudo-Immortal Venerable who split the five regions with his sword, it was fortunate for the people in the world that love changed him'.

Even in the whole wide world, looking at his entire life, the only thing in front of him was the one supreme goal of breaking through to rank nine.

However, challenging the rank nine barrier was extremely dangerous, even the grand Sword Immortal had a feeling that he was walking on thin ice and only had a fifteen percent chance of success at most.

Bo Qing's ambition was lofty, vowing to reach the apex that was rank nine. Mo Yao persuaded him in vain, and as such, she could only tearfully make preparations to assist him.

Bo Qing set up his inheritances and arranged for future events. His first attempt of breaking through failed; he was left in a state of heavy injuries for seventy years, bedridden the whole time without being able to even budge, his everyday life was all taken care of by Mo Yao.

After his injuries got better, Bo Qing once again desired to break through to rank nine.

Mo Yao knew the difficulty level of this, especially during the final trial of breaking through to rank nine when limitless earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations would descend. Bo Qing might have terrifying battle strength but he lacked the sustainability to endure through the trial.

To help her husband, she secretly betrayed her sect and started to make plans towards Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was the famous setup created by an Immortal Venerable and the skillful Long Hair Ancestor, the number one Immortal Gu house in the world. Mo Yao had already started her research on it a long time ago and had gained much insight from it which helped her to deepen her grandmaster refinement path attainment.

She might be a variant human and did not have Giant Sun's bloodline, but Spirit Affinity House had provided many outstanding girls to Giant Sun to become his concubines during his time. Among them, several female Gu Immortals had gained Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's favor.

Thus, Spirit Affinity House was able to obtain many secrets of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable which included detailed information on Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

Mo Yao was able to learn of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building's secret from these resources.

Imperial Court blessed land was situated at the exact center of northern plains, the space inside was as vast as a world and the time was separated into day and night as well, the good fortune in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building was extremely deep. Thus, at every set interval of time, it would attract extremely powerful earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations.

Giant Sun Immortal Venerable considered this point and placed a 'divert disaster Gu' when setting up Eighty-Eight True Yang Building which was an important cornerstone of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

This Gu was a rank seven Immortal Gu and was one of the essence of Giant Sun Immortal Venerable's luck path; it could divert the earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations in Imperial Court blessed land to the outside world. Because of this, the earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations formed into the ten year blizzard disaster that spread over the entire northern plains.

Conversely, Giant Sun Immortal Venerable used this ten year blizzard disaster to set up a rule which formed into the tradition of the Imperial Court contest.

Mo Yao discovered a loophole that was not strictly a loophole in this point.

Originally, Imperial Court blessed land co-existed with Eighty-Eight True Yang Building in symbiosis, and as such, every ten years, there would be vast and powerful earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations. At this time, Imperial Court blessed land would open up a small crack in accordance to divert disaster Gu, to send out the earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations.

Imperial Court blessed land was set by Giant Sun Immortal Venerable to only allow mortals to enter or exit and did not allow the entry of Gu Immortals. But at the time when it had to divert disaster, there would be a hidden crack in Imperial Court blessed land from which the calamities and tribulations would rush out like a flood, and at this time the setup that prevents Gu Immortals from entering would be ineffective.

Mo Yao used this small crack and risked her very life in going against the calamities and tribulations to enter Imperial Court blessed land.

She spent close to ten years investigating inside the blessed land and after suffering countless hardships, she was able to find the crucial node through her grandmaster refinement path attainment -—it was the small tower at Di Qiu area.

Next, she risked the danger of awakening Giant Sun's will and destroyed this small tower, using the backward flow of the heavenly power to sense divert disaster Gu and create a cave that would foster 'calamity beckoning Gu'.

After she succeeded in refining the early stage of the Immortal Gu, she set up the Immortal Gu house Water Pavilion in this nameless valley.

Inside the pavilion, Mo Yao completely nurtured the early stage Immortal Gu to its completed form and brought the calamity beckoning Gu outside secretly using the chance when the blessed land was diverting disaster.

She did not destroy all these arrangements just in case of any accidents. If Bo Qing failed in his breakthrough again and calamity beckoning Gu was also destroyed in earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations, then she would have to enter the blessed land again to refine calamity beckoning Gu.

However, she never returned after this.

Sword Immortal Bo Qing's second attempt at breaking through to rank nine failed completely and he was turned into ashes by the vast heavenly tribulations. As for Mo Yao, she perished alongside him.

"So it was like that. Breaking through to rank nine involves numerous difficulties and dangers. Mo Yao set up this inheritance secretly beforehand but did not explain the true content of the inheritance; it was because this action was betraying the sect. But she still left the preceding clues for the sect in the end. In my previous life, central continent's Gu Immortals schemed against Imperial Court blessed land and destroyed Eighty-Eight True Yang Building by using the clues she had left behind." As Fang Yuan recalled now, he immediately had a feeling of the fog dispersing in his mind and everything had gotten an explanation.

There was a poem left at the ending of the ink text —

The long immortal path is filled with obstacles; encounters occur at faraway places.

Too long has passed, emotions and hatred have already lasted for a long time.

My lord thinks about the apex of immortality, while I think of his safety.

Life and death are separated, I will support my lord's dreams.

This was clearly Mo Yao's work.

The path of a Gu Immortal is long and filled with difficulties, however I was fortunate enough to meet with my lord.

Unknowingly, emotions and hatred tangled, and I was unable to free myself.

Lord's sight was focused on the limit of the immortal path, while my gaze was on my lord himself.

The attempt of breaking through to rank nine was a near death situation. I was not willing to be separated with him by life and death, so all I could do was to help my lord realize his dream in my own way!

To protect her love, to help Bo Qing walk to the peak of a Gu Immortal, Mo Yao was willing to sacrifice herself, using calamity beckoning Gu to draw the earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations to herself.

"A strange woman..." Fang Yuan sighed.

Although he would absolute not make such a sacrifice because of love, it did not hinder Fang Yuan from understanding such a person.

It was to the extent where his understanding of this was deeper than others.

Humans that live in this world had desires, they had their goals and meanings in life.

Mo Yao's goal was her lover. Fang Yuan's goal was to chase eternal life.

The different desires, different goals and different meanings forged all kinds of lives in this huge world to create heroes that had their own independent character.

Fang Yuan's gaze fell towards the center of the giant vermillion bowl.

The cocoon had already burst open and calamity beckoning Gu had already completely formed. Its shape was like a silkworm cocoon with a grey body and the size of a little finger. It was currently moving up and down in the water.

Calamity beckoning Gu was a genuine self sacrifice Gu and was used to abandon oneself for others.

This Gu seemed to have no use to Fang Yuan, but in fact still had an enormous value.

First of all, it was an Immortal Gu. Even if he did not use it, he could exchange it for an enormous amount of immortal essence stones in treasure yellow heaven.

Secondly, it was a luck path Gu that was able to attract earthly calamities and heavenly tribulations. Calamities and tribulations were powerful, but as long as one was strong and tough enough, then they could use it in a unique way to harm others.

Finally, it was formed by borrowing the strength of one of the cornerstones of Eighty-Eight True Yang Building — Divert Disaster Gu. It and divert disaster Gu could be said to be two sides of the same coin; one attracted calamities while the other diverted disaster. This connection would provide huge assistance to Fang Yuan's plans in Eighty-Eight True Yang Building.

However, even though there was a connection to it in his heart, there was a condition before Fang Yuan could completely subdue this Gu.

Mo Yao had mentioned it in detail in the ink text on the side of the bowl.

There was a necessary condition to subdue calamity beckoning Gu. It did not matter whether it was a mortal or immortal, but they had to have the heart of self sacrifice.

If they did not have the heart to sacrifice themselves and forcibly tried to subdue calamity beckoning Gu, in the best case, it would lead to a backlash from the Immortal Gu; and in the most serious case, the Immortal Gu would self-destruct and cause harm to the Gu Master's life.

In the Water Pavilion, Fang Yuan stood in front of the giant bowl, with no expression on his face.

Heart of self sacrifice, did he have it?

　　...

"Cough cough cough." Tang Miao Ming covered her lips with a handkerchief, her beautiful brows furrowing deeply in pain.

"Big sister!" Tang tribe's third young master Tang Fang called out from the side with a lamenting expression.

Tang Miao Ming was lying back in bed; she waved her hand to indicate Tang Fang to not worry.

Tang Fang heaved a deep sigh as he looked at the blood on the handkerchief: "Big sister, why did you risk your life? What good is there in passing this round? Father and the others have already passed away, you are my only relative left, what would I do if anything happened to you?"

Tang Miao Ming lightly caressed Tang Fang's hair: "Third brother, you are our Tang tribe's tribe leader, you should not be lacking in ambition. Our Tang tribe had suffered heavily in this Imperial Court contest and was almost swallowed by other tribes. Now is a very rare opportunity, we need to use Eighty-Eight True Yang Building to make our tribe prosper again."

Tang Fang pouted in a nonchalant manner: "But big sister, you suffered heavy injuries by trying to force your way through the round, the gains do not make up for the losses. I have been very distressed because of this and had no mood to manage the tribe's affairs these days."

"What?" Tang Miao Ming's expression turned solemn and she stared at Tang Fang sharply.

Without any hesitation, she reprimanded him: "Tribe leader Tang Fang, you have a heavy responsibility upon you, how could you still have the sentiments of a child? Reviving the tribe is your duty, it is the meaning of being the leader of a tribe. From now on, I do not want to hear you complain like this ever again, do you understand?"

"Big... big sister, I was wrong." Tang Fang immediately stood up from the edge of the bed and lowered his head to admit his mistake with an ashamed expression. His big sister was the one who loved him the most since young.

Tang Miao Ming's gaze gradually softened, sighing faintly: "Third brother, I know your nature, you like travelling and want to be free from this duty, to live a life without any restraints. But you are the last man in our family, you should be brave enough to assume this responsibility. From now on, the meaning of your life will be to revitalize the tribe, do you understand?"

"Big sister is right, I understand. Don't get angry big sister, you are still injured."

Tang Miao Ming said in a solemn tone: "After returning, copy the first section of chapter three of \<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\> ten times."

Tang Fang's heart was immediately filled with warmth.

Since young, his big sister's punishment to him was to make him copy books.

"Big sister, take a good rest, I will go copy it now."

\<\<The Legends of Ren Zu\>\>, chapter three, first section —

Ren Zu's second daughter Desolate Ancient Moon climbed Cheng Bai mountain and searched for success Gu to rescue her father from the door of life and death.

But at the final juncture, she failed and lost her sense of self, becoming an ugly and powerful monster.

Without his daughter to rescue him, and his eldest son Verdant Great Sun still addicted and dejected, Ren Zu was trapped in Luo Po valley, unable to return to life.

Luo Po valley was like a giant maze, its paths twisted and turned. Occasionally, boundless bewilderment fog would spread and cause the soul to slacken; and occasionally, Luo Po wind that was as sharp as a knife would blow and cut down souls.

Ren Zu had a spiritual body now and was unable to find the way out of the bewilderment fog. His soul was cut down by Luo Po wind, becoming weaker and weaker, and the situation turned even more dangerous.

The soul fragments cut down by Luo Po wind started to converge gradually and turned into a youth.

Like this, Ren Zu's third son was born.

He was Northern Dark Ice Soul.

"My son, thank you for your company. I do not have much time left, having you to accompany me in my final days, father did not have to feel lonely." Ren Zu sighed with deep emotions.

Northern Dark Ice Soul had a cold appearance but was warm-hearted, and although he did not speak much, he was very filial to Ren Zu. And as he looked at Ren Zu growing weaker and weaker every day, his mood also became heavier.

He decided to rescue Ren Zu.

Ren Zu sensed his determination, and felt both happiness and heartache: "Don't be worried my son, I know of your filial heart, I now understand that life and death cannot be forced. Humans will die in the end, this is our fate."

Northern Dark Ice Soul said in a sobbing tone: "Father, I know your words are right. I also know my efforts might be in vain. But looking at you growing weaker like this, if I do not make an effort, my heart will feel even more pain. Let me do something for you."

Ren Zu sighed and could only let him go.

Northern Dark Ice Soul wandered in the vast Luo Po valley; he was born here, as such, Luo Po wind could not cut down his soul and the bewilderment fog could not obstruct his vision.

He searched bitterly but could not find the exit.

Right as he was becoming more desperate, he came across a Gu worm.

"Well, well, to think I would be discovered by you." This Gu was like a ladybug with a chubby spherical body, but it was extremely agile and was flashing around Northern Dark Ice Soul's body.

Northern Dark Ice Soul's eyes brightened as he asked in curiosity: "What Gu are you?"

"I am known as unexpected." This Gu worm replied.

Northern Dark Ice Soul's gaze dimmed down: "So you are unexpected Gu, it is a pity you are not success Gu."

Unexpected Gu sneered: "Young man, do not look down on me. I have a love-hate relation with success Gu. The strength of unexpectedness is very powerful. Do you know what your encounter with me here represents?"

"What?"

Unexpected Gu shook its chubby body and said proudly: "What kind of place is this? This is Luo Po valley, a death realm. You being here means you are already dead. But by encountering me, you have come across an unexpected event in 'death' - that is 'life'. Grab me, I will take you out to the human world and you can be resurrected again."

"Really?" Northern Dark Ice Soul was exulted, "Can I bring my father along?"

Unexpected Gu shook its head: "It is you who encountered me, not your father, so I can only take you."

Northern Dark Ice Soul was extremely disappointed, refusing: "Since I cannot take my father with me, then I will not go. I will accompany my father till his final moment."

Unexpected Gu laughed loudly and spoke in a domineering tone: "Unexpectedness in life is beyond your control. Young man, you must come with me!"

The moment it finished speaking, unexpected Gu forcibly took Northern Dark Ice Soul and instantly left life and death door, arriving in the human world.

Northern Dark Ice Soul obtained flesh body and was feeling extremely bewildered facing this vast world alone.

Unexpected Gu disappeared. He suddenly remembered Ren Zu once saying he had an elder sister who was called Desolate Ancient Moon.

At this moment, cognition Gu took the initiative to find him: "Young man, do not be suspicious, cognition has always been the friend of humans, I am here to help you."

Cognition Gu told Northern Dark Ice Soul about Cheng Bai mountain and also the events detailing Desolate Ancient Moon.

Northern Dark Ice Soul decided to first see his elder sister.

When he saw Desolate Ancient Moon, his tears fell in sadness.

Northern Dark Ice Soul tried to converse with Desolate Ancient Moon, but Desolate Ancient Moon who had turned into a monster kept on repeating questions.

"Where is this?"

Northern Dark Ice Soul thought for a while and answered: "This is the human world, living beings can move about here. Above us is the heavens and below our feet is earth."

"Who am I?" Desolate Ancient Moon asked again.

"You are a human, Ren Zu's second child, your name is Desolate Ancient Moon. You are my elder sister." Northern Dark Ice Soul replied.

"Elder sister, wake up quickly. Our father is trapped in Luo Po valley, dying, we need to resurrect him soon."

"Ren Zu? Desolate Ancient Moon? Resurrect?" The monster shook its head, extremely puzzled, "Why should I resurrect him? Could it be that humans should not die? What disadvantage is there in death? Why do humans live? Why do I live?"

This time, Northern Dark Ice Soul was not able to answer.

Why do people live?

As Northern Dark Ice Soul pondered over this question, bewilderment Gu quietly approached him, making him lose his sense of the surroundings.

Subsequently, love Gu and disguise Gu also approached him.

Cognition Gu felt a big headache when it saw them. These several Gu were famous for their mischief and would often move together, even cognition Gu did not want to provoke them.

"Love, have you not harmed enough people? Why are you not letting them go?" Cognition Gu sighed.

"Don't try to speak reason with me, I am completely unreasonable." Love Gu said in a unruly tone, "Get lost, cognition, I do not like you."

Cognition Gu could only leave helplessly.

"Another human came again? Haha!" Love Gu was extremely happy when it saw Northern Dark Ice Soul, because it had another target to play with.

It and disguise Gu were sworn brothers, and on the spot, it used disguise Gu's power to disguise as cognition Gu.

"Young man, your elder sister has lost herself. If you want to save her, you need to find meaning Gu."

Northern Dark Ice Soul regained his senses and asked love Gu without doubting: "I have seen unexpected Gu, please tell me where this meaning Gu is? How should I look for it?"

Love Gu deceived him in a serious tone: "Oh human, you should know, there is a meaning to why you are all living in this world. As long as you find meaning Gu, your elder sister can awaken. Follow the direction I point towards and keep moving forward, you will eventually find meaning Gu."

Northern Dark Ice Soul expressed his gratitude before immediately setting off.

Love, bewilderment and disguise Gu guffawed as they looked at his receding figure.

In this world, how could there be a meaning Gu?

There was simply no such Gu, Northern Dark Ice Soul would, as such, not find it no matter how much he searched for it.

"Fool, who told you all to anger me? I will let you guys know how terrifying the punishment of love can be! From now on, let's follow him and toy with him in turns."

Love Gu's proposal was approved by the other two Gu.

Thereupon, the three Gu played tricks on Northern Dark Ice Soul in turns, he suffered so much that words could not describe it. But to find this non-existent meaning Gu, he kept on persevering.

Such spirit moved cognition Gu. And when love Gu was not present, cognition Gu approached Northern Dark Ice Soul to help him.

"Cognition, what are you doing? We are having a great time." Bewilderment Gu and disguise Gu were extremely displeased with cognition.

Cognition Gu laughed: "I am afraid of love, but I am not afraid of you two. Young man, use my strength to come to your senses."

Northern Dark Ice Soul used cognition Gu's power to realize the truth; he was no longer bewildered and he had seen through the disguise.

Bewilderment Gu and disguise Gu could only leave in defeat.

Northern Dark Ice Soul expressed gratitude to cognition Gu: "Thank you cognition Gu. Because of you, I have thought of a way to save elder sister."

"Eh? What way is that?"

"In this world, there is indeed no meaning Gu. But why can't I create a meaning Gu?" Northern Dark Ice Soul replied confidently.

Human life might have no meaning, but they could give a meaning to it.

Northern Dark Ice Soul came back to Desolate Ancient Moon's side and personally created a meaning Gu and pressed it into Desolate Ancient Moon's head.

"The meaning in my life is to search for success Gu and resurrect father! I understand now, I get it!" Desolate Ancient Moon's eyes brightened.

　　...

"Meaning in life huh..." Tang Fang put down his brush.

It was late at night, warm silver light covered the land in Imperial Court blessed land.

He was deeply moved after repeatedly copying the book.

"People will feel bewildered as they live in this world. But as long as they can find their meaning in life, they will find their direction and be able to move forward bravely. At the same time, they will also understand what they want to do and what they do not want to do, and they will not be afraid of sacrifice. Big sister's intent in making me copy the book should be this."

He lightly pushed open the window and looked at the beautiful and dazzling sacred palace, thinking of the variety of people in it, some were strong, some were weak.

His mood gradually uplifted: "Every person's life has all sort of meaning. And the meaning of my life is to lead the tribe towards prosperity!"

　　...

At the same time, in Water Pavilion.

"A heart of self sacrifice?" The corners of Fang Yuan's lips curled up into a lofty smile.

Without any hesitation, he moved his hand towards the giant bowl and directly picked up the calamity beckoning Gu.

As it absorbed his aura, calamity beckoning Gu's body flashed with radiance and soon became Fang Yuan's possession. The whole process was extremely smooth with not the least bit of tremor and backlash.

With the identity of a transmigrator and the experience gained in the five hundred years in his past life, Fang Yuan had already seen through life and death; familial feelings, friendship and love were not any his interests.

Only eternal life, this majestic and unattainable target, could make the journey of his life become more interesting.

This was the meaning he gave to this life!

Pursuing eternal life did not mean he was afraid of death or afraid of failure.

He calmly accepted death and failure.

Whether eternal life existed or not, there was no evidence to prove it.

But even if it did not exist, so what?

Fang Yuan enjoyed the process. In the process of pursuing eternal life, he found his meaning and felt that this life was quite interesting.

The lowly lust and desires of his body, satisfaction of love and hatred, he was already tired of them.

Only eternal life was worthy of being his target to pursue.

"As a result, the necessary resolve to sacrifice, I already have it." Fang Yuan's gaze shone eerily as he played around with the rank seven Immortal Gu in his hand.